(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
Do you know what it's like?
I get dizzy as if all the blood drained out of my body,
and before I realise it, my face turns all red.
I'm short on breath like I just ran...
and my heart races.
It feels like my heart...
will burst.
I like you, Young Oh.
Do you mean it?
Your heart races because you like me?
How quickly does it race?
How?
May I touch it?
Scum.
A normal person's pulse...
beats 60 to 100 times per minute.
About 110 when they are in love.
It is similar to when you do light exercises.
A man and a woman meet and fall in love...
purely because of their hormones.
Norepinephrine that speeds up the heart.
Dopamine that makes you feel joy.
Oxytocin that makes you feel closeness.
Phenylethylamine that makes you want intimacy.
- Stop it.
-  Hey.
Stop it.
And the expiration date for those hormones...
is at most three years.
The heart...
What are you looking at?
Is nothing more than electrochemical responses...
to millions of nerves and hormones.
It's fine.
I am...
really...
fine.
(Beautiful Mind)
Go to the bathroom.
Go empty it out.
Stop getting up every hour, whimpering and twisting.
- Hey!
-  Ouch!
That's mine.
Excuse me.
Didn't you move into a study dorm for the bar exam?
What are you doing here?
Tell me.
Does your mum know you're doing this?
Would I be here if she did?
Kids are born to disappoint their parents.
I am doing my best to fulfill my calling.
You are all knotted up.
Play hard.
- Okay.
-  Okay.
Runaway teens are my calling, you punk.
Hey!
Gosh! Gye Jin Sung!
What... What is this?
I know. What is this?
So... The thing is...
A guy...
suddenly did this...
to a girl...
and then left.
What is that?
- Did this happen to you?
-  No.
It's not.
Then what?
It's a case. It's for a case.
I see. A case.
Then it's obvious.
- What is it?
-  A pickpocket.
He took her wallet.
He didn't take her wallet.
Then what is it?
There must be an important clue...
that you failed to tell me.
Well, he said something like this.
I can't feel...
anything.
Nothing at all.
That's apparently what he said.
It's a homicide, isn't it?
- Homicide?
-  A stabbing?
Poisoning?
Or arson?
No, no, no.
- Those are too weak.
-  Too weak?
What is?
What woman would let a guy live after he says that?
How could he hug her like this...
and say to her face that he felt nothing?
He told her she has zero attractiveness as a woman.
Why would she let him live?
Why?
Right? I should be angry, right?
That's right.
That's why you were kicking...
all through the night.
Because you were angry at what the doctor did.
That's it, isn't it?
I said it wasn't me, didn't I?
It's a case.
It wasn't me. It's a case.
I guess I will have...
to pay my brother-in-law a visit.
When you think about it,
Jin Sung is quite cute.
He should look closely. Why is he discouraging her?
(Embrace)
"Suppresses urges and appetite".
"Useful for dieting".
Diet...
Fine. Diet.
Let's think of it as a diet.
It's good. I probably lost weight.
Yes. It's over.
Fine.
Let's say I gave a free hug.
I'm cool like that.
Next time, I should just hug...
My cell phone...
Oh, my. Dr Lee.
Hello.
What brings you here this morning?
I came to keep my promise.
You said to call...
if I win.
Win?
- Did you really win?
-  Yes.
Wow. I never thought you'd win.
What level?
How much?
I've never won before. How much did you win?
Level five.
That's exactly half.
That's 2 dollars and 50 cents.
I see.
I looked...
totally superficial just now, didn't I?
Did you forget?
I can't read people...
or feel any emotions.
So I'm going to ask you something.
What does a woman feel at a time like this
I just have no idea.
Two people...
met more than 10 times.
The woman...
handcuffed him...
and even threw herself in the water.
Just a minute.
But that woman...
ignored the man waiting outside her home.
She ran away as if she didn't see him.
Her vision is fine,
and she doesn't have a facial recognition disorder.
Why did she do that?
Why did she run away? Why?
Tell me.
Why do you keep doing this to me?
What am I to you?
Do you...
enjoy teasing me?
Am I a joke to you?
That is...
what that woman would probably want to say.
- I see.
-  Yes.
That is why I need you,
Detective Gye Jin Sung.
You're sort of like my Wi-Fi.
Wi-Fi?
The patient's feelings that you read and relayed...
was a huge help in my treating him.
That is why I'd like to call it Wi-Fi.
I should...
be happy, right?
Do as you wish.
It's your emotions.
Anyway, I came to say one thing.
In the future,
I'll be expecting your assistance.
When I need Wi-Fi...
for the patient's sake,
whether you're at the precinct or anywhere else,
I will go to you.
So don't be surprised...
or ignore me like you did today.
Do you understand?
Okay, good.
Goodbye.
You didn't...
win anything.
Lee Young Oh.
You said his name is Lee Young Oh, right?
Isn't it interesting?
This is the CT scan of young Lee Young Oh...
who received surgery from Lee Gun Myung.
Would you look...
carefully at the frontal lobe?
If medical technology had been advanced as it is now,
this would never have occurred.
I can't believe it.
I'd like to see...
how my old friend...
would react when he sees me.
Both Lee Gun Myung...
and Lee Young Oh.
Let's go.
My junior alumnus from grade school,
which prides itself in tradition and fame.
I heard you got dizzy and fainted at school.
Why don't you lie down on your way to the ER?
- Mister.
-  Hey.
Mister? Mister?
I'm not that old.
If you don't want to call me by my name,
you don't have to, but what? "Mister"?
How old do you think I am?
How smart do you have to be to go to medical school?
I heard if I get a head start with math now,
I might have more time...
to study science in middle school.
- My mum said that.
-  Your mum said that?
What kind of a question is that...
for a grade school student?
Do you want to go to medical school?
Then do as your mum says.
You'll get into medical school.
I don't know if you'll be happy,
but good luck anyway.
We'll be grade school and college alumni.
Come on, now.
Doctor, please.
Must you play so rough with a kid?
What? What did I...
You're such a weakling. Here.
Excuse me. Where's my child?
He's a grade school student.
He's wearing his uniform.
The school said they sent him to the hospital.
What's his name?
It's Choi Yo Seob. Choi Yo Seob.
Oh. The future medical student.
Yo Seob!
- Yo Seob.
-  Mum.
Are you all right?
You scared me.
Let's go home.
Excuse me.
You can't leave yet.
He's going to get a CT scan now.
Once he's done,
please speak with his doctor. You may leave after that.
It won't take long.
He has to get to his academy. We don't have time.
Excuse me.
Look.
His head hurts a lot. Aren't you worried?
Don't you want to know why it hurts?
It's an act.
It's finals week.
Kids always get headaches during these times.
Let's go.
Let the doctor do the diagnosis.
Doctor. She's his guardian.
Only doctors can judge whether or not...
your son is pretending to be in pain.
Let me take a look.
Parents mistakenly think...
they know everything about their child.
I decide whether or not to entrust him...
with that doctor.
I'm his parent.
Yo Seob!
Oh, no.
The subdural haemorrhage is progressing quickly.
Dr Yang, call Radiology...
and prepare for surgery.
- It is an emergency surgery.
-  Yes, Sir.
Yo Seob.
I'm so sorry.
Please wait out here.
Honey.
Yo Seob is in the hospital...
No. It's nothing serious.
Get back to work.
Wait. Doctor.
Yo Seob will be fine, right?
He has to be.
I heard he got dizzy and fainted at school.
Is that true?
I don't know.
It's not like I'm always with him at school.
Didn't you talk as if you knew everything about him?
We'll know once surgery's over.
We'll know just what's been happening to the child.
Scalpel.
Forceps.
This is totally...
I've never seen black blood before.
How did such a young kid...
Subdural haemorrhage.
The hematoma...
progressed slowly and bruised repeatedly...
for a prolonged period of time.
If he had left the hospital,
this child...
would have died.
His BP is back to normal.
It's looking good.
His vitals are all stable.
The swelling went down quickly.
Doctor,
why did you shave non-surgical sites?
Dr Yang.
Yes?
Next time, remember. Don't ask.
People may lie,
but the body cannot lie.
If someone abused them,
the traces must remain somewhere.
Like this.
Stem cell treatment drugs...
that regenerate brain cells and heart muscle cells,
which we thought was impossible.
Our children may live in a time...
without Alzheimer's or heart transplants.
This has been Choi Sang Hyuk reporting.
- Thank you.
-  Thanks.
That was a great closing.
Children.
It feels more real since you mentioned children.
I'm a fan.
You really are incredible,
succeeding in stem cell regeneration.
It's the success of every citizen of Korea.
Hyunsung Regenerative Medicine Team...
hopes to give the poor and sad...
something to smile about.
Even if it's for a brief moment.
You mean like a gold medal won during the Olympics?
- Correct.
-  We plan to begin...
with selecting patients who are...
worn out from poverty and treating them for free.
That's what everyone does...
to publicise themselves.
It's a bit early for dinner,
but it's the perfect time to get a drink.
My apologies.
Ever since I started doing the evening news,
I don't make dinner plans.
I don't qualify to be an exception, I guess.
Don't bother.
That's his secret...
to being the best anchor for 10 years.
He doesn't do favours and never misses the news.
Anyway,
thank you.
Gosh.
Why is everyone on TV so utterly rude?
Why is he trying to act...
like he's king in front of me?
Gosh.
I'm so tired from restraining myself.
- Would you like one?
-  Go ahead.
That's right, you drink only coffee.
Our commercials during his show...
The moment we pull our commercials,
they'll target us...
with news briefs and other reports.
He doesn't let go once he bites down.
That's why the masses like him.
They think he can't tell a lie.
As you can see, even his personal life is spotless.
What an annoying punk. He's boring, too.
If Choi Sang Hyuk promotes our regenerative treatment,
the nation's faith in it will rise.
Did we finish finding the free treatment patients?
Cho Kyung Tae. Male patient at the age of 46.
He has myocardial asthenia.
He wants to be in the stem cell treatment trial.
Next.
25-year-old male.
Seo In Chul.
He's waiting for a heart transplant.
Sir, is he your grandson?
What do you mean?
He's my son that we had after 30 years of marriage.
Even if death comes for me,
I cannot go.
How could I leave my son here like this?
Next.
Doctor.
Please...
let my son speak at least.
That way, after I die,
he can at least extend his life.
You know that thing that they say creates miracles.
That stem... Stem something.
- Dr Song. Next patient.
-  Yes, Doctor.
Please let us choose new trial subjects.
"Regenerative treatment saved them."
"They became happy and healthy."
That's what we want to show.
Not hope, which may never come.
So...
you don't believe our research will create miracles,
do you?
Why do you think that?
- Is there something...
-  Stem cell treatment...
will soon be in the market.
It is no longer research.
It is a product.
We must raise the demand
in the 200-million-dollar market...
for the product.
I'm glad you understand.
That was pretty quick.
He is a smart kid.
He knows exactly who he is.
It's hard...
for people, especially for doctors,
to be like that.
After living all their lives in a white gown,
they get delusional.
Patients.
Devotion.
Conviction.
They think they are noble.
What are you trying to say?
I didn't have what it took,
so I decided to chase money and success.
But I still think that I'm more decent,
Director.
The anaesthesia should have worn out.
Seeing how he's still sleeping,
I'll have to operate again and wake him.
Dr Kim. Choi Yo Seob...
I'm awake.
The anaesthesia wore out,
but you pretended to be asleep in front of me.
You're afraid of surgery,
but you want to become a doctor...
and make Mum proud. You coward.
Listen carefully to me.
People can lie,
but the body cannot.
Do you know what I mean?
Is this a test?
Try to solve the problem.
Okay.
Who is it?
Who hits you?
Is it your mum?
Or your dad?
No. It isn't true.
This is what you say in this situation.
Remember.
People's lips lie...
from time to time.
What am I going to say next?
See? A person's body cannot lie.
Do you understand what I mean?
If you don't understand it, memorise it.
If you become a doctor later,
it will be very useful.
Okay. People lie, but...
The body cannot lie.
Bingo. Correct. Good job.
I wonder if you can...
answer this correctly.
Will you try it? Will you?
- I'll try it.
-  Good.
Who is it?
Who hurt you?
I'm sure you know.
Tell me.
It's okay. Tell me.
Who is it?
What are you doing to him?
Mum.
Doctor.
We need to speak.
I will file a formal complaint with the hospital.
You sneaked into his room when his guardian was out.
No child could admit...
he is being abused...
in front of his mum.
So,
are you saying I beat my child?
What do you take me for?
Do I look that despicable or something?
I'm not interested in you, Ma'am.
What I care about...
is that my post-op patient...
needs to be protected.
A guardian must protect my patient...
from any impact and infections.
I'm just curious if that guardian...
will be that child's mum...
or his dad.
I operated with my time and effort.
I can't permit it to go to waste.
The most dangerous person for Yo Seob...
is none other than you.
The kid...
must be very cute.
It's the first time seeing Dr Lee Young Oh...
so interested in a patient after surgery.
Not at all.
At our age,
being cute is a survival skill.
It isn't special.
It's because they are too weak...
to survive without the care of adults.
And...
that cuteness,
no, more like that DNA game...
doesn't affect me in any way.
Why? Because I cannot feel...
and I am a sociopath.
You know that.
Did you do it? Why?
What were you thinking?
Tell me. Whom did you tell?
Tell me!
If you want to know...
how child abuse affects the brain,
come see me.
You know...
how much I excel...
in neurology.
Then you must know this, too.
I am incapable of controlling my impulses,
violent nature or rage.
Try and feel...
how hard...
I'm fighting back and resisting...
the urge to do something to you.
Just try.
I need Wi-Fi.
Where are you?
That Wi-Fi just turns on whenever it feels like.
I should ask to be transferred to the mountains.
- What is 2 plus 3?
-  It's 5.
- What's 8 times 7?
-  56.
Okay, what is 3,427 times 21 plus 2?
3,427...
Can you repeat the question?
- 71,969.
-  Wow.
Did you do that in your head?
You really are awesome.
No. As I was watching you walk over,
I counted with my hand.
71,969.
Okay, be prepared.
My next question...
is very, very difficult.
But before that, we should eat.
You look like...
you desperately want glucose.
He was definitely hit,
but there are no signs of abuse?
What a smart way to get away with it.
- What is 2 plus 3?
-  Stop.
I'm not going to answer. Don't ask me.
What I mean is...
that it's a logical problem you can easily solve.
Please continue.
What I don't understand is...
why the child wants to defend his mum...
I'll just say his parent.
Why is he defending...
his parent who hurt him?
What kind of emotion is that?
What is it?
It's like first love.
Other people might not understand,
but I'm sure they have some good memories.
Even though the whole world says she's a bad person...
and his head tells him she's a bad person,
but his heart...
must tell him otherwise.
It's not easy to give up on the first person...
that you've loved and trusted.
Every parent is...
the first person who their children meet in life.
They're the child's first love.
Is that so?
Is it that easy for normal people like you...
to understand?
When I was a child, I often thought that maybe,
normal people who can feel emotions...
are aliens from a faraway galaxy.
I thought they had antennae that I couldn't see...
through which they would communicate...
with each other.
I wondered if I couldn't understand them...
because I was the only one from earth.
I hear that earthlings have...
a Wi-Fi network instead.
That you can easily connect wherever you are.
Wherever you are.
I'll visit the hospital tomorrow...
with a detective from the child abuse division.
Let's stop worrying about the child and eat.
What do you say?
Are you saying...
that I seem to be worried about the child?
Yes. You seem really worried.
We're here to see Choi Yo Seob and his guardian.
Is there a problem with the hospital?
No, we got a report of child abuse.
Child abuse?
Patient Choi Yo Seob?
If you call that abuse, my mum should be in prison.
Dr Lee Young Oh was sure that he'd been abused.
We presume that the child...
was abused for a prolonged period of time.
Oh, my.
I'll show you the way.
Thank you.
This way, please.
Yo Seob, I...
The patient is not here.
Has he been discharged?
Dead.
- Excuse me?
-  I mean...
I'm dead. Dr Lee Young Oh will kill me...
for the negligence of patient care.
Dr Lee could stay quiet for a while...
and then strangle me with his stethoscope like this.
What should I do? I have to find him.
Where did he go...
- I'm in trouble.
-  Excuse me.
- My goodness.
-  Wait.
Don't you know how important the immersion classes are?
Do I have really have to go? I'm still in pain.
You can't survive in this world with such a weak mind.
Think of your dad. He's strong.
You're his son. You should be like him.
My head hurts.
Stop being such a crybaby. It gives me a headache.
Your dad and I are doing our best.
We spend so much time and money on you.
We're doing the best to make your life perfect.
Choi Yo Seob, can't you just keep up with us?
Stop biting your nails!
How many times did I tell you?
Quit doing that already!
Mum...
Did you just pee yourself?
How dare you!
Don't touch him.
Let go. Let go of me.
I said, let go!
- Stop it!
-  Let go of me!
Don't touch my patient.
Let's go.
Mum!
What are you doing?
What are you trying to do to my wife?
Dad...
Wait. Ma'am, where is Yo Seob?
What's wrong with her?
What happened to her?
She's lost consciousness.
Get an MRI,
and call Neurology.
Don't listen to him.
Oh, wow. You're him, right?
He's Anchor Choi Sang Hyuk from "News Briefing".
I'm the guardian of this patient.
Dr Yang.
I can't let a person like him treat my wife.
Please find me another doctor.
Sure. I will.
This patient is suffering from a brain tumour.
Shouldn't you hurry? Go now!
I'm sorry.
My wife was just fine.
You caused this.
I saw what happened with my own eyes.
You assaulted a patient's guardian.
I'll make you pay for it.
Your wife has a brain tumour.
And there's a problem in the right frontal lobe.
Her personality changed suddenly.
Her right eyebrow was raised.
Her left arm and leg jerked.
She also has intermittent urinary problems.
These are the symptoms...
of brain tumour in the right frontal lobe.
What confirms her disease is...
the fact that she's been abusing your son...
for the past six months.
Do you need more proof?
It turns out that his dad is Anchor Choi Sang Hyuk.
I think he looks better in person.
He was exuding his charisma.
All dads are useless.
What's the point of pursuing justice?
He didn't even know that his son was being abused.
That's the sorrow of fathers' lives.
He's been too busy working to support his family...
to see what happens in his family. I feel bad for him.
I hear that his wife has a brain tumour.
Is that why she abused her son?
That's just Dr Lee's opinion.
We'll know when the test result comes out.
I don't want to defend Dr Lee,
but his assumption makes sense.
If you have a problem in the frontal lobe,
your...
personality can change completely...
and you can become violent.
It's possible that she abused her son because of that.
Frontal lobe diseases are...
really scary.
Hang on a second.
Is it possible...
that Dr Lee has a frontal lobe disease?
Think about it. He lacks empathy.
He can't understand others' feelings.
He can't sympathise with others. Right?
You can just describe him with one word.
He's a psychopath.
That's probably why.
Think about what happened to the child's mother.
We can't be sure if it was because of...
her brain tumour or if Dr Lee assaulted her.
It's possible because it's Dr Lee.
(Anchor Choi Sang Hyuk abuses his child.)
That's possible.
So you want me to forge...
your son's medical records.
It's the request of Anchor Choi Sang Hyuk.
That's not what I meant.
I'm asking you to correct it.
You're being discourteous.
I work out at 4pm every day.
It's a strict rule I've been keeping...
for the past 10 years.
Even...
the great Choi Sang Hyuk...
can't make me break that rule.
I like doing business like this.
We give and take from each other.
I gave you something yesterday.
Today, you'll give me something in return.
Shall we...
start talking about business?
Let's see who will benefit more.
Every family has a story.
He has no right to do this.
He stigmatised me and my wife for child abuse...
just because he is my son's doctor.
Who is your son's doctor?
He's Dr Lee Young Oh from Neurosurgery.
Lee Young Oh...
It's hard even for us to deal with Dr Lee.
Then, I'll have to deal with him myself...
using the power of media.
I heard...
that Dr Lee is a psychopathic surgeon.
Earlier today, he assaulted a patient's guardian...
in the parking lot.
I've already secured the security camera footage.
However, the hospital is...
trying to cover up the incident...
by accusing the patient's parents of child abuse.
That's the story I'll tell the media.
Do you think you'll be okay?
I'm not worried it might damage my reputation.
I'm afraid I might lose the power of my words.
If that happens,
who will convince the public...
about the regenerative medicine research at Hyunsung?
Am I the only one to incur a loss?
Rather than the regenerative medicine research,
the expedient transfer of stocks...
using biotechnology stocks,
the succession line for Hyunsung...
and Chairman Kang Hyun Joon's ambition...
would be more useful to get high ratings.
I'll look forward to hearing your wise decision.
Do you understand?
I want you to stop digging into...
Anchor Choi Sang Hyuk's family.
I'd like you to stop...
arousing controversy about child abuse.
(The Rights and Responsibilities of Patients)
"The rights and responsibilities of patients".
"Hyunsung Medical Centre".
Read it.
It's a doctor's responsibility...
to request for help from the police...
when child abuse is suspected.
That's why you should stop treating this patient...
from this moment on.
By my authority,
I'm giving you the order.
You think this is unfair, don't you?
If you're against my decision,
there's only one solution.
You need to leave this hospital.
But you don't want to do that.
There's a reason you stick with Hyunsung.
I don't know what it is, though.
One more thing.
Choi Sang Hyuk...
is aware that you're a psychopath.
He found out about that somehow.
Has Dr Lee been completely defeated?
Choi Sang Hyuk won a complete victory.
Has it been concluded that it wasn't child abuse?
That's why Dr Lee can no longer treat him.
Even the great Lee Young Oh...
can't defeat Choi Sang Hyuk with the power of media.
Hyunsung...
chose the promotion of the regenerative medicine...
over Dr Lee Young Oh.
That's why they took Choi Sang Hyuk's side.
Am I right? What do you think?
Dr Hyun Suk Joo, the new star of this hospital.
Have some pizza.
I'm curious.
Will Dr Lee give in just like this?
Patient Choi Yo Seob will...
take another CT scan.
The doctor in charge is me,
Dr Lee Young Oh.
What...
The boy is missing?
Gye...
He asked for you, Dr Lee,
so I brought him here.
I'll go back to the precinct.
I think we should wait...
until his mum recovers before investigating.
Now that I've completed my mission,
I'll get going.
See you later.
- What is it?
-  Is my mum...
very sick, Doctor?
Come on in and sit down.
Sit here.
Good.
Is that why you wanted to become a doctor?
You wanted to cure your mum's disease?
This is just between you and me.
Since you want to become a doctor,
I'll tell you a secret that I haven't told to anyone.
It's the thing about being sick.
It makes your true self disappear.
A healthy person can become skinny.
Sometimes, people's appearances change.
That's what happened to your mum.
Then,
please change her back.
Make her just the way she used to be.
I don't trust you.
You were afraid of the surgery,
but your weren't...
afraid of your mum.
Or were you?
It was bearable.
You should have told someone.
At least to your dad.
I thought that if my dad hates my mum,
I could lose her.
Then, I'd be left alone.
People in the hospital...
think you've disappeared.
Appear in front of them...
and surprise them.
I just told you to go.
I forgot...
the way to my room.
You forgot...
the way to your room?
Doctor,
what was it?
The test I took.
The thing about the lie...
You said that people can lie...
Our bodies can't lie.
Dr Lee Young Oh is the only one who can do this.
There's a large meningioma...
here in the right frontal lobe.
Honey, I heard that I did it because I was sick.
It was the disease that made me to the things...
to our son.
It was because I was sick.
If Dr Lee performs this surgery,
he'll remove the tumour safely.
It might take some time,
but you could regain your original personality.
If Dr Lee is the only option in this hospital,
I'll transfer her to another hospital.
Sir.
It's a very dangerous surgery.
If the surgeon is not as good as Dr Lee,
your wife's life...
could be in danger during the surgery.
If you continue to insist Dr Lee as our surgeon,
then we have no choice.
We'll be leaving this hospital.
The reason behind your abusive behaviour...
isn't what's relevant.
The issue is that you're my wife.
Whether you're actually ill or not,
don't ever admit...
to abusing our son.
Get your head on straight.
Choi Sang Hyuk speaking.
When your son was admitted,
I implicated you...
as an abusive parent.
What did you say?
The symptoms of physical abuse were clear,
but there were no bruises present.
Being a news anchor,
I figured...
that you could be completely discreet.
But the real culprit was...
your son.
Bumpy and glamorous.
He sang under the comforter alone...
to endure the pain.
The comforter dampened his external injuries.
Tomato.
Your son was afraid...
that exposing the truth...
would isolate him.
Hence, he couldn't tell anyone.
While the poor child...
struggled to protect...
his mother and his family,
where were you?
Admit to your domestic neglect.
Your wife abused your child,
and you...
neglected your family.
He'll need continued treatments after the operation.
If your son's trauma is left untreated,
his frontal lobe will develop complications.
He'll be rendered unable to discern others' emotions.
- That's...
-  That means...
his fear will come to fruition.
He'll become isolated.
He'll become like me.
Please proceed with the operation.
Dr Lee,
please help me.
Honey.
Let's get divorced after the operation.
You'll have to consent to the operation beforehand.
Divorce? Who are you to decide?
You said so yourself.
My illness or our son's abuse is not your concern.
Your problem is that I'm your wife.
I'll be receiving the surgery.
It wasn't on purpose,
but I admit to abusing our son.
I'm going to receive therapy as well.
- Hey, Park Soo Kyung!
-  I'm going to go back!
I'm going to be a good mother to Yo Seob again.
Doctor, I have a favour to ask.
When you remove my tumour,
please remove...
the memories...
of how I caused Yo Seob to suffer...
along with it.
(Surgeon: Dr Lee Young Oh)
(Surgery is complete.)
Did you really perform the surgery...
against Chairman Kang's will?
The meningioma patient abused her son?
Yes.
Good job.
No matter the circumstances,
doctors must never give up on their patients first.
What you said...
was right.
Doctors need to empathise with their patients.
I was able to operate on the meningioma patient...
not because of my skills as a surgeon,
but because...
I had empathy for the child.
So...
Lee Young Oh,
what are you getting at?
You...
really had empathy for the patient?
How?
His experience wasn't foreign to me.
That child...
was just like me...
during my childhood.
Aren't you curious...
about the past...
of those two men?
Thank you, Doctor.
I will be a good mother to Yo Seob from now on.
I'll make time...
for you, Dr Lee.
Let's go grab a drink someday.
I...
don't enjoy drinking alcohol.
However, I understand your gesture of goodwill.
You never impeded on your rule for 10 years.
That indicates...
that I've become a special individual to you.
Let's say goodbye and get going.
Thank you, Doctor.
Goodbye.
I won't forget you.
I'll become a good doctor like you no matter what.
Don't.
Don't remember me.
The time you spent here with me.
Forget it all.
Let's say that such events...
never happened.
Live free.
Live energetically.
Go.
Now's the time.
I need...
Wi-Fi.
Can you believe it?
He didn't say a word.
There were no body signals.
Yet, I knew...
what that child was thinking.
Can you believe it?
- Are you listening to me?
-  Yes.
Are you really listening to me?
Gosh, be careful!
You... You didn't feel anything, did you?
Same here.
Let... Let me throw this ball back.
What is this feeling?
I want to make an effort.
It may be impossible.
But for once,
I'd like to make an effort.
Love...
Dr Lee, your training may be over now.
Did you finally begin...
to love your patient?
Oh, my.
No.
It's you.