(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
(Thank you and goodbye.)
Take care.
Ha Eun. Don't sleep during class, okay?
(Episode 11)
Was "don't sleep"...
that sad a statement?
Teenage girls' emotions fluctuate...
as much as their weight.
It is impossible to predict.
Don't forget.
Laugh when others laugh.
When they cry,
that is when you cry.
The area that feels sadness...
is the limbic system.
Frontal lobe, parietal lobe, temporal lobe,
hypothalamus and cerebro-pontine.
Raised cheeks. Down-turned lips.
Furrowed eyebrows.
Body signals of sadness.
Raised cheeks.
Down-turned lips.
Furrowed eyebrows.
Please.
You're so mature, fighting back the tears.
Thank you for trying so hard.
You've given me courage to say goodbye.
Tears.
A protein substance 0.9 percent...
more concentrated than sweat.
The strongest body signal expressing sadness.
I knew everything about tears,
but I never...
learned how to cry.
(Beautiful Mind)
I want to make an effort.
It may be impossible.
But for once,
I'd like to make an effort.
Love?
Dr Lee, your training may be over now.
Did you finally begin...
to love your patient?
No.
You.
What... What did you just say?
Like you said,
I started to love.
I think...
I've begun to love...
you.
I'm not too familiar with this feeling.
Now, it's your turn. Say something.
What do you want me to say?
What you feel.
Go on.
I don't know.
You don't know.
How could you not know?
I can not know...
since I have a disorder.
But you...
You are my Wi-Fi.
You're supposed to explain to me,
but you don't know.
Then where am I supposed to get that answer...
and from whom?
Tell me.
From whom?
What you said was correct.
I will give you...
an answer.
What... What's wrong?
Is this the ER?
I'm Lee Young Oh from Neurosurgery.
Do you have any emergency surgeries?
I'll do them.
I'll run right over, so wait.
Okay.
The ER called with an emergency.
You just called the ER.
Who made the call is irrelevant.
What matters is that it is an emergency.
I need to go operate because it's an emergency.
So I have no other choice...
but to hear your response another time...
since it's an emergency.
But... Wait!
You said you didn't know.
How could you suddenly have an answer?
Don't grab just one of a slew of thoughts...
running through your brain and say that's it.
Think it through.
Reflect on your thoughts...
slowly.
There's plenty of time.
Think about it carefully.
Kang Shin Joo. Age 32.
She has a migraine and is partially paralysed.
We took a brain CT scan...
and suspect her to have moyamoya disease.
She has a unique condition.
She is 29 weeks pregnant.
Doctor, her BP keeps dropping.
Her brain haemorrhage keeps worsening.
If we wait, even treatment with steroids...
may be inadequate.
What if drugs don't work?
You will need surgery.
An emergency surgery.
No. I can't get anaesthesia.
I won't do anything bad for my baby.
Do you see that?
It's proof the haemorrhage is worsening.
Doctor. Doctor.
Diabetes insipidus.
Diabetes insipidus?
All of the fluids in her body...
is being discharged as urine...
because of the enzyme created in the placenta.
That will be dangerous for the foetus.
Dr Yang,
notify Obstetrics.
Once they've completed their surgery,
we will start the emergency surgery.
Yes, Doctor.
No.
You want me to have the baby now?
The baby is only 29 weeks in. That's crazy!
You want me to have a premature baby?
No. I'm leaving. I'm leaving!
- Ma'am!
-  No.
This is a hospital.
Trust us. Okay?
Shin Joo.
Are you okay? What about the baby?
I'm fine.
How about the kids?
- Mummy.
-  Mummy.
Joon Goo.
I'm fine.
Mummy's fine.
Are you her guardian?
She needs emergency surgery.
I won't get surgery.
Surgery? What...
After labour is induced,
we will begin EVD surgery...
to stop the bleeding in the brain.
Labour?
The baby is only 29 weeks.
It's too dangerous.
If we don't,
the mother may die.
I see she has two kids already.
I understand she loves children,
but her life takes priority right now.
Ms Jang, call Obstetrics.
No.
No! I can't.
Calm down.
This baby...
isn't mine.
It isn't my baby.
We notified Obstetrics.
The doctor is heading to the ER.
Okay.
I got it. Okay.
I'm losing my mind.
Stand up straight!
Punk.
You really became a doctor.
You used to skip classes when you were young...
thanks to your parents' influence.
Who are you?
It's me.
Samgwang Middle School.
It's me, Han Mo. Jung Han Mo.
Han Mo. Jung Han Mo?
Han Mo?
Why have you changed so much?
I didn't recognise you.
- How have you been?
-  Good.
Look at you.
Every time I got new basketball sneakers,
you used to take them from me. Do you want to die?
It's thanks to my taking your sneakers...
that you didn't play basketball and became a doctor.
I'm so proud of you.
You're right. Thanks.
Do you want a taste of my drop kick?
Stop overreacting.
Stop that. I'm tired.
Hey.
It hurts.
Han Mo.
Han Mo. Hey. Hey!
Han Mo. Han Mo!
What are you doing?
Come on!
I don't know what happened.
I need to close this up.
- Bring me the kit.
-  Okay.
Careful.
- Hurry.
-  Hey, you!
What? What?
You seem like a real doctor.
This isn't a joke.
A surrogate? Do you mean...
you lent your womb?
Ma'am.
Did you know about this?
It's good for both parties...
who are in need.
She introduced me to the parents of the baby.
She takes care of me.
Shin Joo.
Be strong...
and tough it out for one week.
There's a difference between...
a 29-week premature baby...
and an impatient 30-week baby that came early.
Which do you think would be better?
I'll try.
I'll do all I can.
Please talk to the parents for me.
Did you hear that?
I won't give birth.
I can't.
Ma'am.
This is no time to think about 29 weeks...
or 30 weeks...
and let your delusions take control.
Your brain already started to bleed.
Nobody can predict...
what will happen.
On top of that,
the baby in your womb...
may not even see...
the inside of an incubator,
which you people detest so much,
and die...
from lack of oxygen.
If you don't get surgery now,
it may die. Do you understand me?
It may die.
If I have it now,
my children and I...
will die.
This baby's parents...
are paying our rent...
and living expenses...
in exchange for a healthy baby.
Don't look at me like that.
I am helping people in need.
I can't have the baby now.
Not for my children's sake.
Decide.
This was your decision.
Okay. Answer me.
Go on.
Dr Lee.
Answer me.
Are you...
asking her to decide...
or trying to scare her?
You push and...
demand an answer and a decision.
You should be understanding of her situation first.
You should give her time to think, too.
It's so obvious.
This is how you treat your girlfriends, isn't it?
I gave her time.
Plenty of time...
to reflect and think.
To whom?
Ms Jang.
Why don't you...
take on that patient?
The baby's heart will struggle to last two days.
If you're so confident, get her to consent to surgery.
What?
While understanding her situation...
and giving her plenty of time.
But...
(Wi-Fi)
Wi-Fi?
Wi-Fi? Why?
Did you hate seeing your unemployed brother...
- play games to cut...?
-  That's not it.
That's not it. I said it isn't.
If you annoy me again, I'll cut off your Wi-Fi. Got it?
Is that your answer?
You punk.
Dr Lee.
Let me make myself clear.
I will not accept an answer like this...
that is not at a designated time and place.
I won't accept a notification.
Wait a second.
Are you angry right now?
Yes, I am angry right now.
It is all your fault.
Seeing a foolish patient make a bad decision...
annoyed and frustrated me.
I've never felt this way before.
And I've been saying stupid things.
When I think about you,
I say stupid things.
Ever since you jumped in the water,
I've been a total...
But what's more shocking is...
that I don't hate...
this side of me.
I heard Ms Kang Shin Joo is your patient.
Neurology was notified that she's getting steroids.
Is she in emergency surgery right now?
Dr Lee.
You may hate me.
But this isn't about me.
We've decided...
to operate,
if the patient decides to.
If the patient decides to?
You're waiting?
I'm waiting...
for Ms Jang to convince her.
The patient is deciding on a surgery...
and you asked a nurse for help?
For your surgery?
Who made you this way?
You've...
changed.
What do you mean?
Why don't we take an MRI or a PET...
of your brain?
Are you still...
playing my doctor?
Dr Kim.
Come any time...
if you still need me.
You're back early.
Weren't you at Hyunsung Group's performance meeting?
They attacked me like crazy...
because we're the least profitable in the group.
I don't need to stay and applaud like an idiot...
every time the others present their profits.
Once the regenerative medicine enters the market,
the group's attitude will change.
It changed already.
My brother is already on guard.
He appreciates how big the market is.
He's looking for losses in the hospital to push me out,
so that he can claim the regenerative medicine.
I need to bring it into the black somehow...
before the next fiscal period.
We don't have a method...
Yes, we do.
The fastest and most effective way.
Downsizing.
Manpower is only useful when you need it.
If you don't need it...
If it's sweet, you swallow. If it's bitter,
you spit it out any time.
Outsource whatever you can,
and convert expensive, experienced workers...
into contract workers.
Get rid of anyone on maternity or paternity leave.
It'll get rid of any notions of getting money for free.
Nice.
I'm 30 weeks pregnant, too.
I'm turning 40 soon. It's so late, isn't it?
The nurses took turns getting pregnant.
I don't want to hear it.
I don't have a job.
I'm protecting this baby to protect my children.
If your brain haemorrhage persists,
your children...
will end up as orphans.
Even if her brain haemorrhage persists,
the baby in her womb will be fine...
as long as she has a respirator, right?
It's better than an incubator.
The parents of the baby would prefer...
What did you say?
Be realistic.
Do you want to be out on the streets?
It's a hospital. They'll keep you alive.
Tough it out for one week.
No. Just 3 to 4 days. You have to.
Mr Nam.
Can you throw out this woman?
- What?
-  I can't listen any more.
It's bad for my baby.
Oh my gosh.
Oh my gosh. Excuse me. Oh my gosh.
Excuse me. Oh my gosh. Excuse me.
Don't lose to jerks like that.
Even if we get swayed by money,
let's not lose.
The kids need a mum...
in this crazy world.
Live.
Be healthy.
Don't give up.
This is where you were.
Go in and see your mummy.
- Mummy!
-  Good.
How did it go?
Will she...
get surgery?
If I choose a patient,
it means she will get surgery.
I've always wanted to say that.
It sounded cool.
I'll let you know...
once the surgery has been scheduled.
Ms Jang.
I need you...
during my surgery.
When I want a staff member,
that person...
must be in my OR.
Do you understand?
If I choose a patient...
Once was enough. Don't overdo it.
Okay, then.
Mr Nam.
All that working out paid off.
I almost fell for you.
Fine. Be that way.
Sorry that a mum fell for you.
What?
What's wrong? Did something happen?
Log into the intranet...
and check for yourself.
There are new assignments.
(Jang Moon Kyung)
(Cardio-cerebrovascular Centre, PA Nurse)
(Hyunsung Museum of Medicine, Manager)
We have all the volunteers for the free treatments.
Once treatments begin,
we'll begin media propaganda...
Mr Lee.
Director Lee.
What have I done wrong?
Did something happen?
I got pregnant after seven years of marriage.
I'm almost 40.
The hospital told the nurses to take turns having kids.
You said to reduce my hours...
during pregnancy because it's tiring,
but I never once did that...
for the hospital's sake.
Ms Jang, what do you think you're doing?
There is a process for everything.
If you have a complaint, you should...
Is it because I am pregnant?
Is that why you transferred a PA nurse...
to manage a medical museum?
It's the group being considerate.
A way to protect a mother's health.
It's better for the foetus to be in an office...
than working on your feet in an OR.
You're telling me to resign on my own...
because with my maternity leave,
I won't benefit the hospital.
Ms Jang.
It is true...
that the transfers were planned.
However, it was not planned to get rid of...
seasoned nurses as yourself.
I'll look into it.
- Director Lee.
-  Would you...
please trust me and wait?
Is Mr Kang in his office?
Why?
Contrary to the planned downsizing,
the experienced nurses are being cut.
I need to check for myself.
Please, don't do that.
Dr Hyun.
Bringing Hyunsung into the black...
is critical for our regenerative medicine.
If we stay in the red,
we'll have to get outside investors...
to get the funding for our research needs.
Then our research...
will be controlled by money.
If the results are influenced by money...
Think about it.
Rather than prioritise safety,
the patients will be used for profit.
I want to prevent that...
from happening to our regenerative medicine.
Dr Hyun is correct.
If it isn't the best option,
you need wisdom to choose the lesser evil.
Please accept...
the downsizing.
Tell me.
What is it?
Ms Lee Hae Joo...
will assist Kang Shin Joo's surgery.
The nurse that I want...
is you, Ms Jang.
You know Ms Lee.
She's light and quick,
so she won't upset you.
If I want someone with quicker hands than you,
I can find over 100 in this hospital alone.
Look, Ms Jang.
If Ms Kang changes her mind during surgery,
you are the only one...
who can change her mind back.
That's why I can't do it.
It's humiliating.
It's humiliating?
Why?
I thought I was fighting well with my baby.
Because of the low birth rate,
they made it sound like as long I had a baby,
society would help raise it.
I thought I was a working mum.
But?
But I am...
nothing but a way to cut costs here.
A money-eating hippo.
How could I dare tell Ms Kang...
to be strong,
that it'll be okay...
and to have the baby?
I can't do that.
- Poor Ms Jang.
-  I heard.
I feel so bad for her.
How could they do that?
What's going on?
She's pregnant, too.
- What will she do?
-  I heard.
Did you eat?
What are you chatting about?
Ms Jang, I have a favour to ask.
My patient is a total idiot.
When we were in middle school,
he'd steal all of my basketball sneakers.
I can't believe I met my enemy here.
It's a small world.
You should be a good person.
It was insane yesterday.
Blood was gushing from his temporal artery.
I didn't know if I should...
just leave him or stay with him.
But I'm a doctor after all.
- I was choosing between life and death...
-  And?
Dr Schweitzer that lives in my DNA spoke to me,
so I stitched him up perfectly.
I bet you made it crooked...
and made sure it hurt a lot.
How did you know that?
You need to pinch it hard...
when you stitch up the temporal artery.
Did you hear that?
You're awesome. High-five.
High-five!
Give him a strong antibiotic.
An antibiotic?
Unasyn?
Yes, of course.
Make sure it hurts.
That's what matters.
- Dr Yang.
-  Yes?
- Thank you.
-  For what?
For comforting me.
What, did I get caught again?
Why am I so nice and considerate?
I better run away.
Dr Yang Sung Eun said you're a friend of his.
He asked me to take good care of you.
We were in the same class, but not very close.
He got good grades, and his family was rich.
He was good at sports, too.
He was a jerk though, right?
Rub here.
The jerk is here.
I heard what you two said.
I did what you asked me to do.
Do you mean the antibiotic, Unasyn?
Not that.
I made the injection as painful as possible.
Gosh.
Your test result just came out.
You're suffering from malnutrition.
Let me take a look.
Goodness. You really have malnutrition.
- You have an ulcer in your mouth.
-  Gosh.
It's not like I'm a poor kid in Somalia.
Why don't you rest for a week and get a check-up?
I'll get fired.
If I take one week of unpaid leave,
I'll be kicked out because I can't afford the rent.
You're still the same rich boy...
who never went through any hardships in life.
That's ridiculous.
You have no idea what I've been going through here.
I work 12 hours a day every day.
I don't even have time to go home.
I don't have time to date, either. It's hard.
My monthly salary is less than 2,000 dollars after tax.
Next year, I'll start my fellowship.
It's practically an unpaid work.
Okay?
Still,
you're a doctor.
When we were in middle school,
we sat side by side,
but now,
we live in different worlds.
Do you know...
why I stole your sneakers?
How would I know that?
I wanted to see the boy who has everything...
get angry.
But I failed.
You came to school in a new pair of shoes.
They were nicer than the old ones.
Be quiet. Listen to me.
There's an artery right here.
I'm getting angry as I think about that incident.
My hands are starting to shake.
If my hands keep shaking, I might damage your artery.
Do you still want me to get angry?
I'm sorry.
I was young.
Gosh. Life is so unfair.
I remembered you, but you didn't recognise me.
Hey, that's just because...
your appearance changed so much.
You look a bit burnt, too. That's why...
Hey! Hey!
What's wrong? Hey!
Nurse!
Gosh.
Where is Ms Jang Moon Kyung?
Why do you ask?
She gave my patient...
an antibiotic and he's in anaphylactic shock.
Where is Ms Jang?
Why is he in anaphylactic shock?
I gave him Unasyn as you told me.
Did you do a skin allergy test?
It's essential to do that before giving Unasyn.
Of course, I did.
I attended to patients longer than you did.
I would never make that kind of mistake.
You can't...
Maybe you were mistaken.
What else could have caused it?
Ms Jang probably thought...
the transfer was unfair,
so she decided to get back at the hospital.
She wouldn't make such a basic mistake.
She's too soft-hearted to do that.
She's carrying a baby, too.
Dr Yoo.
Not everyone is like you.
She must have been distracted.
You know how hard she worked...
to become a PA nurse despite her pregnancy.
It really is unfair.
Why would she work at a museum?
They want her to resign.
They couldn't say they didn't want a pregnant employee.
Use your brain.
Ms Jang has a good reputation.
The union won't let this slide.
So the hospital is giving her the choice...
to accept the transfer or quit her job.
It's a conspiracy theory.
Hyunsung Medical Centre is the conspirator...
in this theory.
Why did you ambush us like that?
Goodness.
How long have you been here, Dr Lee?
I was here before you came in...
and started this enthusiastic discussion.
So...
regardless of whether or not it was a mistake,
or if the hospital administrators conspired,
the patient is suffering from anaphylactic shock...
because of what Ms Jang did.
Is that correct?
How is he doing?
He was...
He was brought here for malnutrition.
Now, he's suffering from anaphylactic shock.
My friend here...
can't even afford a health examination.
Your friend?
Is he your friend?
He and I went to the same school.
He's a friend of mine.
- No reaction.
-  It seems...
that he hasn't eaten well maybe because he was busy.
He has an ulcer in his mouth.
I examined him yesterday.
All of his joints are damaged...
probably because he worked too hard.
He has joint pains, as well?
Let me see.
Dr Lee, we always...
complain...
that we work more than the maximum hours.
But he...
Are you worried because he's your friend?
Or are you pitying him...
because he's poor?
If you let your emotions cloud your judgement,
you won't find out what caused the anaphylactic shock.
Although, you may be able to comfort yourself...
by thinking that you're a good person.
Pardon?
You said you didn't see Ms Jang...
doing a skin allergy test, right?
Yes.
Where is Ms Jang?
I...
didn't do anything wrong.
I've worked in this hospital for a long time.
I don't want to leave being falsely accused like this.
I believe you're not in a position...
to argue what's right or wrong in this matter.
At least...
give me a chance to prove it wasn't my mistake, please.
Please put off the transfer until then. I'll stay...
He's in anaphylactic shock. What more should I say?
If you complicate this situation,
it'll damage the reputation of the hospital...
and you'll be labelled for committing malpractice.
She didn't...
make any mistakes.
What happened to the patient...
wasn't because of Ms Jang.
It wasn't medical malpractice, either.
It turns out that he doesn't have malnutrition.
He has lupus.
His face was sunburned severely...
due to light sensitivity, a symptom of lupus.
The mouth ulcer...
and the joint pains...
are symptoms of lupus, as well.
He has lupus?
Then, he shouldn't have been prescribed Unasyn.
That's correct.
It wasn't Ms Jang...
who caused the anaphylactic shock.
It happened because there weren't...
seasoned nurses like Ms Jang...
in the emergency room.
The culprit is the cheap substitute workers...
who didn't look into the patient's medical history...
and didn't do the drug allergy test.
More precisely,
the real cause was...
Chairman Kang Hyun Joon's cost cutting plan.
Ms Jang...
isn't the cause of losses for this hospital.
She's my surgical assistant.
Ms Jang,
do you think you can assist me...
on the surgery of Patient Kang Shin Joo?
Ms Jang?
I'll book an OR.
Wait for me.
- Yes, Mum.
-  Yes, Mum.
Ta-da.
You two wait here, okay?
- Okay.
-  Good boys.
I'll begin the surgery.
I'll start with an EVD.
Let's begin.
Are you happy?
Why are you smiling at the reflection of yourself?
I'm not. A doctor should know how to treat diseases.
Is your first task as the director...
fighting against me over authority?
You want me to cancel the reorganisation of manpower?
The mistakes of inexperienced nurses...
are causing medical malpractices.
The complaints will lead to lawsuits,
and the legal expenses...
will cost the hospital a fortune.
This balance sheet will show you...
how much more the unreasonable reorganisation...
will cost the hospital.
Like they say, "Office changes manners."
You're learning very quickly.
Chairman Kang Il Do, your father,
is looking at the same report as we speak.
You're good at calculating profits and losses.
I believe we will come to the same conclusion.
You once said...
that a monster like me...
doesn't belong in this hospital.
This hospital values profit more than lives...
and you are the current director of this place.
Which one of us is the real monster?
Oh, wow. What's this?
Where are your manners?
When you receive a present,
you should at least pretend to be happy or open it.
Let's call it even.
I know they're not good enough for your preference.
You can wear them when you work.
I think...
I feel like the burden of guilt has been...
lifted off my shoulders.
Fine. I'll buy you a drink later.
Let's not make promises we won't keep.
I don't think we'll ever meet again.
Take care.
Doctor.
Wait up.
Hey, Patient.
Lupus is not a fatal disease.
You should take good care of yourself.
Be careful in the sun.
Try to avoid working too much and getting stressed.
Answer me.
I work outside in the sun all day long...
to install air conditioners.
I always work overtime.
So thank you for your advice.
- Just go.
-  Get back to work.
Bye.
Dr Lee,
I was a good doctor to my friend thanks to you.
He even gave me a present.
Thank you for your help.
You should be thanking...
Ms Jang.
Don't you think so?
Ms Jang, please.
I'm really sorry.
He bought me shoes.
Let me take a look.
Patient Kang Shin Joo decided...
to give up on this baby.
She can't afford to raise the baby.
The baby was needed by everyone,
but in the end, wanted by no one.
Still, I'm happy that you came into this world.
Sometimes in life,
someone you didn't expect reaches out to help you.
I saw a miraculous thing like that happen.
It will happen to you, as well.
You'll figure out how to go on with your life.
Welcome to this world.
Dr Lee.
Yes?
Would it be okay if I give you my answer now?
Right here? On this street?
You want to give me your answer...
on this crowded, noisy street?
Then, where should we...
So,
may I tell you my answer now?
I thought a lot...
about you...
and about me.
I mean, about us.
- I've decided...
-  It's so nice.
The air tonight is so nice.
Dr Lee...
Please give me your hand.
- Your hand.
-  My hand?
- Come on.
-  Why?
- Stand up.
-  Okay.
You're very nervous.
- I am?
-  Yes.
Wouldn't it be better to talk later...
when you feel more relaxed?
Playing a sport...
is the best way to relieve nervousness.
- Shall we play a game?
-  Pardon?
Throw it.
- Can I just throw it?
-  Yes.
- Did you see that?
-  Yes, I saw it.
You pulled it off at your first attempt.
- One more time. Good luck.
-  Here I go.
I'm good at this, right?
You're not bad.
Give me the ball.
Here I go.
All right.
Foul.
- Stop.
-  Goodness.
That's it. No!
Wait!
It's in.
Wait. No!
- You're travelling!
-  I am!
- Goodness. No!
- Come this way.
-  This way?
Like this?
Shoot!
That was the first half.
- What?
-  The second half begins now.
Dr Lee, I'm too exhausted. I can't play any more.
Why not? You're on fire today.
Let's keep playing. It's fun.
Gosh...
Are you really tired?
Yes.
I guess that's it for today.
Since you're tired,
let's leave our talk for tomorrow, too.
Well...
Hold on, Dr Lee.
I...
Don't you see why I'm being this way?
What?
I...
have never been afraid...
in my life.
Not even once. However,
right now,
you're the one making me most afraid.
I'm afraid of what you might say...
and upon hearing your words,
I don't know how I'd react.
That's...
what I'm afraid of.
Let's have our talk...
tomorrow.
This is my answer.
You wouldn't let me speak.
I know I'm not ready for this,
but if it's with you, I'd like to give it a shot.
Thank you for the drink.
Min Jae, you were right.
I'm...
I'm changing.
I want an MRI.
The result is out.
It's just as I expected.
Director Lee.
The worst scenario happened.
We got a massive amount of foreign investments.
Is it true...
that we're accepting foreign investments?
It's been a long time, my friend.
What happened?
He fell off a building at a construction site.
He fell while installing air conditioners.
Sir, Sir.
There was no safety bar there.
He was installing them without any safety equipment.
Epidural.
Get him an epidural right now.
Yes, Doctor.
- Where's the emergency patient?
-  In the ER.
Thank you.
What happened?
I...
just discharged him.
What happened?
He fell while installing...
an air conditioner.
Darn it.
How could this happen?
I saved his life...
only hours ago.
How is this possible?
Get out of my way.
Doctor, please save him.
Please save him.
This doesn't make any sense.
How could he die so easily?
How can it be this easy?
We did everything we could...
in order to save him.
Doctor, we can't just let him die like this.
This isn't right.
Han Mo.
I...
never learned how to cry.
The dysfunction on your frontal lobe...
is just as how it was.
Nothing has changed.
Dr Lee.
Is now the time...
you need Wi-Fi?
No.
The signal...
was never there.
Not even once.
I have been fooled all this time.
I...
don't want to deceive you.
Did something happen?
I never changed.
I'm still the same,
and I will always be like this.
You and I are over now.
End of...
transmission.
(Beautiful Mind)
Can you pretend that nothing ever happened?
Is that possible for you?
What about me?
Should I tell her that she's going to be paralysed...
and needs a respirator for the rest of her life?
Surgery won't be easy.
I'm asking you to give us some time...
so we can be together.
"Time so we can be together..."
Is it your patient's wish or your own?
I'm curious myself.
Dr Lee Young Oh.
I wonder which side he'll take.