(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
I am happy.
Dr Lee.
This isn't right.
You can't drag this child...
into such a dangerous surgery because of your son.
Didn't you hear?
His parents abandoned him.
My doctor appeared like an angel...
and operated on me.
Shouldn't we tell his guardian?
Dr Lee.
This is malpractice.
I am his guardian from this day forth.
Then, he became my dad.
He must have liked me.
I am very happy.
(Beautiful Mind)
Is it true...
that we are accepting foreign investments?
Does that mean we no longer own...
the research on regenerative medicine...
and stem cell treatment?
Will a multinational pharmaceutical firm own them?
In exchange, Hyunsung Group will be mine.
We poured so much effort on the regenerative medicine.
We can't just hand it over...
to those who only care about money.
Will you please reconsider it?
I beg you.
Gosh, I had no idea you'd be this easy.
Come on, stand up.
I just arranged this occasion...
in order to introduce you to an old friend of yours.
You would be very glad to see him.
Do you remember Doctor Oh Young Bae?
It's been a long time,
my friend.
Gosh, why would you be against such a good friend?
President Oh Young Bae of Green Pharmacy...
made a large investment for our regenerative medicine.
Your son has grown up well.
With his frontal lobe damaged,
he's unable to empathise.
You didn't say anything,
but you must have been waiting.
I'm talking about the MRI scan.
You thought there would be a change...
and that you'd be able to feel emotions.
Am I right?
Not at all.
I'm glad how things turned out.
I found out how uncertain and temporarily feelings...
could change people...
or make them unsure.
I know for certain now.
That's enough for me.
Right now,
I'm at peace with the way I am.
This is what you always say.
"Your lips may lie,"
"but your body..."
"can't hide it."
All right.
Which patient do you need my second opinion on?
My face hurts everywhere.
It feels like I was either cut by a knife or got burnt.
She had brain tumour surgery a year ago.
The tumour has been moved,
but she's suffering from chronic facial pain.
I've heard about you.
You've cured Kim Myung Soo...
and Kang Il Do of Hyunsung Group.
Doctor.
I can't live like this any more.
Please make my pain go away.
There are nerves...
in my face, right?
Please remove them.
I'm all right with that.
I will do anything to get rid of this pain.
Please, Doctor.
- Ma'am.
-  Yes?
The nerves on your face...
have already been removed.
They were removed during your surgery a year ago.
It still hurts.
Are you sure?
My face still hurts.
The medical term is neuropathic pain.
To compensate for the loss of nerves,
your brain is making you feel pain that isn't real.
Just like other people,
are you saying...
that I've lost my mind?
I'm suffering so much that...
every day is difficult to bear.
Why?
Perhaps,
suffering is necessary.
Life without suffering is not real.
That's what she's saying.
Young Oh.
You were...
the only person who was kind to me...
without any reason.
When...
I found out that you were being fake,
my life seemed fake, too.
I couldn't bear it.
I was angry.
I thought it was just rage,
but I know now.
I was just in pain.
It was pain?
What do you mean?
If it becomes...
possible one day,
accept...
suffering as is.
Perhaps, that's what...
normal people do.
I didn't know, either.
Do you think we can start over?
From the beginning?
Isn't it funny how life turns out?
You and I get to meet again.
What do you want?
Why did you appear in front of me again?
Joint investment...
in regenerative medicine.
Patent for the stem cell treatment.
Join my Green Pharmacy.
What are friends for?
Regenerative medicine?
I put my life into that research.
I wanted to give patients with incurable diseases hope.
I dreamed that...
no surgeons would be needed any more someday.
Why don't you want to work with me?
There's no other company that contributed to...
the public health as much as us.
Your international pharmaceutical company...
has done enough.
I know enough.
To get patents for new medicine,
you lobbied...
and spent tremendous amounts of money,
but you had no interest in treating or curing patients.
Then,
with patients' lives as collateral,
you only cared about raising the price of the medicine.
If I hand over the stem cell treatment to you,
patients won't die of diseases.
You'll kill them by not providing them the treatment.
I won't let you do that...
to what I've sacrificed my life for.
You told me that...
you'll devote your life to help that child...
live like a normal person.
I'm starting to wonder...
what your focus is on.
You don't have the right...
to ridicule my life.
Are you sure...
I don't?
Look at me. I'm in a wheelchair.
Is Dr Lee in Neurosurgery?
I heard he's now a better surgeon than you are.
I wonder...
if he can fix my legs.
I think I'll ask him in person.
He knows, right?
Does he know his frontal lobe is dysfunctional...
and that he's a psychopath...
because of your mistake?
Does he know it was medical malpractice?
Goodness.
Does he not know?
Please wait.
Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
(Wi-Fi)
Pardon me.
Why aren't you picking up your phone?
I thought about it.
You're smarter and more eloquent than I am.
I can't win by arguing, right?
Can we not complicate things?
What I wanted from you...
and what I wanted to do for you was...
to spend time.
I want to spend time with you.
Is that not enough?
It's Ewing sarcoma in the cervical vertebrae.
Surgery won't be easy.
Should I tell him that he's going to be paralysed...
and needs a respirator for the rest of his life?
It'll be terrible for the wife to hear.
They're newly-weds, and she's eight-months pregnant.
He wants to hug his baby at least once.
That's the reality of every emergency case.
They ask to be hospitalised and ask for surgery.
What's the point when the patient has no hope?
It's nonsense.
Don't be so harsh on the newly-weds.
Is it that difficult to tell your patient...
your diagnosis?
The patient is yours.
Good luck.
You'll do great.
We're leaving.
It's Ewing sarcoma in C3.
You have a tumour.
Surgery in this area is risky.
Paralysis...
Until the cancer spreads,
he'll need a respirator for the rest of his life.
If the tumour spreads to the nerves of the spine,
radiation treatment is the only way.
If oedema occurs, there's nothing you can do.
Did I miss anything?
You seem to know what you're talking about.
We were turned down by 12 to 13 hospitals...
for the same reason.
Shall I continue?
Isn't she smart?
She's my wife.
Doctor, you must be mistaken.
I'm not asking you...
to cure my husband's disease.
I'm not asking you to extend his life for 10 years.
I'm asking you...
to buy him time until our baby is born.
Time we can spend together.
I'm not...
asking you to do something impossible.
Please help him...
live just one more month.
He deserves to see his baby.
He has to see who it resembles.
I'm saying the surgery is difficult.
Pardon me.
I will take...
this surgery.
Is it confidence...
or arrogance?
The surgery is risky.
Why won't he just stick to chemotherapy?
It's risky,
but the patient and his wife want it.
I think it's a risk worth taking.
The patient wants to see his baby.
How can you ignore such a wish?
What's going on between you two?
After working with him a few times,
are you being duped by the look in his eyes?
Look.
Red sun.
Dr Lee can't empathise with his patients.
He just wants to do that surgery...
only to satisfy his curiosity in medicine.
Dr Soh...
has something personal against Dr Lee,
but his analysis is accurate.
The surgery is possible because it's Dr Lee.
It's true. Success rate is minimal,
and it's a risky surgery.
Most surgeons would be too scared.
It'd be a disaster from the start, right?
I didn't expect this.
You've chosen patients based on probability so far.
Why would you...
choose a patient...
who has little...
to no chances of survival?
Is it the patient or you who's desperate?
Are you desperate...
to prove your superiority by taking on a risky surgery?
I'm very curious...
about the reason why I...
chose to do this.
If you become my business partner,
I'll only think about our future.
What would happen...
to Lee Young Oh once he finds out the secret...
you've been keeping from him?
Will you be okay?
It's a consent form.
The surgery will be very difficult.
Ewing sarcoma is a tumour in the bone.
It may spread easily.
If the surgery result isn't good,
you'll live the rest of your life...
as a quadriplegic while depending on a respirator.
I'm already in a wheelchair.
What I want to know about...
is you.
No one recommended the surgery as it's risky.
It probably means it's risky for the patient,
but doesn't it also mean it's risky for the doctor?
Responsibility, honour.
It may negatively impact those things.
Why did you agree on this surgery?
I mean, why did you choose me?
Why would you ask that?
Don't be so moved by him.
He's a surgery machine.
He wants to become more famous.
He wants to show the world that he can do it.
Right?
You learn things just by walking around the hospital.
Are you all right?
You're so precious.
Please understand even if it's uncomfortable.
Which shall I understand?
A surgery machine who wants to be famous?
Or this act?
It doesn't matter what you think, Doctor,
as long as...
you keep him next to me.
Please help...
my husband...
live a little longer.
Sign the consent form for the surgery.
Agree that you'll follow my decisions and methods.
You signed the consent form, which means...
that you'll follow...
my methods of treatment and decisions.
Ma'am.
Acting overly affectionate...
towards your husband doesn't help him.
I don't think it's time for your regular check-up yet.
Are you feeling sick?
I...
transferred to the Violent Crimes Division.
I wanted to get a check-up before I get one...
for the transfer job.
It was hard to get into that division.
I don't want my heart condition to stop me.
That's great.
You wanted to join the Violent Crimes Division.
You're working hard...
to commercialise the regenerative medicine.
I'll get going.
I'll call you when the test results are out.
Dr Hyun.
I have a question.
Thinking is done in the head,
but when I think about someone,
why does my heart hurt instead of my head?
- Wait a minute.
-  What's going on?
I can't do it.
I can't let him get this surgery.
Ma'am, what did you say?
This surgery...
is way too risky.
There's a reason why no doctor would do it.
What if...
he doesn't wake up after the surgery?
You signed the consent form.
That's because the doctor told me to.
That consent form isn't important.
- Let's go.
-  Ma'am, what are you doing?
Dr Yang, she's right.
Let me ask again.
Are you giving up...
on this surgery?
- Yes.
-  No.
Let's think this over, okay?
I'm scared.
I want this surgery.
Come on.
Didn't you hear me?
I'm scared.
I don't want it.
Eun Joo.
Be quiet and wait.
I'm going to make it.
Let's go, Doctor.
How can you treat me like that?
I'm going to tell our baby what you did.
Please forgive her, Doctor.
To an immature girl...
like her,
I am the world to her...
despite my incurable disease.
She means the world to me, too.
We have no other family members.
That's why we come off as offensive.
We're just trying...
to protect each other.
That's also why...
I couldn't give up this surgery.
I want to see my son.
I need to see...
if I can trust him enough...
to protect her...
when I die.
That way, I'll be able to die in peace.
Doctor.
Please promise me.
Let's begin.
I heard Young Oh...
is doing a risky surgery.
He enjoys risky surgeries...
just like you.
He's definitely...
someone you made.
Haven't you decided yet...
as to which side to take?
Doctor.
The surgery went well.
Tumours found during the test...
were all removed.
Don't make it complicated.
Does that mean...
my husband is alive?
You're saying he's okay, right?
He is so far.
Honey.
Dr Lee is incredible.
He removed all the Ewing sarcoma tumours.
I saw the scans.
It was clean.
Only Dr Lee could do the surgery.
It was good for both the patient and Dr Lee...
to have taken the risk.
Recovery is more important.
What's the point if the patient doesn't survive?
- That's right.
-  Hey.
How's the patient?
Do you think he'll recover soon?
It's needless to say.
Of course, it won't be easy.
Are the results that bad?
I'm saying there's not much to say.
Patients Dr Lee chooses always survive.
- What?
-  What?
The surgery went well.
The results are good, too.
The patient is going outside today.
- Going outside?
-  Going outside?
We had to hurry to the hospital,
so we didn't have time to prepare for the baby.
We'll be right back after buying some baby clothes.
Just don't be late for our appointment.
You said we'd be eating out.
Okay, let's do that, too.
Thank you, Doctor.
I'd kiss you if I could,
but my husband might get jealous, so I won't.
Thank goodness.
Thank you.
The surgery must have gone well.
The patient even went out.
No.
Tumour I didn't detect in the scans...
spread to the nerves of the spine.
I'm planning to switch to radiation treatment.
Why did you allow him to leave?
Doctors...
don't save people's lives.
They only extend their lives.
Arguing, laughing, talking and eating...
with loved ones.
Those daily, meaningless things.
People on average tend to find happiness...
in those things.
Happiness that I have not...
felt yet.
Those are feelings I've never learned...
or experienced.
You took on a risky surgery.
Based on the results,
you may be held responsible.
I hope the radiation treatment works.
Is that why you took the risk?
Is it?
Was it because of the patient's desperation?
What I wanted from you...
and what I wanted to do for you was...
to spend time.
I want to spend time with you.
I'm asking you to buy him time.
Time we can spend together.
Please let him stay with me longer...
so I can...
see him...
as long as possible.
Time.
Time to spend...
with someone.
- He's an emergency patient. Make way.
-  Oh, no.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry that I asked you to go out with me.
I didn't know...
Are you okay?
Take him to his room and call Dr Lee Young Oh.
- Please hurry.
-  Yes, Doctor.
Doctor.
I'm sorry...
for nagging you to let me go out...
despite your warning.
I'm...
not going to make it.
Right?
I'll treat the tumour on your spine...
with radiation treatment.
Please...
let me...
hold my baby just once.
Stop talking.
I already made you a promise.
You say nice things...
in such a mean way...
just like my wife.
You have to promise me...
that you won't give up...
and will follow my decisions on your treatment.
Do you think you can do that?
Dr Oh, I heard Dr Lee started the radiation treatment.
I told you surgery wouldn't work.
The patient desperately wanted the surgery.
Should he have told the patient to give up?
We should consider the risks.
If patients don't recover,
would they try to understand their doctors?
The first thing they'd do is file a lawsuit.
Sincerity always touches people's heart. Here you go.
Sincerity?
Can sincerity treat his tumour?
Can you prevent side effects with sincerity?
He's not in a condition to receive radiation treatment.
He'll have oedema and difficulty in breathing.
The radiation treatment caused the oedema. Don't worry.
Put the oxygen mask on him.
- Give him the medication.
-  Yes, Doctor.
You didn't forget your promise, right?
We'll continue your radiation treatment.
Don't give up, okay?
You're looking down on us, right?
Is it because we don't have family or anyone else...
Listen to me.
There's no one else...
but your husband who would adore you...
when you act like a child.
I, for one, can't stand it.
I asked you to give me more time.
What I need is...
time to spend with him when he's okay.
I don't want to see him in pain like that...
lying in bed as if he were dead.
I promised your husband...
that I'll give him time to hold his baby in his arms.
So I'm going to do everything I can.
I need you to hang in there...
just as your husband is doing.
There's no miraculous treatment...
in this world that can prolong his life...
without pain.
Now that Dr Lee doesn't cause trouble any more,
Director Lee Gun Myung is giving me a headache.
Is it a hereditary disease they have or something?
Gosh.
Is he...
refusing to hand over the regenerative medicine patent?
He won't hold out for long.
Director Lee Gun Myung has...
What on earth is the dirty secret...
that Director Lee is hiding?
Is it related to Dr Lee Young Oh?
Is he hiding secrets about Dr Lee's birth?
A secret has power...
only when it's a secret.
We need to keep it a secret...
because Director Lee wants it to remain that way.
Gosh.
Do you want to satisfy your curiosity?
Or do you want to make a deal?
If I were you,
I would choose to make a deal.
We're doing a business.
Try to be patient, Sir.
How is the clinical trial going?
This is the first stem cell treatment to be put to use.
It's a heart muscle sheet.
Who are the patients?
I'm planning to treat patients...
with cardiomyopathy and heart failure...
to promote the efficiency and effectiveness...
of stem cell treatment.
I decided to follow your decision as you're in charge.
I also desperately hope that you'll succeed...
in commercialising the stem cell treatment.
I believe you'll never hand over the patent...
to the multinational pharmaceutical company.
What we should do now is...
to make the stem cell treatment safe to use.
Dr Hyun, let's focus on that for now.
Ki Ho.
Have you prepared the ECMO?
Oh, that?
The patients for our clinical trial have heart failure.
Prepare the ECMO in case of an emergency.
Yes, Sir.
The safety of these patients...
will decide the success of our research.
Take good care of them.
How is the patient doing?
He developed a complication as expected.
Does he have an infection?
Yes. Dr Lee has been attending to the patient himself.
Doctor.
His heart is failing due to stress.
ECMO.
I need the ECMO.
ECMO?
If I have the ECMO,
I can buy some time.
ECMO?
How can I get it right now?
We only have three in our hospital.
One of them is...
in the VIP room.
I heard that another one is at the ICU.
There's another one at Cardio,
but Dr Hyun is in charge of it.
Hey, have you seen my gown?
It's complicated.
What's the problem?
We have a heart failure patient, too.
We don't know how the situation will fluctuate.
All due to your patient's uncertain status,
my patient with imminent needs...
should be let go?
Is that what you're saying?
There's only one ECMO, and to patients,
it can be their lifeline.
My clinical trial patient's well-being...
is beyond my personal feelings.
He has the full attention of the media.
- Dr Yang.
-  Yes, Doctor?
We're transferring the ECMO immediately.
Yang Sung Eun!
If something happens to my patient,
all the efforts...
will go down the drain in a single moment.
Dr Hyun Suk Joo.
This will be the first and last time...
I will beg you.
I...
must...
save my patient.
You cannot.
There is no chance for survival.
ECMO will only prolong his life.
Don't you choose patients...
based on their probability of survival?
I can't relinquish the ECMO to a patient...
who has less than a 10 percent chance of survival.
- Dr Lee.
-  What is going on?
- Yang Sung Eun.
-  Yes, Doctor.
Didn't you hear me?
I told you to move it.
Whatever, I'm just going to do it.
Hey, hold it.
After what you just said,
are you still...
a good doctor?
- Is the ECMO running well?
-  Yes.
Mr Jo Yoon Ho.
That equipment will buy us time.
I'm keeping my promise.
You should...
keep your promise, too.
He's trying to use the ECMO...
for a patient with low survival probability.
Unlike his usual self,
he's too attached to his patient.
It's a very expensive piece of equipment.
The hospital has ruled that it is to be reserved...
for patients with high possibilities of survival.
The regenerative medicine team needs it the most.
Yes, Dr Oh.
I need to see you now.
So you've made a decision?
I decided to accept...
your suggestion...
regarding the research team team and the patent.
I will work with your company.
So you wish to keep...
what happened to your son...
buried forever?
In the end,
you have chosen your son.
My son...
is finally becoming complete.
He's becoming...
closer to becoming normal.
The long-time efforts...
to educate him...
are finally coming to fruition.
Epinephrine. Epinephrine.
Charge.
Dr Lee, call the patient's guardian.
He's not going to make it.
His wife is in labour.
Charge, 200J.
Charge it again.
Doctor. Doctor.
Look.
Is that possible?
He's in cardiac arrest.
Listen, I'm...
keeping my promise.
You should...
keep your promise, too.
You can stop.
Don't give up.
You need to live.
You'll live.
You said you want to meet your child.
I'll help you meet him.
Okay.
You're going to live.
Charge, 200J!
Stop.
You didn't...
choose Lee Young Oh.
Once again,
you chose...
to protect yourself, Lee Gun Myung.
Just like 25 years ago.
What are you talking about?
Dr Lee, do you consider...
patients to be alive...
just because they breathe?
Do you think you're superior?
Do you now understand...
why I was always against a monster like you...
becoming a doctor?
What do you mean?
Tell me.
The person who made Lee Young Oh a monster...
is you.
But there's something you don't know.
The surgery you performed...
wasn't a failure.
What?
If there was anything that went wrong,
it was me.
What are you talking about?
Isn't it funny?
Your surgery didn't fail,
but you...
created a monster after all.
Director.
You said you knew.
You saw my son's old CT scan results, right?
Yes. What's the matter, Sir?
Where did you see it and when?
- What's the matter?
-  Tell me now!
It was at a small town hospital.
You used to work there.
It was at the Hyunsung Hospital branch archive.
It's where you adopted Dr Lee.
(Neurosurgery: Lee Young Oh)
Was my son normal back then?
Was he normal after the surgery?
I told you before.
Had medical technology been as advanced as it is today,
what happened to Dr Lee...
would never have occurred.
Yes, I remember that.
I was wrong.
I realised it today...
when I saw Director Lee who has remained stagnant.
Since that day,
everything that occurred to Dr Lee Young Oh...
cannot be attributed to medicine.
It's the human condition.
Ambition,
selfishness, humiliation...
and fear.
Now,
what will happen...
to Director Lee and Dr Lee?
I'm not sure.
What's important for us...
is that Director Lee...
has given us the ability...
to control the regenerative medicine research team.
(Moving Hearts with True Medicine)
The central nerves for emotional control,
the frontal lobe and the amygdaloid nucleus...
have been damaged.
Was he normal after the surgery?
Stop it.
I'm keeping my promise.
You said you want to meet your child.
I'll help you meet him.
I knew you'd be here, Dr Lee.
It's a nice place to hide...
for the both of us.
Min Jae.
Who am I?
No matter how much I try and struggle,
nothing changes.
Am I a monster?
Will my inner self continue to be hollow...
so I'll have no other choice...
but to live as a monster?
You said...
that you know me the best.
Answer me, Min Jae.
Please answer me.
You...
are not a monster, Young Oh.
You are...
a victim of medical malpractice.
What?
Under the guise of perfect education,
you were victimised to discreet and persistent abuse.
That's who you are.
As the best neurosurgeon in Korea,
Director Lee Gun Myung...
wanted to conceal you...
in order to maintain his reputation.
You're his failure.
That's who you are, Lee Young Oh.
Dr Lee.
Promises are like traffic lights.
People rub their necks.
Let's watch it once again.
When people are nervous...
You're different from others.
Be quiet and discreet.
Breathe and do nothing else.
Don't let the world find out.
I am his guardian from this day forth.
I'll devote my life to him.
On my way home,
I thought about it a lot.
Yet, I couldn't come up with an answer.
Father.
In this situation,
what kind of expression am I supposed to make?
You saved my life.
You are my only family.
You taught me everything about life.
When I found out that you are,
in fact,
the true monster...
who raised me to be a monster,
what expression was I supposed to make?
You never taught me...
how to deal with this kind of tough emotion.
I...
no longer...
want to live as your failure.