(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
The images were switched.
This child...
Gun Myung's surgery was fine.
(Episode 13)
Hey.
Have you seen Lee Gun Myung?
Where is he?
He looks so smart.
So this is the boy you adopted?
You are incredible.
It's hard enough raising your own child.
You are so honourable.
You are too kind. We need each other.
You're incredible.
Just incredible.
He's cute.
Look at him.
I know.
You're good-looking just like your dad.
You are incredible, Dr Lee Gun Myung.
This man, who is infamous...
for not letting anyone close to him,
took an orphan...
and operated on his brain.
He even adopted him to be his son.
You're drunk.
But why?
Why did you have to go so far?
Why?
You people...
You people are being fooled.
You don't know how hideous a monster...
hides behind this mask that looks all noble.
Dr Oh!
You should congratulate people with a kind heart!
You shouldn't do this...
just because you lost the professorship to him!
Please blame the alcohol, not the person.
Don't worry about it.
That's enough.
You must be smug.
To package a medical malpractice on an orphan...
as a kind gesture of a surgeon...
who is incredibly generous.
What a perfect crime.
I did my best...
in the OR that day,
and I will continue doing my best...
for that child.
How long...
do you think you can fool the world?
You can threaten me or ridicule me all you want.
No one will believe you anyway.
You saw for yourself.
You...
You jerk!
This is the Shin Academy House.
A person fell.
Please send an ambulance.
Father, you're a doctor, too.
Why didn't you help him?
(Beautiful Mind)
I...
did my best.
I wanted...
to create...
a perfect world for you.
"A perfect world"?
You needed that world...
not for me, but to prove that you did your best.
Your perfect world...
collapsed.
What? What did you just say?
We'll hold a mortality conference...
regarding the death...
of Jo Yoon Ho, the Ewing sarcoma patient.
You'll request it yourself?
Why would you?
Was there a problem?
Why did Dr Lee...
request a mortality conference?
Do you think there was a problem with...
Jo Yoon Ho's death that we don't know about?
Do you think he'll complain about us?
We were there...
for the CPR.
Did you do anything wrong?
He's the one who stopped the CPR. Don't blame me.
He never gives up on a patient. Why did he do that?
I'm so confused.
I find that strange, too.
- My gosh.
-  Goodness.
- Goodness.
-  What?
That's it!
Yang Sung Eun!
It's you. The mortality conference is to get you.
What? Me? Why me?
I'm just a third year.
The ECMO that you took from Cardio.
Did you do something wrong?
- Did you make a mistake?
-  That's right.
You know,
when I ran with the ECMO up against my chest,
I decided to bet my life on Dr Lee Young Oh.
I swear I did not make any mistakes.
Then what is he thinking?
Why a mortality conference?
(A mortality conference has been scheduled)
We will now begin the mortality conference...
regarding Jo Yoon Ho,
the Ewing sarcoma patient who died on July 26.
Dr Lee.
When I saw the patient,
he was suffering from Ewing...
We didn't know you'd be attending.
I came as a surgeon, not as the hospital director.
Please be seated.
- Dr Oh.
-  Yes?
If you don't mind, may I oversee...
the mortality conference?
Yes, Sir.
When Jo Yoon Ho was brought in,
he had a slim chance of survival with surgery.
The tumour was in a bad location...
and the tumour cells had entered the spine.
Why did you insist on such a difficult surgery?
That surgery...
was the only option...
he had at survival.
I heard...
you ceased the CPR.
Why did you stop?
Stop...
Dr Lee.
Answer the question.
Why did you stop?
We all know...
that you...
did the best for the patient.
We surgeons...
always look for an answer.
But there are times when there is no answer...
other than that we tried our best.
I hope this will be...
a means for Dr Lee to accept that.
We will now end...
the mortality conference.
Do you know...
why I requested the mortality conference?
When that patient was dying,
do you know...
why I stopped...
the CPR?
Because I couldn't feel what he was feeling.
Because I was afraid I'd make him reliant...
on life support...
because of my selfishness when it's not what he wanted.
Because...
I am not normal.
your best efforts at making me normal...
made me this way.
But you tell me...
to accept your shameless effort...
because you tried your best.
Dr Lee Gun Myung.
There is...
no such exoneration in this world.
Especially in here.
We said...
we didn't want surgery.
My husband...
suffered until he died...
because of your stubbornness.
This is his message...
expressing how he truly felt.
Please stop.
Don't give up.
You promised...
to live.
Stop...
You can start over, Dr Lee.
Both you...
and us.
I was relieved.
If it isn't brain damage,
but because of a traumatic experience,
it may...
be more possible.
You have me.
I...
will help.
Min Jae.
You already saw...
that regardless of the cause,
the result is the same.
This is who I am.
Too many patients...
will be put in danger...
because of me.
Charge.
Doctor.
Is that possible?
He's in cardiac arrest.
Please stop.
You promised...
to live.
Stop...
Do you remember...
when I said...
I have to live...
because I can't leave Eun Joo alone?
You were...
the first person ever...
to listen...
to how I felt.
And...
you did your best...
to keep...
your promise.
Thanks to you,
I wasn't alone...
in my final moment.
Dr Lee Young Oh.
You...
kept...
your promise.
Thank you...
so much.
Dr Lee.
If it weren't for you,
nothing would've happened to me.
I wouldn't have struggled so much to save him.
If it weren't for you, I would've lived in peace...
as I have all these years,
being thankful for being completely alone.
If it weren't for you,
I wouldn't resent someone for making me this way.
I wouldn't do something stupid...
like having hope because of some stupid tears.
If it weren't for you!
I despise you more than anyone...
in this entire world.
So please...
disappear from my life.
Whatever you say,
I hear it as...
"I love you."
I'm sorry, but I can't do as you asked.
I can't leave you alone.
I hope...
you like...
my gift.
Please...
hug...
my son...
for me.
I baptize you in the name of the Father,
the Son and the Holy Spirit.
Dr Lee.
This outfit is a bit...
I made a promise.
I need to keep it.
I am not embarrassed at all,
since I'm a psychopath...
who can't feel emotions.
This is Jo Jin Joo.
I...
baptize you...
in the name of the Father, the Son and the Holy Spirit.
Should we get some cold noodles?
It's so hot. It would be perfect.
Anything is fine with me.
Whatever you want.
No. We should have a hearty lunch.
I know a good pork cutlet place. Should we go there?
Sure. We can go there.
No.
You don't want to walk around too much in that.
Should we get something quick?
Whether we have kimbap or tteokbokki, let's just eat.
Once they enter our stomach, it doesn't matter.
Don't you have any common sense?
Come on.
- And does this shirt embarrass you?
-  Pardon?
I'm not embarrassed at all. I love it.
I'm going to keep wearing this.
I'll get it in every single colour out there.
I'll wear them all. Just watch.
I just meant...
And are you fickle or greedy?
Why do you want to eat so many things?
Why do you keep changing your mind?
You should've just said...
you wanted to go to a hotel!
What do you mean, a hotel?
A hotel buffet, where you can eat everything.
Where you can eat anything you want.
I told you,
I hear everything you say as, "I love you."
- But...
-  Let's go.
-  Come on.
I'm going to eat a lot.
You do that.
What's wrong?
- Did you see that?
-  What? What? What?
When you wake up.
With someone by your side.
Dr Lee.
Were you calling me...
or did you blurt that out in shock?
I blurted it out.
It looks good on you.
Everyone lies, don't they?
Do you have my schedule for today?
Yes. Here you go.
Okay. Dr Yang.
I'm still in shock.
- This is when you say it, right?
-  What?
Why must we be the ones to be embarrassed?
- Good morning.
-  Good morning.
He must've been traumatised.
I haven't seen him since the mortality conference.
Now,
all we have to do is add patients with lung diseases...
to our clinical trials before it goes public.
Yes, we're getting it prepared.
If the clinical trials prove it to be safe,
the value of stem cells will exceed our expectations.
With this market,
you won't need to worry...
about investments or stock price.
I'm so happy to have met...
a dependable partner.
Dr Song, when you were an assistant professor,
you specialised in the respiratory system, right?
That's good.
You can work on the research article...
Green Pharmacy wants.
It would be an honour.
I'll recruit study subjects...
among patients suffering from respiratory disease...
at our hospital.
Did Green Pharmacy request the research...
to include patients with respiratory diseases?
Unlike the liver or kidney,
the lung cannot be transplanted...
from a live donor.
It is...
a critical organ after the brain and heart,
which does not regenerate.
You weren't interested...
in incurable diseases...
or regenerative medicine.
It was the money and power you'd gain.
That's why you killed Director Shin to get here.
That's right. So what do you think...
would make me hesitate? What would I have to fear?
It doesn't matter who it is.
If anyone gets in my way,
I will get rid of them...
as I did Shin Dong Jae.
This should be...
enough to prove you murdered...
Director Shin in court.
- Why you...
-  I'm warning you.
The regenerative research...
won't go as you want any more.
I told you before.
The moment I chose to be a good doctor,
I gave up on being a good person.
You had...
several chances to fix your mistakes.
When I said the surgery went wrong,
you should've taken that child to another doctor.
When I realised my mistake and went to see you,
you shouldn't have mocked me.
And when I fell,
you shouldn't have left me.
In all those moments,
you chose this result.
I lost everything.
If I hadn't operated on that child,
I would've shared my son's final moments.
If you hadn't made that mistake,
I wouldn't have lived with...
guilt and responsibility...
and wouldn't have turned him into a monster.
Do you know...
why I put my life into regenerative medicine?
Do you know why I wished surgeons would disappear?
I hoped no one would live with regrets like I do.
So?
Are you saying regenerative medicine was...
your way of making up for your mistakes?
If you want an apology from me,
don't bother.
I...
will not give up.
You mean it? You can't take it back.
I dislike everything about you,
but your overreacting is the worst.
I didn't say I'd date you.
I'll just eat with you if you solve this.
Plenty of women have never eaten with me,
but no woman has eaten with me just once.
Why do you think that is?
You always pay, don't you?
I don't buy affection from women with money.
Don't forget.
You need to solve this for us to eat together.
Wait a second.
This is for the medical licensing examination, right?
Sort of. Good luck.
I'll buy dinner.
Look at her. Goodness. That girl...
Why doesn't she just admit she likes me?
Why is she playing games?
What choice do I have? I should play along.
Okay.
Two with endocarditis caused by mold and fungus.
One with a cerebral aneurysm.
What do they have in common?
Wait a second. Why am I solving this?
I should ask the power rangers.
Why am I bothering?
- Tell it to me straight.
-  Yes?
Do you want to study or date?
I want to do both.
There are two things you can't get help with.
One is studying,
and the other is dating.
I understand, but please help me.
Dr Hwang is right about that.
He has...
- a bad memory.
-  What's that?
When he joined the army,
he asked his friend to take care of his girlfriend.
- His friend saved her seat in the library...
-  Hey.
- every day.
-  Duk Joong.
- His girlfriend ended up...
- cheating on him.
-  He's lying.
His friend in this story is me.
No.
- She wasn't my girlfriend.
-  Is that true?
I'm sorry about that.
I just had a fling with her.
- I'm sorry about that.
-  Wow, Dr Kwon.
I'm sorry, Dr Hwang.
She wasn't my girlfriend.
Don't worry. You can go ahead if you can.
Not everyone can get help with things like that.
All right.
I was bored anyway.
We'll help you solve the problem.
Let's work in two teams. The losing team buys drinks.
I like that idea.
- I'm in.
-  Me, too.
A question for the medical licensing examination.
- Fried chicken and beer.
-  We'll add sea snails.
We'll add cream draft beer.
Then, we'll add grilled dried pollack.
- Deal.
-  Okay.
Don't push me.
That's tricky.
Don't do that.
Let me see... Gosh.
Are you sure this is for the medical licensing exam?
Yes, I'm sure.
Timeout. We need to change players.
The person who gave the question shouldn't be here.
Sung Eun, you should leave.
Am I out?
Yes, you are.
Who will replace him?
- Dr Soh.
-  Yes?
I have no idea.
Dr Yang Sung Eun.
Yes, Sir.
Is this patient in this hospital?
I'm not sure about that.
It's a question for the medical licensing exam.
Since it's not a patient in this hospital,
I don't have to solve this problem.
- That's right.
-  Yes.
What a shame.
Dr Lee, please wait.
I made a bet with Dr Lee Shi Hyun.
Do you know what it feels like to make a bet...
just to have a meal with someone you like?
It's a romantic feeling.
Please help me, Dr Lee.
- You made a bet?
-  Yes.
You have to win it no matter what.
Make sure you have a meal with her.
- Step away.
-  But...
- My goodness.
-  How dare you?
This is cheating.
Dr Lee.
Your test results came out, Jin Sung.
I know.
I guess that's why I'm here.
Your heart is holding on well.
I'm relieved.
To be honest, I was so worried.
I was so afraid to come here.
Thank you, Doctor.
Jin Sung.
There's a problem...
with your lungs.
As a result of taking heart medication for a long time,
you developed pulmonary fibrosis.
I think that when Dr Lee Young Oh treated you...
because your lungs filled with fluid,
your lungs began to have problems.
Let's run a thorough examination for now.
What are you doing here?
What brought you here?
I wanted to see you.
I'm here to see you, Dr Lee.
Now that I've seen you, I'll get going.
Wait.
I've been thinking about how you call me.
I want you to change that.
Most of those who call me "Doctor" are my patients.
I don't like you calling me "Doctor".
How else can you call me instead?
Give it a thought.
I don't like "Mister", either.
Let's go. I'll walk you out.
Come on.
I'll get going.
Okay. Bye.
See you later.
I need an ABG and an EKG!
Hurry up!
I'll treat her as I'm her doctor.
She just had a consultation with me.
Ultrasound scan.
She has acute interstitial pneumonia.
It will...
develop rapidly.
She already developed pulmonary fibrosis.
I'll administer antibiotics and an antiviral agent.
If she doesn't get better,
there will be only one solution left.
We'll put her on the transplant waiting list,
and wait for a donor.
We'll have to wait for a lung transplant?
We can't transplant lungs from a living donor.
We can't be sure how long she'll have to wait.
Are you saying...
that she has to wait for that?
I should apply for a lung transplant?
Yes.
Your heart has been weak for a long time,
which caused a problem in your lungs.
It's your heart's turn to help your weak lungs,
but your heart...
isn't strong enough to do that.
Also,
you won't be able to rely on a machine...
for a long time.
Applying for a transplant...
isn't treatment.
You mean I have to wait...
until luck finds me, right?
Ma'am,
would you like to receive treatment?
You suggested Gye Jin Sung...
our clinical trial?
Yes, I did. It's a good opportunity.
It's free and she'll receive high-quality care.
If we can treat her pulmonary fibrosis,
she can return to her normal life without a transplant.
What's the problem?
Suk Joo, do you...
still have doubts on our research?
Are you...
giving those heart failure patients...
regenerative medicine treatment...
despite your doubts on the treatment?
Is that true?
Dr Lee.
You're here to solve the problem, right?
I didn't know we had such good teamwork.
Dr Lee, have you found any clues?
- "Lungs"?
-  "Lungs".
- "Lungs".
You've become so down-to-earth recently...
making a mistake like that.
You can tell him. We're on the same team.
- Can I?
-  Sure.
We found...
a similarity...
among the three patients.
All three of them...
had the same surgery in the past.
- It's heart valve surgery.
-  Heart valve surgery.
- Here we go, here we go.
-  Here we go.
Heart valve surgery.
How dare you wake a third-year resident?
- Who are you?
-  Dr Yang.
My goodness!
The three cases for the quiz...
aren't for the medical licensing exam, right?
I... I'm sure they are.
Why would Dr Lee lie to me?
Where is she now?
Dr Lee Shi Hyun!
I think she went that way.
Dr Lee Shi Hyun.
Dr Lee. Dr...
Your quiz.
Who are the three patients?
Which hospital are they at?
I can't say here.
They were our patients.
I think you already knew that.
You're more interesting than I thought.
Why did you make a quiz...
with those three cases?
You even asked Dr Yang solve it.
The patients developed the same lesions...
at the same time.
Their personal information was kept secret.
When I raised a question about them,
I got replaced by another resident.
I couldn't ask anyone because I wasn't sure...
who in this hospital was related to the cases.
I was afraid.
So?
I wanted to let as many people as possible know.
I thought Dr Yang was the perfect person to do that.
You said they had the same lesion, right?
All three of them had...
endocarditis and cerebral aneurysm, right?
Yes.
It's a rare lesion. I couldn't find out what it was.
Do you have any idea?
What's wrong?
Please...
tell me.
Will I survive...
if I receive the regenerative medicine treatment?
Are you sure it's safe?
- Jin Sung.
-  I've doubted you,
and hated you,
but you're the only person who can give me an answer.
So please tell me.
Are you okay?
Doctor.
I want to live.
I don't want to die.
I think I know...
who these patients are.
Who are they?
They're clinical trial patients...
of the regenerative medicine research.
They're part of the project...
led by Dr Hyun Suk Joo for commercialising...
the regenerative medicine.
Ki Ho.
Let's begin...
the stem cell treatment for Gye Jin Sung.
I have to save her.
Call Dr Hyun. Hurry.
Neither antibiotics nor the antiviral agent worked.
We don't have much time.
ECMO... Get the ECMO now.
Even with the ECMO,
she won't be able to hold on for long due to her heart.
I won't ask if you slept well...
because I know you suffered a lot.
I won't ask...
if you were worried...
because I'd feel bad.
I have...
decided to receive the treatment.
The regenerative medicine treatment for my lungs...
from Dr Hyun Suk Joo.
Why aren't you asking me...
if I doubt him,
or if I trust him?
You made me a promise.
You promised...
you won't leave me alone.
Keep your promise. That's all I need.
Why did you want to see me?
Dr Hyun Suk Joo.
Young Oh, are you out of your mind?
Are you out of your mind?
You want to use...
the regenerative medicine on Jin Sung?
Don't you know what that means?
That will never happen, as long as I'm around.
It was you.
The reason she wanted to live so badly.
Our regenerative medicine...
is her only hope.
Look, Suk Joo.
Three people developed...
infectious diseases...
due to abnormal lesions.
They were all patients...
from your clinical study.
Do you...
still believe regenerative medicine is safe?
What do you mean?
We had no patients with negative effects.
We tried our best to make sure it was safe.
I checked the data every day with my own eyes.
Anyone can lie in the reports.
The problem is...
with medicine,
those errors are people.
Dr Hyun. I'll give you a chance to right it.
All three of those patients...
have received heart valve surgeries and Jin Sung...
also received that same surgery.
Do you still think her only option...
is regenerative medicine?
Fine.
If you'll raise issue with that,
I'll have to remove them from the results,
so that they never would've existed.
Were there no problems in stage three...
which let us get approval so quickly...
because you deleted the test subjects...
that showed abnormalities?
What?
Do you need evidence for court again?
Will you record me?
Don't forget.
You're the one who told the world...
that stage three is safe.
I'm sure you want to expose the truth,
but think long and hard.
All you'll get...
is a revocation of your license.
You wanted to be a good doctor.
You are right.
What I wanted from the start...
was to be a good doctor.
Gye Jin Sung, was it?
Lung regeneration stem cell transplant.
It's our first project with Green Pharmacy.
Mr Kang is very interested too.
Make no mistakes.
What do you want us to do?
We just solved a quiz for chicken and beer.
You want us to do something that dangerous?
Just because there are five of us...
doesn't mean we're the Power Rangers.
Look.
Duk Joong.
Kyung Jin.
Ji Yong.
Jung Hwan.
And you.
Jang Bae.
You started this,
so please,
take responsibility and finish it.
Do you still think her only option...
is regenerative medicine?
She doesn't have time to wait for a donor.
We can't transplant a lung from a live donor.
Then,
what choice can we make?
The one that is the best for the patient.
Transplant...
a lung from a live person...
into her.
Let me ask you again.
Lung transplants from live donors...
are illegal because it endangers the life of the donor.
Do you still want to do this?
It is illegal...
and very dangerous,
but it has a high rate of survival for the patient.
That is my favourite type of surgery.
Okay.
Shall we begin?