(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
(Final Episode)
Stop this.
It's too dangerous.
If you go through with the surgery,
your life will be in danger.
Must you go through with that illegal surgery?
Can you handle it?
You'll regret it forever.
I'm against it.
As a doctor,
I can't permit you doing something so reckless.
As your father,
I can't permit...
you risking your life.
Now,
I understand how you feel.
How you felt that day when you took me...
into the OR...
when...
everyone opposed.
Yes.
We will begin the stem cell implantation surgery...
on Gye Jin Sung starting tonight. I'll check on her.
(Gye Jin Sung)
Oh, dear.
Ms Jang. Where did Ms Gye Jin Sung go?
I think she's getting a CT scan on her lungs.
I see. Okay.
She just left after getting her CT scan taken.
Maybe they took her to Dr Hyun's office...
for examination?
Okay, thank you.
- Dr Hong? - Yes?
Take a look at this.
What do you think?
Do you think...
any of them are candidates for stem cell implants?
- I'm in a rush right now... - Hey.
- Is it more urgent than their lives? - No, but...
Take a look.
Look closely. Sit down.
Sit.
Look closely...
and tell me what you think as a specialist.
I really...
You're good at things like this.
- But... - Just take a look.
Where did she go?
Let me ask you again.
Lung transplants from live donors...
are illegal because it endangers the life of the donor.
Do you still want to do this?
It is illegal...
and very dangerous,
but it has a high rate of survival...
for the patient.
That is my favourite type of surgery.
- Hello. - Hi.
Have you seen Dr Hyun?
- I have. - You have?
- Yes. - Where is he?
- Come with me. - Okay.
- Oh, that's right. - What?
Goodness.
Why are we going to the lecture hall?
I thought he was here.
Maybe not.
- Dr Yang. - Yes?
Yang Sung Eun!
You...
Are you sure Dr Hyun is here?
Hyun... Dr Hyun Suk Joo?
Oh, no.
I got confused with Dr Hyun of Pathology.
- I'm so sorry. - You...
You'll pay for this.
I'm so sorry. Doctor. Doctor!
Doctor! I'm sorry!
Doctor! I'm very sorry!
They'll buy us time.
Once this surgery is over,
we will have to take...
Responsibility for this illegal surgery.
Dr Hyun.
Thank you for taking the courage.
Okay.
Shall we begin?
Sir, we're in trouble.
As you can see,
our hospital's PR regarding stents is insufficient.
Namin Hospital's second and...
fourth quarter figures aren't as high as ours,
but people think they are the leaders with regard...
to stents for the heart.
Okay. I'll review it.
No, Sir.
If you review and then give orders, a month will pass.
I'd appreciate it if you'd review it now...
and give your instructions right away.
Sir. I can't find Gye Jin Sung or Dr Hyun Suk Joo.
- What? - It's been a while already.
I can't find them anywhere.
Sir, can't you approve this first before you go?
What's gotten into you today?
- Let's go. - But this is...
important for the hospital's...
performance...
You want us to do what?
Please buy us time, so that Mr Chae...
can't interfere...
with what we want to do.
Mr Chae? Why?
You want us to do something that dangerous?
Just because there are five of us...
doesn't mean we're the Power Rangers.
Look.
Duk Joong.
Kyung Jin.
Ji Yong.
Jung Hwan.
And you.
Jang Bae.
You started this,
so please,
take responsibility and finish it.
The regenerative medicine Mr Chae is pushing...
had deadly effects on patients...
who had heart valve surgery in the past.
You're the ones...
who told me that.
We just solved a quiz for chicken and beer.
So? Will you watch Mr Chae insist upon...
regenerative surgery...
on other patients?
That should be enough.
That was plenty of time to begin surgery.
Are you sure Suk Joo took her into the OR?
Yes. I checked the surveillance videos.
He has something up his sleeve.
There's no reason to pull up the surgery in secret.
(Kang Hee Soo, Kim Jin Joo, Lee Ji Hyung)
Tonight,
we planned the first lung regenerative surgery.
Tomorrow morning,
we were going to tell the world...
that we had attempted at lung regenerative surgery.
But that first project...
Bring them.
Bring Suk Joo and that patient to me!
Yes, Sir.
How dare you barge into my OR?
I'm sorry.
I'm in agony.
What is medicine?
Why is there no security by the ORs?
What if you spread germs into the OR?
Which department are you in?
- I'm sorry. - Why you...
What is he trying to do?
We will now begin the lung transplant.
I thought I made myself clear.
Is this your response?
I simply did my best as a doctor.
Do you know...
how I got to where I am although...
I didn't attend Hyunsung University?
I was someone those above me needed...
and someone those below me feared.
You'll regret this.
We did as we were told, but will we be okay?
What could they do?
Are you afraid of being fired?
They wouldn't fire all five of us.
- Move over. - We don't know anything, okay?
The surgery schedule changed but that's all we know.
Why did Dr Lee donate his lung to that patient?
- I don't know. - Think about it.
It's so dangerous.
The likelihood of success...
and the donor's survival rate is so low, it's illegal.
Could you do that?
For a stranger who isn't even family?
Maybe she isn't a stranger, but his love!
- Maybe she's his love! - Come on.
How is that possible for someone like him?
He has no heart, remember?
- That's true. - Right.
You never know with men and women.
- Goodness. - Goodness.
- Gosh. - What's with you?
- Sorry. - Goodness.
Hello, Mr Chae.
What a beautiful day.
I don't see the write up I was expecting...
about the lung regenerative surgery.
I came out for a run to calm myself down.
He scored a suicide goal, so we should pull him.
It doesn't matter who.
Total time, 10 minutes. Total distance, 2.5km.
It cut me off.
This is so annoying.
They took the patient that we notified...
Green Pharmacy of being our first case...
of regenerative surgery...
and performed an illegal surgery.
We were robbed...
in my own hospital.
We were robbed,
so we must slit their throats.
Slit their throats?
They performed an illegal surgery.
We must end them using the most legal...
and ethical way possible.
This is insane. Live lung transplant is illegal.
I can't believe two doctors worked together on it.
It's a total disregard for ethics.
Still, the patient survived.
If we don't say anything now, the next one may die.
We must take strict measures.
It isn't for us to argue about among ourselves.
The illegal surgery...
violated our ethical rules and warrants termination.
Lee Young Oh and Hyun Suk Joo.
They should both be terminated.
Dr Lee?
We assume you have no objections.
Gosh.
Where are you going? Do you have plans?
You had surgery just yesterday.
You need your rest. You know that.
And you were...
You were the donor for an illegal surgery.
Go back in.
Dr Yang...
Gosh. Dr Yang.
Clinical studies show...
that after a lung removal surgery,
the patient...
may exercise lightly after a day.
In order...
to show...
how safe the surgery is,
I must exercise.
I don't know where you plan to go and exercise,
but I'll tell you this. Gye Jin Sung...
needs to rest and can't have visitors.
There's no point grunting your way there.
Are you no longer a patient...
but her guardian?
No. But...
that woman...
How is Gye Jin Sung...
doing?
You don't need to worry.
She's stable so far.
I'm sure you guessed,
but I'm sorry to tell you this.
The board decided...
to terminate us.
I was expecting it,
but I'm sorry...
this happened to you.
You really wanted to do regenerative medicine.
It was the most valuable thing for you.
You gave up on being a good doctor...
and betrayed...
people close to you.
You may mock me, but I still...
can't give up...
on regenerative medicine.
This is all trial and error.
If we give up now,
no one will do...
anything dangerous to save lives.
Saving lives...
is always a dangerous risk, isn't it?
Just as you did...
for Jin Sung.
Ms Jang.
Can Jin Sung receive visitors?
Really?
The responsibility of a donor toward his recipient?
Anyway, I'm glad she can have visitors.
Okay.
If she can have visitors, I should go visit her.
My brother!
Ever since I first met you,
I knew right away.
You're a real man.
You said you broke up,
but wow. Talk about a gift.
You didn't give her a ring or a car,
but your body.
Talk about a pro at dating. Here's the pro.
Quiet.
I need my rest.
By the way,
did you see your sister?
If not, let's go together.
There's no point in visiting her.
You see her every day anyway.
I guess Dr Lee Young Oh...
will really be fired this time.
It won't be easy.
A doctor conspired with another doctor...
to perform an illegal surgery.
Thank goodness the patient survived.
Ethically, this is a huge problem.
The hospital director must be in shock.
What if word gets out? Dr Lee is no ordinary doctor.
A psychopath surgeon...
undergoes an illegal live transplant.
This is like something out of a movie.
If the board fires them,
it'll be hard for them to find new jobs.
What will they do?
I feel bad for Dr Lee.
He gave up his left lung.
He lost his health as well as his job.
Shouldn't we go visit or something?
That's too sappy. Why would we go there?
Since when did we consider him family?
- He has a point. - Yes.
Gosh.
I shouldn't have said that.
No one will check on him.
No, no.
Fine. He has no friends.
I'll check in on him.
This is humanism.
Okay. Good.
Dr Lee!
Dr Soh.
Please ask Ms Jang...
to put up a sign that says...
I need...
to rest.
I simply...
did my best.
I wanted...
to create...
a perfect world for you.
No effort...
by a doctor can be perfect...
for a patient...
who has no tomorrow.
This is...
the reason trying your best...
cannot exonerate you.
Now, I understand how you feel.
How you felt...
that day when you took me...
into the OR...
when...
everyone opposed.
(Do not disturb.)
How do you feel?
The ethics council...
will vote on your termination tomorrow.
You'll both be given a chance to explain,
but this was too huge.
As a doctor,
you can't avoid being held accountable...
ethically.
I expected it...
when I decided to do it.
You became a doctor although I was against it.
And you came back to Hyunsung where I was.
I'm surprised that you're accepting your termination...
so easily.
Because...
I no longer need...
your acceptance.
Your acceptance...
that I am not a monster,
but a normal human being.
I wanted to ask you something.
What did you mean...
when you said you understand?
You said you understand how I felt.
What did you mean?
The fear...
of knowing that...
you may lose the person closest to you.
The sense of incompetence...
that you can't do anything for that person...
as a doctor.
The sense of defeat...
after the surgery,
when you feel like you were completely wrong.
I'm sure...
whenever you saw my face,
you thought...
you had failed as a doctor...
because I was a disgusting reminder...
of that failure.
I thought I had feared you,
but you were the one...
who had feared me.
Because you were...
the biggest abuser in our relationship,
but also...
the biggest victim.
I don't have the courage to forgive you.
But now,
I want to try...
and understand.
So please...
be free now,
as I am now.
I'm glad.
I heard the surgery was a success.
I was curious about you.
I couldn't do it no matter how hard I tried,
but you did it so easily.
I never imagined...
Dr Lee would change...
so much.
I...
was only by his side.
You haven't seen him yet, have you?
I heard he's recovering quickly, too.
You don't need to worry.
What do you mean?
Did something happen to him?
You didn't know.
The ethics council...
is meeting now...
to discuss his termination for what he did.
He'll probably expelled.
What do you mean? What did he do?
Dr Lee...
was prepared to lose everything...
and gave you his lung.
It's illegal to take a lung...
from a live person.
It holds a very high risk for the donor,
and he went against every rule in the book.
But that's how much...
he wanted to save you.
So desperately.
Is that why...
Will he be kicked out...
of the hospital because of me?
We will now begin the conference...
to discuss the illegal surgery...
performed by Lee Young Oh and Hyun Suk Joo.
They should've begun.
They'll decide on their termination by this afternoon.
I don't understand...
Dr Lee Young Oh.
He has that...
anti... What was it?
Antisocial disorder.
It is a personality disorder.
Don't those people...
operate solely to benefit themselves?
Why did he do such a thing?
What does he gain?
Don't try to understand him. He isn't worthy.
There's one more thing I don't understand.
Dr Hyun Suk Joo.
I thought he was one of your favourites,
but you showed no mercy.
He pushed me onto the ledge, so I had to push him off.
I'll reach out to him when he's bloody and disgraced,
so that he won't act out again.
I get it then.
Dr Lee Young Oh.
Dr Hyun Suk Joo.
You both knew...
that a lung transplant from a living donor is illegal,
but you carried out the surgery...
in this hospital secretly, correct?
Yes.
It is safer to transplant lungs from two donors...
to one person.
Why did you carry out the surgery...
breaking all the principles?
The patient's condition deteriorated rapidly,
and her heart was too weak...
to hold on until we found another donor.
Does it mean that you two admit everything...
about your lung transplant surgery?
No.
You're mistaken.
It's not...
the truth.
I heard they're holding...
an ethics council meeting because of me.
Have they made a decision yet?
I heard it just began.
I guess it was you, Detective Gye.
Dr Lee Young Oh said...
that he gave his girlfriend a lot of time...
to think things through.
Don't worry. You need to focus on your recovery.
Don't make Dr Lee's effort go down the drain.
Dr Hyun Suk Joo was against this surgery...
from the beginning.
If you check Dr Hyun's original surgery schedule,
you'll know that it's true.
What do you mean by that?
He didn't want to do the surgery?
I'll submit evidence.
Please watch this footage.
As you can see,
Dr Hyun was forced to do the surgery...
that he shouldn't and didn't want to do.
He did it...
because of me.
As you all know,
I can't...
empathise and have an antisocial disorder.
People call me a psychopath.
He had no choice but to perform the surgery...
because I threatened him.
- That's not true. - I'm sure...
you would have made the same decision.
You know that Dr Hyun...
is an exemplary doctor.
Dr Lee.
You'll have to take full responsibility...
for the illegal lung transplant.
Would that be okay with you?
If that means I'll be dismissed,
I'll take full responsibility.
But...
I don't think what I've done is wrong.
There are a few countries where a lung transplant...
from a living donor is legal.
The higher being who we believe loves us...
gave us diseases.
The medical science to cure incurable diseases...
still has...
a long way to go.
Saving someone who is dying in front of you...
is an inevitable choice...
a doctor has to make.
That's why...
I'm not ashamed of what I did.
I'll accept the termination...
willingly.
Director Lee,
please give me a chance to explain.
It wasn't Dr Lee's sole decision.
I think...
we've heard enough.
The ethics council...
will discuss the termination,
and notify you two later.
You may leave now.
Why did you do that?
Did you think that I'd be grateful?
Listen to me, Dr Hyun.
I didn't do that because I thought you'd be grateful.
Then, why did you say that?
I started it,
so I have to take responsibility for it.
- But we made the decision... - Don't you...
have something else...
to take responsibility for?
Did you plan this from the beginning?
From the moment I decided to get the surgery?
Why did you do that without even telling me?
It's because...
I had what you needed.
You know how selfish I am.
I thought about it objectively and thoroughly...
before I made the decision.
So you...
don't have anything to feel sorry about anything.
I'm...
different from normal people.
While I was seeing you,
I thought I had changed a lot.
But I didn't.
I was mistaken.
A miracle like that won't happen...
in the future, either.
I will...
baffle you...
from time to time.
I may...
make you feel lonely,
and you'll be disheartened...
because I won't be able to change.
Even in those moments,
I won't know how to...
comfort you.
So please...
Please don't forget.
Every breath you take,
please remember how I feel about you,
and what you...
mean to me.
What do I mean to you?
You're recovering more quickly than I expected.
Your breathing is quite stable.
It's not bad.
Let's conclude that Dr Hyun Suk Joo...
will stay considering the circumstances,
and that Dr Lee Young Oh...
will be terminated.
Please withdraw...
the termination of Dr Lee.
What are you saying, Director Lee?
Can't you separate work and personal life?
He's a doctor who did his best to save a patient...
risking his own life.
Dr Lee didn't hesitate to perform the surgery...
because he lacks empathy.
If word got out about this surgery,
it'll damage our reputation and reliability.
If Dr Lee's empathy disorder is the problem,
the person who should be punished...
is me.
Dr Lee developed this personality disorder...
because I abused him...
to cover up my mistake.
Despite that,
Dr Lee was...
a better doctor than the one I've been trying to be...
my entire life.
I don't know what laws or regulations...
I have to hold him by.
However, I know...
that in an organisation...
responsibility must be taken.
I will take full responsibility for...
the lung transplant from a living donor.
I'm willing to accept...
any punishment.
So please withdraw...
the termination of Dr Lee.
I thought it was a trap to catch Dr Lee Young Oh,
but you caught Director Lee Gun Myung instead.
Director Lee...
declared his resignation.
At the ethics council meeting?
Dr Lee Young Oh saved Dr Hyun Suk Joo,
and Director Lee...
sacrificed himself to save Dr Lee.
Can you believe this fairy tale...
happened in my hospital?
But fairy tales are fiction.
Now, I'll tell the story from my point of view.
Don't mess up...
the collaboration project with Green Pharmacy...
because of what happened yesterday.
If you manage to finish commercialising...
the regenerative medicine without a hitch,
I promise you...
that you will...
become the next director.
I'll do my best...
as I always have.
You were right.
Our research wasn't a failure.
We just went through trial and error...
like all research teams do.
Now that you're on the verge of getting fired,
you're becoming mature.
I just checked on our clinical trial patients.
Are there any patients suffering side effects?
No.
None of the heart failure patients...
developed side effects.
The treatment was successful.
When the patients took the stem cell medications,
they developed the side effects.
It was a mistake in the clinical trial...
that you could've fixed easily.
But you murdered...
Patient Kang Chul Min and Director Shin Dong Jae...
to cover up your mistake.
If that became known to the public,
we couldn't have made this far.
I had to stop that!
You turned our team's mistake into a crime.
That's what I can't...
- forgive you for. - Hyun Suk Joo.
We still have time left.
We should reveal everything before it goes public,
and start over again.
What are you doing?
Ki Ho.
- Let's start over again. - Pardon?
The stem cell medication for the patients...
with heart valve diseases...
had a side effect.
That can't be true.
There was an error in our research.
It can happen to anyone.
Hold on a second.
As you said, it can happen to anyone.
- We did nothing wrong. - I...
want to be a doctor who can admit his limits.
I can't commit a crime...
for the sake of perfecting our research.
I've made up my mind.
Wait, Suk Joo.
Suk Joo.
I've been thinking.
This research is my life,
and I can't forgive...
anyone who ruins my life...
whoever that may be.
Even if...
it is you.
Suk Joo, I'll make you a hero.
- For the purity of our research, - No!
you take all the blame, and we'll go on.
I'll make it possible.
Ki Ho. Ki Ho, come to your senses!
Let go!
- Suk Joo. Suk Joo. - Stop it.
What am I supposed to do now?
What about me?
- Suk Joo! Suk Joo! - Come out!
I assumed...
that someone would attack you,
but I didn't think it'd be your colleague...
who you trusted so much.
So what are you going to do now?
I have to take responsibility...
just as you did.
Okay.
Things are going to get ugly, aren't they?
I think so.
Don't worry.
I have a plan.
- Sir. - That's right.
We're at the Prosecutors' Office.
You can stay here in peace.
Turn yourself in.
My family's attorney will do his best...
to reduce your sentence.
You went too far when you murdered Director Shin.
As long as Dr Hyun holds the evidence,
we can't win this case. Don't you see that?
Do you think...
you'll be safe if I confess everything?
You can't tell them the truth...
because...
once you lose me,
you'll lose everything.
You seem resentful.
In your next life,
I hope you're born...
with more power.
I heard...
my termination has been withdrawn.
I also heard that you're resigning from your post.
Must I consider it...
as an apology...
for what...
you have done to me in the past?
I didn't dare...
conjure up such a thought.
I am...
the best doctor among the others I recognise.
I just wanted to leave a legacy here.
What are your plans...
from now on?
I think I can finally put my feet up and relax...
freely...
like you told me to.
(Beautiful Mind)
(Doctor Show)
According to Neuroscience,
you must love one another if you wish to live young.
Love is important to healthy lifestyles.
I'm Neurosurgeon Kim Min Jae.
Kim Min Jae. It was Kim Min Jae.
It wasn't Lee Young Oh.
Kim Min Jae was the reason why I didn't get casted.
The game is over, Dr Soh.
You can't compete with her looks.
Should I introduce you to a plastic surgeon?
Instead of a TV show,
why don't you try running a podcast?
She should be spending her time on planning her future,
instead of hosting a TV show.
Doctors need to stick to their expertise.
My gosh. Dr Kim Min Jae!
- Min Jae! - Let go of me!
Dr Kim, you look great on television.
Thank you.
Why don't we work on a research paper together...
for the upcoming neurology conference?
We can be academic celebrities.
I'm sorry.
I'm not keen on listing people who don't contribute.
Min Jae. Min. Hey, Min Jae.
Kim Min Jae!
Oh, my.
I just visited Director Shin's grave.
I heard the research team developed...
a myocardial sheet...
without side effects for valve patients.
Yes. How did you know?
Dr Lee told me.
My son visited me recently.
The director told me...
that you aren't taking any painkillers.
Isn't it too painful?
I'm doing great.
I want to...
live out my life...
being the person I am until the end.
Dr Hyun,
I'm really proud of you...
for being so brave at such a young age.
In exchange, I'm tightening my belt...
to cover the research funds.
Yet, I'm happy.
Nam Gun Ho.
The test results are out.
I fainted during the rehearsal.
I guess I'm getting older.
Nam Gun Ho.
This is a jazz piece by Shostakovich.
Do you know it?
There's an acoustic nerve glioma.
You have a tumour in the acoustic nerve.
Will I be okay...
with the surgery?
As you suspect, you will lose auditory function.
What happens if I don't undergo surgery?
It's like a ticking bomb...
that can cause a fatal...
cerebral haemorrhage.
If the surgery is successful,
will my auditory function...
remain at least a little bit?
Sometimes, hope...
makes you expect the impossible.
Nam Gun Ho, I want you...
to make the right decision.
Your acoustic nerves...
cannot be saved.
What do you know about music?
You have...
never had a chance to appreciate music.
That's how you can make such a stoic expression...
towards a cellist.
That's how you can tell me...
that I'll lose my hearing.
Darn it.
Tell me if I'm wrong.
You may continue.
I...
cannot feel...
your pain.
I can't be in pain for you.
I have a disability that impairs...
my ability to empathise with others.
As you have said,
I cannot even appreciate music.
That's why...
I'm planning to stand by your side.
I won't ever turn a blind eye to your pain...
or feel exhausted.
Whenever you need me,
I will extend out my hand...
until the moment...
you leave the hospital with a healthy body.
Gosh, this woman.
You're climbing up...
the stairs.
They must be very steep.
Do you really expect me...
to believe you can feel that?
I cannot feel...
your heart.
I am more sensitive and delicate than others.
I ended up meeting you, who is more obtuse than most.
That's how I ended up lying everyday.
Then,
can you feel where I am headed?
I cannot even empathise with you.
That's not something...
you feel.
That's called logical reasoning.
It's called logic.
When it comes to you, it's very...
- easy to deduce. - In this case,
"easy" isn't the right word.
"Consistent" is the right word.
Like the way...
I was to you?
The only choice I can make...
is...
to love you.
(Thank you for watching Beautiful Mind.)