(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
(Episode 2)
Is that you, Jin Sung?
Hey. Your surgery is tomorrow!
You shouldn't be eating anything.
That's why I'm going to drink.
Listen to me.
I don't want to place a burden on my family.
I'm not getting the surgery.
Why don't you trust me one more time?
Okay?
It's not only misfortune...
that comes without a notice.
She was a patient with a valve deformity.
She underwent valvuloplasty at our hospital, but it didn't go well.
Now, she's waiting to get artificial valves.
It was clearly medical malpractice...
No,
it was fraud.
You're only in your first year as an operating surgeon.
Are you saying I made a mistake?
Professor,
if you admit your mistake...
and take responsibility for future treatments,
you may be forgiven.
After all, we're only human.
Forgiven?
Take off your glasses.
Take off your glasses!
Do you want to be fired?
If we don't admit our mistakes,
we'll be no more than monsters with scalpels.
I don't want to live like that.
- My gosh.
- My goodness.
Hey, First-year.
What's with the condescending look? It doesn't suit you.
Are you not confident enough to take responsibility?
Are you just going to run away?
Is that it?
Are you planning to write an autobiography saying that...
you didn't do anything wrong?
Professor.
Go apologise. Beg for his forgiveness.
Tell him you weren't in your right mind.
Beg for his forgiveness.
I'm sorry.
Suk Joo.
That's the only way I can ask you to be my assistant.
In exchange, I will fight on your behalf.
I'll get the hospital to cover the expenses for the surgery.
If that doesn't work, I'll deduct it from my salary.
It's your fault if my wife leaves me.
Young lady, stop eavesdropping and go back to your room.
It's almost time for rounds.
I know you're hiding under the staircase.
You know,
I do a bad job stitching up patients...
who skip rounds.
What are you doing?
Come out.
Go to your room.
Professor!
(One More Bottle)
(Beautiful Mind)
The patient with cardiac tamponade...
underwent an emergency pericardiocentesis.
When Pathology sends the result on...
Gye Jin Sung's pericardial fluid,
get ready to transfer to the Department of Internal Medicine.
This is amazing.
Will I ever be able to do this?
He doesn't even need to look at the ultrasound.
He was very accurate.
That was a dangerous procedure.
The fact that he only relies on his instincts...
may mean 1 of 2 things.
Either he is a genius, or he is arrogant.
Either way, he's a dangerous man.
I thought it was you.
Then, who is that dangerous man?
It was a critical situation for me, too.
An officer who was suspicious of the death of a patient...
sneaked into the office of the operating surgeon...
and died.
It could stir up the imagination...
of those who are curious.
That's unlikely...
since I was in the operating room.
I see.
There was another operating surgeon in the operating room at that time.
Then, would people take you...
for a witness...
or an accomplice?
By the way,
what brings you to my office?
I came to express my gratitude as the patient's doctor.
- Patient Gye Jin Sung...
- Yesterday.
What I'm curious about is what happened yesterday.
Why did she come to my office last night?
Kang Chul Min's surgery footage...
was deleted.
If that's what you're here for,
I'll gladly give it to you.
Here you go.
As her doctor, you should give her a warning.
Tell her that her sense of duty as a police officer is important,
but she should take better care of herself.
Dr Hyun, would you prefer grape juice?
It's supposed to be good for overcoming fatigue.
Thank you.
Your pericardial fluid...
- is fortunately...
- Oh!
That's right.
Apple Juice. Apples are great for you in the morning.
Fortunately, the results of your test...
came out clean.
Once the culture test is over, we'll see if there's any infection...
Oh, right. What about orange juice?
We need vitamin C and orange juice has vitamin C.
Never mind. It's tangerine juice from Jeju Island.
I'm full.
Dr Hyun,
why can't the other doctors take care of my dressing?
I'm no longer the little girl from 10 years ago.
Didn't you know?
You've been my patient in need of special care for the past decade.
And I don't think that's going to change any time soon.
You treated me like a VIP patient...
last night when you saved me.
You saved my life once again.
That should be directed at someone else.
It was Dr Lee Young Oh...
who saved you last night.
It was Dr Lee Young Oh.
Dr Lee Young Oh?
I want to die!
Leave me alone...
and let me die!
Why won't you leave me alone?
Why won't you let me die?
It's okay. It's okay.
- Hold on.
- Don't come near me!
Doctor!
Doctor, he's holding a scalpel!
Look.
If you come near me, I'm going to kill you.
Let's die together.
- Dr Lee.
- Don't go near him!
- Doctor!
- Oh, no!
- Don't come near me.
Don't come near me.
Don't come near me!
Sir,
I'm on your side.
Next time,
you need to slit your wrist along the ulnar artery.
From the top...
to the bottom.
You need to slit exactly from here to here.
After two minutes,
you will be pronounced dead.
That's what you wanted, right?
This doesn't show me that you really mean it.
You lack decisiveness.
It's very sloppy.
- Stop him!
- Let go!
- Let me go!
- Stop him!
Stop...
the patient!
Hold him down!
Let me go!
Dr Lee. What's the matter?
Are you all right?
I'll be fine if you can get this patient off of me.
My goodness.
What a funny way of saying thank you.
Let's just say that...
we're even now for what happened last night.
I don't think so.
I'm sure...
you have a lot to say to me about last night.
Well,
I guess you're right.
Don't you think we need some privacy?
It's...
It's not what it looks like.
Dr Lee!
My heart is about to pop out of my chest.
What in the world...
- Right?
- Excuse me?
It's not just my heart that beats this fast, right?
Isn't it normal for your heart to be pounding in this situation?
Yes, that would be normal for most people.
Are you into me?
I'm really flattered,
but I need to ask my mum...
Ms Lee.
Dr Lee.
Hold on!
Should we continue our conversation from last night?
Well...
That's...
Why is the missing surgery footage...
in your office?
Dr Hyun also has a copy of that surgery footage.
I watched the surveillance video of the morgue and saw you there.
So you're saying that I killed the patient during surgery...
and destroyed the evidence.
Yet, you followed me all this way.
Aren't you scared?
This place doesn't have surveillance cameras. It's a blind spot.
What if I lured you here on purpose?
What do you mean by that?
You know everything about this case,
and you suspect me as the murderer.
We are...
the only ones here.
You may find it unfair, but no one will suspect me.
I'm a doctor who saved your life.
Do you really think people will suspect me as the murderer?
Will Hyunsung Medical Centre...
allow such suspicion?
Is that why you saved me?
You will never be able to investigate and reveal...
what happened in the operating room that day.
A person should live up to their title.
A doctor saves people's lives.
A police officer catches bad guys.
Just wait and see.
I will let the world know...
what you've done.
Nobody will be on your side then.
Not the doctors in this hospital,
and not even the hospital.
You are all here for the patients.
That's what I believe.
The word "believe" means it doesn't exist in this world.
"I believe in Santa Claus."
"I believe in a higher being."
"I believe in love."
You believe hospitals exist for the sake of patients.
I also believe that,
Officer Gye Jin Sung.
What happened to Kang Chul Min was unfortunate.
So what? It's over now!
Sergeant Park!
The hit-and-run of a stolen car lacked evidence,
so we couldn't proceed with the case any further.
All evidence was destroyed because the car was scrapped.
Unfortunately, Case 70-37...
will remain a cold case.
There's more behind this case!
The body was switched at the hospital.
You're the only one that thinks that.
You don't have any evidence.
"Police go by the case and is evaluated upon performance."
"Central Police Station".
Traffic Division has already closed this case,
Officer Gye Jin Sung.
- Will you approve...
- It's hot!
if I bring evidence of murder?
Transfer this case to Violent Crimes Division so I can find the murderer.
If you act independently,
I'll write you up as being absent without due notice.
Officer Ji, did you hear me?
Did you say that Traffic Division has already closed the case?
How can it be over already?
The victim is dead but his family cannot accept his death.
We haven't even started investigating this case.
Besides,
I'm the only witness.
Sergeant Park.
I studied for seven years to become a police officer.
I gave up on dating, relationships and men.
All I did was study.
That's why I'd like to solve this case...
No, I don't want to live as a cop who didn't even try.
Could you give me...
just one more day to find the evidence of murder?
Please, Sergeant Park.
Officer Ji, you heard her.
Put her down...
as taking paid vacation.
What you're doing is not our jurisdiction,
so you won't be getting extra pay.
Sergeant Park.
Go by the case.
I will evaluate you based on your performance.
Yes, Sir.
She sure is something else.
I am Officer Gye Jin Sung from Central Police Station.
We cannot release any documents...
without a warrant.
We have high expectations for this surgery.
If you have any other questions, feel free to ask.
Director Shin.
Officer Gye.
What's the matter?
I'd like to discuss something with you.
Is that so?
Could you talk to Dr Hyun instead?
I'm quite busy today.
- It's about Dr Lee.
- What?
Are you talking about the surgeon who will operate on Mr Kim?
Are you?
That's right.
Chief Chae,
I guess the reporters are very interested in Dr Lee.
I see that.
All right. I will especially show you the press release regarding...
Mr Kim's live surgery.
- Let's go.
- All right.
I will pretend that I didn't hear any of this.
It's inconceivable.
I saw it with my own eyes.
Regardless of whether it's true or not,
what you're saying...
is a death sentence for the hospital and the staff.
Please help me so that I can investigate Dr Lee.
I can't begin the investigation on my own.
Dr Lee is...
going to operate on Mr Kim tomorrow.
Everyone's eyes are on Hyunsung Medical Centre and Dr Lee right now.
That means...
you're afraid of the media.
I dedicated my whole life to Hyunsung Medical Centre.
Even if it's you who is asking,
I won't allow you to insult the staff and...
discredit the hospital.
I was wondering if your plan was going smoothly,
but I guess there's no need to ask.
I will never be able to disclose what happened...
in the operating room that day on my own.
(Lee Young Oh, Assistant Professor, Department of Neurosurgery)
Shall we begin,
Dr Lee?
The patient is...
a presidential candidate for the next term.
He wants to appear...
- before the public...
- What a big hit.
as a healthy man.
You're right.
Even a neurologist...
is interested in a live surgery.
I'm not interested in the surgery.
It's the surgeon.
This is it.
A pipeline stent.
(Pipeline stent: Diverts the blood to treat the aorta)
Oh, my!
Isn't that what Professor Altos Alps published about?
Wow. I've only read about this.
I can't believe I get to see it in person.
I'm so lucky.
Anyone can imitate.
I will refer to the screen...
to explain tomorrow's surgery.
What's going on, Dr Lee?
It's my turn now,
Dr Lee Young Oh.
I'm Officer Gye Jin Sung of Central Police Station.
Why is the police here?
On June 20,
there was a table death...
in Hyunsung's OR.
That patient...
was a victim of a murder disguised as a car accident.
Unfortunately, an attempted murder victim...
died on the operating table.
Are you curious...
about the cause of death?
I am as well. However,
we were unable to determine the cause...
because...
someone swapped out the body.
- What is she saying?
- What's going on?
The person who switched the body...
is in this room.
What?
Is that Dr Lee?
Isn't that him?
Even as a police officer,
this video is insufficient to determine who did it.
Therefore,
I plan to investigate thoroughly from now on.
Central Police Station.
A traffic officer?
Is she pretty?
I need to see her face-to-face.
Let's go.
We should go to Mr Kim before he backs down on the surgery.
We need to calm him down.
Did you eat?
Did you?
Please explain yourself, Dr Lee!
Your reputation is at stake.
Okay, okay, okay.
That's enough.
Fellow interns and specialists.
Let's not suspect...
and rebuke amongst ourselves. That's disgraceful.
Sir.
The live surgery is tomorrow.
He is the surgeon for the live surgery and it's a rare case,
so all attention is on him.
- For Hyunsung...
- He's trying so hard.
We should learn from him.
I care...
deeply about the patient and...
Dr Soh.
What is the most critical aspect...
of Assemblyman Kim Myung Soo's surgery?
We place the pipeline against the aorta...
to divert the blood flow...
and make the aorta expire on its own.
We will change the surgeon for tomorrow's live surgery...
from Dr Lee Young Oh to Dr Soh Ji Yong.
Thank you! I'll do my best, Sir!
Sir.
Give me a chance to explain.
You may...
explain in front...
of the ethics council.
I don't understand what's going on.
Did Dr Lee really do it?
I can't believe it.
The proof is undeniable. He was caught on camera.
On camera? Whatever.
Hey.
Don't criminals cover the camera first?
But he smiled.
He smiled.
Smile. Just like that.
Anyway,
that's what's weird.
Wait. Do you think...
he had the arrogance to think it was the perfect murder...
- or something like that?
- You're right.
Let's look up his past.
Yes, yes.
- Perfect murder.
- Let's stop...
the ridiculous deductions now.
Watch what you say.
I heard they will fire employees for their social network posts,
and I believe it.
As the surgeon who will perform Mr Kim's live surgery tomorrow,
I'd like to hear your opinion.
So here are some gifts.
This wasn't necessary.
But I'm grateful and so is my baby.
Just ask. What is it?
There are so many options,
and I have no experience,
so it's difficult.
There will be many viewers.
Wash up.
Peel off.
Masks.
What would be best...
for my skin?
Dr Soh is the winner.
He has great timing.
It's impeccable.
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Sit.
I wonder if Dr Soh ate.
I should've brought him.
Come on, Dr Kwon.
Don't get ahead of yourself.
Who said Dr Soh will be Kim Myung Soo's primary care doctor?
You can kiss up to him after he becomes President.
I brought my own food.
Okay.
I was shocked at Dr Lee.
He totally laid it on his own son.
What happens now to Dr Lee Young Oh?
If the ethics council determine there is a problem,
he may be dismissed...
or he may lose his license.
What do you think?
I'm going back now. Enjoy.
Dr Hyun must know.
You operated with him.
I guess we'll all find out when the ethics council tells us.
I'll see you later.
Okay. Bye.
Sure, I couldn't talk either.
Word spreads so quickly.
He may gain Dr Lee's disfavour, too.
Or...
he may end up getting implicated, too.
Thank you.
No, no.
Here. Cheers.
Don't drink too much.
Your wife will call me again.
Hey.
When my wife calls,
consider it a voice phishing call and hang up.
Suk Joo,
do you know...
what my dream is?
I know the answer to this.
You want the amount of doctors who apply to Cardiothoracic...
to double, right?
I've wasted my life.
Do you want 10 times the applicants?
It's the opposite.
It's for every single surgeon to disappear.
I wanted to make a lot of money...
under the name of Hyunsung and Cardio-cerebrovascular Centre.
That way, my wallet...
would always be nice and fat.
That way,
there will come a day when people can be cured...
without surgery.
Hey.
Wasn't Jin Sung awesome today?
She really looked like a police officer and a woman.
Our little kid is all grown up.
Sergeant Park.
I'll return to work tomorrow.
Hyunsung Medical Centre...
will investigate Kang Chul Min's case.
They'll find evidence that he was murdered.
It's still a hospital.
We have to have faith.
I am the surgeon...
who will perform the live surgery.
What happened to the body?
Even among cerebral aneurysms,
it is a unprecedented, rare case.
Tell me...
what happened in the OR that day.
I prepared this surgery. It is mine.
You're wrong. Again.
Look at me.
Look at me in the eyes.
Don't think only about...
what you want to say and what you think,
but read the other person.
His eyes are wide.
His eyebrows are raised.
His voice is confident.
His lips are curled upwards.
You are very angry...
at my behaviour.
This arm confirms his authority over me.
It means both you and I know...
that I am...
still under your control.
Don't forget the times...
we've spent together.
If it's for your sake,
I can...
start over, even now.
Let me ask again.
Why did you go to the morgue?
I wanted to confirm something before the autopsy.
What did you confirm?
Nothing.
A patient who died naturally and one who died a table death...
have no difference.
That's good.
That's what you should say to the ethics council.
If you say that much,
they'll believe you.
Forget the ethics council.
What do you think?
I trust you.
- Should I not have asked...
- Change the time for your shot.
We can add quetiapine as well.
(Quetiapine: Medication for repressing impulses)
Let's try it.
Can you...
handle it?
He can live...
like a normal person, right?
He can't process emotions.
It is impossible for him to read other people's emotions...
or empathise. At all.
Then...
It's called anti-social disorder.
They can't socialise at all.
He may be...
much more dangerous that you can imagine.
What...
must I do?
When people are happy,
this is how they look.
So,
it's like...
a signal.
They touch their necks.
Let's go over it again.
When people are nervous...
Forget the ethics council.
What do you think?
His pupils were shaking.
His eyebrows drooped down.
Suspicion.
He forced himself to make eye contact.
I trust you.
The subtle smile.
Lies.
Fear, that he does not...
want to show.
How do you feel?
Is there a reason why you're disclosing your surgery?
Cerebral aneurysms...
are a representative ailment faced by society.
Based on my long experience...
I will experience our nation's medical abilities...
and will be healed.
Please have faith in me and in our medical industry,
and support us.
I, Kim Myung Soo,
will be healed completely.
My dear citizens who are fighting illnesses even as of today,
let's be strong.
Send out the press release...
as soon as the surgery is over.
Yes, Sir.
Mr Kim, it's time.
I'm relying on you.
Let's go.
I'll start the anesthesia.
Wait. Wait.
Be careful.
Call my assistant. I have more orders for him.
Or call the chairman.
Go on.
Yes? You may speak.
Call the reporters.
Can I trust...
the replacement surgeon?
You should trust Hyunsung.
They are nothing but employees...
whom Hyunsung hired.
Think of it as a nice nap.
I'll be fine, right?
Everything will be fine, right?
People are all the same.
No one wants to be sick or die.
This will make good money.
I guess...
medical science is really the last hope...
for this country's economy.
All he cares about is his business.
For my business,
you are essential.
This is a promise from a trader who cares more about money than lives.
Does that...
make you feel a bit relieved?
(Dr Soh Ji Yong's Live Surgery)
(Notice of the Ethics Council)
Isn't it funny...
how these two are put together?
Officer Gye...
must be really excited now.
She took the live surgery away from me...
and made me stand before the ethics council.
Dr Lee.
Did you advise her...
that her sense of duty as a police officer is important,
but she should take better care of herself?
Oh, no.
I guess...
I should teach her myself.
The stent insertion is going along nicely.
Now,
I'll use this new technology.
Through the pipeline,
I will remove the aneurysm.
The surgery will be done successfully...
- without even bleeding.
- Excuse me.
Have you seen Dr Lee Young Oh?
No, I haven't.
Three bears are
In the same house
Daddy Bear, Mummy Bear
And Baby Bear
Daddy Bear is fat
Mummy Bear is slim
Baby Bear is so cute
They're dancing together
Excuse me.
This is a school zone. You shouldn't...
I'm here to turn myself in.
His BP went up.
Why?
Dr Soh, his BP is increasing.
I think the blood vessel is clogged.
What's going on?
What's happening?
I think he's having an embolism.
(Embolism: When an artery has a blood clot)
Here you go again.
You have to use jargons that I don't understand...
so I can't blame you for failure. Aren't I right?
It means that his blood vessel is clogged.
Do you think Dr Soh can handle this?
Shouldn't we stop the live surgery?
If the media starts talking about this...
Sir.
I'm sorry.
- Record this.
- What's going on?
Will he be okay?
- And then, put it in...
- Dr Soh.
- Dr Soh...
- Get out!
I can't lower his BP.
The aneurysm might rupture, Dr Soh.
The patient will die!
He's a very important patient.
I can't let him die!
Dr Yang, tell me.
You read the pipeline stent thesis, too.
Tell me what to do now!
Dr Soh.
Ms Jung.
Yes, Sir.
- What's going on?
- Why is it turned off?
Everyone, don't worry.
Emergency situations during surgery happen all the time.
We'll give you the details of the rest of the operation...
and the recovery process...
through the news release and a press briefing.
We'll move the patient to an operating room...
for an open brain surgery.
It's important to save his life.
The vital signs are unstable and he has intracerebral haemorrhage.
Do you think open brain surgery is possible?
You and I...
have never chosen which patient we should save.
Whomever the patient was, we always did our best.
And this is no exception.
- Dr Oh.
- Yes.
Prepare an operating room now.
The operating surgeon...
is me.
You said you would turn yourself in.
So why are we here?
A doctor saves people's lives.
A police officer catches bad guys.
I'll give you a chance to live up to your name.
Officer Gye...
Jin Sung.
Watch carefully...
what you have done.
His BP is still increasing.
Dr Lee.
You need to do something.
Has he...
begun the operation?
Sorry? Why do you ask?
I asked if he has begun the operation.
Irrigation.
Suction.
Is it because of the unusual lesion on his aneurysm?
Well...
It's... It's... I mean...
Answer me.
Is there a lesion?
There is...
a lesion. It's an unusual one.
His BP is still increasing.
The aneurysm will rupture if you don't do anything.
Mr Lee.
We're running out of time.
If we don't take it out now,
his life will be in danger.
What do you want, Dr Lee?
You said you're the only one who can perform this surgery.
I want full authority.
The authority that belongs to the head of the centre.
I want that.
Full authority?
The authority to decide on operations,
the use of research funds and the personnel matters.
- There are procedures to follow.
- It's still increasing.
He'll become brain dead.
Are you going to kill him?
It's...
up to you.
That's unexpected.
"The procedures to follow".
They must be more important to you...
than Mr Kim.
Fine.
Start the operation now.
You're the operating surgeon.
I need another surgeon.
You want me to do the operation?
I thought it was an aneurysm operation.
Don't worry.
I'm aware that you're a cardiac surgeon...
who's quite good and quick with his hands.
- Why me?
- Are you refusing an emergency?
That scary police officer is watching.
What do you want to show me?
This operation will be a perfect...
statement.
Dr Kim of Anesthesiology.
Please adjust the operating table.
I need to see the external carotid artery more clearly.
You can't do that.
Even a slight impact could put this patient in danger.
He is a ticking bomb.
If we move him,
the thinned blood vessel will burst.
We'll remove that blood vessel.
You're removing the parent artery?
The patient will die.
Dr Kim, didn't you hear what I said?
Adjust the table.
Suction.
- Suction!
- Yes, Doctor.
Dr Oh.
This isn't medical school.
Do you expect me...
to be patient enough to explain every step of surgery...
while I'm performing...
an emergency operation?
Dr Hyun.
Please extract the radial artery.
(Radial artery: Supplies blood to the lateral side of the forearm)
But the radial artery is in the wrist. What does that have to do...
You're planning to perform a brain vessel bypass.
Let's begin.
Dr Lee, that's...
It's a giant cerebral aneurysm due to the cirrhosis...
caused by fungus.
It's hard to locate the spot for clipping.
It's difficult to find the lesion...
using CT, MRI or an angiography.
You can't find that out...
unless you open the brain and do a biopsy.
This is a rare case.
How did you know about this?
You didn't open his brain to do a biopsy.
I've seen a similar patient.
It was the patient who died...
during our collaborative surgery.
I found this tiny fungus...
that I hadn't seen before in the patient's brain.
As I hadn't seen it before,
I wanted to look into it.
That's why I watched the surgery footage.
Normally, it flows into the blood vessel from the heart.
It seems to be a type of infectious fungus.
Infectious fungus...
It's common among endocarditis patients, drug users...
and immunosuppressant users.
Dr Lee.
Please keep this a secret.
I want to use it for my research.
Mr Kim was being treated...
for endocarditis.
I wanted to examine the body of the patient who died...
during the surgery to see if the fungus in his brain...
was caused by endocarditis.
As I had expected, his body showed signs of infectious endocarditis.
They were not car accident wounds.
Considering these symptoms,
I was certain that it might be a mycotic giant aneurysm.
I was sure.
And it needed an open brain operation.
Why didn't you say that at the conference?
I'm sure...
that those who were at the conference...
know better.
Why here?
Why did you choose the hospital I'm working in?
Why?
When I told you not to become a doctor,
you promised...
that you would become a good doctor like normal people.
However,
you made a deal over a patient's life.
To make it worse, it was as soon as you came back.
Why did you do that?
I came to realise...
that the best asset I have as a doctor...
is this completely hollow heart of mine.
That's how...
I was able to save Mr Kim.
I wasn't distracted by emotions.
I had no fear.
Did I tell you...
that I'd become a good doctor like normal people?
I'm sorry, Father.
I don't think...
I can keep that promise.
I'm already...
superior than anyone else...
as a doctor.
I have a question for Dr Soh Ji Yong.
I heard that there was a problem during surgery.
What's the cause?
That's enough. Please read the news release for further information.
We prepared a meal...
Is it true that Mr Kim's life could have been in danger...
without Dr Lee Young Oh's open brain surgery?
Was it a misjudgement of the operation method?
Was it medical malpractice?
That's what this hospital is all about.
Keep your chin up, Dr Soh.
We won't apologise to them...
because of your incompetency.
It's true that Mr Kim's life was in danger.
However,
it wasn't medical malpractice.
It was an emergency situation that could happen to any one of us.
The time when we hope for...
a miracle made by one genius doctor is over now.
What happened today...
proved that our hospital has a great medical team...
and how well we can respond to emergency situations...
because of our medical staff.
Dr Soh Ji Yong...
helped prove this.
Aren't I right, Dr Soh?
Yes. He's right!
This is how our hospital is!
I have another question.
Did you find anything unusual...
other than the signs of endocarditis...
when you examined Patient Kang Chul Min?
- For instance...
- For instance,
that his heart was missing?
You're such a bad liar.
You knew...
that his heart was missing.
As I expected,
I wasn't the only one that visited the morgue.
Because you, Dr Hyun Suk Joo,
were there as well.
Isn't that true?
I'm glad you're here.
You'll find this interesting, too.
Look forward to it.
I know what you want to know...
is this.
You're wondering if I was the one who took the heart.
I'm not interested in...
the 300g lump of muscles that can only pump blood.
However, I know who did it.
It's either someone who you know well...
or someone Officer Gye trusts.
Dr Hyun,
you might be the one who did it.
(Beautiful Mind)
You can't do this to me.
You made me trust you. How can you do this to me?
Don't you think you were cruel?
I hope he didn't cause any trouble.
Just stay quiet...
in fear that I might be the one who really did it.
Can I see you now?
Are you hiding something from me?
Did you know that?
I'm going to perform an emergency operation.
The patient is Director Shin Dong Jae.