(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
Endocardium.
Interventricular septum.
It separates the lower chambers of the heart.
Left pulmonary vein.
Pulmonary artery.
Arch of aorta.
Superior vena cava.
That's enough.
I cannot approve this.
You can't do it.
The trapezius muscle.
Scalenus.
Sternocleidomastoid muscle.
Spinal arteriovenous.
I memorised everything, Father.
- Young Oh.
-  I want to attend medical school.
I want to follow after your footsteps.
It's my dream.
You shouldn't have dreams.
You're different from normal people.
Lee Young Oh.
Live quietly,
just enough to keep breathing.
Make sure no one discovers who you are.
(Tissue Engineering: Regenerative Medicine Scholarship)
(Episode 3)
Thank you.
- Professor!
-  My goodness!
-  Doctor!
He needs urgent care.
- Doctor!
-  Professor!
- Professor!
-  Let's move.
Wake up, Professor!
- Are you all right?
-  What's the matter?
It must be Parkinson's or Alzheimer's disease.
He was showing symptoms of...
hallucination and forgetfulness.
Can nothing be done?
Professor Yoon, you can't be like this now.
Please do something.
There's no need to worry.
Who is he?
It's chronic subdural haemorrhage.
Blood must have been accumulating...
under his skull for quite some time.
The symptoms of Alzheimer's disease, dysbasia...
and logoplegia often seem similar.
Is he correct?
Find out where the ambulance is.
Professor!
What are you doing? Call the ambulance, now!
He doesn't have much time left.
Yes, Sir.
Father, it's not too late yet.
Thank goodness.
I was afraid I'd never see Professor Yoon again.
We need to keep track of his progress at the hospital.
Are you being discrete or secretive?
What do you mean?
Him.
Why did you hide such a brilliant son for so long?
Come here.
Look at you. Are you a medical student?
Which school do you attend? Preparatory or regular?
I'd like to attend...
but I still need my father's approval.
Dr Lee disapproves? Why is that?
I don't think I meet his expectations.
That's nonsense. He's brilliant.
He's better than me.
Right?
Dr Lee, is there a particular reason why?
It's not an easy path for young folks like him.
Father, you will approve, right?
He is quite spirited.
Answer him.
I'll become a good doctor.
Just like you, Father.
(Beautiful Mind)
My gosh.
I'm glad you're here. You'll find this interesting.
Look forward to it.
What Dr Hyun wants to know...
is whether I removed the heart from the cadaver or not.
I have no interest in the 300g lump of muscle...
which only serves to pump blood all day.
However, I know who did it.
It's either someone who you know well...
or someone...
Officer Gye trusts.
Dr Hyun.
You might be the one who did it.
What are you getting at?
Anyone with a bit of medical knowledge would know this.
Maybe I have been overestimating your ability.
The fungus discovered in Kang Chul Min's brain...
was caused by a mutated lesion from his heart.
In order to conceal the lesion,
someone stole the heart.
Someone must've had a dire reason for doing that.
Paging Dr Hyun of Cardiothoracic.
An urgent patient is in need of CS.
Please head to the emergency room right away.
Yes?
What is the patient's blood pressure?
Go on ahead.
I'm done talking.
I'll see you later, Jin Sung.
What you just said...
Are you speaking the truth?
Dr Hyun...
Do you really think he is responsible?
If you're asking for my opinion,
I'm not interested.
It was just a case I needed for Mr Kim's surgery.
Well, whether you reveal the truth...
or apprehend the culprit,
the rest is up to you.
A doctor saves people's lives...
and a police officer catches bad guys.
Live up to your title,
Officer Gye.
The patient is a 13-year-old girl. Unconscious.
She's went from a state of being drowsy to stupor.
Her blood pressure is 170.
We need an IV here.
She fainted while stretching before soccer practice.
ICH.
Intracerebral haemorrhage.
Her frontal and parietal lobes have...
multiple brain contusions and subdural haemorrhages.
Should I get the OR ready, Doctor?
There's no need to ask.
If we don't finish the surgery within an hour,
it'll be hard for her to play soccer again.
She's a very lucky girl.
Dr Lee will take great care of her.
I'm a big fan, Mr Hong Il Bum.
Thanks.
She must have taken after you...
to play soccer.
Yes, she's a full back just like me.
She'll make the national team someday.
Min Kyung will be okay, right?
Min Kyung is my daughter.
She's tough.
I heard she fainted during the warm up.
That's correct.
Nobody made contact.
She fell into a state of stupor...
without any previous symptoms.
(Stupor: Unconsciousness)
Yes, I assumed she was anaemic...
since she's still growing.
What's wrong with my daughter's body?
Honey, did you know about this?
You're with her 24 hours a day.
She doesn't like spending time with me...
and tells me that she's grown up now.
Were there any reports...
of her getting bullied at school?
No.
She's kind-hearted.
She's nice to everyone.
Ma'am, they're the ones who usually get bullied.
That's not true.
The tryouts...
for the Youth Soccer Team is coming up soon.
Min Kyung spends all of her time...
practising with her dad.
She doesn't even go to school.
What's the matter?
Are you suspecting me...
of hitting my daughter?
Min Kyung is my daughter.
She's my one and only girl.
I can give up my life...
for her.
Why? Why would I do such a thing?
Is that true?
- Of course.
-  Yes.
He's a good father and husband.
I'm asking if he's the patient's biological father.
Are you accusing me...
of abusing her...
because I'm not her biological father?
Do you think I'm responsible for her condition?
In most cases, child abuse...
is committed by biological parents.
That's not what I'm curious about.
Please hold.
Dr Lee, the OR is ready.
I'll ask you once again.
Are you really the biological father of the patient?
Yes, that's right.
She's my own daughter.
My goodness.
Hold on a second, please.
Orthopaedics is also looking for an OR.
- Please tell them that we don't need it.
-  What?
- Hold on!
-  Dr Lee.
You said earlier that Min Kyung...
needs to be operated on within an hour.
If we operate on her now,
she'll face a table death from excessive blood loss.
(Table death: Death during operation)
That's right.
Blood is being congested without external shock.
There are signs of internal bleeding around the joints.
Her consciousness is fading at a rapid rate.
On top of that, both of you are lying.
If I'm correct,
she is suffering from intracerebral haemorrhage...
caused by haemophilia.
Only specialised medication and surgery...
can halt the excessive bleeding.
That's why we are urgently asking for surgery.
What's the matter?
Is it because of the money?
Haemophilia.
Haemophilia is...
hereditary.
It's uncommon, but if a child suffers from haemophilia,
either the mother...
or the father...
should also be a haemophilic patient.
You can see what that's like.
Here's my conclusion.
If you were suffering from haemophilia,
you would have never made the national team.
Let's verify the information.
I'll ask one last time.
Is he really the biological father...
of the patient?
Why aren't you answering?
She's my daughter.
Go on, tell the doctor.
Min Kyung is my daughter.
She's my one and only child.
I see.
- Dr Yang.
-  Yes?
Please ready the patient for a transfer.
Yes, Doctor.
The surgery...
Please proceed with the surgery.
Please save...
Min Kyung.
Irrigation.
Bipolar.
Retractor.
You were amazing, Dr Lee.
There aren't many surgeons...
who are capable of operating on haemophilia patients.
An accurate diagnosis followed by a perfect surgery.
You think you're a good doctor, don't you?
Will you still be considered a good doctor...
once she wakes and looks for her father?
Your opinion seems to be a predetermined "no".
Did you really have to go that far?
An haemophilia exam could've been carried out.
Should I have waited two weeks for the results...
before operating on her?
Don't you think you were too cruel?
Min Kyung.
It's Mum.
You are a good girl.
Thank you...
very much.
Dad?
Do you want to see Dad?
Don't be a crybaby and get better soon.
Look how weak you are.
How will you become a national team player?
Sleep tight, okay?
Let's just consider...
all of this...
as a nightmare.
I'm not the one who lied to him...
and made him raise a kid that was not his.
"I will do anything and everything for my child."
I'm not the one who made...
such a grandiloquent statement.
One more thing.
I'm also not the doctor...
who almost misdiagnosed a patient...
with CT results alone.
The surgery is over, and the child lives.
Do you really think...
I'm cruel?
Is Dr Hyun...
still in surgery?
Yes, it involved a aortic dissection,
so it's still ongoing since yesterday.
It'll take over 12 hours.
Leave the message with me.
I'll pass it on.
By the way,
has the table death murder suspect been caught yet?
Dr Lee is no longer a suspect.
Why are you looking for Dr Hyun anyway?
It's a personal matter.
I have something to discuss with him.
Thank you.
Dr Nam, you said it was Dr Hyun, right?
The person looking for Kang Chul Min's...
surgery footage before that officer...
was Dr Hyun, right?
Yes.
For instance,
a heart may be missing.
As expected,
I wasn't the only one that visited the morgue.
Because you, Dr Hyun Suk Joo, were there as well.
Dr Lee was the only person...
who was captured in the morgue security footage.
Dr Hyun.
Thank you. There's wasn't much to see.
That's what I said.
It's the same boring footage.
Why did they make such a fuss about deleting it?
I'm sure it's because they don't want the exposure.
Did the cardiothoracic surgeon ask personally?
No. That's always handled by the secretaries...
So they did make the request...
to delete Dr Hyun's footage.
(Surgery Board)
(Dr Hyun Suk Joo: Complete)
The operation took over 12 hours.
Witness statements are crucial for the investigation.
Dr Hyun isn't a flight risk.
He isn't likely to destroy the evidence either.
The heart is missing.
The heart.
We'll find out soon...
what really happened.
We'll uncover who really took the heart.
Dr Hyun...
would never lie to me.
All human beings...
lie without exception.
Even when their child faces a life-or-death situation,
people lie until the very moment they're caught.
It's what humans do.
Like you, now.
Hyunsung Insurance.
What's the price of the stock?
It's at 98 dollars a share.
It's fallen quite a bit.
My father will summon my brother...
and show him some fatherly love.
Perhaps, a swift kick as well.
My goodness, Dr Lee. What a brilliant performance.
You rescued a little girl from haemophilia.
Not many Korean surgeons are capable enough to do that.
That's right, Sir.
That's a shame that doctors can't do their jobs.
With the current cost of insurance,
diagnosing and treating patients...
with such rare and incurable diseases...
will thoroughly hurt any hospital's profit.
So...
Then it's not a matter of skill.
Brilliant doctors are refusing to operate...
because it hurts profits...
unlike our great Dr Lee here.
I won't hold you responsible this time.
You learned to prioritise the budget, operate...
and know what it is to be the head of the centre.
Let's consider this...
an expensive private lesson from my pockets.
I didn't know...
that you were trying to profit from a hospital.
There must be a reason why Hyunsung Medical Centre,
a hospital unfit for the nation's public insurance,
was passed unto such an ambitious person...
such as yourself.
You need a hospital with specialised care...
for yourself or a family member...
who might become afflicted with an incurable disease.
The institution must match...
your wealth and power with thorough service.
You need private health insurance...
that caters to the highest class.
To give an example,
Hyunsung Insurance.
Mr Chae,
did he just read my mind?
Did he just figure out why...
a black sheep like me stands among white-robed angels?
I am not interested in the affairs of a princely heir.
However, I know why someone like you...
would need me.
Advertising balloons...
lure people in with elaborate catchphrases.
You need to assure wealthy clients...
that top-notch service and care...
can be found at Hyunsung Medical Centre.
I, Lee Young Oh,
plan to float very high up.
High enough that no one would dare bring me down.
Someone told me...
that you are like a pretty knife.
You seem attractive, but you can be very harmful.
Indeed, I am a brat that my family abandoned.
Let this brat grab that knife and do a sword dance.
Is that why you needed...
to become the head of the centre?
Do you want to be recognised...
as the doctor everyone looks up to in front of me?
It's because you don't deserve the title,
Father.
A corpse had been switched,
and the corpse's heart went missing.
But you didn't even look into it.
What?
You seem more righteous than anyone else.
You seem to be fair and impartial.
But in your heart,
all you did was suspect your own son.
You were afraid it was me.
You were in fear.
- That was...
-  Tilted chin.
Puzzled.
Moving Adam's apple.
A silent affirmation.
Your mouth may lie,
but your body...
cannot.
Where did it go?
My goodness.
Excuse me.
What is she doing?
- My goodness.
-  What's wrong with her?
There it is.
You're buying drinks tonight.
Gosh.
Come on, give it to me.
I bought you the drinks.
One more bottle of soju, please.
Someone who can drink alone...
has nothing to fear...
because that person has figured out the secret to life.
They've figured out that you're alone in this world...
and that life is bitter.
Oh, wise one.
Let's drink.
What gave you courage...
back then?
Is it because of Suk Joo?
Why are you hesitating?
Just go and tell him.
Mr Shin.
Did you know?
You punk.
How can you call yourself a brave police officer?
"Dr Hyun Suk Joo,"
"I like you."
"Do you like me?"
Okay?
That's not it.
You can't fool me.
I know you inside and out.
Don't even try.
That isn't it. It isn't.
Then what else are you stressed about?
Tell me. Tell me.
Goodness.
I'm leaving. You're drunk. Let's go.
Then you don't need this, right?
I don't need it either. What should we do with this?
Should I throw this away? Where should I throw it?
- Where...
-  The heart is missing.
What do you mean?
Kang Chul Min, the patient that passed away.
His heart is missing.
That's why the corpse was switched.
That's probably why they tried to kill him too.
Dr Hyun...
knew from the start.
Jin Sung.
Don't tell me he didn't know.
He isn't the only one...
I can't trust right now.
Hi. Can I see Kang Chul Min's records?
There is nothing in our system.
Are you sure?
Thank you.
A corpse had been switched,
and the corpse's heart went missing.
But...
you didn't bother finding out the truth.
(Dr Hyun Suk Joo)
Hi.
What are you doing here at this hour?
This is right outside my lab...
and this is when I always leave.
You are still young, aren't you?
Okay. Good night.
Hey.
Are you keeping something from me?
You're not an intern...
or a specialist. You're the director.
There's no emergency surgery.
What made you run here at this hour?
An accident?
Come on.
I came to look through some research papers.
I've been doing too much administrative work.
I'm not as sharp as I used to be.
Is that really it?
Are you the only one who studies...
and conducts research?
I did better in school. Come on now.
There really was an accident...
if you thought about research papers while drinking.
- Dong Jae.
-  Yes?
Someone with diabetes shouldn't drink every day.
What about your medicine?
Yes, Sir.
I'm taking them without fail.
I have three wives.
My old lady at home.
Suk Joo nags me to take my meds in the hospital.
Now, you too?
What? Are you scared?
Do you think I'll die first?
Whom else...
do I have?
Good night.
Bye.
The fungus discovered in Kang Chul Min's brain...
was caused by a mutated lesion from his heart.
In order to conceal the lesion,
someone stole the heart.
Someone must've had a dire reason for doing that.
(7 missed calls)
Can we meet right now?
Why did you want to see me...
Dr Lee.
That...
Kang Chul Min's file...
May I see it?
Do you hear me?
The fungus found...
in the lesion of Kang Chul Min's heart...
I need to know what it is.
I...
I have an emergency surgery.
The patient is...
Shin Dong Jae.
Sudden loss of motor skills.
Loss of tactile sensibility on one side of the body.
Brightness.
Paralysis of motor skills.
Acute cerebral haemorrhage.
(Operation in process)
Dr Hyun.
He just went into surgery.
Why... Why?
Why does he need surgery?
(Lee Young Oh)
Shin Dong Jae. 59-year-old male.
He's suffering from cerebral haemorrhage.
I'm the lead surgeon, Lee Young Oh.
We will begin surgery now.
You must have been shocked.
We have to wait for the results of the surgery.
But thank goodness...
he was in the hospital with Dr Lee Young Oh.
He was really lucky.
I was playing golf when I heard the news.
I came as soon as I heard.
I see.
Sir. Well...
What happened?
-  Well...
The director...
You can never be sure of your health.
How was the CT?
Good. There wasn't too much blood.
And Dr Lee is the lead surgeon.
Isn't it too easy for him?
That's right. He's the VIP specialist.
Just accept it.
Life is unfair, especially when it comes to talent.
He was born gifted. You know that.
No, I don't.
I don't.
Cottonoid.
Gelfoam.
I don't know what's going on.
I was with him last night...
and he seemed perfectly fine.
I know. He said he was coming home.
Why did he come to the hospital?
The hospital?
At that late hour? Why...
Dr Lee.
The bleeding won't stop.
Cottonoid.
Irrigation.
Dr Lee, I can't stabilise his blood pressure.
Suction.
He'll die on the table at this rate.
- It's not too late...
-  I've decided to operate.
That means he will live.
Administer the antihypertensive,
and I need two more bags of blood.
Let's focus.
He's in cardiac arrest.
Cardiac arrest...
Cardiac arrest.
59-year-old male.
Height, 178cm. Weight, 82kg.
Health conditions. Diabetes.
Regular insulin injections.
June 26, midnight.
Lost consciousness due to cerebral haemorrhage.
CT scan confirmed blood in the brain.
Surgery began at 2am.
Surgery duration, three hours.
Source of bleeding sealed.
Dr Lee.
Removed blood clot, a source of pressure on the brain.
It was to prevent potential infarction and edema.
Dr Lee.
What...
I was not wrong.
My surgery...
was not a failure.
I was not wrong.
How could you say that right now?
Mr Shin passed away.
How could you say that...
in front his family who trusted you?
You're the lead surgeon.
Aren't you the lead surgeon? That's not right!
Aren't you...
As the lead surgeon,
I'm telling you the surgery was perfect.
My surgery was perfect.
My surgery was perfect!
Young Oh!
Let's hear...
the rest of that at the mortality conference.
(Mortality Conference: doctors discuss cause of death)
That is still my right as the head of the centre.
I apologise...
for my son's mistake.
No words can express...
-  Dong Jae...
the loss we feel.
I was so worried.
Are you okay?
Move.
Talk to me. I can comfort you.
Comfort?
Comfort.
Do you think that's possible?
Fine.
Dr Lee.
Are you sure...
you're okay?
Of course.
I am...
very fine.
Don't you think...
Dr Lee Young Oh is a bit off?
At first, I thought,
"Here's another arrogant jerk."
But in front of the OR,
he looked like he was alone in this world.
The more I see him,
the more different he seems.
Even a talented person gets scared.
The director died on his operating table.
And he was his father's best friend of 40 years.
That's right.
He was the nicest man in the world.
He was so nice.
He seemed like a soft old man,
but I got hit a lot when I was a student.
We all feel lousy, so I'll buy. Hold on.
Drink.
What's gotten into him?
Hey.
- Here.
-  What is that?
What is this?
You need to give us this before you order.
The menu is different.
That's why I'm giving it to you now,
in case you give us nasty food.
Come on now. Treat us on a night like this.
This won't help you buy a building.
Don't bother.
Goodness.
I really can't stand...
being a surgeon on a day like this.
Something is very strange.
It shouldn't have been a table death.
What happened to the director?
Cheers.
Someone who can drink alone...
has nothing to fear...
because that person has figured out the secret to life.
Here you go.
They've figured out that you're alone in this world...
and that life is bitter.
What are you doing here?
The funeral has begun.
Let's go and say goodbye.
I can't go there.
I won't go.
Jin Sung.
He died because of me.
What do you mean by that?
I told him everything.
I told him Patient Kang Chul Min's heart was removed,
and that you visited the morgue.
I believe...
that someone in this hospital killed him.
Last night,
Mr Shin came to the hospital to confirm that.
And he died.
I asked the National Health Insurance Corporation...
to fax the original copy of...
Patient Kang Chul Min's medical record.
I think the person...
who killed Patient Kang Chul Min...
did the same thing to Mr Shin.
This can't be true.
Patient Kang Chul Min...
had never been treated in this hospital.
Hyunsung has nothing to do with that patient.
Do you think I can trust you?
Why didn't you tell me the truth?
He was my patient...
and I was afraid.
I didn't want you to see me that way.
Jin Sung.
Why don't you take a break?
Let me look into this.
Even though you don't trust me,
I still care about you.
No.
I will do this.
I will pay my respects to Mr Shin later.
I don't deserve to cry over his death yet.
I'll fight on your behalf.
The hospital won't charge her for her surgery.
If that doesn't work, I'll deduct it from my pay.
Young lady.
I know you're hiding under the stairs.
Professor!
Jin Sung.
I'm sorry.
I hope it's not too late...
to tell you...
that you can trust people in this world.
Can you give me a chance...
to prove it to you?
When I'm done,
shall we have a drink together again?
Cottonoid.
Irrigation.
He's in cardiac arrest.
Dr Lee.
The bleeding won't stop.
Dr Lee, I can't stabilise his blood pressure.
Administer the antihypertensive,
and I need two more bags of blood.
I'm home.
I've been thinking about...
why you came back.
I want you to apologise...
to the patient's family for what you did today.
If I apologise to them,
would it bring him back?
It wouldn't bring him back,
but it would console them.
Normal people...
call this a sense of responsibility.
Normal people.
So a sense of responsibility...
is just like a collective punishment.
It's like being punished...
when you've done nothing wrong.
That's not fun.
You showed too much of yourself today.
You don't have a guilty conscience,
sympathy...
or a sense of responsibility.
You don't feel anything...
when you see a patient suffering.
You showed your true face.
You had better apologise to them...
if you want to hide your true self.
It was a buy one, get one free deal.
You're a piece of work.
When you drive a car,
you just have to keep an eye on traffic signs.
You can avoid accidents that way.
So?
What traffic sign should I see right now?
A stop sign.
When a car in front of you obstructs your way,
there's nothing you can do about it.
What if the brake doesn't work?
What if I can't stop the car?
What do you mean?
What would you do?
I should turn the wheel.
Because I'm a wise one, capable of doing anything.
My team?
Why should we?
It's not a hit-and-run any more.
Wake up.
So?
Please transfer me to Violent Crimes Unit Two...
so I can investigate this case.
What case?
I need to find the evidence that Mr Shin found.
I also need to ask around.
I need a warrant to find evidence of murder...
I...
really should find the killer.
Please give me your permission.
My goodness.
You're talking like you're declaring war...
- when you're surrendering.
-  Why would I...
Didn't you say that the suspect works at Hyunsung?
Why should I be on the losing side of war?
I'm not going to lose.
She's out of her mind.
Okay, then.
Find the evidence and specify the suspect.
- Pardon?
-  Then, I'll take you in my team.
Both you and this case.
Sir...
I... I'll be back.
I'll be back!
- Sir!
-  Sir!
What? Why?
- She's a bit...
-  She's out of her mind.
She might file a complaint of gender discrimination.
I should make her give up.
She never gives up.
There are three kinds of people the police can't catch.
Prosecutors, lawyers and doctors.
It's Hyunsung for crying out loud.
No way.
Do you think they're easy to deal with?
Please allow the autopsy.
If we can show that he was murdered,
the Violent Crimes Division...
who are better than me can start the investigation.
I'm not sure about it, Jin Sung.
Would that be okay?
I don't know.
I'm not sure what is good for the sake of Mr Shin.
What do you all think?
She wants an autopsy on Mr Shin...
to find out what went wrong with his surgery.
What do you think, Dr Soh?
The leading surgeon was Dr Lee Young Oh.
I don't think...
that Dr Lee made any mistakes.
Mr Shin...
loved and cared about...
his junior surgeons.
It won't be good...
for the reputation of Mr Shin or this hospital.
Do you all agree with him?
Rather than leaving behind suspicion...
-  We would...
like to remember him...
as a doctor who dedicated his life for his patients...
and as someone who was generous to fellow doctors.
Officer.
Mr Shin loved this hospital.
There's no one here who wants...
to see him wrapped up in a scandal...
before we let him go.
- Ma'am.
-  Are you trying...
to bring Mr Shin...
into derision like last time...
because of your ambition?
It is now time for us to say goodbye to him.
But we still have hope...
of meeting him again someday.
By grieving our loss today,
we can show our love for him,
help each other overcome the grief...
and give each other hope.
Dear Father,
We pray for the soul of our brother, Shin Dong Jae.
Please forgive him for his sins...
and let him rest in your kingdom with the saints.
In Jesus Christ...
Please allow me...
to give the eulogy.
I want to take responsibility...
as the doctor who operated on him.
The cause of death...
for Mr Shin Dong Jae...
was murder.
This is the medication that he took for five years...
to treat diabetes.
I...
Mr Shin's death...
was caused by...
one bag of pills.
This isn't the place...
I'm sorry.
A bag of pills can't be a lethal dose.
It's basic pharmaceutical knowledge!
It's just a bag of pills.
But when insulin...
meets pseudoephedrine,
a drug found in common cold medicine,
it becomes like a dynamite...
that causes acute cerebral haemorrhage.
Cerebral haemorrhage caused by hypertension...
must have been the best way for the killer...
who wanted it to look like a natural death.
You can do an autopsy...
if you're not...
trying to avoid being blamed...
for the failure of your surgery.
That's not possible.
Because someone...
might do something to his body...
just like they did with Patient Kang Chul Min.
But don't worry.
I took...
a blood sample...
and sent it to Pathology.
(Blood test results)
(Evidence of insulin reactions found...)
(with lethal levels of pseudoephedrine.)
Clearly, Mr Shin Dong Jae was murdered.
And the person who killed Mr Shin...
is right here.
He is here with us.
(Beautiful Mind)
A homicide in Hyunsung Medical Centre.
Do you think that's possible?
You can't do this to me.
I must be being punished, Suk Joo.
Are you sure that you're a good doctor?
You and I are the only ones who believe it was murder.
Are you saying that it's Dr Hyun?
I'm not a police officer. You are.
I'm not sure if I can keep it a secret.
Everyone, please leave.
There will be no more deaths occurring in my OR...
that I cannot come to terms with.