(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
You almost killed the patient...
I saved with the emergency operation!
Pneumonia nearly took her life, all because of you.
- Kim Min Jae.
-  Yes.
You're a senior intern.
-  Yes, Sir.
You're supposed to know everything by now.
My patient contracted pneumonia...
because you didn't put the L-tube in properly.
This is why I don't like lower-tier graduates.
Demonstrate sincere effort if you lack intelligence.
You don't do anything right.
There's a reason why people...
value the right background.
Don't you agree, Dr Lee?
You're right.
They should be earnest at least.
That doesn't exclude the alumni of Hyunsung University.
The area where the stomach was adjoined...
seems to be deformed.
The medical records show...
that this patient had a gastrectomy in the past.
The French L-tube that you ordered...
was inappropriate for use in the first place.
The French L-tube wasn't a good call.
Let's do this.
Prescribe her clindamycin for three weeks.
That way, filing a death certificate...
for aspiration pneumonia won't be necessary.
Do you find this funny?
He's got some nerve for a second-year resident.
Excuse me, Dr Lee.
Excuse me.
Yes?
Aren't you hungry?
I'm starving.
I'm hungry.
There's a new chicken shop by the main gate.
I heard it's delicious.
The portions are a bit too large...
for a woman to eat alone.
I always wanted to pay the place a visit.
I'm starving,
but I don't know anyone here,
so I'm reluctant to go alone.
Curve your palm back for percussions.
Compress the pressure.
Give it a try.
All right.
Roll your hand, like this.
Just like that.
Why are your hands so drained of strength?
Are you really that hungry?
Yes.
That's good.
You'll be able to finish a whole portion.
Go ahead and don't worry about me.
I'll take care of it.
Go ahead.
What?
Did you have enough fried chicken?
Lee Young Oh.
Do you also...
despise me that much?
Why?
Is it because I'm a lower-tier university graduate?
Is it because I'm struggling to pay off my loans?
Is that why you brush me off so easily...
when I sincerely ask for a date?
What are you talking about?
I swallowed my pride and asked you to eat with me.
How is fried chicken...
and dating...
related?
Stop pretending like you don't know...
what I'm talking about.
What are these markings?
Do you...
really enjoy being a neurosurgeon?
The responsibilities are clearly defined.
I need to save the patient in front of me.
No matter what,
vital signs...
should never...
drop.
As long as I keep these rules,
no one will bother me.
Your background doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter what kind of a person I am.
It's the perfect place to hide.
You're telling me to be a good doctor, right?
When it comes to asking me for dates,
you should look at me in the eyes...
so I can read your mind.
Kim Min Jae.
(Beautiful Mind)
(Episode 4)
I will give you five minutes.
Patients will be arriving soon.
There was a murder case at Hyunsung Medical Centre.
The director died, too.
Do you think this makes any sense?
How could this have happened?
Murderers exist in every corner of the world.
Assuming that one doesn't exist here...
is a logical contradiction.
Dr Lee.
He's not incorrect.
So you're saying...
that there's a murderer...
who killed Mr Shin at Hyunsung Medical Centre?
Who is it?
There is a doctor who prescribed a lethal dose...
of pseudoephedrine to Mr Shin, a known diabetic,
in this hospital.
That's after assuming that Dr Lee is correct.
The culprit could've solicited a staff member.
- That's right.
-  Do you really think...
that Dr Lee knows who the killer is?
That's uncertain.
We don't know...
what on earth he's thinking.
I'm planning to corner the suspect...
at the Mortality Conference.
(Mortality Conference: Doctors discuss cause of death)
I will prove to everyone that my operation...
was error-free.
Let's pretend that it never happened. It was a mistake.
I'll make sure your record is clean.
If you're concerned about your honour,
you can gripe about it in a diary entry.
It's useless to profit generation.
You know well that I'm a businessman.
All I count is money.
The JCI evaluation is next week.
Dr Lee,
it's an international accreditation for patient safety.
If this incident is leaked to the public,
we won't be able to qualify.
It will cut off the demand from foreign patients,
the largest source of revenue.
Bingo. This conversation is over.
Pointing out the murderer at the conference...
will not be detrimental to business.
I guarantee it.
We have a murderer loose at the hospital.
It's an unfortunate coincidence.
However, at Hyunsung Medical Centre,
there is a reliable system that sorts out...
unethical doctors.
The Mortality Conference will prove...
that Hyunsung Medical Centre is a safe place.
We strive to meet and exceed JCI's global standard.
Do you know why scandals are scary, Dr Lee?
People only remember the shock.
The solution is never remembered. Why?
It's not interesting enough.
That's the Korean psyche.
Gosh, you must be devastated.
I heard Mr Shin passed away suddenly.
I heard an interesting story.
Maybe it's bad news for Hyunsung Medical Centre.
Gosh. Reporter Kim, let's go grab a cup of tea.
Old sayings are never wrong.
"Those who chase gossip are always hungry."
Mr Chae,
ask if he wants to lose our advertising sponsorship.
Whether it's print or television broadcast,
we'll withdraw everything.
I don't live off Hyunsung Group's sponsorship.
It's more than what I deserve.
We live off the story-starved curiosity...
of potential viewers.
Dr Lee, you'll be held liable for everything.
Let's do it then. Let's meet the global standard.
Let's go with that system of ethics you mentioned.
You have one week...
until the JCI evaluators arrive.
Before the media gets their dirty hands on us,
let's handle it internally...
within Hyunsung Medical Centre.
I'll see you at the Mortality Conference, then.
A child, age seven.
She is a patient suffering from a cerebral aneurysm.
She was admitted as Dr Hyun Suk Joo's patient.
Is she a patient...
under Dr Hyun Suk Joo's care?
She's a family member of Dr Kim from Anaesthesiology.
She received surgery for congenital valve deformity.
She's also suffering from cyanoderma.
Her cerebral thrombosis seems to have evolved...
into an aneurysm as a cyanoderma complication.
What did CS say?
Pardon?
As the patient's guardian, Dr Kim wants surgery.
That's dangerous.
The size isn't ideal.
The location makes things worse.
Her heart will not endure the surgery.
If it ruptures during surgery,
she'll die immediately.
What do you think, Dr Lee?
Dr Lee.
Why are you asking him?
Are we voting now?
Hey, kid.
- Tell her we can't operate.
-  Excuse me?
Is that what I should tell her?
It's a medical opinion given by specialists.
Dr Kim will understand, too.
Don't you agree, Dr Lee?
My goodness.
It seems Dr Lee is mentally overloaded with thoughts...
of who to accuse at the Mortality Conference.
What on earth are you doing?
Dr Lee.
Did you say that you will point out...
the murderer at the Mortality Conference?
Yes, I did.
As of this moment,
Dr Lee and the surgical staff...
present at Mr Shin's surgery...
cannot operate on any surgeries...
at Hyunsung Medical Centre.
Even the surgical staff?
Dr Lee,
do you still hold me responsible...
for the surgery of Mr Shin?
How can anyone save a patient in an emergency...
if the surgeon and the surgical staff...
cannot trust each other?
I don't think it's possible.
Determine who's responsible for Mr Shin's death.
I will not approve...
of you to operate until then.
Do you expect me to give up on the surgery?
You want me...
to sit back and watch my daughter die?
I'm a doctor,
yet you want me to do nothing about it?
Yoon Kyung.
Discuss this with your husband.
We're divorced.
Still, he should come since he's the father.
I'm being punished.
For the past several years...
while waiting for Ji An's new heart,
do you know what I prayed for the most?
I desperately prayed for a donor every day,
hoping that another child's accident would save my own.
Are you doing undercover work?
You're searching for a clue...
that the criminal left, right?
Not at all.
I have more than enough clues.
The criminal knew Mr Shin well enough...
to know that he was diabetic.
He treated him with a lethal dose of pseudoephedrine...
without raising any suspicions.
That person had gained complete trust of Mr Shin.
And the criminal was afraid that Mr Shin...
would find out the truth about the heart...
that went missing.
Are you saying that...
Dr Hyun is guilty?
I never pegged...
Dr Hyun as the criminal.
Not even once.
Aren't you, Officer Gye,
the one who believes that Dr Hyun is the criminal.
Listen carefully.
It's just you and me who believe this to be murder.
Therefore, starting today,
we are on the same team.
Without my help,
you won't be able to find out who killed Mr Shin.
That is why...
you need to help me...
so that I can point out...
the culprit...
at the Mortality Conference.
First, we need to retrace Dr Hyun's steps...
when he went to meet...
Mr Shin that night.
Thank you.
There must be a record of the doctor...
who secured a lethal dose of pseudoephedrine.
"A prescription of pseudoephedrine".
You aren't thinking that Dr Hyun would have...
prescribed it under his name, are you?
Isn't that obvious?
Then, who do you think prescribed it?
I'll only use it as a reference, so don't worry.
If that's the case, I'll tell you.
I'm not the police.
You are.
Officer Gye Jin Sung.
Oh, my. Hello, everyone.
May I join you?
Sure.
You want me to question the hospital staff...
to see if anyone was solicited by Dr Hyun?
Is there anything wrong with that?
Then,
they will take him as the murderer.
Would that be all right?
Pick one.
Either act like an officer...
or a girl who has a crush on him.
You are the staff members...
who participated in Mr Shin's surgery, right?
You were...
in Kang Chul Min's surgery as well with Dr Hyun.
No way.
Are you saying that Dr Hyun is the suspect?
Among the staff members...
My goodness!
You're the one closest to Dr Hyun.
You're his patient.
Shi Hyun, what are you doing?
If the patient you saved accuses you as the criminal,
would you still want to wear that doctor's gown?
That is what you do for your job.
This is how I do mine.
I do this for the safety of the people.
Then, do it right.
I suspect Dr Lee more than anyone else.
It seems that he's putting the responsibility...
on others in order to cover his mistake during surgery.
Did you hear about Dr Hyun?
Gosh, the Mortality Conference better be over soon.
The hospital feels gloomy and restless.
I feel like I have to be as careful as a squirrel.
I know.
People are not fond of doctors these days anyway.
Dr Hyun can't be...
the criminal, right?
No way.
Dr Hyun isn't someone who would do that.
That's like something out of a soap opera.
Do you know why soap operas have high ratings?
It's...
very rare,
but it does happen once in a while.
Why would Dr Hyun do that to Mr Shin?
That's enough.
People are listening.
There's no evidence yet.
Of course there is.
The art of medicine is based on evidence.
- Dr Soh.
-  Yes.
He was the operating surgeon for Kang Chul Min.
The patient's heart went missing.
He must have made a mistake during the surgery.
Mr Shin found that out,
so Dr Hyun...
killed him.
Is there anything I can help you with?
Dr Hyun, what I mean is...
that science starts from forming a hypothesis.
Can I check...
Dr Lee's schedule?
Dr Lee?
I wonder where he is.
All of his surgeries have been cancelled.
You need to find circumstantial and physical evidence.
I will find medical clues...
so that he can't deny the charges.
How?
I'm going to invite him...
to a place where I'm the most comfortable in.
Most comfortable?
This is a CT scan of Dr Kim's daughter.
She has congenital valve deformity.
Due to the failures of past surgeries,
her organs faced necrosis...
from inflammation and recurrence.
She's been waiting for a heart for three years.
There's a condition.
I need you, Dr Hyun,
for CS.
I don't need anyone else.
It's you I need, Dr Hyun.
Okay. Let's begin by meeting with the guardian.
You can operate?
Can you really save my child?
I plan to stop the heart.
Look.
If the heart is stopped,
the blood flowing to the cerebral aneurysm...
will be reduced.
It's the only way to prevent it from rupturing.
It looks highly risky.
The bypass will minimise the damage to the heart,
but if my fingertips mistakenly touches a blood vessel,
if the bypass duration is prolonged...
or if the anesthesiologist makes a mistake...
while monitoring the heart,
she will...
die on the table.
Please promise me.
Please let me...
hold my girl every day after the surgery.
Please.
I don't decide this surgery.
You do, Dr Kim.
You are the guardian.
Sir.
I had my reasons for prohibiting Dr Lee from operating.
He's the only one willing to operate on my child.
That is...
Dr Lee...
openly suspects you and the operating staff...
as the murderer.
Is that all right with you?
If by chance...
that surgery was murder...
as he claims,
he is the first person who will be suspected.
Is that all right with you as well?
Please permit it.
Get up.
I won't...
You need to save my child.
You can't...
You can't do this to me.
Dr Kim.
My daughter is still alive.
She's still alive.
Are you...
telling me to do nothing and watch her die?
There's nothing I can't do.
Please, I'm begging you.
Please.
(Mortality Conference)
(Date: June 30, 2016, Place: Conference Room)
(Surgeons: Lee Young Oh, Hyun Suk Joo)
Must you...
do this surgery?
Aren't you off today?
Don't you have a blind date?
This is so dangerous that no one from NS will operate.
Isn't it strange that Dr Lee...
asked for you specifically?
I have a bad feeling about this.
It feels like a trap.
Ji An...
is my patient.
Do I need another reason?
Whether it's a trap or not, you need an assistant.
Dr Hyun.
Is the bypass ready?
May I begin?
Dr Kim.
Are you ready?
Yes, I'm ready.
Mr Lee, I'm counting on you.
Of course. I'm going to walk Ji An down the aisle...
on her wedding day.
Okay, let's begin.
There is no pulse.
The heart has stopped.
We have 30 minutes.
Let's begin.
(Lee Young Oh, Hyun Suk Joo)
Add another timer...
for four minutes.
Now.
What is it?
I don't see the source of the aneurysm.
If we continue as is,
it may rupture...
before I find it.
- Then...
-  In that four minutes,
I will clip the artery and stop the blood flow...
and start over from the beginning. Hurry.
We have under five minutes...
to use the bypass without damaging the heart.
Any longer and we won't be successful...
(Bypass Weaning: Discontinuing the bypass)
with the bypass weaning.
The heart will stop before we remove the bypass.
The brain will be without oxygen...
if we go beyond four minutes.
It may cause cerebral infarction or convulsions.
I already know that!
Set the timer. I'll finish it in four minutes.
Now!
Suction.
Suction!
One minute on the clock.
You have 30 seconds.
No.
We've clipped it.
Thank you.
Dr Hyun.
Is the heart hanging in there...
without problem?
As of now,
it is doing fine.
Dr Lee, it's our turn now.
Mr Lee. We will stop the bypass now.
Raise the temperature please.
We've removed the cannula.
We'll seal her up now.
Ji An, thanks for hanging in here.
Good job, Dr Kim.
Thank you, Dr Hyun.
Okay, then.
Dr Lee.
Yes?
I thank you from the bottom of my heart...
for not giving up on Ji An.
You shouldn't thank me.
The person who didn't give up and made this possible...
was you, Dr Kim.
Right.
Was Dr Hyun the attending the entire time?
Yes, he was.
Did he do all the treatments?
Without missing a single one?
Dr Kim.
Yes.
It was Dr Hyun Suk Joo.
I see.
Congratulations.
Flustered.
A secret she cannot tell.
Guilt.
She made eye contact to hide that she's lying.
She clasped her hands together.
People do it when they want to believe their own lie.
My suspicion was correct.
You are...
not the one who killed...
Mr Shin.
What do you mean?
I just confirmed that you did not steal...
Kang Chul Min's heart...
in the operating room.
This patient's heart...
had the same rare lesion as Kang Chul Min.
You look like you had no idea.
I needed those four minutes...
to be absolutely sure.
I already know that!
Set the timer. I'll finish it in four minutes. Now!
Because if you were the one who killed Mr Shin...
and had taken Kang Chul Min's heart,
you would've been flustered when you saw...
the same lesion on the heart.
So...
Is that why you needed me for this surgery?
You needed an emergency situation.
You fooled everyone in the OR.
As for the cerebral aneurysm,
I had already clipped it before the four minutes began.
The child was safe.
It's a happy ending.
From the start,
you were suspicious about Kang Chul Min's death.
But you didn't know then and now...
that there was a rare lesion.
During that time,
Mr Shin, whom you respected,
died because of that secret.
Are you...
really a good doctor?
As much as people think?
Dr Lee was very curious about Ji An's treatments.
He asked if Dr Hyun was her attending...
and seemed to want to verify something.
I don't know...
how long I can keep this a secret.
Can we find out...
what caused that lesion?
Do you need it for the Mortality Conference?
I can't do that.
I'm a professional after all.
For Kang Chul Min, it was necessary for surgery,
but beyond that...
Sorry I can't be of help.
You've got me wrong.
I was trying to help you.
Why don't I remember...
any of your articles?
What was that?
Patient Kang Chul Min.
When his heart first disappeared,
I thought it was one doctor's act.
However, Mr Shin died...
and the same lesion...
was discovered on another child.
Do you think this is a coincidence?
That third lesion holds the answer.
You will be...
the star who discovers the cause.
All the media and academia...
will focus on your research article.
If it's something that the medical field...
will be interested in,
I'm all for it.
It's the responsibility of a scholar.
I just need to check its immune response...
and its reaction to different drugs,
so give me a day.
- Ki Ho.
-  Yes, Doctor?
Our research...
is going well, right?
We are ready to file for a patent...
once we get the accreditation from JCI.
The stem cell article is scheduled to publish...
at the same time, too.
Does that mean it's going well?
Companies from China push their way in with money,
but we won't lose the title as the first in Asia.
Don't you worry.
Get back to work.
What do you really want to know,
Dr Hyun?
I looked over...
the test subjects' treatment records.
Is there a problem?
No, Sir.
There is no problem.
That concerns me more.
To me, this regenerative medicine...
is the late Director Shin Dong Jae's life.
There cannot be...
and must not be any problems.
I've put...
the rest of my life on the line.
Hi, Min Jae.
You wanted to meet my dad, right?
Let's do it.
What is it?
You told me to find out who prescribed pseudoephedrine.
Here. Take a look.
Look closely.
See if there's a clue...
that shows Dr Hyun gave him the drug.
So you did all this...
to look for clues to prove that Dr Hyun did it...
just as I asked.
Looking like that, at this hour, this inefficiently.
No.
I wanted to prove that Dr Hyun...
did not do it.
I checked all the security footages...
and Mr Shin's call records.
I checked Kang Chul Min's medical records, too.
I questioned the staff from the surgery,
and there's no way Dr Hyun...
met with the director that night.
Therefore,
whatever leads you found in the OR,
you need to rethink things.
Dr Hyun is not the killer.
He is...
too good of a person to do something like that.
Listen to me.
There's no one like that in the world.
In this world,
there are only two types of people.
Those who have failed to hide their true selves...
and those who haven't failed yet.
If Dr Hyun is all you have to talk about,
you can go now.
I already knew that he wasn't the killer.
What...
What did you just say?
Then why did you tell me...
Dr Hyun has been misunderstood because of you.
Why did you do that?
Why on earth?
I wanted the killer...
to think that he or she was off the hook.
Does that hurt?
You're the one going around hurting everyone.
And that hurts?
You have never...
given your heart to someone, have you?
You've never accepted someone's heart either, right?
Why didn't you defend yourself?
You could have said...
that you didn't kill him.
If I had, all the staff in this hospital...
would have suspected each other.
It would've been a nightmare.
Why are you still here?
I...
Well...
I just...
I'm sorry.
I will tell...
each and every person in this hospital...
that I was wrong about everything.
You can...
hate me for the rest of your life.
I will... I won't hate you or anything like that.
I won't speak ill of you, either.
Who says I'll keep you around?
Have you eaten yet?
I'm hungry.
Let's go eat something.
Hey. What's wrong?
It's okay. Let's go.
Come on.
Let's go.
- Father.
-  Yes.
We're getting married.
We should have told you earlier. I'm sorry.
That's unexpected.
I didn't expect good news at a time like this.
I thought I wouldn't have a chance to tell you...
after the Mortality Conference.
How well do you know my son, Dr Kim?
I could write a PhD thesis about him.
Please don't ask her hard questions.
She must be really nervous right now.
Her future father-in-law is...
a man whom all the fellow doctors trust and admire.
He is moral and dignified.
He's Lee Gun Myung, the head of the centre.
Please continue.
I'll be back soon.
What are you thinking?
It's too risky to live with her.
Is that because...
she's a neuroscientist who wrote...
a great thesis about the relationship...
between brain science and morality?
Are you afraid she might find out about me?
In the past 10 years,
I have been...
an ordinary man to Dr Kim.
- Still...
-  I'll do my best...
to make her happy for the rest of my life.
Then people will consider me normal.
Just as you wish.
Did you make any progress...
with the preparation for the conference?
Yes.
It's getting more and more interesting.
Look forward to it, Father.
Could you at least pretend in public places?
Normal people...
don't describe someone's death...
as something interesting.
Isn't death...
like losing?
It's being defeated.
Doctors lose to diseases.
People lose to ageing.
Oh, and there are...
people like the director...
who are betrayed by someone whom they trusted.
It's just the way of the world...
that the strongest survive.
That's enough.
If death is such a great thing,
you and I should quit being doctors.
Doctors should dedicate their lives to save...
as many lives as possible and for the sanctity of life.
That's what you used to tell me all the time.
Did you change your mind?
However, I will follow what you have taught me.
The person who dared to corrupt my OR...
in order to murder the director, Shin Dong Jae,
is still living with his head held high.
I will point him out during the conference.
At all costs.
I'll see you at the conference.
I would like to move up the Mortality Conference...
to tomorrow.
As if I'd go there...
(The conference has been advanced to 4pm on June 28.)
I'm sorry.
I had only a bit of the lesion sample,
and it's a rare type that I haven't seen before.
I'm sorry, Dr Lee.
She's moving her knees away from me.
It means the negotiation broke through...
or that she changed her mind.
Congratulations, Dr Shim.
You found out the cause of the lesion.
I thought you were smart.
I'm disappointed.
Patient Kang Chul Min died because of the lesion.
He was the first to die.
Mr Shin died while trying to find out the truth.
He was the second to die.
All the people who knew the truth have died.
The third person...
who knows the truth...
is you, Dr Shim Eun Ha.
Do you know...
what I'm trying to say?
Reveal everything you found out to everyone...
at the Mortality Conference.
That's the only way to secure your safety.
I need to confirm something with you.
I heard that the Mortality Conference will be held...
today.
The clues, witness, evidence and suspect.
Hand over everything you know.
From now on, you need to help me.
Help me arrest the killer...
and investigate this as a violent crime case.
I don't...
want to be fooled by someone like you any more.
One more thing.
It's kind of a ring.
It's...
It's the lid of a soju bottle.
Did you happen to see it?
Wasn't it in your car?
You're smart. Try to remember.
You saw it, didn't you?
Did you see it?
No, I didn't.
(Professor Shim Eun Ha, Pathology Laboratory)
(Out of office)
I thought it would be appropriate...
to call you...
before I hand this over...
to Dr Lee Young Oh.
If the 200 million-dollar...
regenerative medicine project...
goes down to drain because of my research,
it would...
break my heart as well.
(Dr Shim Eun Ha)
Yes, Dr Shim.
Dr Shim.
Where are you now? Dr Shim...
- What happened?
-  I'm on my way.
Hurry up.
Watch her head.
She fell off the rooftop of this building.
Book an OR. Hurry.
-  Yes, Doctor.
- Check her vitals.
Prepare an OR right now.
Officer Gye Jin Sung?
- Gelfoam, please.
-  Okay.
With this operation,
I will save Dr Shim.
There will be no more deaths occurring in my OR...
that I cannot come to terms with.
Everyone, please get out...
of my OR.
Are you saying that the patients who died...
Do you think the killer is among us?
She's suffering from traumatic subdural haemorrhage.
36-year-old female.
Patient Shim Eun Ha.
I'm the lead surgeon, Lee Young Oh.
I'll begin the surgery now.
Are you suggesting I arrest Dr Lee?
An arrest without a warrant will be possible.
Irrigation.
Suction. Suction!
Forceps.
Retractor.
Retractor!
Green retractor.
Gelfoam.
Can't you keep up with me?
Keep up with me.
Gelfoam.
I'll give you a chance to redeem your mistake.
The time the patient can give us...
is exactly four minutes.
Mr Lee Young Oh.
You have the right to an attorney.
You have the right to remain silent.
Get out of my way.
My patient is waiting for me on the table.
I'm the lead surgeon...
of this surgery.
You are under arrest for the murders at Hyunsung.
(Beautiful Mind)
There's a serial killer at Hyunsung Medical Centre.
He's a doctor. He's smart and good-looking.
Why would he do such a thing?
Who is that person you're trying so hard to protect?
Someone else did it.
Why can't I be better than this?
The patient is in cardiac arrest.
Dr Shim.
Call Dr Lee. He's the lead surgeon.
We're running out of time. She'll die!
What happened? Is she alive?