Me! I'll go.
I volunteered wholeheartedly.
I'll end up going to the countryside hospital anyway.
I'll think of it like a two-year military service.
I mean, I can finish my training...
and maybe even become a fellow...
Two years is too long for me.
It won't be easy driving long distance...
every weekend while studying.
You're saying you'll come visit me, right?
You'll come every weekend, right?
I'll miss you, Kim Min Jae.
I was worried that you'd want to break up.
Me too.
What?
This is saying,
"I love you."
Did you just...
take my pulse?
I won't let go of this hand.
Ever.
I'll be back soon.
(Episode 6)
Yes, this is Kim Min Jae.
Oh my goodness.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
- Are you okay? - Yes, Professor.
- My goodness. - Yes, Sir.
I'll find the documents and bring them up.
Yes.
Yes, Sir.
(Moving Hearts with True Medicine)
(Department of Neurosurgery, Lee Young Oh, Age 8)
Due to damage to the frontal lobe...
and amygdaloid nucleus which control emotions,
he cannot sense what others feel...
or empathise.
Look me in the eye when you ask me out on a date,
so that I can read your mind.
Among people who receive prolonged training,
there are some who live...
among normal people and hide their condition...
by imitating...
people's emotions.
This is saying,
"I love you."
Dr Lee, I'll go up this weekend.
May I ask you something?
Why are you dating me, Young Oh?
I feel the same way, too.
I love you.
(Beautiful Mind)
Dr Lee Young Oh...
is a dangerous person who should no longer be here.
He is unable to feel emotions or empathise.
Thus, he can't have any real relationships...
or feel guilt, which every human being should feel.
He has antisocial disorder.
He is a psychopath.
This is the opinion...
of his doctor who has been monitoring him...
closely and for a long time.
Why didn't you say...
you were Kang Chul Min's doctor?
Did you know about his missing heart?
That strange lesion was because of our research.
An adverse side effect.
That is why the director...
ran into the hospital to see you and collapsed.
Can we meet right now?
Are you really the one...
who did that to the director?
Catch your breath first, Mr Shin.
What happened during our research?
Suk Joo. The director...
died because of that.
Nothing will change by digging into the past.
His anxiety got him ill.
I'm worried that will happen to you, too.
Then what will happen to our research?
Wasn't our research...
intended to save lives?
It's 200 million dollars.
It's a 200-million-dollar market.
You want me to keep quiet...
just for money?
No.
I'm saying...
that money will silence you,
whatever it takes.
Kang Chul Min, Director Shin Dong Jae...
and Dr Shim Eun Ha.
Who do you think will be next?
Now, I understand.
You cannot feel or empathise with others' pain.
Which means,
you could never have a conscience like a doctor should.
Is that why you did it?
Dr Shim Eun Ha's surgery ended well.
But once you administered the drug,
her heart stopped.
You didn't think we didn't know, did you?
No!
What are you trying to protect...
by doing something like this?
Perhaps she's trying to protect Hyunsung...
which puts the patients' safety first.
Lee Young Oh.
You are under arrest for the murders at Hyunsung.
You have the right to remain silent.
Everything you say may be held against you.
You have the right to an attorney.
Let's go.
Was he really the killer?
I can't believe it.
- I guess so. - Oh my gosh.
Do you really think Dr Lee did that to Dr Shim?
I know he was awkward, but that's extreme.
You may see only what you're familiar with.
But people who dealt with him know.
Look. How many strange things happened...
after Lee Young Oh showed up?
We should've known then.
He was so talented.
No one could've suspected.
This is what still baffles me.
He's the son of the head of the centre.
What was he thinking, bringing him here? What?
Who can foresee what their child will do?
The nurses said...
that Dr Kim Min Jae and Dr Lee Young Oh were engaged.
What? Kim Min Jae?
She almost became Dr Lee's daughter-in-law?
Why? Did you do something wrong?
No. I didn't do anything.
What was he thinking?
This is a great research article, Dr Kim Min Jae.
It's exactly what Hyunsung needs.
Hyunsung needs a sacrificial lamb,
and...
it might as well be a repulsive evil monster.
Because that will relieve us of our guilt.
Congratulations on becoming a professor, Professor Kim.
Thank you, Sir.
Was this why you got close to my son?
No.
At first, I couldn't tell at all...
since he was so well-trained.
Do you really think Young Oh killed those people?
I simply gave my opinion as a specialist...
for the patient's safety.
What do you think?
You know...
Dr Lee the best,
since you have a special father and son relationship.
Mr Lee Young Oh.
I know people like you very well.
You're smart, you're a good speaker...
and you adapt well to any circumstance.
But don't try to do anything.
It's just a waste of time.
I...
don't trust you.
I trust this.
Okay?
Let's begin.
State your name and occupation.
Lee Young Oh.
Neurosurgery specialist at Hyunsung Medical Centre.
You were in Shim Eun Ha's hospital room...
around 3pm on July 4, is that correct?
That is correct.
Why were you there?
I was her attending physician.
Did you use your position as her attending...
to murder Shim Eun Ha?
The surveillance video from the hallway...
shows the time you left her room...
coincides with when her heart stopped.
What happened in that room?
Mr Lee Young Oh.
Did you murder Shim Eun Ha?
Say it.
Suk Joo.
What is it?
We're the only ones in here.
I won't listen to excuses. Don't try to run.
What's wrong? You're scaring me.
Is Ji An...
involved with our research?
Why didn't you tell me?
Why didn't you say she was involved with our research?
I had to do something.
What couldn't I do?
They promised to put her on top of the donor list.
Were Kang Chul Min...
and the director...
part of what you had to do?
Tell me.
Tell me. Were they?
Are you insane?
Stop acting so high and mighty.
You act all good and just, but you can't save my child.
You can't make her better.
How dare you judge me?
What right do you have?
It wasn't me.
I didn't do anything.
I only...
I only lived as Ji An's mum.
It wasn't me.
Doctor.
Have you heard? It's huge.
Did the CS OP patient's scan results come out yet?
You don't know, do you?
The hospital is flipped upside down.
What's more important than a patient's scan results?
An allergy will delay surgery by a week.
It's an aortic dissection patient. It's urgent.
What if something goes wrong?
Dr Lee Young Oh was the killer.
He was just arrested for the murders of...
Kang Chul Min, Mr Shin and Dr Shim Eun Ha.
He was?
I didn't...
I didn't do anything wrong.
Dr Kim.
Doctor.
Yes.
I killed them.
Mr Lee Young Oh.
Dr Shim Eun Ha.
Director Shin Dong Jae.
And Kang Chul Min, too.
I killed...
all of them.
With Kang Chul Min...
and Director Shin Dong Jae,
it was in the OR.
And...
with Dr Shim Eun Ha,
it was in her hospital room.
Without anyone knowing...
or seeing.
It was perfect.
I dreamed of the perfect murder.
Yes.
That's it.
You call yourself a doctor?
How could you?
It's because monsters like you...
are wealthy and powerful,
that this world is a mess!
Detective.
Please stop.
It may affect the results.
Is it true?
Mr Lee Young Oh.
Did you really kill...
No.
I didn't kill them.
None of them.
Lee Young Oh.
Mr Lee Young Oh.
I am a murderer.
No, I'm not a murderer.
I am...
a doctor who highly values life.
No. I don't value life at all.
I'm not even a doctor.
I am a man.
Are you a woman?
I am a human.
I am not a human.
Am I alive?
- No, I am dead. - Stop it.
- Let me ask again. - I...
love you.
You love me as well, right?
We...
made love...
many times.
In the ways that you wanted.
Stop it right now!
I warned you not to pull any tricks.
I guess being nice to you doesn't work.
Isn't this what you wanted...
to see from me?
Fine.
Then let's start over.
What? You punk!
Is that possible?
Because you're not a monster like I am,
you people can feel...
how much...
pain another person is suffering.
Let's try it.
Why you...
Now,
tell me.
Does it hurt?
Can you...
feel my pain?
I just don't lie like that, that's all.
I did not kill anyone.
You freak.
We can't feel exactly what it is,
but we can guess.
They don't want it,
and it doesn't help much,
but you have to do something.
Did that answer your question?
You should return to the OR.
Lee Young Oh is innocent.
Didn't you agree to remain a traffic cop?
Please include these as evidence.
They were the murder weapon.
Murder weapon?
It's potassium.
It's easy for an anaesthesiologist to obtain,
and it doesn't appear in an autopsy.
She administered it to stop the heart both times.
- Who did? - Anaesthesiologist Dr Kim Yoon Kyung.
Are you sure? Where is the suspect?
She had been using drugs because of her guilt...
and injected herself with the potassium by mistake.
Dr Kim Yoon Kyung...
confessed.
I need to stop becoming evil.
I'm going to turn myself in.
Please look after Ji An.
How could a doctor be so weak-hearted?
Didn't you say Dr Kim was a mum?
Her child is in our hospital.
How is the child supposed to live? How irresponsible.
Wow. What a story.
Drug addict anaesthesiologist.
Uncaring mum. What do you think?
Or a psychopath surgeon with a scalpel...
is after your heart.
Is that better?
You should write real stories now.
How long will you make up stories just for the clicks?
He made a position for you at Hyunsung Times.
You're part of the Hyunsung family, so I'll tell you.
Nothing happened...
at Hyunsung Medical Centre.
(Kim Soo In, Hyunsung Times)
I'm back.
The chairman...
proposed your dismissal...
to the ethics council.
Just to make myself clear,
it was a false accusation.
For all these years,
I was proud that I did all I could do for you.
I don't know...
what I did wrong.
(Hyunsung Medical Centre, Accredited by JCI)
Dr Lee.
You've got skills.
You have a knack for surprising people.
It's strange.
All I wanted from you...
was very simple and easy.
I just wanted to return to the quiet...
operating room.
You need to...
withdraw my dismissal request.
You have a knack for asking a favour like a threat.
You must know better than anyone...
that I was innocent from the start.
I can't put a scalpel into a psychopath surgeon's hand.
That goes...
against my conscience.
Do you fear me that much?
Are you afraid I'll find out the secret...
that you and Chae Soon Ho are desperately...
trying to hide,
one by one like this?
Not at all.
A psychopath fired for being suspected of murder.
Would this world... No.
Would a single person listen to a word you say?
Think about it. Think.
Is that why you needed Dr Kim Min Jae?
It was Dr Kim...
who came to me.
(Antisocial Personality Disorder)
Kim Min Jae.
Now,
it's my turn.
Let go of me.
Let's go.
I've been waiting for you.
How long has it been?
Why didn't you tell me?
That's...
what I wanted to ask you for the past few years.
It was you...
who used me first.
You needed me to look like other people.
It's the same for me.
That's not true.
You...
never lied to me.
Not once.
You...
loved me.
Isn't that true?
Raised eyebrows.
Raised eyebrows. Wrinkled nose.
Stepping backwards.
Those indicate contempt and fear.
You're trying to read my body signals.
Love?
What kind of gestures do people make to express love?
Joy.
Sadness.
Fear.
Anger.
Which one is similar to love?
It's all of them...
and none at the same time.
That's what love is like.
You wouldn't be able to read that signal...
because you didn't learn it.
You probably...
never will.
So it was easy to deceive you, Young Oh.
You're okay, right?
I know...
things like this...
don't hurt your feelings.
I tried.
I did my best.
For you,
I did everything I could do.
You did...
your best...
to pretend.
If you're late for school again...
Being a teenager doesn't give you privilege!
You shouldn't act like that!
What now?
Are you going to transfer...
to the division for women and adolescence this time?
I'll work in the Traffic Division forever.
It's my job to help a victim of a car accident.
What a smooth talker.
The taxes I pay is used...
for his tuition and payment for school lunches.
I'll make sure he graduates. I will.
Hello. Can I have a bowl of noodles please?
Sure.
- I'll have a bottle of this. - Okay.
(One More Bottle)
Yes, Dr Hyun.
Officer Gye.
Don't you know your surgery is tomorrow?
You shouldn't be eating anything.
Mr Shin once said...
a person who can drink soju alone has nothing to fear.
Because he or she knows...
the secret of life.
That life is bitter...
and that everyone is alone in this world.
I got fooled.
I thought it was a secret he didn't tell anyone else.
Even up above,
he's probably making up millions of excuses to drink.
I used to think...
that the police investigate a murder...
to catch the killer.
What do you think now?
Now, I think it's for those who are left behind.
Because they need to know how the victims lived...
and what they were like.
It's so that they can treasure those memories.
What are you staring at?
What are you doing?
I was thinking, I wish I could fill this up for him.
You could help him out.
I'll see you later.
Come here.
Come on.
Isn't this pretty?
What do you mean?
It's 130cc.
It's 20cc more than earlier.
It's 130cc now.
This patient will live.
He's my first patient.
I'll get going now.
You're a first-year resident in Cardio, right?
I've seen you in the OR.
Let's shake hands since we just met.
It's...
Okay. I just...
I'm Kim Yoon Kyung from Anaesthesiology.
You're so handsome.
Please...
look after Ji An.
So...
when will the regenerative medicine...
be put to practical use?
It should be done before the end of summer...
so I get votes at the presidential election next year.
Stem cells that create miracles.
The country with the best medical technology.
A country with a strong economy.
Who would make money...
by using the stem cell technology?
You should make money...
by investing in biotechnology stocks.
Treatment isn't what matters.
What's important is the fact...
that research is being conducted.
Don't you agree, Mr Lee?
Yes, but in order to proceed,
we can't leave the director's seat vacant any longer.
That's right.
Hence, we'll make an internal announcement...
I'll have someone submit my application.
- What? - Are you saying...
that you'll apply for the position, Mr Lee?
Do I seem incompetent for the role?
No, not at all.
People are...
truly mysterious.
I'm quite entertained.
I'll be returning to my work now.
You have a strong competitor now, Mr Chae.
It seems so.
You could have notified me earlier.
I wasn't aware of your ambition.
Since you were close to Mr Shin,
I didn't think you'd be interested in his position.
Shin Dong Jae.
I'm doing this for Director Shin Dong Jae.
I cannot allow the Regenerative Medical Centre...
to be dragged into the political world...
to become a stock market advertisement or voting bait.
How will I be able to face him?
I'm impressed by your deep friendship.
There must be someone to keep the chairman in check.
That is the duty of the director's office.
With all due respect,
you must be aware of the hospital's state of affairs.
Considering what happened to your son, Dr Lee Young Oh,
do you think you'll be okay?
Come on. Dr Lee Young Oh is coming this way.
It's Dr Lee Young Oh.
There he is.
Isn't he unbelievable?
He's probably clueless...
about how others view him right now, right?
He must be aware. He's very intelligent.
How can he conduct himself so normally?
It's only possible because he lacks empathy.
Sir, can you hear me?
Tell me the details.
Male, 44 years old.
He fell down the stairs on his way home with his wife.
My wife...
Sir, do you know where you are? You're at the hospital.
Where is my wife?
My wife...
Are there any other areas of discomfort, Sir?
Good. I'll call an orthopedist for you.
My goodness!
His physical state is abnormal.
He's been hospitalised for a long time...
with multiple surgery scars.
He also has biopsy markings.
It's very likely that he's suffering from glioblastoma.
Please take him in for a CT scan.
Sir, are you suffering from any medical conditions?
Please call my wife. My wife...
He said he was fine earlier.
You're right. He has glioblastoma.
Are you okay?
It'll be over soon.
You were frightened, right?
He is suffering from glioblastoma.
Dr Yang, please take him in for a CT scan.
Ma'am, excuse me.
Considering the position of the surgical wound,
if the glioblastoma spreads to the medulla,
even a minor haemorrhage...
can be fatal.
Yes, Doctor. I'll be back.
Doctor.
I have something to tell you.
Okay.
We're going home.
You don't need to treat my husband.
If he leaves now, he could die.
This is his will.
And this is his advance directive.
(Advance directive: Written statement...)
(of a person's wishes regarding medical treatment)
He's decided not to take any treatments...
to prolong his life.
He also entrusted the decision on treatments to me.
I've made my decision.
I don't want him to receive any more treatments.
Does the patient agree with you?
Please do...
as my wife says.
You did well.
I'm proud of you.
Are you satisfied?
Sir, listen to me carefully.
If you leave without treatment, you could die.
Did you hear that clearly?
I said, you could die.
He shows overwhelming signs of fear and stress.
He needs someone to trust.
It's what he wants.
He's suppressing his emotions and hiding what he feels.
Don't worry.
I'll save your life no matter what.
Doctor.
He's in a lucid interval.
(Lucid interval: Acute loss of consciousness)
The minor bleeding caused by the trauma...
reached the tumour in the temporal lobe.
We can stop the bleeding with an EVD. Dr Yang.
Yes, Doctor.
Dr Lee, please.
Please. I want this to stop.
Doctor, he's in cardiac arrest.
Cardiac arrest?
I'll make the decision.
I really need...
to save his life!
- No. Please don't do that. - Get her out of here!
- Doctor, please. Don't do that! - Ma'am, please.
Please.
Epinephrine!
Ambu bag.
Intubation.
- Dr Yang. - Yes, Sir.
EVD!
He's pulse is back to normal.
I saved him. I treated his cardiac arrest.
I saved him.
His heart rate and blood pressure...
are all normal.
The patient...
I mean,
your husband is alive.
Dr Lee.
I heard the glioblastoma patient...
and his family weren't seeking prolonged care.
The patient...
could not communicate effectively...
due to his lengthy battle with the illness.
However, it was clear...
that he wanted to live.
How can you be so sure?
The patient clearly mentioned before...
I ascertained the possibility of his survival.
As a doctor, I did my best...
to save him.
Dr Lee from Neurosurgery, there is an emergency.
What on earth are you doing right now?
Why are you doing this?
You made me do it...
myself!
I told you so many times.
I begged you so many times.
That is why...
Should I go...
to the police station now?
This is...
unbelievable.
This is preposterous!
Dr Lee.
As of this moment,
you are dismissed from your post...
at Hyunsung Medical Centre.
What...
did I do wrong?
I...
only saved a patient's life.
Are patients worth putting on life support...
simply because they breathe?
Dr Lee, thanks to you,
the family member of the patient...
was compelled to commit the murder of a loved one.
What's worse is...
that you still don't understand what's wrong.
Do your superior skills give you authority?
Do you now understand...
why I was always against a monster like you...
becoming a doctor?
The ethics council at Hyunsung Medical Centre...
authorises your dismissal.
Dr Lee.
Dr Lee, please.
I want this to stop.
You made me do it...
myself.
Love?
What kind of gestures do people make to express love?
You wouldn't be able to read that signal...
because you didn't learn it.
Do you understand why I was always against...
a monster like you becoming a doctor?
- My goodness. - What's his problem?
What's wrong with you?
Stop it!
- My goodness. - Stop it.
- What's the matter? - Call the police.
What did I do wrong...
as a doctor?
Are you blind?
Are you all right?
Don't worry. Nothing happened.
Let's go.
Help me.
Please.
(Beautiful Mind)
Are you saying that our research was flawed?
You want me to convince...
the Food and Drug Administration to approve...
stem cell treatment options ahead of schedule?
You won't be able to prove it on your own.
You lack both witnesses and evidence.
You won't be seeing Dr Lee any more.
His absolute self-belief in being a perfect person...
has been shattered in front of his patient.
I'm planning to return to Hyunsung Medical Centre.
I will be needed.