Say hi to Daddy.
Hi.
How precious.
That's a family.
A man and woman meet and have a baby.
They become parents and raise the child.
You must...
live like that someday,
so that the world will think you're normal.
Do you understand?
Young Oh.
Father.
You always say...
if I do as you say,
I can live like other people.
Of course.
Then,
if I try much harder,
can I?
Can I someday...
be able to feel?
Not pretend,
but really feel things...
like normal people.
It's late. Let's go.
(Beautiful Mind)
Hyunsung Group's successorship is making headlines.
Chairman Kang Il Do held a press conference...
and stated that they plan to shuffle businesses...
to focus on their next growth engine company...
through the transfer of shares of stock.
Once the reorganisation is completed this month,
Chairman Kang Il Do will step down...
into a supporting role for his successor.
Call Kim Myung Soo and tell him I want to see him...
right now.
Within the month?
Is that possible?
It has to be.
That is the very reason why I need you.
So, you want me to convince the FDA to approve...
the stem cell treatment sooner than scheduled?
Stage three trials went smoothly.
There won't be any problems.
The problem is, we don't have much time...
My point exactly.
What's the sudden rush? I need to know, so...
Mr Kim.
You are such a curious person.
The health of the citizens is on the line.
A small mistake can kill my chances for presidency.
Health.
The health of the citizens.
Health. That's nice.
Hyunsung Bio's DNA treatment brings in 1.5 billion.
Hyunsung Medical's digital health devices.
A 173-billion-dollar market.
Hyunsung Tech.
Hyunsung Electronics.
And Hyunsung Insurance,
which is in a market...
that you can't even calculate its worth.
And Hyunsung's growth engine...
that my old man can't live without,
which will make...
the troublemaker son the successor of Hyunsung Group.
That's what health means...
to me.
Now, do you understand...
why I'm rushing?
Will a week suffice?
You're working so hard for the citizens' health.
We can't hold you back because of formalities.
You should go.
A week isn't that long.
Get the car. Let's head to the FDA.
Don't worry too much. It'll go smoothly.
It has to. Dr Lee Young Oh is gone.
There are no more obstacles to our research.
Are you saying something's wrong with our research?
Suk Joo.
Strange lesions different from cardiac muscular tissue.
A whole new immune system.
Strange tumours that develop out of nowhere.
Ki Ho.
What would you conclude?
Strange lesions and tumours.
That's right. Side effects of stem cell treatment.
That's... That's ridiculous.
- Ki Ho.
-  I...
I don't know what you're talking about.
No.
You do know.
You fear...
exactly what I fear.
Right?
(Petition for Divorce)
I slept on a chair in this lab more than at home...
for the past three years that I've been married.
What woman would stay with me?
Suk Joo,
you think our research is wrong, right?
You know,
I never even imagined that.
Because it would be so unfair to me.
Hello.
It's hard dealing with kids, isn't it?
That's how kids are.
They don't listen.
We have no choice but to tell them until they listen.
Like this.
Listen carefully.
Our research was perfect through second stage trials.
We've completed stage three trials as well.
We've accomplished something that will shock the world.
I'm sure the world will be shocked plenty...
just based on...
what you've done thus far.
Dr Hyun Suk Joo.
Whatever you think, whatever suspicion you may have,
it's fine.
However,
can you prove it on your own?
You lack both witnesses and evidence.
This patient's heart...
had the same rare lesion as Kang Chul Min.
You look like you had no idea.
Are you really a good doctor?
I heard Dr Shim is in a coma.
You seem very interested in her now.
Have you become more interested in the lesions on...
Kang Chul Min and Dr Kim's daughter's hearts?
This is what they mean...
when they say, same pose, different look.
Why are you trying to hard?
Your greatest rival is gone.
Think about it.
What hospital would take Dr Lee Young Oh?
That worries me more.
Even Assemblymen...
become TV personalities if they lose elections.
People want characters with a story.
Lee Young Oh is definitely a character.
- Are you all right?
-  Dr Lee's contact information?
Yes, please. I need to see him.
His address or any other contact information is fine.
There's no point.
Dr Lee Young Oh will never return...
to Hyunsung or any other hospital.
What do you mean?
He can't treat patients any more.
His faith that he is perfect shattered...
in front of his patient.
I'm telling you so you don't waste your time.
They must have dated for a long time, right?
She's cruel. So cruel.
Dr Kim.
You know, don't you?
Where is Dr Lee Young Oh?
I need to see him.
For the Dr Lee Young Oh I know,
this hospital...
was the best place for him to hide.
I'm sorry I couldn't help.
(Assistant Professor, Kim Min Jae)
A doctor?
He is a doctor.
At Hyunsung Medical Centre, too.
Why is he here?
It's hot.
A grown man came to a woman's home.
Somewhere this far, too.
It's obvious.
You did it. Good job.
You were always at the hospital since you were young.
You made it. I can't believe you're dating a doctor.
I am not. How many times must I tell you?
Then why did you bring him here? People will talk.
I see. You want people to talk, so he can't run away.
Then just mess around and do the deed.
Messing around is your speciality.
Mum always was called in by the principle.
I bet Mum went to school more often than you.
- You punk.
-  Hey.
Not that kind of messing around.
I should've known better. What did I expect from you?
You've never kissed a guy, have you?
Have you ever held a guy's hand?
What? You punk.
See? Look at that.
You must be really unattractive...
since you're still single.
You should repent.
How can you eat? Or sleep?
Get your act together.
You'll get dumped without even holding hands.
Who was that? Your 10-year crush.
You never even told him how you felt...
Mum, that's not it.
- It is true.
-  Hey.
-  I told you, it is not.
- You liked him.
-  I've done everything.
- You never told him.
-  I did all that I could.
- Fine. Fine.
-  You little!
Goodness.
Oh, no.
I'm so sorry. Oh, no.
Hold on.
Of all those things you say you've done,
spraying someone with water wasn't one of them.
And did you put the blanket on me?
I don't know if you're trying to kill me or heal me.
That's not it.
Mum. That's... That's not it.
Gosh.
I gave you a huge hint this time.
It's time you stopped being single.
Come on.
Brat.
Mum.
Don't you look down on me.
I may live in the countryside and be old-fashioned,
but I'm not unreasonable.
I'm with the times.
Mum, the thing is...
When young people like each other,
they can do that.
It's not shameful.
You shouldn't worry about people talking.
Wait.
Mum, what... What are you talking about?
What's the problem? You can just get married. Right?
As long as you get married.
Mum, it's not like that.
- Not like what?
-  What are you saying?
What do you mean?
Young Oh!
You're a doctor, right?
What's wrong with you?
Take a look at our neighbour.
Oh, my. Why are you alone? Where's your mother?
Don't even mention that evil old woman.
I told you.
She always picked on her, saying she killed her son,
and now she's getting revenge.
You brat. She'll throw a fit if she finds out.
Why did you bring her here?
Should I have left her to die?
She left her in the middle of the street this time.
Goodness. That old woman.
Maybe the doctor from Seoul could take a look.
I'm sure a big hospital is different.
Can you?
Is she...
very ill?
Mum, let's take her to a hospital later...
You see,
maybe living with a tough mother-in-law was unbearable,
or maybe it was hard living without her husband,
but she suddenly stopped talking...
and her arms and legs gave out...
and she's been like this for a year now.
Do you think you're superior than the other doctors?
Do you now understand...
why I was always against a monster like you...
becoming a doctor?
Later. I'll explain later.
What?
Do you think Jin Sung loaned him money?
Maybe he cons women into giving him money.
Who was it?
Who ran off with my belonging?
He didn't run off.
He felt bad for Gye Sook sitting alone in the street...
so he brought her here.
Stop it.
It's not like it has any value.
My gosh.
Are you waiting for your husband? You brat.
Don't you lay a hand on her.
I'll call the police on you.
What?
You young little runt.
Be good to her.
She's sick.
Stop it.
Why do you care what I do with my belongings,
whether I boil it or beat it?
You'll be punished.
- Stop it.
-  She's like that because of you.
-  What?
Oh my gosh.
- Wow.
-  Goodness.
That old fart belongs in the hospital, not Gye Sook.
It's tough enough nursing a parent with an illness.
It can't be easy taking care of...
your daughter-in-law whom you're not even related to.
I'm sure every day is torture.
Goodness.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to put you on the spot.
My brother...
must have really wanted to help.
That's how everyone here lives.
Whether or not you're family, you're not strangers.
I think his desire to help her blinded him...
regarding how awkward it would be for you.
So?
Is that why you brought me here?
Is that why you brought me...
to this tiny Oceanside town...
where everyone helps and loves each other...
as if they were all family?
Did you hope my rotten heart would heal?
I wanted to let you rest somewhere...
where people didn't look at you differently.
I only thought about helping, just like my brother.
You didn't want to help, but rather, confirm.
"I hurt less than you."
"I'm happier than you."
"I have the power to help you."
"Thus, I am superior to you."
With your nose in the air.
People always want confirmation and comfort...
when others are in pain.
Love, friendship, pity.
Those are nothing more than a cheap relay of signals...
that people use as they need it...
by calling it a different name.
That's how people are.
Normal people who take pride in feeling emotions.
You're this angry because of yourself, right?
You're angry at yourself...
for being afraid and running away from a patient.
Because you're afraid you'll keep running.
This is how people are.
That is why people can never help others.
The other person's weakness becomes...
a sweet sore spot that you can attack...
or a disgusting burden...
that you want to throw out if no one were looking.
Take back your request for help.
She made her choice...
regardless of whether someone sees her or not.
Do you want to make a bet?
What are you trying to pull?
Why did you go so far?
Did you want to risk your life?
What are you trying to show me?
I said let's make a bet.
I wanted to show you...
that in the world I know,
Granny isn't such a bad person...
that she'd kill her sick daughter-in-law.
Why don't you...
treat her if you aren't afraid of treating patients?
If she starts to talk, we'll know then...
whether you're right, or I'm right.
- Congratulations.
-  Congratulations.
- Applause.
-  Applause.
Applause.
My daughter. You've been so brave.
Don't cry. This is a good day.
Young Joon is starting a new, healthy life.
Please take good care of her.
Her temperature, BP and allergic reaction...
all look good.
We can operate as planned.
- Where's the extraction team?
-  They're en route.
They're on the train.
Isn't there a way?
We need to get there in 30 minutes.
I don't know. There must be an accident.
I'm losing my mind.
Hey look up the fastest route.
Do you think others haven't searched?
There's no special fast route just for us.
- Even Alpha Go can't find it.
-  Dr Yang.
If we don't arrive in 30 minutes, the heart is useless.
Then the patient waiting in the OR...
- Die already.
-  Dr Yang!
Why...
did you sign up for the extraction team?
Helicopter.
- What?
-  You see that in dramas.
The extraction team rides helicopters...
and land on hospital rooftops. It's so cool.
I didn't know we'd take the train to Daejeon.
Why do you think I came with you today?
Because you're off today?
Because you get paid overtime, which you love?
In case...
you kill a person.
In case you stick your neurosurgeon nose in the air...
and declare someone brain dead without hesitation.
Or in case you delay declaring someone brain dead...
and patients who needed organ transplants die.
That is why I came with you, to try to teach you.
Don't be a quack. Be a real doctor, punk.
Hi, Dr Lee Shi Hyun. We're stuck in traffic.
There must have been an accident.
We're stuck.
You must be stressed out.
I heard it's your first transplant surgery.
- Hey. What are you doing?
-  What?
- What are you doing?
-  I know a shortcut.
Fire!
Excuse me.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
He is such a nag.
All he had to say was "Lee Shi Hyun".
The heart that I'm receiving...
Was it from a woman or a man?
It's against policy to tell you.
Don't worry about it.
What if my heart starts to pound one day...
when I see a woman on the street?
And it turns out you have her dead lover's heart?
You must have learned about love from soap operas...
while you were in the hospital.
Tell me if your heart races when you see a pretty girl.
That's an irregular heartbeat. You'll need medicine.
You must have learned about love in books.
Careful.
So, what do you want to do first after surgery?
Something you couldn't do before. Date?
I definitely want a boyfriend.
I want to ride a roller coaster with him.
I want to scream with my boyfriend and ride it...
100 times from dusk till dawn.
And I want to go clubbing without telling him.
I seem so pathetic,
don't I?
To be honest, I didn't plan anything.
For years, I've had only one dream.
That dream is coming true today.
I don't need a boyfriend.
I don't need roller coasters or clubs.
I don't need to wait for a transplant any more.
I won't hold my breath every time the phone rings.
On the waiting list, I went from 173 to 1...
in four years.
Do you know something?
In our OR, transplants aren't even considered surgery.
Because it's so simple.
Connect the blood vessels, and you're done.
It won't be pretty though.
But I will make it strong,
so that it won't shake after 100 roller coaster rides.
I'll see you later.
What are you doing?
What?
I feel like my heart will explode because of you.
I ran...
from the intersection to the hospital...
with the heart for your patient.
You should...
buy me a meal or a drink.
Why should I?
Wait. I deserve a reward.
I feel like I'm going to pass out,
it's hard to breathe and my lips are dry.
- And I...
-  So what?
My patient felt that way for the past four years.
Do you really want to take credit? Shame on you.
That's not...
Dr Yang.
Yes?
Have you seen Dr Hyun Suk Joo?
He promised to assist with the surgery.
I haven't seen him.
Is there any way...
to contact Dr Lee Young Oh?
What is it about?
Did he do anything wrong to you?
Dr Lee is...
the first person who made me feel ashamed.
I guess something happened between you two.
Is it related to hospital affairs?
Do tell.
What happened?
The person who can answer that question is...
Dr Lee, not me.
That's why I need to see him.
I'm looking for my son just like you.
Are you going to blame me for being a bad parent?
- Then...
-  I'll tell him to call you when he's back.
Because I really need to know...
why you're looking for Dr Lee.
I'll count on you.
Don't you regret?
That you threw out your family,
Dr Lee Young Oh...
to be faithful to your principles.
You must be very concerned, Dr Hyun.
It's me.
Haven't you found my son yet?
Are you her guardian?
You don't need to worry.
She has a mild fever.
She wasn't under the water for that long,
so it doesn't seem like there's water in her lungs.
I'm sure you're aware that she had a stroke.
We need to run some tests on her,
so I requested a transfer to a bigger hospital.
That's all you need to know for now.
Who are you?
She swore at her daughter-in-law all the time.
She put her daughter-in-law in danger after all.
There's no way she did such a horrible thing to her.
They've lived together for a long time.
We all know it's been a nightmare for her.
It's obvious.
She pushed a woman into the sea.
That means she tried to kill her.
I saw everything.
She pushed the wheelchair like this...
I don't even need to explain this.
Why else did she run away? She's not at home.
Is she not at home?
Shouldn't we report her to the police?
Where is Jin Sung?
Her hair is thin and weak.
Her skin is dry.
Her neck is abnormally thick.
She seems to have gained weight suddenly.
She's suffering from long-term paralysis.
Also, she has lost mobility.
Can you hear me?
Listen to me carefully.
The person who pushed you into the water...
is your mother-in-law, right?
You can tell me.
If not,
there's no way to explain your condition.
She can't seem to speak.
She swallows saliva instead of answering.
- It means...
-  Raised eyebrows.
Wrinkled nose. Stepping backwards.
Those indicate contempt and fear.
You're trying to read my body signals.
Hello.
She did?
Yes.
My goodness. I don't know what's going on.
Gosh. Ma'am, are you saying...
you pushed your daughter-in-law into the sea?
You pushed her wheelchair like this, right?
Ma'am!
Were you trying to kill her?
Granny...
just turned herself in.
That means...
my diagnosis...
was correct.
So I won...
the bet...
as I expected.
I'll get her started on an IV before she's transferred.
Hey.
A pen, please.
This patient isn't suffering from a stroke.
Sure.
- Pardon?
-  She's suffering from...
Hashimoto's disease.
Advise the doctors at the hospital she'll go to...
to begin with a hormone treatment.
One more thing.
This patient will recover very slowly.
But I assume that it won't be easy...
for them to live together like a family.
Excuse me.
- I asked you earlier. Who are you?
-  If I were you,
I would never tell a patient's guardian...
what I hope for the patient.
I would never say that her lungs were fine...
when she had a fever,
like you did to me earlier.
I would never do that.
Oh, no. Hold on.
What's wrong with her? What is happening to her?
Pen light. Pen light!
What's the matter?
- Do something.
-  I can't.
I just graduated from medical school.
She needs to go to a bigger hospital.
- Why isn't the ambulance coming?
-  Wait.
Was I wrong?
No. I wasn't wrong this time, either.
There must be something.
There must be.
Dr Lee Young Oh.
Wait, Dr Lee!
Metzenbaum.
I'll remove the heart.
Hold on.
The heart is okay, isn't it?
The hospital checked the heart before sending it,
and the extraction team arrived on time.
It developed infective endocarditis inside the valve.
We can't use this heart.
We can treat the infection after the transplant.
We can do that.
I'll look after her through the night by myself.
I can pull this off.
Pull yourself together, Lee Shi Hyun!
Even if you transplant this heart,
will that be all?
You can't treat the infection...
while using immunosuppressants.
That's basic knowledge.
This patient might not...
be able to survive waiting for another donor...
- with her heart.
-  Without her heart,
she'll die right now.
Is that what you want?
Suction.
Doctor.
Something's wrong with my heart.
Why is it pounding?
Are you okay?
I get it.
It's because I'm in front of a pretty woman.
I guess...
it was a man who gave me this heart.
A very healthy man.
Thank you, Doctor.
Dr Hyun.
I tried my best to save her life.
But no matter how hard I try,
there's nothing I can do for her.
How much longer do I have to fight this fight?
Still,
I would choose to fight it every day...
until the end.
I'm sorry, but can I borrow your handkerchief?
Thank you. I'll give it back later.
I couldn't just go home.
It was my first surgery, too.
It was my first surgery as a professor.
I feel terrible.
Dr Hong.
We all knew that you'd get the promotion.
You're short-tempered and foul-mouthed.
You're perfect for Anaesthesiology.
I'm going through a hard time lately.
I can't release my anger.
I wish I could swear saying how an anaesthesiologist...
could do that and let it go, but I can't.
I wish I could yell as much as I want...
saying that it's not right, but I can't do that.
Gosh.
I guess that's why I miss her.
Dr Kim Yoon Kyung.
I'll get going.
Was there a little child involved in the accident?
Is there a little child?
Is there any child who can give my daughter a heart?
Suk Joo, you must succeed.
Promise me that you'll succeed.
I heard about the surgery.
You gave up on the transplant during the surgery.
He can be cruel sometimes, Dr Hyun.
The Creator isn't exactly generous.
We can live even if we give half of our liver away.
The fingernails grow back when we trim them.
However, the brain and the heart are the more crucial,
but they can't be regenerated once they're damaged.
Must I hear more of this?
Do you really need to find Dr Lee Young Oh?
What can be done now?
We'll be getting the approval from the FDA soon.
Once we succeed in regenerative medicine,
we won't need to worry about transplants.
No one would have to go through...
what Dr Kim had to go through.
If you wait just a bit longer, regenerative medicine...
- will replace the Creator's job.
-  Tell him...
that you're a scumbag.
Are you all right?
I lost...
this bet.
I wasn't able to diagnose her properly.
I couldn't...
read the patient's mind any further.
Are you satisfied now?
If it wasn't Granny who pushed her into the sea,
what happens?
This is why she was being so nasty and stubborn.
This is why she tried so hard to make money.
Her daughter-in-law wasn't a burden for her...
to get rid of.
She was the future that pushed her to work harder.
There is no one...
who would throw away...
the future into the sea.
Didn't you have a moment...
when you desperately needed someone...
although you knew they wouldn't be of any help?
We're making the transfer right now.
It wasn't the granny who pushed her.
We'll know more when we run more tests,
but it seems she's suffering from cerebral haemorrhage.
She needs to undergo emergency surgery.
Are you her guardian?
No.
It's not a stroke and also not cerebral haemorrhage.
What she needs before anything...
is immunosuppressants,
not surgery.
Who are you?
Paralysis, loss of speaking skills, unconscious.
They're all symptoms of a stroke.
She fell into the sea and the external shock...
caused a vessel to rupture.
She fell into the sea,
so it's not cerebrovascular problem.
She jumped into the sea herself.
Look.
That doesn't make any sense.
Why would she do that?
She was hallucinating.
- Hallucination?
-  She constantly had hot flashes.
She was hallucinating that someone set her on fire.
That is why...
she fell into water to survive.
How would you know that?
She can't even speak.
It wasn't about the medical symptoms.
I tried to read the patient's mind...
for the first time.
I tried to see her as a human being.
It has similar symptoms as a stroke,
but she was hallucinating.
That proves that she doesn't have a stroke.
Her autoantibody...
targeted her brain. She has autoimmune encephalitis.
This patient has...
autoimmune encephalitis accompanied with...
Hashimoto's disease.
Are you saying that my diagnosis was incorrect?
Don't just stand there. The hospital is two hours away.
She may not make it in time for surgery.
Where do you keep the immunosuppressants?
Are you trying to kill the patient?
I need immunosuppressants!
If she dies before she gets to the OR,
you'll be sent to military camp right away.
I'm a police officer.
Article 12 of the Emergency Medical Service Act says...
no one may interfere...
with an emergency medical team treating a patient.
This is an emergency situation.
From this moment on,
nobody can interrupt...
this doctor.
Where are immunosuppressants?
Where?
What do you think you're doing?
She needs an operation.
Why are you giving her immunosuppressants?
Are you trying to kill this patient?
- Hold on.
-  Wait a second!
Hold on.
Are you out of your mind?
Do you realise what you've just done?
Oh, my. Doctor.
Mother.
Where is my mother-in-law?
I was right.
Why did you turn yourself in?
Gosh.
The police officers have enough on their hands.
People would think you were senile.
I was afraid she did that to run away from me.
Once I'm gone, the government will look after her.
She'll be sent to a facility, right?
I wanted her to live like that...
without having to deal with me.
I see you gave it some thought.
Did my daughter-in-law really ask for me?
My gosh.
Who was that...
earlier?
The doctor who saved me...
Oh, well...
I assume you don't mean me, right?
Should I go bring him?
I won...
the bet.
You also believed Granny's sincerity.
That's how your diagnosis was accurate.
Did you bring me here...
to tell me that?
Not a chance.
A human's body never lies.
The world I live in...
is a perfectly logical place...
that isn't polluted by emotions or sincerity.
That is why...
I still love medicine.
Still?
You asked me earlier...
if I needed someone desperately...
although he won't be of any help.
I did.
But...
it wasn't as bad as I expected.
This is where you were.
The patient is asking for you.
Excuse me.
You're a real doctor, right?
Which hospital are you with?
I'm Lee Young Oh.
I'm a doctor.
I'm Doctor Lee Young Oh.
(Beautiful Mind)
Dr Lee? Are you really Dr Lee Young Oh?
- Sir!
-  Father!
What is wrong with all of you? Do something!
Without a proper diagnosis, the risk is too high.
Your father is going to pass away.
- It's too late.
-  You're wrong. It's not too late.
Dr Lee is way too dangerous.
I'm planning to return to Hyunsung Medical Centre.
It's where I used to belong. Do you want to bet?
I really hope that you will win this bet.