(Episode 8)
You're a quack, aren't you?
Did you play basketball instead of studying?
Why don't you test me?
Let me cut you open and see...
how many rooms there are...
in that player's heart.
Again!
My wife is almost due.
I will be...
a dad soon.
Okay, here I go.
People don't change.
Hey.
What's wrong?
Chang Soo. Wake up.
Chang Soo!
Chang Soo.
There was an accident at the factory.
A worker lost his sight...
from exposure to methanol!
The chairman is about to have dinner.
Let go.
It's because you used methanol instead of ethanol...
to save a few bucks.
The company should pay for medical and living expenses.
Give him compensation for damages, too.
This is an industrial accident, Father.
Our factory did nothing wrong.
He was careless.
He was just unlucky.
When you built the factory,
you said Chang Soo was family.
Tell him...
if he complains about this,
we will sue for damages for the loss...
the company suffered due to his injury.
Sit down.
Let's talk about something more suitable at the table.
I will never sit at this table again.
I'm afraid even I'll go blind in this house.
The world is a battlefield!
In a battlefield where bullets are flying,
those with warm hearts die first.
Is that how you want to end up?
You...
are my son.
You've always had...
everything you could possible want.
You're used to winning.
You'll end up picking up a gun.
When you do,
you'll want to shoot it...
with all your might...
without consideration,
just like your old man.
No.
I will never end up like you.
I will do everything I can...
to be different.
(Beautiful Mind)
- BP.
-  180 over 60.
His BP is unstable and dangerous.
He's losing consciousness.
Did he collapse while working?
- Without any symptoms?
-  Yes.
Mr Chairman.
Father.
What happened?
Why out of the blue?
Why now?
You dropped your towel.
So,
how long have you been a member...
at this gym?
Do you want to know?
Shall we make a bet?
Buy dinner if you win.
I'll tell you if I lose.
What are you doing?
I've already completed my workout.
I'm not curious about you enough...
to burn more calories.
That's right.
"Shall we make a bet?"
Don't say that.
It doesn't...
suit you.
You're racking up a lot of points.
Drive carefully, or your license will be suspended.
- I will. Thank you.
-  Okay? Good.
Dr Lee Young Oh?
Funny seeing you here.
This is my zone.
You just went the opposite way in a one-way street.
Excuse me...
Are you really Dr Lee Young Oh?
I mean, why are you here...
in this area at this hour?
And it's not like you...
to get caught so easily, either.
You seem very strange right now.
- I feel like...
-  Don't tell me...
you think...
I came...
to your zone...
during lunch time, of all times,
and intentionally...
got caught...
- by you.
-  No. That's not what I was saying.
I thought...
you'd be...
working very hard to return to Hyunsung Medical Centre.
I will not work at trying to return...
to Hyunsung...
Medical Centre.
Why would I?
You thought and supposed all on your own...
and came to an incorrect conclusion.
If you want to know what I'm thinking, just call.
Okay?
What is it?
You said to call if I'm curious.
I'm calling.
Have you eaten yet?
What's the cause?
Sudden quadriplegia and loss of consciousness.
Tumour Centre.
Dr Hwang, have you checked the file?
Yes. There was nothing suspicious.
Neurosurgery. Anything wrong with the brain?
No. The MRI and angiography both came back clear.
Neurology. Didn't he have a check-up recently?
Didn't you say everything was fine?
- Yes, Sir. The...
-  It looks like...
a temporary paralysis caused by...
high blood pressure diabetes.
It's a TIA and myoischemia.
He'll be fine with the proper medicine.
Goodness.
Are you sure?
With the proper medicine,
will he really wake up...
as the nasty old man screaming at me?
Even with medication,
we can't control how he treats you.
You'll hear it again, even if you don't want to.
You are so easy-going.
How can you...
laugh right now?
My heart is pounding like crazy...
and I feel like I'm drying up right now!
What if that old man...
never wakes up...
and I can't become Hyunsung's successor?
What if Dr Chae Soon Ho, whom I respect greatly,
is found guilty of a horrid murder...
and ends up in prison...
during the prime of his life...
and never becomes the director at Hyunsung?
I am just so concerned.
I've been the chairman's doctor...
for 15 years.
None of the things you worry about will happen.
The chairman will recover soon,
and the regenerative medicine...
will receive FDA approval...
and bring hope to all who wish for cures...
for incurable diseases.
Shouldn't they reopen investigations...
for the Hyunsung serial murders?
We know Kang Chul Min's secret doctor...
is at Hyunsung Medical Centre.
He's either the serial killer...
or the one calling the shots is at Hyunsung.
Look. The case has been closed.
Everyone else wants to bury it,
but you want to reopen it.
You're a traffic cop nonetheless...
trying to take on the great Hyunsung.
Why are you so reckless?
You'll never win. No one else would even try.
Well?
Because I want a drink.
Mr Shin...
promised to have...
a drink with me after we uncover the truth.
He didn't pass away due to an unfortunate accident.
I'm going to tell the world what happened.
That way...
I can enjoy a drink again.
So what do you plan to do?
I should...
start from scratch, right?
It'll be hard since I have no clues or leads.
Do you think you couldn't catch the killer...
because you had no clues or leads?
No. This world...
doesn't care about...
the truth.
Then this time,
I'll give the world a chance.
One more time.
It's kind of like a ring,
but it's a soju bottle cap.
Have you seen it?
I have not.
Shall we make a bet?
This is...
the lead that you're looking for.
It's also Hyunsung's secret...
that Mr Shin wanted to expose.
It's the study results of Dr Shim Eun Ha,
who I wanted to speak at the Mortality Conference.
You said with this lead,
you can catch the real killer, right?
Fine. Go ahead.
Let's make a bet.
Will I win, or will you?
However,
you will be unable to read this on your own.
Someone with expertise...
and knowledge about medical science...
must be with you.
You may have to bother that person every day.
For example, by calling...
or needing to meet.
Do you understand?
Here.
Hey.
Give it...
Why won't you...
Thank you.
I'm surprised...
that you won't return to Hyunsung.
I never said I won't return.
I said I don't need to work at it.
Because...
Hyunsung will call me.
What is it? What's wrong with him?
Did you give him the medicine that I ordered?
Did you check his blood sugar level?
This shouldn't have happened.
It is not TIA and myoischemia.
Tell Dr Chae, the chairman's attending,
that we need to rerun the tests.
Tests. Tests. Tests!
What?
Where? How?
We've run every test that Hyunsung can run.
We've used every top-of-the-line equipment,
but we were unable to find anything wrong.
What does a paper-writing lab rat like you...
with no experience know?
His ACTH, the adrenocorticotropic hormone level...
is very high. There's a high probability of a tumour.
That is my opinion as a specialist.
If you won't do it, I'll tell him myself.
Is it me this time?
Tell me, Dr Kim.
Do you want to ignore proper protocol...
and step on me this time...
to become Chairman Kang's attending? Is that it?
- Doctor.
-  Quiet! All of you!
I am Chairman Kang's attending.
I will think and decide.
What's wrong with the chairman?
Doctor, it's an insulin shock.
This is a huge accident.
Poor Dr Yoo.
He should be banished. He misdiagnosed him.
- You may be the one banished.
-  Why?
Imagine they find a neurological illness.
You'll be the one being exiled for life.
- Hello.
-  Out of my way!
That's why Joseon failed.
Why would you banish the royal physician?
I'm speechless.
Wow. These people...
It's like a war broke out or something.
You can't blame them.
When he first came in, they said it was myoischemia,
so I thought he was testing his children's devotion,
but now, he's fighting for his life.
Goodness. Chairman Kang's life?
I'm more worried about myself.
Dr Chae, the next hospital director,
was my dad's classmate,
so I thought I'd get hired once I'm done.
- Darn.
-  Then,
is Dr Lee Gun Myung's chances better now?
The hospital director position isn't the problem.
With the owner's sons fighting,
the owner of the hospital may change entirely.
I should look...
at other hospitals for the specialist positions.
Hi, Mum.
Yes, don't...
Don't worry too much. This is also Hyunsung.
The top doctors from the nation...
are on alert and tending to Father.
He'll be fully recovered before you return...
from your business trip...
You're the one who wants...
to end his life right now...
since you want to take over Hyunsung.
You won't have to kiss up to that ill-tempered old man.
Right?
Listen to me.
I'm the one who wants...
to save that old man the most. Why?
That way Hyunsung will be mine.
Because I need time.
So,
stop pretending to be so worried.
I can smell the stench of your nag even from here.
Got it?
You slime ball.
Sir.
He hung up a while ago...
because of his temper.
Do you have a religion?
Go pray...
that a thunder storm will cancel his flight.
No, forget that.
It would be better...
if his plane blew up...
in the middle of the Pacific.
Pray for that, please.
What is it?
I need to discuss Chairman Kang's condition with you.
With me?
Why?
Do only ambitious doctors...
who want to get ahead like I do care about his care?
That isn't what I meant.
You seem...
to be nice to everyone.
But why do I feel like you're always fighting...
like I am?
Disrespect. Discrimination. Oppression.
Those are what I'm fighting against, but you...
You said you were here about Chairman Kang.
Please help me...
treat Chairman Kang Il Do.
I'm sorry, Sir.
I'm terribly sorry.
I asked you for...
a precise diagnosis and treatment for Chairman Kang.
Not a cheap apology like this!
Yes, you are right. I'm sorry.
Oh, dear.
What are all of you doing?
Do something!
Based on the test results,
it is impossible to make a diagnosis.
Not many doctors...
can prescribe something unsure for Chairman Kang.
This risk is too high,
both for the patient...
and for the medical staff.
Are you honest or shameless?
Don't you realise...
what you just said means...
you don't want to take responsibility?
Chairman Kang...
may have lung cancer.
A tumour?
The tumour centre didn't find it during the screening.
What proof do you have?
Are you sure?
It didn't show up on the PET scan or CT scan,
but while he was hospitalised,
his ACTH level had been rising.
The tumour is probably hiding where it can't be seen.
There is no other way to explain...
his present condition.
What if we open him up and you're wrong?
Do you want to play find-the-tumour...
with a man nearing 80?
Opening up his chest may be deadlier than the tumour.
Answer me.
Can you...
take responsibility?
We should do it without opening his chest.
As long as we don't open up his chest,
Dr Kim's opinion...
is the best we can do at this time.
It may be our last option as well.
They plan to remove a tumour in the lung...
without opening his chest or spilling any blood.
Did...
Did you say the lead surgeon is Dr Hyun Suk Joo?
That's correct.
May I trust you this time,
Dr Chae?
Let's go.
Chairman Kang's BP and vitals...
are all stable.
Dr Hyun opted for a thoracoscopic surgery.
It will be quite difficult.
Chairman Kang's BP has to hang in there.
I want just one thing.
Seeing Father wake up and back to normal...
before my brother lands in Korea.
You should do that much for me,
shouldn't you?
I'm surprised.
I never thought...
you'd be so proactive about Chairman Kang.
I'm also surprised.
Do you still not know why I am being so proactive...
about operating on your patient?
I've located...
a tumour.
The tumour has been removed.
BP, blood sugar level,
vitals...
are all stable.
When you have a dangerous surgery,
you need a great assisting surgeon.
My decisions have always been consistent.
The patient's life.
Let's check his bleeding.
Chairman Kang Il Do, who had announced...
he'd be stepping down,
is in the hospital...
after receiving surgery for lung cancer.
Because of his health scare,
Hyunsung's successorship will likely become of issue.
What a relief.
Hyunsung needs to remain strong...
for the sake of this nation's economy.
Is that right?
The chairman and his sons...
are all patrons of my shop.
That's right.
It's your first time here, isn't it?
I haven't seen you before.
Shops like ours that make custom-made suits...
are all about our regulars.
I'm saying that's how good our quality is,
and that you'll be satisfied.
Because we tailor it...
to fit perfectly on you.
What you sell here...
isn't the clothes.
It's the price of fame, is it not?
- What I meant was...
-  It doesn't matter,
because that is exactly...
what I want to purchase.
Good job.
It was a tough surgery,
but it was perfect from diagnosis to performance.
Suk Joo,
you are one of the best.
The tumour removal was a success.
When...
can I be discharged?
Are you uncomfortable here?
Just let me know and I...
-  You.
You make me the most uncomfortable.
I wonder how much you'll brag...
just because you saved my life. Gosh.
Don't tell me...
you see this as an opportunity...
to become the successor...
or claim more shares or anything like that.
Me?
How would I dare...
All you did was play all your life,
but you can't make...
a baby that everyone else does,
just so you won't be inconvenienced.
You are...
really useless.
Let me help you.
Just bring me some water.
Okay.
- Father!
-  Mr Chairman!
Father, are you all right?
Father. Father?
We removed the tumour,
but...
we may have failed at treating him.
What do you mean by that?
Dr Chae, this is bad.
Chairman Kang...
The surgery...
went well for sure.
You all saw.
He doesn't have the possible side effects...
of the surgery,
such as bleeding or infarction.
Then why?
Why?
His BP keeps spiking.
He may have...
another insulin shock which may cause brain damage.
Do something.
Open up his head or his chest. Make him breathe.
Just make him breathe!
We have only one option...
left.
Dr Lee Young Oh.
Lee Young Oh?
Not that Lee Young Oh.
Dr Hyun.
I don't approve.
Hyunsung,
with the top physicians...
and top-of-the-line medical equipment,
can't find the cause.
What can Dr Lee Young Oh do?
Dr Lee Young Oh...
was banished by the hospital's ethics council.
We cannot allow it.
He cannot treat patients again.
What did you say?
Antisocial disorder?
You want that psychopath...
to treat my father,
Hyunsung Group's Chairman Kang Il Do...
I'm losing my mind.
His blood sugar level is increasing.
His BP is 220 over 180. It's too high.
We need to do something.
We can't just give him an antihypertensive and wait...
considering his age.
We don't have much time.
Dr Lee will take a completely different approach...
from what we've tried thus far.
Dr Hyun!
Unless there's another reason Dr Lee shouldn't be back,
call him in before it's too late.
Lee Young Oh. Lee Young Oh!
Is he our only option right now?
Dr Lee is...
- too dangerous.
-  He may be dangerous,
but he'll save the patient's life.
Sir.
Your brother just arrived at the airport.
He's coming straight here.
Darn it!
Call him in.
Sir.
Call him in. Call him in. Call him in now!
Bring Dr Lee to me.
Right now. Bring him here right now!
I'm planning to return to Hyunsung Medical Centre.
Even if you're against it,
you won't be able to stop me this time.
The hospital...
will...
need me.
I won't say that I'm glad to see you again.
I'm not that brazen.
I'm sure that you have heard about my father...
through the media.
I thought you'd go to see my father first.
Why did you ask to meet me first, Dr Lee?
Did I?
When did I do that?
I made it clear.
Me and you...
and your brother.
I said,
I wanted the three of us to meet.
I was hoping...
that you would tell me...
what my father's illness is before my brother arrives.
("Gender Trouble", "The Broken Image")
You can do that for me.
Let's tell people that it was you...
who didn't show up.
Okay.
All right.
Now tell me...
what my father is suffering from...
and how you'll treat him.
It's you two...
who must confess.
Even at this moment,
you're killing your father.
Why didn't you tell the doctors...
about the changes in your bodies?
To be exact,
the hereditary disease that Chairman Kang Il Do...
and the two of you have.
The three of you...
are hiding this important fact.
That is why the elite doctors...
at a top-notch hospital like Hyunsung...
couldn't make a diagnosis with the test results alone.
All right.
It's time for you to confess...
if you want to save your father's life.
Hereditary disease?
Do you...
He's being ridiculous.
I don't have any diseases.
You're well aware...
that I love sports and working out.
Do you...
Are you in good shape?
It's beautiful that you yield to each other.
But we're running out of time. Tick-tock, tick-tock.
While you two remain silent,
your father, Chairman Kang, will pass away...
without getting any proper treatment...
or even a life-saving surgery.
The head of Hyunsung Group...
who can do anything with his power and money...
will die in his own hospital...
because his two sons...
are too proud to reveal their diseases.
If you don't think you can treat him,
you can give up now.
If word gets out about a supposed hereditary disease,
it will affect the group's stock price.
Do you expect us to talk without our attorney present?
I can take Father...
to the States tomorrow.
I'm sure they have...
physicians of a higher caliber.
- Wait.
-  I'll leave the discharge procedure to you.
It's not difficult to do.
Your brother just made a choice.
He chose to leave your father to die like this.
That means he wouldn't mind succeeding his father...
with the share of inheritance...
that he's entitled to.
But it's not the same for you.
I know you want to save him.
You must want to desperately.
Because your future depends on it.
Tell me now.
Okay. I'll count to five.
What on earth do you want me to say?
You already told me the answer.
You couldn't look at my fingers.
The youngest son of the Hyunsung family,
the ambitious chairman of the hospital, Kang Hyun Joon.
You are...
turning into a woman.
Isn't that true?
That's nonsense.
I'm a woman?
I'm turning into a woman?
That makes no sense.
All right, then.
Your father will pass away in this bed...
without knowing what disease he has.
You will live as a woman,
and die as a woman.
I should respect...
your decision.
Please save him.
Please save him, Dr Lee.
Tell me whatever you want. What do you want?
I'll give it to you.
What else would a doctor want...
other than saving his patient?
I will return to Hyunsung Medical Centre.
I will return to my original post.
Let's talk about that...
after you save my father.
Did you forget?
If I choose to treat him,
it means...
that he will live.
Gosh.
Dr Lee made such a splendid comeback.
I know.
But how did he do that?
Does he really know what disease...
Chairman Kang has and how to treat him?
Whether he gives medication or operates on him,
we'll never know until he wakes up.
Just accept it, Dr Yoo.
He was born talented.
That's what you said to me.
What disease does he have?
Heterogeneous FIPA.
Familial isolated pituitary adenoma.
It's the hereditary disease you and your father have.
In your father's case,
the tumour here is so small...
that no one would have noticed it...
if you hadn't developed the disease.
How on earth...
did you know about this?
A person who loves working out...
avoided using the showers at the gym.
Later on, you avoided the gym altogether.
I assumed that you had your reasons.
At the shop you go to...
that makes custom-tailored suits,
I found out that only your chest size increased.
I was also able to confirm that you lost...
your peripheral vision.
Your chest became abnormally large.
As you can see here,
a sex hormone called prolactin increased.
You've been...
anxious and afraid because...
your body was slowly changing into a woman's body.
I'll operate on you and your father...
for the pituitary adenoma...
simultaneously.
What about my brother?
There's an exception to everything.
It's the same for hereditary diseases.
This disease is determined by dominant genes.
Your bother didn't develop the disease,
fortunately.
Then, why did you...
make it look like he was hiding it?
By doing so, I knew it would make it easier for you...
to tell me about your condition.
Lee Young Oh.
How dare you?
How could you do that to me?
Did you forget who I am?
I get what I want...
by any means necessary.
I don't care about others' feelings or pain...
because I lack empathy.
I'm a psychopath.
Oh, right.
You and I look alike, don't we?
We look like brothers.
Smile. Come on.
One, two.
I would like you...
to operate on Chairman Kang.
The ethics council at Hyunsung Medical Centre and I...
didn't allow you to come back to the hospital.
You're not allowed to do that surgery, either.
That's why I'm suggesting you do the surgery.
I know you need a good reason.
It must not be that you disobeyed the chairman...
to have me reinstated.
It was for your patient who needed surgery.
You came to a conclusion...
that you had no other choice but to have me reinstated.
I already told you...
that I would return to this hospital...
and you...
wouldn't be able to stop me.
(Surgeon: Dr Lee Gun Myung, Patient: Kang Il Do)
(Surgeon: Dr Lee Young Oh, Patient: Kang Hyun Joon)
You were right.
I agreed to this surgery...
only because I need a reason as you said.
Never...
use a patient to achieve your purpose.
Next time, I won't allow you to do that.
I heard...
that you have the same disease that I do.
Thanks to you,
they were able to diagnose me and do the operation.
This is why...
I never approved of you.
If I had been you,
I would've realised this disease...
could make us money right away.
Tell your brother...
to prepare to start...
a bioinformatics...
business.
Are you feeling better?
His surgery went well.
Don't worry.
Haven't we gotten the approval from the FDA?
As soon as it's approved,
we'll announce the commercialisation...
of the regeneration medicine.
Sir.
Before that old man dies,
I have to prove myself to him.
Could that be a lead?
I want to reopen the case of the murders at Hyunsung.
This will only prove that...
there were victims of clinical trials in the process...
of the research conducted by Hyunsung.
We should let the world know.
The public will make this an issue,
and Hyunsung will have to explain.
Then, we'll find out what really happened...
at Hyunsung.
And the police...
will be able to reopen the case.
Suk Joo! Suk Joo!
Suk Joo. This isn't the proper way.
The culture cells...
that were used at the third stage trial...
are very clean.
The immune and tumour responses are clean as well.
Now, look.
Check for yourself.
It can't replace organ transplants just yet.
However,
isn't this definite evidence of cell regeneration?
You can stop worrying now.
Once this gets approved by the FDA,
it can be used for treatments immediately.
Suk Joo, our dream will finally come true!
Come on.
Great job.
Well... Suk Joo.
- Dr Hyun!
-  What's the matter, Shi Hyun?
Ji An.
- Vaccine.
-  Come quickly!
Hae Joo.
Where have you been? I've been looking for you!
Dr Hyun.
No, Ji An.
Ji An.
One, two, three, four.
Get the sodium bicarbonate, Ms Lee.
- Ms Jang!
-  Yes?
Should I congratulate you?
Or should I bid you welcome?
I thought you wouldn't...
be able to treat patients any longer.
That's if you're the person I know.
You wouldn't be able to read...
body signals, either.
Did something happen?
I thought you'd call me earlier, Officer Gye.
Thanks to you,
I may be able to reinvestigate this case.
I'd like to show you...
that there's still a world that cares about the truth.
I really hope...
that you'll win this bet.
No.
Ji An, no.
You can live, Ji An.
Dr Hyun!
Dr Hyun.
I'm going to perform a cardiac massage.
It's not too late yet.
It is too late, Dr Hyun.
You know it, too.
Ji An has...
suffered long enough.
Let's send her to her mother's side.
You are so conceited, Hyun Suk Joo.
You always maintain a kind and righteous attitude,
but you can neither save nor heal my daughter.
How dare you judge me? What right do you have?
Suk Joo.
You have to be successful.
Promise me that you'll succeed.
Do you know what my dream is?
I want surgeons to disappear forever.
That way,
there will come a day...
when people can be cured without surgery.
What a surprise.
As long as my heart beats like this,
I will remember...
what a good person you are.
For the first time in human history,
Hyunsung Medical Centre's...
Regenerative Medicine Research Team,
has succeeded in regenerating myocardial cells.
I heard it's impossible to regenerate myocardial cells.
Are you certain?
Were all the clinical tests successful?
On the 2nd and 3rd stage clinical trials,
we achieved results that got our patients' attentions.
We safely passed...
all the FDA criteria...
without a problem.
Make sure to fasten your seat belt. All right?
Please drive safely.
(The First Successful Myocardial Cell Regeneration)
He told me that...
he'd help me reinvestigate the case.
I began investigating the case to find...
either the criminal or the one behind the murders,
so that Mr Shin's death would not be in vain.
That's not it.
Mr Shin's death was a mere accident.
It was an unfortunate accident caused by Dr Kim,
a drug addict.
This is the fact.
It's the root cause of everything that happened...
at Hyunsung.
This is not...
what I wanted to show you.
You won the bet this time.
You do know...
that I am not...
interested in what you're thinking...
or what you're feeling...
at all.
I can't empathise, either.
From now on,
I no longer exist.
You can...
cry as much as you'd like...
right here in front of me.
(Beautiful Mind)
Didn't I tell you it'd be a beautiful knife, Dr Lee?
I've been transferred to the Violent Crimes Division.
I don't want to suspect you.
Say that I made a good decision.
Tell me that our research will be successful!
You were wrong.
As expected, I can't change myself.
I kept thinking to myself on the way here.
I really didn't want to bump in to you.
I didn't know how to face you.