(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
Please.
You need to pay first.
You can't get examined or go to the ER until then.
He's sick.
Let me at least see a doctor.
That's the rules. You can't keep doing this.
He can't get treated until you take care of the bill.
What are you doing? The child is sick.
Doctor.
You know the hospital rules.
Doctor, please take a look at my child.
This is the test results from the other hospital.
This child...
It's just like your son's...
What's your name?
Can you speak?
It's Lee Young Oh.
He's the 205th child at Grace Home. Lee Young Oh.
He grew up in the facility.
His parents gave up on him because of his illness.
Please, Sir.
Doctor.
Dr Lee. You don't...
No, right?
Get me an OR.
- Doctor.
-  Thank you.
You can't do this.
I will take...
full responsibility.
Dr Lee. This isn't right.
You can't drag this child...
into such a dangerous surgery because of your son.
Didn't you hear? His parents abandoned him.
- Lee Gun Myung.
-  I won't give up.
No on this child. Not on my son.
I will save him no matter what.
I promise.
(Surgery in progress)
Honey.
I've succeeded.
Hyun...
Hyun's gone.
What?
While you were...
locked up in that OR all night,
our Hyun died.
He left forever...
without getting a goodbye from his dad!
No.
- I...
-  Live in the OR for the rest of your life.
You've never...
needed a family.
Dr Lee.
You've made...
a mistake you can't undo.
You must've touched the frontal lobe during surgery.
That child...
will have a disability for the rest of his life.
He won't be able to feel any emotions.
Shouldn't we tell his guardian?
Dr Lee.
This is a malpractice.
No.
I am his guardian from this day forth.
I traded my son's life for his.
I will...
help him live like a normal person.
I'll devote my life to it.
(Beautiful Mind)
(Episode 9)
The regenerative medicine research team...
at Hyunsung Medical Centre...
succeeded at...
regenerating stem cells for the first time in history.
Are you saying you succeeded in...
the impossible stem cell regeneration?
Please.
Isn't it time to make your decision?
Our research is a success.
There are...
countless Ji Ans out there for whom transplants...
are the only answer.
And yet,
is being good and righteous...
still more important to you?
- Even after Ji An died?
-  Stop it.
Suk Joo.
Do you want to be a good person...
or live as a good doctor?
Were all the clinical tests safely concluded?
Both the second and third stage tests...
showed positive results for all the subjects.
In addition,
we passed all the test by the FDA...
with flying colours.
Promise me...
that there will never be another Ji An.
Suk Joo.
Tell me...
that you'll make sure our research a success,
no matter what it takes!
Say it's the right choice...
and that I won't regret it.
Say it!
Regenerative medicine must really be great.
As long as they have...
"Hyunsung" and "bio" in the name,
they're set.
Let me see that.
Dr Hyun is...
so inconsiderate.
I misjudged him.
If he had such good Intel,
he should've shared it with us.
We're family, after all.
That's called insider trading.
You could get in big trouble.
And this is okay because it isn't free?
You'll go to prison, you punk.
That's enough.
Oh my gosh.
Ms Jang,
is my schedule not ready yet?
No, I believe your appointments...
begin in the afternoon.
In the afternoon?
Yes.
Why don't you sit and have some coffee...
- Don't give it to him.
-  I already have coffee.
Hot Americano. Tall.
- Okay then.
-  Okay.
- That's mine.
-  What's wrong with you?
- I was caught off guard.
-  Why would you do that?
Don't make things awkward.
Don't make it uncomfortable.
Oh my gosh.
To be honest,
I knew...
that you...
welcome me back.
Thank you.
It's good.
Thanks.
How scary.
I can't believe Dr Lee Gun Myung.
Blood is thicker than water, is that it?
He kicked him out so cruelly.
How could he let someone like that back in?
Don't you know anything?
How could he go against the chairman in these times?
The vote...
for hospital director is today.
Let me see.
It's now.
Drum roll please.
Will it be Dr Chae Soon Ho or Dr Lee Gun Myung?
Was this necessary?
Suddenly announcing it to the nation...
without the research team's consent...
You should focus...
on just the research.
You will be the first surgeon ever to succeed in...
a stem cell transplant.
I will handle hospital administration.
I'll support you whole-heartedly.
To further Director Shin's mission...
Director Shin and I...
began researching regenerative medicine...
in hopes...
that there will come a day when surgeons...
will no longer be needed.
Not to be the first in something...
and definitely not to pursue fame and stardom.
But did you know...
that Director Shin...
was very paranoid.
He hated letting anyone know of his illness.
Did you...
also know...
that he had diabetes?
Wasn't it already proved...
that Dr Kim Yoon Kyung was responsible for his death?
I simply wanted to confirm the truth.
I thought you didn't know him well enough...
to claim to have the same goal as Director Shin.
Sir.
The results of the vote must be out.
Mr Chae.
Please continue to work hard for the hospital.
- Of course...
-  You'll continue to support...
Director Lee, won't you?
Of course, I will.
Congratulations, Director Lee.
It was by unanimous vote.
Unanimous.
You are quite popular.
Please help with the commercialisation of...
the regenerative medicine.
I want it done smoothly and perfectly.
I will do the best I can.
Was the hospital director vote...
your father's wishes or yours?
Director Lee Gun Myung, who values reputation,
will not let Dr Lee Young Oh cause trouble.
That's why...
I put our reputation in his hands.
Director Lee Gun Myung is stiff and upright.
I want him to wag his tail at me, not bark.
He won't be able to do much even as the director.
Eventually,
the patients will know that one of our surgeons...
is a psychopath.
Will you be able to handle that?
(An empathetic word is the beginning of treatment.)
So...
one eye...
keeps shaking.
One eye keeps shaking.
I have a splitting headache which won't go away.
You have a splitting headache which won't go away.
And your eyes shake. Just a minute.
I see...
you were treated for alcoholism before.
I presume that you still drink.
No, I don't.
I'm not trying to kill myself.
Not at all. No way.
Look into the patient's eyes.
Sir.
Give him a warm greeting.
It was tiring coming to the hospital, wasn't it?
Yes. Pardon?
Be courteous...
and listen to the patient.
Please tell me.
As your doctor,
I am ready to listen...
to anything you have to say.
You still drink, don't you?
I'm not crazy. Why would I drink?
I don't drink!
Look, Doctor,
just prescribe me my medicine.
It's hard coming to the hospital for a prescription.
I need to make a living.
Think from the patient's perspective.
There is no need to think.
This fly doesn't belong in the hospital.
Sir.
It's hard to make a living,
so you decided to die, is that it?
Don't you know...
how deadly alcohol is...
after having surgery for a brain hemorrhage?
I don't want to be a doll...
that just smiles at you.
I also don't want to be a priest...
to whom you can vent.
I am a doctor. A doctor.
I decide what is...
the best for you.
Come to the hospital once a week from now on.
If you quit drinking,
it will become once every two weeks,
then once a month.
Do you understand?
If you don't,
the only doctor you will be seeing...
is a mortician. Do you understand?
Do you?
Yes, I understand.
You may go.
Now, you seem like yourself.
I'll bring in the next patient.
(An empathetic word is the beginning of treatment)
Look into the patient's eyes?
Give him a warm greeting?
Awesome. She's back.
She's back. She's back.
- She's back.
-  What are you talking about?
Gye Jin Sung is back.
What's the fuss?
What is that?
She doesn't belong here.
I'm Gye Jin Sung, and I have been transferred...
to the Violent Crimes Division.
- I look forward to working with you!
-  Transferred?
Who said you could join us?
I did. I took her in.
You can't do that on your own.
I promised to take her in if she found the suspect.
A public official shouldn't lie.
You're not making any sense.
Why you...
I will...
work really hard.
That's what scares them the most.
You working really hard.
How could you take her in knowing that?
You know she's a ticking time bomb.
You don't know what she'll do.
That's why I took her in.
Once she bites down, she won't let go.
- She's perfect for Violent Crimes.
-  But...
You punk.
If you see someone die before your eyes,
a police officer of Korea...
should get involved with everything they've got.
I hope I run into an officer like her...
if I get in an accident.
That's just great.
Then why don't you train...
- the new detective?
-  What?
- Thank you!
-  You two can be partners.
What? You punk.
We're going to a crime scene.
- Hey.
-  I'll see you later.
Why those...
Did you check your horoscope for today?
I don't believe in that.
You should read it.
I'm sure it is...
filled with good fortune...
with respect to new jobs, people, career and the like.
What? Was that too difficult to understand?
Yes.
I mean you lucked out with a great lieutenant.
Thank you.
Don't forget.
You must become a Violent Crimes detective first.
Reopening Hyunsung's investigation...
comes after.
Got it?
You knew?
Is that why you took me in?
Then do you...
Armed robbery at a jewellery store in Jungbu 7 dong.
Violent Crimes detectives requested.
Congratulations.
It's your first case.
Get ready.
Yes, Sir.
Call the police if you want!
Hold your hands up.
I have nothing to fear.
Call the police if you want!
- Calm down.
-  He's a first-time offender.
How can you tell?
I can tell just by looking at the back of his head.
It is strange.
He has a weapon,
but the robber is the one who's shaking.
He's doing something out of character.
It's so obvious.
Here.
You've been trained, right?
Let's go.
What is it?
Drop your weapon.
Drop your weapon!
Do you want trouble?
Put it...
down.
Good.
Let me go!
Let's walk out together.
Okay.
No one will get hurt.
He fainted at the crime scene.
He's a patient here, right?
It wasn't a suicide attempt this time.
Get his records and his chart.
Yes, Doctor.
He tried to kill himself?
Yes.
What do you think is wrong with him?
We'll know when the test results come out.
Let's call his family.
Yes, Sir.
That patient...
Do you remember him?
He left a huge impression last time.
Are you all right?
Try to lie back down.
Get off of me! Who said to bring me here?
I know what you mean,
so please stop.
You know who I am, right?
You hurt yourself last time because of your illness.
It means your illness worsened so much...
that you couldn't help but hurt yourself.
But it was a foolish decision.
Next time, ask for a painkiller.
We have painkillers that aren't addictive.
These are good times.
Don't say that.
Stop it.
- Don't say that!
-  Doctor.
Doctor. Please listen to me.
I didn't do that to come back here.
I need to get out of here. Let me go.
- Please?
-  That's enough.
Please, doctor. Please.
We're going to call the police.
He's a thief.
He was caught at the scene.
The Violent Crimes detectives brought him in.
I'll get the police.
Officer Gye.
She's a detective.
I see.
How is he?
We need to process him...
I refuse to be treated.
I refuse.
Let go. I need to go. I need to go right now!
I need to go!
I need to drain the fluid from his head.
Hurry.
There is no problem...
as of now.
There is no problem?
He looked pretty serious.
Of course.
Stage four lung cancer and it spread to his brain.
On top of that, he developed...
a tolerance to the chemotherapy drugs,
so regardless of what treatment he gets,
it will have no effect.
Then what do you mean, there is no problem?
Do you see it?
The physicians couldn't find a treatment,
and the patient refused treatment.
He won't receive treatment.
Both sides came to the same conclusion.
So, there is no problem.
Where are you going?
You say many things...
that sound correct the first time,
but when you think about it,
it is completely wrong.
That's exactly this situation.
Everyone wants to be treated.
At least,
that's how it was for me.
It isn't true, is it?
It's not like you to do this.
Say something. She'll get sick.
Give us an excuse or an explanation. Something.
You brat. Did you really do it?
What is wrong with him?
Are you trying to kill Mum, too?
Do you know what we're...
What? What?
What? What are you going through?
So...
please stop.
Don't think about...
selling the store just to try to save me.
I have no hope anyway.
It's all over.
Why is it over?
You have me.
Your mum is alive.
How could I let you go?
I won't let you go.
Detective.
How long do I have to wait?
Take me to jail, detention, anywhere!
You punk.
Don't say that in front of your mother.
Why don't you come with me?
Who has family take care of them in this time and age?
Money is the best solution. Don't you agree?
What are you doing?
Are you just going to stand there and watch?
If you're so lazy with your weight,
it'll be hard when you have kids.
Move.
I'm allergic to anything non-organic.
Next time,
call the service worker, okay?
Your husband must not make much money.
Why?
It just breaks my heart...
seeing you work so hard just to make a few bucks...
with your belly that big.
I'm just built this way.
I could have 2, 3 kids like this.
You're right.
You remind me of a poster I saw while in school.
If you have babies without thinking it through,
you will end up being homeless.
- Ma'am!
-  That's what the poster said.
Ma'am. The MRI results are out.
Where's your guardian?
Don't be lame. What guardian?
Tell me.
I'm my own guardian.
Take a look at this.
What school?
- Pardon?
-  What school did you graduate?
Hyunsung?
No, right?
Was it at least in Seoul?
- Ma'am.
-  Even when you eat fruit,
you question its origin.
Is it wrong to ask where my doctor went to school?
Did I trigger your inferiority complex?
- Let me explain.
-  Forget it.
Get me another doctor.
I'll tell my attending.
If you're obvious about being poor,
it makes people who have a lot like me uncomfortable.
You make me feel like I did something wrong.
Please leave.
Sure. I am terribly sorry...
for being so obvious I grew up poor.
- Doctor!
-  Oh my gosh.
This is why I hate hospitals.
It's hard to control the humidity.
It's the absolute worst for my skin.
Oh, no! Ma'am!
Ma'am!
Dr Hyun!
Please contact Neurosurgery.
Isn't it nice?
It's so refreshing.
I invented it.
How is this an invention?
It's so nice and cool.
Here you go.
That's cold! What is this?
- Here.
-  What is this?
Take care of your skin.
Stop looking so poor.
I almost socked it to her, but barely refrained myself.
And what? Quit, start a business and go into debt?
Who does she think she is?
I asked every resource I have,
and they all say different things.
Some say she has the Blue House in her back pocket.
Some say she's Chairman Kang's woman.
There's a street called "Yoo Street" in Gangnam...
because that street is filled with her buildings.
Are you saying Kang Hyun Joon can't do anything either?
- Of course.
-  That's right.
She's powerful, well-connected and wealthy.
She lacks only one thing.
Respect for others.
I know you're offended, but don't be too upset.
- I'm sure we've all been there.
-  Really?
Yes. You've been insulted, too.
Someone said you were too tall and stupid-looking.
Someone said they couldn't stand Dr Hwang's arrogance.
- You are arrogant.
-  They were right.
They say Dr Hyun is spineless and shouldn't be trusted.
What about Dr Song?
I don't have a story.
Yes, you do!
He has a big one.
Remember the live surgery incident?
- That's right.
-  Yes.
Word about that spread like wildfire,
so they won't even say his name.
Are we making fun of ourselves...
or that witch?
We started making fun of that witch,
but...
Anyway,
so...
who's the lucky doctor...
who was chosen to treat Yoo Ok Kyung?
I operated on her before for lung cancer.
The targeted therapy...
ended up forming a brain tumour.
It isn't large,
so I recommend gamma knife radiosurgery.
She's become very weak...
- and can't withstand invasive surgery.
-  No.
I disagree,
Dr Hyun.
This is incredible.
The patient who hurts himself... I mean, Lee Sang Joon.
The location of the tumour, the rate...
and process in which the cancer spread are the same.
One more thing.
She developed a tolerance for the targeted medicine...
so we can't use chemotherapy...
on her any more.
Even that is the same.
Didn't you say there is no treatment option?
We can't operate and there's no suitable drug.
Is metastasis and brain tumour a trend or something?
I have a patient to see.
Do you think there is no treatment available?
Nothing legal.
What does that mean?
I'm sure you know.
It'll be very pricey...
and highly dangerous.
And it is even illegal.
Osimertinib.
(Mutated epidermal growth factor receptor cancer drug)
Is that what you mean?
It's the most powerful and effective...
and the only option.
As her attending, I'm against it.
I'm surprised.
It is illegal to use osimertinib.
We need to do a biopsy first.
A biopsy of a brain tumour.
There is a high risk of death...
and a low rate of success. You know that.
If we administer an illegal drug,
the hospital will incur a huge financial loss.
You know the reason...
the drug is illegal is not because of...
the effect of the drug or safety.
It's because it is expensive.
Because it creates a division of classes.
Health must not discriminate between the rich and poor.
Equality.
That's a great sentiment.
But why must only the sick...
maintain that equality?
In exchange for subsidising healthcare for the poor,
certain treatments are forbidden.
Society took the easy way out.
The drug is out there,
and money is not a problem,
but it's illegal, so you must die.
Do you call that legal?
Must I obey that law?
I'll say this as her attending physician.
You may not give illegal treatment to my patient.
And her neurosurgeon...
will be changed from Dr Lee Young Oh...
to Dr Oh Kyung Jin.
You want me...
to treat Yoo Ok Kyung?
What about Dr Lee Young Oh?
He is considering something dangerous.
I'd like you to take her on.
The administration of osimertinib?
That probably...
is the only option she has.
It is illegal to give her that drug. You know that.
- Dr Hyun.
-  The penalty for breaking the law...
will fall on the hospital.
If the hospital gets hurt with things like that,
we'll have problems with the regenerative medicine.
I'm against it.
Is that how it works?
There are plenty of legal options...
for treating her.
You know...
just how dangerous...
a biopsy is, right?
It's the best we can do.
Fine.
I'll take her.
Dr Lee.
Do you live here?
I wanted to ask you something.
What happens...
if a patient wants treatment?
Lee Sang Joon...
wants to live.
How do you know?
How are you so sure?
Lee Sang Joon...
hasn't given up yet.
It may be a piece of meaningless paper for others,
but to me,
it seems like he's still holding on to hope.
We have different perspectives.
Ordinary people...
may consider this some sort of hope,
but I...
don't consider it as hope at all.
Here.
If you aren't willing to help,
I guess he has no chance.
I never said it was impossible.
What are you...
There is an option...
that is dangerous,
illegal and highly costly.
Hold on.
That means...
the detective in charge...
needs to meet...
the doctor in charge often. Are you aware of that?
Do you...
understand what I'm trying to say?
Do you?
I'm sorry. Are you all right?
I'm okay. I was out of it.
Were you thinking about a guy?
I'm joking.
This is essential for a beautiful person...
like you in the summer time, right?
Of course.
Goodbye.
My objective is...
to plead for a favourable settlement.
You can't go to prison in this state.
It's none of your business.
This is exactly what I wanted.
We all...
need help from others.
It's not...
shameful to ask someone for help.
When you reach out for help,
I believe someone will help you.
That includes someone who's looking for a solution.
The hope of ordinary people...
Who are you?
It's late.
How are you going to take responsibility?
Do you know how hard it is for me to fall back asleep?
Get out now.
Get ready for a disciplinary measure tomorrow morning.
Don't worry.
The tumour in your brain...
will help you sleep for a long, long time.
The tumour you have...
makes surgery too risky...
and drugs won't work,
either.
That's why there are people like you.
That's what you get paid for.
So...
what must I do?
Are you saying that you can cure my tumour?
Now, we're talking.
Every doctor in this hospital is against the idea...
because it is highly dangerous...
and...
illegal.
And the most important factor is money.
It is very costly.
By illegal, do you mean I must break the law?
Will I be punished?
Don't worry.
The hospital will take full responsibility.
Ms Jang. Yoo Ok Kyung from Cardiothoracic Surgery...
needs a biopsy.
You're going to take her again?
You're too nice. I don't even want to see her again.
I took her as my patient on purpose.
- What?
-  I'll make the biopsy extra painful.
I'll make her pay for what she said.
Doctor, do you need my assistance?
Sure. See you soon.
You're dead now.
What are you doing here, Dr Lee?
She's my patient.
This is against the regulations.
That's why I've been waiting for you.
I'm sure you are well aware...
that a biopsy is too risky for her.
The location of the tumour isn't optimal.
Legality, regulations, rules.
Are they more important than a patient's life?
I only think about probability.
The probability...
of the patient's survival.
As long as...
I'm here,
you will never go in the OR with her.
Dr Yang, call Ms Jang...
and see if everything's ready.
What are you waiting for?
Be quick. We're doing this right away.
Should we begin, Dr Oh?
Operator.
Did you check the location of the tumour?
I don't need you to coach me.
This isn't a lab at a medical school.
That's good to hear.
Ommaya reservoir is something...
I've gone over hundreds of times in my head.
My wife...
passed away from the same thing.
My choice back then was a biopsy.
Even though the risk of dying from a biopsy is high,
I thought...
my wife would beat the odds.
I had no idea...
I'd be listening to your confession in an OR.
Promotions were coming up,
and I didn't dare violate a regulation...
the hospital wouldn't approve of.
It's ironic, isn't it?
That regret is helping you save this patient.
Injection.
It's done.
Check, please.
How much is the penalty?
Call Dr Lee Young Oh to my office.
Put an oxygen mask on him.
Sir, can you hear me?
Sir.
Dr Lee.
Does Patient Lee Sang Joon...
have to pass away like this?
Is that option...
still possible?
Dr Lee Young Oh.
By my authority, I ban you from treating patients.
I want to make it clear this time.
Since you don't seem to understand,
I'll tell you one more time. Listen!
I need a doctor who helps me make money...
more than one who treats diseases.
Did I...
make myself clear?
If so,
I'm sure...
that Dr Lee Young Oh is the one you really need.
You need to allow...
Dr Lee to treat patients again.
It's because...
he can promise you a profit...
that wasn't possible to make at Hyunsung...
and that no one has every imagined.
I am...
planning to make a donation to this hospital...
under Dr Lee Young Oh's name...
that's much more than the loss...
caused by the incident.
It seems that you'll have to allow me...
to treat patients again. Don't you think so?
Are you sure you understand what donation means?
If you survive,
would you be interested in having...
what you haven't had before?
Honour, hospitality, acclamation...
and true respect.
These are what you've been trying to get...
but couldn't...
while throwing harsh words to others.
Of course, it'll cost you a fortune, though.
The more it costs,
the more valuable it must be.
I like the idea.
- Dr Yang.
-  Yes?
How is the patient doing?
I've given him emergency treatment.
He refused treatment, didn't he?
Are you sure...
that you won't regret...
giving up like this?
I have said...
all that I had to say.
In my opinion,
you don't have a high pain tolerance.
People have different pain tolerances.
But there's no shame in having a low pain tolerance.
Even if you start treatment again,
it'll only become even more painful.
And your family,
who you love and adore,
will suffer even more.
Even if you get really lucky...
and have surgery,
there will be something more important than that.
It's to desperately seek to survive...
with your own will.
Are you sure...
that you have given up on this reality?
I'll take that as a yes.
I want to live.
Is this what you wanted to hear?
Why did you ask me that?
From the beginning,
I had no choice.
I couldn't afford the treatment.
Still,
I want to live.
Whatever it costs,
I want...
to live.
We found a benefactor.
Come in.
I'm here as the detective in charge...
to report to the doctor in charge.
Come on in and report to me properly.
He's a first-time offender...
and his predicament was taken into consideration.
We were able to get a settlement,
so he won't have to go to prison.
Thank you.
It's all thanks to you.
He said that...
meeting you was like winning the lottery.
Keep it just in case.
Call me if you win it.
You know we should split it evenly, right?
Do you really think...
that this can give hope...
to normal people?
Do you...
think that way, too?
That this can give hope?
Such a trivial thing like this?
Anticipating that tomorrow will be different.
To me, that's what hope is.
In that sense,
you're the most hopeful person I know.
You show me a different side to you whenever I see you.
I'll get going.
Don't forget...
to call me if you win the lottery.
You have to.
"Don't forget to call me."
"You have to call me..."
"if you win the lottery."
You're the most hopeful person I know.
You show me...
a different side to you whenever I see you.
Wait.
What...
Excuse me. Dr Lee.
I can't feel anything.
Nothing at all.
You were wrong.
Just as I thought,
I can't change.
I'll call you...
if I win the lottery.
That's Dr Lee Young Oh.
He is the son of Dr Lee Gun Myung.
He grew up better than I thought.
Is that so?
To me, he always seems dangerous.
If he finds out...
what his father did to him,
what will happen?
(Beautiful Mind)
I'm here to keep my promise.
Why do you keep doing this to me?
I need to learn how to sympathise with my patients.
It's normal for me to get angry, right?
I'm going to need you from now on.
Today could be the last day.
Who is it? Who hurt you?
Are you saying that you sympathised with the patient?
How?
You'll know when the surgery is done.
Stop it. Don't touch my patient.