Subtitles by DramaFever
Let go of me! Let go!
Let me go!
[Episode 10: On My Way to You]
Dad, you're surrounded by me!
I'm putting you down.
- You're so good!
- Dad, I can do this now.
- Can you do this too, Dad?
- Should I try it?
This?
What kinds of sounds did you
record on Jeju Island?
The sound of the waves, wind,
and people. Everything.
- Dad, do you like sounds?
- Yes.
Why?
- Because they disappear.
- Do you like things that disappear?
Once you acknowledge that
things are transient...
you don't waste your energy
on useless things.
From here to over there.
Let's see who can get there faster.
- Ready. Set. Go!
- Hey, that's foul play.
That's a foul. No!
Now in reverse.
How could you kiss me like that
and not even call me?
That son of a bitch. That bastard.
I'm not going to call him.
No matter what, I'm not going to
call him first this time.
Mom! Is this all the laundry you have?
Just give her something.
You just couldn't put it down
nicely for me.
If he doesn't call me
by today, that's it!
I'm going to end it for real!
Hey.
It's nice out.
Let's get something to eat.
I don't want to waste a single day.
Being in jail has taught me some things.
Come. Are you busy?
- I just have some things to get done.
- What is it?
I need to do laundry.
Never mind. I've got it.
I'll see you later.
Okay.
Who is it?
Because of whom are you acting this way?
Is it because of Tae Jin
or the guy next door?
Is it Tae Jin or the guy next door?
I need to go out.
Mom, please wring them out
and hang them up to dry.
I won't accept either of them!
I'm going to kill you
if you date either one of them!
Mr. Park Do Kyung isn't
picking up his phone either.
Please give me his address.
Here you go.
I thought something had happened to you.
Why didn't you come in today?
I'm not your doctor starting today.
I'm just a friend from the neighborhood.
I live around here.
I can talk with ease, right?
Sure. Go right ahead.
I've been thinking all night long
about how I should explain this to you.
Listen carefully.
You are in a car accident,
and you're lying on the road right now.
Is it confusing
because I said "right now"?
I understand. It must be.
You think time passes in the order of
past, present, and future, right?
That's not true.
If you hypnotize a 30-year-old person
and take him back in time by 100 years
a different voice comes out of him.
It means he's in a different life.
This works in reverse too.
If you take him forward
in time by 100 years
a different voice comes out of him.
So what does this mean?
It means your mind
isn't constrained by time.
Only your body is constrained by time.
Your mind knows
the complete story of your life.
To your mind, life is like
a completed scenario.
Do I seem crazy?
If I do, tell me. I'll stop.
It's interesting. Keep going.
I've been dying to talk about this.
But I feared I would be seen as a weirdo.
Listen to me carefully.
Spiritually enlightened people
are sensitive to their minds.
But you're not necessarily spiritually
enlightened. You're a special case.
You can't foresee
everything from the future
but you see very particular episodes.
About one woman.
Right now, you're in a car accident
and you're missing that woman
before your death.
I'm confusing you again
with the term "right now," right?
All right. Let's say "soon."
Although the mind
isn't constrained by time
we see things from
our bodies' perspective.
To make it easier, let's say "soon."
You'll soon be in a car accident
and you're going to miss that woman
as you stare into the night sky.
Because your feelings
for her are so strong
you started seeing visions of her
even before you met her in real life.
Why?
Because our mind knows everything
about our life stories.
It's not very hard for
our minds to do this.
So in conclusion...
I'm going to die soon
and I'm going to miss that woman
while I'm dying?
You're a weirdo, right?
I'm sorry.
I don't think I can make it today.
Something urgent came up at work.
No. I think it'll take a long time.
Yeah. I'm sorry.
See you.
Do Kyung.
Let's try to get through this together.
There could be a different conclusion!
Do Kyung!
So in conclusion...
I'm going to die soon
and I'm going to miss that woman
while I'm dying?
Aren't you coming?
I'm not coming.
(In French)
Aren't you coming home?
How long are you going to
get drunk like this?
My life is too embarrassing...
for me to live in my sober state.
Congratulations.
And celebration.
Congratulations to Soo Kyung.
Congratulation--
Am I getting married?
How did you know?
This guy I know wants to marry you!
You want to die, don't you?
Hear me out.
His ideal type is a strong woman!
A woman who hits, scratches,
grills, and kicks him.
Apparently he goes crazy
over a woman like this.
And importantly, he sleeps sitting down.
Isn't that great?
He owns a 52 peyong-sized apartment
and has an annual salary
of 220 million won.
Both of his parents are deceased
and he has no older or younger sisters.
According to himself,
he's a great-looking man.
Just go with the flow and get married.
He said you just need to
bring a spoon.
Seeing the perfect man for you
put me in such a great mood today.
So I had something to drink.
You crazy bastard!
Am I a man to you?
Talking to me while peeing...
Even if you don't see me as a woman...
What? What did I do?
You shouldn't do this to me.
I'm a woman too! I'm a woman!
I guess you're a woman too.
She's being shy.
I was just saying she should go
with the flow and get married.
Congratulations. And celebration.
Soo Kyung is finally getting married.
Oh my god. He kissed you on the street?
He has exploded. He must like you a lot!
But he hasn't called me since.
Just wait. He'll call you.
After getting burned by Oh Hae Young,
he's with another Oh Hae Young.
Based on his boring personality,
he probably can't accept that easily.
- And you two even know each other.
- It's not even a big deal.
You hesitated at first too
because he dated Oh Hae Young.
He likes you for sure
but I think he needs some time
to gather his thoughts before
he can be with you in front of everyone.
And he doesn't seem like the type
to date you in secret or something.
How does he hold himself back?
I can't. Not even for a single day.
The longing...
How does he hold that back?
Just wait.
Don't barge in and push him away.
You need to give him some time to
gather his thoughts and make a decision.
Listen to your big sis.
He has fallen for you.
He'll come to you soon.
Why are you holding back?
How is it possible for you to hold back?
If you like me, you like me.
Why are you being so cautious?
Right now, you're in a car accident
and you're missing that woman
before your death.
Are you okay?
Hey. Don't touch him!
Where are you?
Park Hoon!
- Wait. Hold on.
- Are you okay?
I've missed you.
Me too.
Should we just live together
starting today?
You're so scared.
Thank you. Have a nice day.
I'm so happy that you're my boyfriend.
Beyond happy!
If you date other women,
I'm going to kill you.
- Do you like it that much?
- Yeah.
It has an amazing ending.
After he has killed everyone
he finds his bottle opener,
all covered in blood.
He then opens a bottle of beer
with that bottle opener and drinks it.
I could present it to
a producer right now, right?
Right now. Show it to them right now.
This is going to hit big.
There's a producer who
works with new directors.
I worked as a sound producer for
that person's movie not too long ago.
As soon as she approves this,
I'll instantly become a famous director.
It's a woman?
Half of the world's population
is women. But you're my only woman.
Didn't you say your mom is a producer?
- Why won't you work with your mom?
- My mom?
- Nah. That won't work.
- Why?
- Just because.
- What do you mean?
- Hello.
- Welcome.
Because of my neck disc pain
I can't even play golf
in this beautiful weather.
- Just doing this here...
- Good shot!
- Let's go.
- Okay.
He's a master in flattery.
I was going to fire him next month.
But I should just fire him this month.
- Let's play a game today.
- Sure. I would love that.
If AlphaGo and I play a game of omok,
who do you think will win?
AlphaGo would win for sure.
- How about a flicking game?
- AlphaGo.
What type of game
could I win against him?
Why even bother?
Just buy one and use it for yourself.
That works. This is why I like you.
I like you...
But I heard you almost
got married to Do Kyung?
Is this true?
Why did you guys break up?
You don't have to tell me
if you don't want to.
That's not what's important.
If I get married to Do Kyung's mother
that means my past stepdaughter
and a future stepson had a thing.
Although you two are not blood-related...
You know how the gossipers are.
They make up lies and let them circulate.
Do Kyung's mother was adamant
that you two were done.
Is it over between you two? For sure?
I'm okay now.
If I see you on the streets,
I can now smile and happily greet you.
Anything more than this would be weird.
It would be right to end things here.
You two aren't over yet. Am I right?
It is over.
But I still like him.
I thought it would be over
once my scars had been healed.
I thought I would be able
to go my own way
once I were healed.
I feel like throwing up.
Listening to the high-pitched voice
of an actress for a month.
Whenever I have to work with actors
with annoying voices
it's a pain until
I'm done with that movie.
It must be.
Please let my ears rest with your voice.
There was a man named Park Do Kyung.
Out of all the voices in the world
he liked Oh Hae Young's the most.
Whenever he heard Hae Young's voice
he slowly fell asleep.
He loved her so much.
Very passionately.
[Passionate Bottle Opener]
I'll take my time and look through it.
But I think we should change the title.
It sounds so low-class.
Yes. But if you read the scenario,
you'll see how fitting it is.
It's about men's fight over pride,
caused by a single bottle opener.
The pettiness of men. Noir of men.
Sounds fun.
Sure. It'll be really good.
By the way. About my brother...
please keep this a secret.
By the way,
what is Director Park doing nowadays?
He's the same as always.
Being temperamental and fussy.
You're coming to
CEO Jang's 70th birthday, right?
- Why would I go?
- What do you mean?
You've used him when you needed him.
Now you won't go to his birthday party?
I heard he did you a favor.
I heard he helped you
ruin someone's business.
He has a relationship with your mother.
How could you not go?
Don't just give him
one or two million won.
Bring him something nice and rare.
Not some common brand product.
So that I'm not embarrassed. Okay?
Excuse me.
Are you done with the recording?
It's almost finished.
I swear.
I think he's going to introduce me
to his people at this party.
- As his fiancée.
- Isn't this enough?
- Two marriages weren't enough for you?
- What's wrong with you?
This isn't just for my sake.
You could have a rich man
as your father.
Am I a little boy?
Why do I need a father at my age?
Other people would kill to
have him on their side.
You should be grateful.
You can just come home with your family
and live a normal life now.
You're at that age now.
That old man will constantly have
women problems--
What if I'm dirt poor when I'm old?
Are you going to take care of me?
How much could you give me every month?
You bastard.
His "women problem" is all a rumor.
He didn't see any other woman
once we started dating!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry!
I didn't know it was you.
So what if it was someone else?
It would have been okay to hit him?
That's not what I meant. I'm sorry!
Welcome.
Please give me an ice Americano
with two shots.
Sure.
This is ridiculous.
It's ready.
- What are you doing?
- Oh my. Hi.
Long time no see.
I occasionally hear about you
from Hae Young.
You must be busy nowadays.
Are you reading anything good?
He told me to keep this
a secret from you.
- Can't you just forget you saw anything?
- Is it that bad?
You can't expect much
from new directors.
This just sounds like Hoon.
You were reading it with contempt.
I wasn't reading it with contempt.
But you must know too.
His level of writing.
I feel a little offended.
I'm reading it for him
because he asked me to.
It feels like I've committed
a grave crime against you.
["I... just came for what's mine."]
[Scene No. 2: Nighttime]
I'm starving to death.
I was going to eat pig feet after
Anna is done with her part-time job.
I should just eat ramen.
Do you want some?
Do you want it? Or no?
Don't you dare take some of mine later.
Whom have you given this to?
What?
[Passionate Bottle Opener]
How did you get this?
Who gave it to you?
- Whom have you given this to?
- Just to Producer Kim Hee Ran.
Do Kyung, I...
I want to give it a shot. I'm not
saying I'll quit my job right now.
I'll take my time with it and...
- Don't do it.
- Do Kyung...
How many years have you
worked as film crew?
You got paid only
five to six million won a year.
You had to adulate directors
and do all the hard work.
They never even fed you.
You had to freeload off others.
And every time you present your script,
you have to beg like a beggar.
You get belittled like no other.
That's what you did for eight years.
You want to do all of that again?
Do Kyung, but still...
If you learn some skills from me,
you'll be able to make a living.
And you won't get belittled.
- I still want to give it a shot!
- Your writing is embarrassing!
You can't do anything with this.
It's embarrassing.
So get a hold of yourself.
How could you say that to your brother?
Scripts that are worse than mine are
produced into movies just fine.
People come watch them too.
What did you say? Embarrassing?
Life itself is shameful! You know?
Being alive is shameful.
Eating is shameful too.
And it's shameful to hear
that I'm an embarrassment.
What's so wrong with being embarrassed?
Embarrassment isn't a death sentence.
You can't stand being embarrassed, right?
You just can't, right?
I won't die from embarrassment.
That's why I'm a winner. You know?
I'm going to get pushed around by people.
Listen to them criticize my writing.
And live with embarrassment!
So just let me be!
I can't watch you
get belittled by people!
So just quickly learn how to
produce sound from me.
Do Kyung.
You think people respect you, right?
No. They badmouth you.
What's the point of being that proud?
You only live once. So let me do
whatever I want to with my life!
What's the matter?
What is it?
Aren't you going to tell me?
My brother said
my scenario was embarrassing.
Let's kill him, Park Do Kyung.
That son of a bitch thinks
he's so much better.
I will kill him.
Hey, hey!
- Hey!
- Don't stop me!
I will kill him.
Let me go!
Damn Park Do Kyung!
It's so frustrating.
Park Do Kyung is so irritating.
You think people respect you, right?
They all badmouth you.
What's the point of being that proud?
Do you like things that disappear?
Once you acknowledge that
things are transient
you don't waste your energy
on useless things.
Dad!
Dad! Dad!
- Dad!
- Yes.
- Dad.
- Yes?
What sounds did you get from DMZ?
Well...
The sound that soldiers make when doing
a routine check around the wire fence.
And the announcement from North Korea.
And the bird sounds.
What sound do you like the most, Dad?
Well, for me...
I like your voice the most.
It's Children's Day tomorrow.
Are we going anywhere?
- Where shall we go?
- Well...
You can't stand your wife
but you still like to see your kids, huh?
You're bothered to stop
by the house occasionally.
Gosh, if it weren't for
your job acquiring sounds
I wonder what other excuse you
would come up with not to come home.
You chose the right career.
Don't you think?
- Do Kyung, hurry up.
- I'm coming.
- Dad!
- Do Kyung, it's dangerous.
- Play on this side.
- I will.
Dad.
Is there a sound
when a butterfly flutters its wings?
Why don't you listen for it?
- It doesn't make any sound.
- Listen carefully.
Dad.
Dad!
Dad! Dad!
Wake up!
Dad, wake up!
Dad.
I can't walk any farther.
Wake up now.
Once you acknowledge that
things are transient
you don't waste your energy
on useless things.
Why did you leave without asking me?
Why?
I will never leave ever!
[The Guy Next Door]
I was going to wait
five rings before I answered it.
I ended up answering after three rings.
I'm just too easy. Don't you think?
If you've called, you should talk.
Why aren't you saying anything?
Are you still testing the waters?
Come here.
You think I'm so easy that
I'd come if you ask me?
I miss you.
I'm so easy that I'd come if you ask me.
Now.
What else do you want me to do?
Can you give me a hug?
How come you don't ask
where we're going?
It doesn't matter where we're going.
Because I'm easy.
I'm glad you're easy.
Do you know how hard it is
for a woman to decide to be easy?
If you have a change of heart
I will kill you.
How come you're not answering?
You're planning on having
a change of heart again, huh?
I won't have a change of heart.
Yeah!
I'm loving this!
Ah, it's cold!
When did you start liking me?
Do you want me to guess?
When you first met me.
- No.
- Then when?
When you said you voted for yourself
in the election for class president.
What? Why? It's so embarrassing.
You had the courage
to admit it was embarrassing.
I liked it.
So random.
I have so many embarrassing stories.
Do you want to hear more?
Well...
I got 20 out of 100 on my first
spelling test in elementary school.
And...
In my freshmen year at college
on the way to a school trip,
I had to stop the bus for a bathroom.
Gosh, that was so embarrassing.
Well, I've fallen out of a bus once.
You know how high
the last seats get on the bus.
I was dozing off in
the last seat by the window.
I fell out of the bus,
but what's amazing was
I wasn't hurt at all.
I was so embarrassed
that I ran to get away.
Thanks.
Wow, you will drink tonight?
Ouch. Hot.
- Give it. I will do it.
- It's okay. It will go away.
What if I say it hurts right here?
What would you do
if I ask you to blow on my booboo?
I would kill you.
I knew you'd say that.
What if I ask you to feed me saying "Ah"?
No, I won't do that.
So no worries and drink up.
Don't cut it. Eat it as a whole piece.
Wow, it's so juicy. Try.
No, just eat it without any sauce.
It's tastier that way.
It's good, right?
The time when we had
pork belly with your parents.
Yes?
- It was nice.
- What?
After you rejected me so hard...
Was it fun to see
my parents put on an act?
Your mom said...
I wanted to thank you
for the security bar last time.
I've been wanting to treat you.
It took us this long. Have some.
She put the meat on my rice.
Why were you touched by such a thing?
It was nothing.
Just say the word.
I will put meat or kimchi
on your rice at every meal.
Go ahead.
I will spend all night
putting these on your plate.
This may be too big.
Hello, miss.
(in French)
You've come home early today.
Wow, off to a hot date?
My dress code for tonight is...
Rooftop party.
Rooftop party, hey!
You know what it is, right?
In Korean, it's a rooftop party.
All the hot ladies
show up there these days.
See you later.
Rooftop party.
Rooftop party!
- See you.
Damn.
(in French)
It's farther back there.
- Hurry.
- We will be late.
- Shall we go?
- We've just finished our shift.
We're serious.
Gosh, you're the lady without a face...
Let's go, shall we?
Let's go.
Please slow down.
- Did you have dinner yet?
- Pardon?
I am... proud of you guys.
Ladies of the neighborhood.
Juice.
Have a seat.
We're really okay.
You've escorted me home safely.
I can't just let you leave.
Please.
We're really okay.
I said please have a seat.
Take your time and enjoy.
Can I ask you something?
How many men have you slept with?
Well, back in our days...
I am... 44 years old.
The number of men I've slept with is...
Two and a half...
I'm guessing you've slept with
more men than I have, huh?
Once I sleep with a man
I fall in love with him.
It's not that I sleep with him
after I fall in love with him.
Once I sleep with someone...
I fall in love with that person.
But...
Why in the world did it
happen to be that loser?
Everybody says I'm cool and chic and all.
But I don't know how to be any of those.
Once I sleep with someone
shouldn't I start
a relationship with him?
Out of all these bodies
that inhabit this vast universe
and take into account the chances
that two bodies would collide
wouldn't that mean those two bodies
are destined to be together forever?
But...
why in the world does
he have to be this loser...
who sleeps with
different women every night?
Why? Impossible!
Why that bastard?! Why?
Get out.
Get out. Get out!
It's that way, not that way.
Get out. Get out. Get out!
Get out!
Ever since I first met that bastard
at the age of six
I knew right away
what a bastard he was.
I was chasing him around
calling him brother all week.
Do you know what he said after a week?
You go back to your home.
But I'm still living
in the same house now.
You two have the same last name.
Aren't you two biological brothers?
Come on. Those with the same
last name are all siblings, then?
In order not to show
that we have different fathers
my mom must have tried to marry
a man with the same last name.
Let's live together.
If I tell my brother I'll live with you
he'll go crazy on me.
I was debating what I should say...
But I don't care about him anymore.
He's not really my brother, either.
I have the guts now.
I won't live in that house anymore.
I wanted to kill that man earlier.
Now I want to give him a hug.
Whom do you want to give a hug?
- Mr. Park.
- Why him?
I wanted to kill him when I thought
he was your real brother.
Now that you two
are not really related...
it feels as if he really loves you.
I want to give him a hug to thank him.
Seriously! What have you heard until now?
He's such a son of a bitch.
Oh no.
It's a good thing you're my boyfriend.
I'm glad that you are in my arms.
If you were with some other woman,
I'd be very sad for you.
Go away. Now we're even.
- Come on.
- Go away. I don't like that.
- Ah! Stop it.
You seem very drunk.
Shall we go in someplace?
I already called for a driver.
What?
Wait a second. Wow.
Wow. I'm totally sober now.
How can you possibly
call for a driver now?
Does it make sense to call for
a driver at a time like this?
Why not?
No, I mean... think about it.
Huh? Think about it.
From here to Seoul, it will cost
us about 200,000 won at least.
- It's 300,000.
- 300,000?
It's 300,000, not 30,000?
Like you can find money when you
dig a hole in the ground, huh?
I'm so baffled that I can't even talk.
Why don't you ask for a discount then?
Right now...
that's not what
we're talking about, is it?
Well, when we're this good like now
we came to the shore and had a drink.
We kissed, hugged, and did other things.
Does it make sense that
you called for a driver now?
Are you asking me to drive then?
Is it Hongik University or Gangnam here?
Where can you possibly
find a driver here?
Hello, did you call for a driver?
- You're going to Seoul, right?
- Yes.
- Can I have the key?
- Sure.
Hold on.
Isn't 300,000 a bit too much?
With that amount, you know...
I will drive you for 200,000.
I was going back to Seoul anyway.
Or 180,000?
Fine. 150,000 then.
Let's go for 150,000, shall we?
I need to make something too.
[Come in to rest. Last motel]
Women shouldn't sleep at motels.
If that's true
only men go to all these motels
by themselves then?
That's enough.
You're being so picky.
When the woman tries to be easy...
Let's have our first night together
at a nice place next time.
When will it be?
Let's go.
Let's go all the way.
[Many thanks to Lee Pil Mo
and Lee Yu Ri.]
Subtitles by DramaFever