Subtitles by DramaFever
[Another Oh Hae Young]
Let's go.
Let's go all the way.
[Episode 11: In pain, in pain...]
Hae Young isn't picking up her phone.
Why would she answer your calls?
I'm sorry.
I've done wrong.
There's no need for you to be like this.
Leave.
I can't accept you.
Get up, okay?
Come on. Get up.
I heard you've been through a lot.
How did this even happen to you?
Hae Young probably slept over
at her Pyngchang-dong place.
She's been living there
by herself for some time now.
Hurry up and come in!
What are you doing?
All right!
I... Just...
- Here you go. Thank you.
- Thank you. Thanks.
My entire body aches.
It feels like I've just traveled abroad.
You should take the morning off
if you're too tired.
Isadora will kill me if I do.
I have to notify her well in advance.
Oh my! I'm late. I need to get ready
and go! I'll see you after work!
I'll see you later.
I've been doing fine these days.
Is this "Memento" or something?
Oh my. Where is it?
Hey. Where did I leave my car?
Haven't you seen it?
Are you going to work
or coming back from it?
My goodness.
I need to...
have a go at Park Do Kyung today
and leave the house.
But...
you've made me look ridiculous like this.
What am I supposed to do?
Hey.
What time did I come home last night?
I said what time did I come home?
How would I know?
I don't even know when I came home.
Let me use your phone.
Hey. Is Attorney Kim there?
Let me talk to him.
Hey. Who in the world
did I drink with yesterday?
I don't have my phone. Or my car.
I don't have anything. What's going on?
- Sorry.
- Do it properly! With your two hands!
Please put some on for me.
Have you lost it?
Don't you have hands?
I'm going to temporarily
pretend like I don't have one.
I wake up and find out
this is what she has done to me.
She says she'll kill me
if I remove them.
I was going to fabulously
have a go at you and leave.
But it's embarrassing to do so
with this hand.
And it would be funny to do so
with one hand behind my back.
That's why
I'm not leaving the house today.
Just come at me. Then leave.
I can't just have a go at you.
That won't look cool.
I'm going to do it the right way.
I've planned all of my movements out.
I've meticulously thought out
my facial expressions too.
You just wait.
Once I get these removed
I'm going to have a go at you.
The right way.
Maybe you two should fight
with gloves on.
Do you want me to give you
some leather gloves?
I feel like I shouldn't
fight with him now.
I just get this vibe.
Apparently my car is parked
in front of Yanyang Prison.
Why did they say you went that far?
According to my witnesses
from our gathering...
With a gold digger
who was on a prison furlough...
Who called you a gold digger?
Honey, you're just a flower.
A flower. A flower.
Apparently I tried to get her released.
Begging and crying...
That's what I did before letting her go.
You piece of trash.
You. Go back to your house.
Don't set a foot in this house!
You're dirty.
What do you mean dirty? Hm?
Don't you think that's
taking things too far?
How flawlessly clean are you?
You had a thing with a married man!
- I was at least in love!
- I was the one who was in love!
- I was in love at that moment!
- Really? Because I was the one in love!
- Do you hear me!
- You never do!
No, no, no.
You're always yapping!
Always!
- I'm here to see Ms. Oh Hae Young.
- Please hold on.
Which Oh Hae Young?
There are two of them.
I'm here to see
Assistant Manager Oh Hae Young.
Please hold on.
Someone is here for Assistant Manager Oh.
Could you check if she's here?
Okay. I've got it.
- She's not here yet.
- Is that so?
All right.
Hello.
We've met before with Hae Young.
Is that so?
Who is he?
The man Hae Young was going to marry.
I've seen him a couple of times.
- Let's go, Manager Oh.
- All right. Let's go.
Are you still mad at me?
I thought you had forgiven me.
Do I need to beg you more
for forgiveness?
I will. Until your anger subsides.
Please forgive me.
Let's meet up tonight.
I have something to tell you.
Let's hang out tonight after work.
I think I'll be a little late today.
Why?
I'm meeting up with someone.
- Will you be late?
- I don't think I'll be that late.
I'm briefly meeting with
the guy I was going to marry.
It's not that we got back together,
but we did kind of see each other.
So I think I should meet with him
and end things.
See me before you meet with him.
Finishing things off
with him comes first.
I should come first. Talk to me first.
It won't take long. It'll be brief.
Meet with me first.
I have something to tell you.
What's with you all of a sudden?
Talk to me first.
I'll stop by your work.
Did you plan something for tonight?
Was I supposed to dress up
all nice and pretty today?
I'm telling you this ahead of time.
Don't do things like bringing flowers
and getting down on your knees.
So embarrassing...
And don't plan things with
the staff at a restaurant either.
Don't put on a weird show
in front of a lot of people.
I just can't understand women
who like those things.
- Stop overreacting.
- All right.
- I'll see you later.
- Okay.
I won't push you away anymore
out of guilt.
I just want to love you.
No matter what I tell you
please don't abandon me.
Please hold onto me tightly.
You blew me off yesterday too.
What's wrong?
- Let's hang out for a little bit.
- I'm sorry.
Let's meet up tomorrow.
I'll keep my promise tomorrow.
For sure.
I have something to tell you too.
Not even for a few minutes?
Let's meet up tomorrow. I'm sorry.
I don't get why I have to
keep apologizing to you.
All right. I'll see you tomorrow then.
- No need for you to be sorry.
- All right.
I've got it.
It's ready.
I just want to give something
to you before I go.
I'll see you in front of your workplace.
I'll get going then.
See you guys tomorrow.
- See you tomorrow.
- Bye.
I'm outside. Where are you?
Are you all right?
At least tell me why
you're doing this to me.
What have I ever done to you?
I've looked into everything,
but I couldn't find anything.
You aren't related to me in any way.
Why the hell did you ruin my business?
You bastard! You bastard.
What are you doing?
Let go! Let go of him!
Hae Young.
Get away from that bastard.
I said get away from him!
Who do you think you are?
Punching this guy!
Do you still think I'm your fiancée?
Since when were you two this close?
Why should I tell you?
This is the bastard
who ruined my business.
He's the one who ruined my business
and made me go to jail!
Hey.
Did you send me to jail
because you liked her?
Is that it?
To prevent us from getting married?
I went to see CEO Jang,
who ruined my business.
I asked him why he would retrieve
his investment for no reason.
Then this is what CEO Jang told me.
He said that bastard Park Do Kyung
had asked him to do it.
I thought long and hard about it,
but he and I weren't involved in any way.
There was this one thing
a lawyer told me while I was in jail.
He said Park Do Kyung did what he did
because he thought
I was getting married to Oh Hae Young.
My "Hae" is written like this.
Oh Hae Young.
Hae Young.
How do you know that bastard?
How long have you known him?
Did you know that he liked you?
It wasn't me.
What do you mean?
Let's go.
I'll explain everything.
You're a man! How could you stab another
man in the back and steal his woman?
Stand up, you bastard.
Get up!
Are you a human being? Huh? Are you?
How could you laugh hysterically
after breaking off your marriage?
[Dad is now abandoning you.
Mom has agreed. Live well. With decency.]
So all those things I've been through
were because of Oh Hae Young?
Because Park Do Kyung
was in love with Oh Hae Young?
[The Man Next Door]
[15 missed calls]
Who were you in a fight with?
You look cool.
Tell me. Tell me right now.
I won't be as shocked
if you tell me right now.
Before I fall for you even more,
tell me right now.
Why did you call your wedding off
the day before, big sis?
You...
You!
Where are you going?
Where are you headed?
Hello, sir.
Hey. Park Hoon. Where...
- Why are we doing this?
- I don't know.
She broke off her wedding
with Do Kyung like that
and was about to get married
to another man?
What a bitch!
Good for Do Kyung for
breaking the wedding up.
You idiots.
Have you been listening to me?
He didn't break off
that Oh Hae Young's wedding.
He broke off another
Oh Hae Young's wedding!
Who's another Oh Hae Young?
- There are two Oh Hae Youngs. Two!
- How could there be two of them?
- Does she repeat what the other says?
- They have the same name! You idiot!
You should have said that
from the beginning!
We were confused because you said
there are two Oh Hae Youngs we know!
So that Oh Hae Young was
playing a double role?
I thought you had understood everything.
Also, get that nail art removed!
- So annoying.
- She said she'll kill me if I do!
So whose wedding
did he break up exactly?
So to be clear, he broke up the wedding
of a stranger! That Oh Hae Young!
So what's the problem then?
She wasn't the woman he loved
and was a complete stranger.
But the problem is
Do Kyung has fallen for her.
He likes her now. Okay?
But you said that's not
the woman he likes!
Anyway, that's what has happened!
So we're...
Hey. Forget it.
Don't try to understand it.
- Don't you dare try to understand it!
- This is the most difficult thing ever!
- It's so freaking confusing.
- I've understood everything.
Seriously?
Do you understand all of this?
So ultimately, what we have to do is
just kidnap the person he wants to see.
Which Oh Hae Young
are you going to kidnap?
- You're going to complicate things more.
- Of course the prettier one.
You're going to complicate things
even more that way!
Does he like the ugly one?
I think I started this whole mess.
I told it to Park Do Kyung.
My friend has gotten very lucky.
He was even on the news and stuff.
His name is CEO Han Tae Jin.
Which high school did she go to?
That's right. He even asked me
which high school you went to.
He must have thought
you were that Oh Hae Young.
Oh no...
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
What to do...
I've found Oh Hae Young.
You know who I am.
Hurry up and come over here.
Park Hoon! It's not that Oh Hae Young!
You idiot!
Hey! Pick him up! Quickly!
Bunch of idiots!
Don't do anything! So useless!
So are we just going to
chase after Do Kyung all night long?
We need to do something!
Aren't you a lawyer? What are you doing?
We were all supposed to get away today!
- Have you forgotten about it already?
- Have you?
- Hurry. Come on! Let's go!
- Let's go.
- Come on! Hurry!
- Step on the gas.
- Here we go!
- Let's go!
- Let's go! Yeah!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
Go! Go! Charge forward!
Hey. The sun has risen.
Hey. Wake up!
Wake up! Get up!
Wow! It's the beach!
- Nice! The beach!
- Yay!
Do Kyung. Get up. We're at the beach.
- We're at the beach!
- The beach!
Don't you even think about it.
I'm going to kill you.
All right.
Take his clothes off! Go! Go!
Just like the wave that comes and goes
women come and go too.
You're with them one moment.
Then you're not the next.
Damn. Your comment sucks.
This is why you don't have a girlfriend.
That was a little
embarrassing for me too.
But we need to say something!
- Should I just do nothing then?
- Yeah. Stop being gross.
Fine. I won't do anything.
You all try to console him then.
- Console him for what?
- Don't you know?
We've come all this way because
Director Park got dumped by a woman!
- Hey!
- What?
- My goodness!
- I've been dumped over 20 times!
What? What now?
Hey. Step on him! Come on!
That's enough. You might kill him.
Hey. There are women at 9 o'clock.
- Hey! Hey! There are women!
- You're like an animal.
Have you lost something by chance?
That ideal type
you've been searching for.
Don't you think
you'll find him over there?
Hey, there are three more ladies.
We have the perfect matching number.
You go have fun.
We won't have enough men
if you don't join us.
Just sit there and do nothing, okay?
The fact that we've met
as a group of six on this beach
means that we were destined to meet.
- I'm Lee Jin Sang.
- I'm Oh Hae Young.
- Pardon?
As in Hae.
Is your real name seriously Oh Hae Young?
Yes.
- Seriously as in Hae?
- Yes.
- So what happened? Hurry up.
- Say it now.
Assistant Manager Oh
went after Manager Oh.
I really thought
she was going to kill her.
Do you know why she did that?
There had to be a reason.
I have no idea why.
She came back and just cried.
She was actually like a crazy woman.
- Your call is being redirected...
- Gosh.
Her phone is switched off.
I wonder what Manager Oh did to her.
What a bitch.
Something must have happened
between you two.
- You were beat up without a reason?
- I don't know.
So you're saying that
she did that without a reason?
Isn't it always the fault of
the person who threw a punch first?
Why are you taking her side?
What do you mean I'm taking her side?
Since she isn't here
I'm asking you instead.
You know I wouldn't do something bad
enough to someone to deserve an attack.
Then why are you taking her side?
Why do you keep saying
that I'm taking her side?
You are taking her side.
Every time.
You know that it's not true that
I left because I didn't love Do Kyung.
Then why are you acting so harsh?
When you're this harsh to me
why are you taking her side
when you have no relation to her?
Explain to me why you did
what you did yesterday.
You need to explain.
If you eat that uncooked ramen
and drink water like that
your stomach will feel bad.
What is it? Tell me.
What is it now?
- Mom.
- What?
When I was in high school
do you remember there was
another girl with the same name?
I remember.
What about it?
- What was she like?
- What do you mean?
She had big round eyes.
What about her?
Why suddenly her?
All the boys liked her.
Because of the boys who liked her,
our windows were smashed a lot.
Bitch! Have a good life!
Hey! The pretty Oh Hae Young
doesn't live here!
The plain Oh Hae Young lives here!
What is odd is...
I never received
candy or flowers by mistake.
How come a rock smashed
our windows every time?
Don't you think it's odd?
It seems that I was born to
take all the bad luck for her.
Crazy. What nonsense.
Who says you are, huh?
If the universe weren't on my side
wouldn't it make me so pathetic?
I'm on your side.
Why would you be pathetic?
Mom, let's move.
To a rural place, not Seoul.
If we move to a rural place
wouldn't it make me seem
like a better catch?
If I live in a place where
no one is better than me
wouldn't it help me
feel good about myself?
What is it? What happened?
Tell me what it is.
Don't just keep it to yourself
and tell me this time.
I was crying for my friend last night.
My eyes are all puffy today.
I tend to get puffy easily.
I read your scenario.
You didn't learn how to write
a scenario professionally, did you?
- No, it wasn't my major at all.
- Fine.
Scenarios written by people
who were trained are kind of boring.
They often use boring lines
and obvious characters.
This needs some modification.
But I'm a loyal friend.
I don't feel comfortable working with
the brother of the guy my friend hates.
My friend is Oh Hae Young.
Park Do Kyung broke up her wedding.
I wonder if you know what I'm saying.
- I do.
- Do you?
- Yes.
- When did you know?
Yesterday.
Everybody found out yesterday, huh?
I'm really ticked off right now.
I'm the one who started the whole thing.
I'm the one who talked to
him about Oh Hae Young.
But is she the only
Oh Hae Young in the world?
It's such a common name, right?
Back in school, there were
five or six Hae Youngs.
Because he fixated on her that much
he thought there was only
one Oh Hae Young, huh?
Plus, after he broke up
her wedding like that
how could he lead her on
without saying anything?
Is he crazy or what?
I'm sorry to say this...
I was so shocked
when I heard that yesterday.
I pushed him to the ocean to kill him.
He survived.
He came out begging for forgiveness.
I told him to go beg for
her forgiveness no matter what.
If he weren't my brother
I would've put on a leash
on his neck and dragged him to her.
You should have dragged him.
Should I? It's not too late now.
By the way.
What do you have on your nails?
- It was my girlfriend...
- Take them off. It bothers me.
It does, right? Should I then?
These don't come off easily.
They do come off easily.
- Hey!
- Listen to me first!
Listen to what?
Hold on!
Why did you take them off? Why?
You know how important they are.
Why did you take them off?
I had them on for three days.
How much longer did you want them on?
How could you do that to a guy's nails?
It means that you have a girlfriend.
Shall I put a tattoo on
your forehead that says you're mine?
I go around and tell people that.
I tell people that I have a girlfriend.
I don't need to have
such things on my nails.
What is it? You think I'd cheat on you?
Do I look like someone
who would cheat on you?
Yes, you do look like one.
- You really look like one.
- Then let's break up.
- You're pushing it, huh?
- You're the one who is pushing it here.
What girl would hit
a guy's head this much?
I'm 33 now.
I don't know how it was going out
with someone about your age.
You colored the nails of
a 33-year-old man.
You hit me with a book.
I won't tolerate such behavior!
I told you not to leave me after a fight.
I told you that it wasn't
what a 33-year-old should do.
Come back. If you don't,
I wouldn't leave you alone.
Come back!
Fine! Walk away!
By the way, I can sense things
faster than anybody.
I already sensed something was going on.
Don't do anything embarrassing.
Okay?
What does she mean
she sensed something?
What did I ever do?
[I'm sorry.]
I'm sorry.
I waited thinking
you'd write more after "I'm sorry."
I thought you were taking
time to write and delete.
I waited for a long time.
I've waited for two hours.
How can it be one single
sentence of "I'm sorry"?
How can you end the sentence this way?
You've gone mad, right?
You don't know what's going on, do you?
You've gone mad, haven't you?
Where are you?
I'm sorry.
I was wrong.
I was such a coward.
You've managed to say
more than sorry now.
You must have been thinking about
more to say on your way here, huh?
I'm sorry.
Are you sorry?
I hate that sentence so much.
Can we go somewhere inside and talk?
Why? Are you embarrassed by me?
If I see myself in the mirror...
I look like a moron.
I deserve what happened to me.
I look so gullible.
I got caught in the middle
of your love quarrel.
I look that naive.
I hate myself.
I want to have a different face
and be someone else.
So I put on this much makeup
hoping I'd feel better.
But you're saying you're sorry?
You're just sorry?
I'm very sorry.
What are you sorry about?
Why are you sorry?
How sorry are you?
Let's go somewhere and talk.
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
You loved Oh Hae Young, so you
wanted to break up her wedding.
Why didn't you tell me that you
ended up breaking up my wedding?
I did want to tell you.
But I couldn't do that to you
when you were already down.
You said you were compared to
Oh Hae Young all through high school.
You said your life was this tough.
You wondered how her life was.
I just couldn't tell you the truth.
I couldn't tell you
not to make it even worse.
Do you know what hurts?
You wanted to break up her wedding
until recently because you loved her.
You threw a rock at her,
but it ended up hitting me.
While I was in pain from the rock,
you were thinking about her.
I was confessing my love
for you without knowing all that.
When you knew that I had feelings for you
you should have told me everything.
You should've told me everything
so I could completely walk away from you.
Why?
Why did you have to lead me on this far?
- I'm sorry.
- Stop saying you're sorry.
I'm saying that because I'm sorry.
What else can I do?
I'm sorry.
I'm just so very terribly sorry.
What else can I possibly say?
What would others say in this situation?
What would be the right thing to say?
Just tell me, please.
I'm sorry.
I'm... so very sorry.
Beg.
Beg on your knees.
- I'm sorry.
- Beg.
Beg.
I said beg! Come back and beg!
You've never said anything to me.
That you loved me...
You've never said that.
I bet you've said that to Oh Hae Young.
Among the kids whose moms I've married
Young Joo seemed to like you.
I liked you because you seemed cool.
Now that I'm getting married
to Do Kyung's mom
wouldn't it be weird
if we continue to hang out?
It's weird, isn't it?
Let's stop hanging out.
Don't call me.
It's okay if you think
I'm being too harsh.
No, you're not being too harsh.
- I understand.
- Stop having feelings for Do Kyung.
- Stop.
- I will just end our relationship.
I will end my relationship
with Young Joo too.
- But with Do Kyung...
- End it.
I've married too many times.
My family tree is already complicated,
so don't add more to it.
I will just talk to him.
- I'm just going to talk to him.
- What is it?
Come in.
- Who are you?
- I'm Han Tae Jin.
Hello.
I met you with Hae Young a while ago.
Did you?
You look familiar.
You pulled out your investment
in my company because of Park Do Kyung.
- My company was ruined.
- Ah!
I heard that you were arrested.
- I was acquitted and released.
- I see. That's great.
I thought you were a realistic investor.
I guess you get swayed
by a couple's love quarrel.
Don't twist your words
and just say it straightforward.
Gosh, this lunch has gotten
very uncomfortable.
I don't know if you knew.
But Park Do Kyung was after my fiancée
and wanted to ruin me.
When you had the reputation
of being a good investor
if the rumor gets out that
you were swayed by such a thing
it would hurt.
Wow, Do Kyung is
such a passionate man, huh?
He's just like me.
You should end it with Do Kyung.
I guess he is into some other woman now.
Is your fiancée's name Oh Hae Young?
You should've gotten
on your knees when she said so.
Hey, you couldn't do this?
You couldn't do this?
Why couldn't you do it?
You should be on your knees
when she says so.
You should get beaten up
if she throws a punch at you.
Is it a big deal that you get
embarrassed on the street now?
When I saw you yesterday,
you looked like you'd do anything.
Why couldn't you do it? Why?
I said I was sorry so many times.
Will that ever be enough?
You should've gotten on your knees
after saying you loved her.
You should've done
everything she asked you.
You should've even rolled down the
streets of Myung-dong if she asked you.
Are you sure you like her?
- Do you really like her?
- You don't know that?
I don't know. You don't say it.
How am I supposed to know?
You can't even give me a straight answer
to such a simple question.
Why so cautious? Why?
Why do you live your life that way?
Why wouldn't you let her in?
After we broke up
I opened my mailbox several times a day.
I was hoping to read
some hate mail at least.
I got disheartened when
I didn't hear anything from you.
It was torture when I was
the one who dumped you.
I thought you seemed to live your life
just fine after you were dumped.
I thought to myself,
"Did I mean nothing to him?"
"Did he even love me?"
You thought I married
that man, didn't you?
That's why you made his company
go bankrupt, isn't it?
Thank you.
Now I can finally breathe...
How can you say such a thing
at a time like this?
I ruined someone else's life
because of you.
I don't care.
Whether you ruined
100 or 1,000 people...
You did that because you loved me.
You did that because of me.
I... still love you.
I love you so much.
I love you.
I will leave first.
Her name is Oh Hae Young.
She and Do Kyung were
going to get married.
It wasn't me.
With that woman
I think it's right to end it this way.
Do Kyung.
Are you okay?
Hey, don't touch him.
I think it's right to end it this way.
For her.
I will die anyway.
Subtitles by DramaFever
Can you go down with me to the end?
It's right to end it
when I'm the only bad guy.
Just regret because everything began
the day you disappeared.
She fell in love without
realizing he was the enemy.
It speaks to itself that "Oh Hae Young"
is the most searched topic now.
- Hurry to apologize to her.
- What are you doing?
I will do my best.
Thank you for trusting me.
I want you to become so unhappy.