Subtitles by DramaFever
Are you sick or what?
If you are, tell me.
I'll get you some medicine.
It's still morning!
I think she has lost it again.
I don't know what's wrong
with her this time.
[Episode 12: Wish You Misery
Once You Leave Me]
While drifting, create a wilder sound.
Got it.
While drifting,
please create a wilder sound.
Ki Tae. Ki Tae!
You know how Do Kyung
has been down lately, right?
Tell him a cliché joke.
Those old jokes actually work on him.
Give it to me.
Director Park. This is Ki Tae.
Can you hear me?
Talk.
I fed a lot of food
to my dog yesterday.
So do you know what happened to him?
Three. Two. One. Time is up!
He became chubby!
- Isn't this funny?
- Let's get back to work.
All right.
Don't make me do these things.
Jokes should be told to
people with feelings.
I'm so embarrassed. Take this!
No. No. Do Kyung is laughing right now.
It will come a little later.
He's laughing so hard on the inside.
We're almost there.
Director Park. This is Sang Suk.
What is the most delicious
ramen in the world called?
Stop with the jokes.
Ramen with Director Park!
I'll follow you till the end
of the world! Cheer up!
- That's enough. Sprinkle water.
- All right. Got it.
Are you feeling frustrated
like no other?
This section of our radio show
serves to resolve that frustration.
Please take care of the frustrated ones!
Even Confucius and Mencius, who are
enjoying their time in the other world
immediately get up to hear
the wise words of this man.
He's someone who can
completely resolve your frustration.
The wisest man of all sages.
If you would like to receive
counseling from Lee Byung Joon
please give us a call right now.
- Hello?
Hey. You've been connected. Hi.
It's nice to meet you.
You can just talk with ease.
Am I really connected? Wow.
This is amazing.
I've asked for my voice to be modulated.
Sure. It's being modulated right now,
so you don't have to plug your nose.
It's being modulated. Don't worry.
You can talk with ease.
I also wanted to remain anonymous.
Don't try to reveal my name by
saying you'll send me gifts and stuff.
I've got it.
So what are your concerns?
So when I was in high school, there was
this girl who had the same name as me.
- Sure.
- Because she was so awesome...
I'm not saying I wasn't.
But because she was so freaking amazing,
I was constantly compared to her.
And I was just mistreated
because of her.
There were just so many things
that happened.
Anyway, I had
a tiring life because of her.
But...
I...
The man I used to like was...
once her fiancé.
But their wedding fell apart.
So he wanted to take revenge on her
but accidentally,
my life was ruined instead of hers.
Without knowing any of this...
Hello? Hello?
Could you tell us
your story in detail again?
So what happened is...
Because he couldn't forget
about what happened with her
he ruined my wedding,
thinking that he was ruining hers.
Wait. Hold on. Hold on.
How could he mistake
your wedding for hers?
Because she and I have the same name!
We have the same name.
So that man thought
she was the one getting married
and ruined my wedding instead!
I get this feeling. This feeling...
But without knowing any of this
I fell for that man.
Hold on. Hold on.
So you didn't recognize your nemesis
and fell in love with him?
So what is your problem now?
I just don't know what to do.
One moment,
I want to kill him out of anger.
But in another moment...
- But again...
- Just go to sleep.
Don't stay sad and gloomy. Don't go on
useless blind dates. Just go to sleep.
Once you wake up, you'll be hungry.
Then eat. Then sleep again.
Once you wake up,
you'll be hungry again. Then eat again.
Excuse me.
This isn't why I took
the courage to call you guys.
- Then just be reborn.
- Do you think that makes any sense?
Are you saying my current life is ruined
so I should just die and be reborn?
It sounds like you're very upset.
So please calm down.
That's not what we meant.
What's so hard about being reborn?
If you completely let go of your past,
you can be reborn.
Have you seen infants
with past memories?
"I've experienced these things.
Thus, I'm this kind of person."
If you let go of that mindset
and your past, you can be reborn.
Do you think that's
as easy as it sounds?
How could I pretend like
nothing has happened?
"Here we go. Let's erase all of
your past. Let go of your memories."
Would that just make everything go away?
If you want to be miserable,
then hold onto your past.
It's your call.
That's what life is about.
Who could stop a person
who's determined to be miserable?
How cruel.
You should give me realistic advice.
Do you know how much pain
I'm in right now?
If I could, I would like to kill both
that man and Oh Hae Young!
I'm sorry, but didn't you say
you would like to stay anonymous?
- Oh my god.
- Yeah. I've revealed her name. Not mine!
But you told us earlier that
you two have the same name.
Hello?
- Hello?
- Has she lost it?
Hello?
My goodness. There are so many people
with the name Oh Hae Young.
Your name doesn't mean anything.
My name, Lee Byung Joo, means nothing.
So what does it matter?
Ms. Oh Hae Young?
I see you have "Oh" in your name.
Your name means nothing.
And the other Oh Hae Young's name
doesn't mean anything either.
Our DJ Shin Young's name
means nothing too.
Sir, you've said her name too many times.
She's supposed to remain anonymous.
Is that so? Okay.
I'll maintain anonymity.
All right.
- Anonymous Oh Hae Young.
- Sir.
- You said her name Oh Hae Young again.
- Did I?
Everyone from our class is talking
about you. What are you going to do?
You just leave
that group chat immediately.
Don't even check it. Just delete it.
And leave your phone turned off.
All right.
Just stop it already!
Can't you guys let it go?
If you guys keep calling Hae Young
I won't forgive you all!
So the reason Hae Young's
wedding got called off
was because of that?
Deok Hee!
Does Hae Young have no pride?
How could she fall for a man like that?
- Is she crazy?
- She liked him because she didn't know!
My goodness.
Listen to it. She even asked for
voice modulation to remain anonymous
but she revealed her name on her own.
How could Assistant Manager Oh come to
work now? How embarrassing for her!
This clip has been circulating all day
as one of the funny clips!
When I tell people I work with her,
they want to come see her face!
So that's why she beat Manager Oh up
that day and caused a scene.
That was after she found out her wedding
was ruined because of Manager Oh.
Yeah. And yet she kept on saying,
"I'm the one who called the wedding off."
That's enough!
- Are you having fun?
- What's wrong? This is funny.
What if she was your little sister?
- Still funny?
- You're looking after your team member?
Sorry.
He's making me look like the mean guy.
You guys are being mean!
The things that you are saying!
Imagine if your little sister's marriage
was ruined because of a stranger.
How would you feel?
- Would you still be saying these things?
- Stop it. That's enough.
Why even bother?
Are you guys even her colleagues?
- I'm sorry.
- Let's go. Come on.
- It was just for fun.
- Come one. Let's go. Sorry.
Manager Oh.
That man must have loved you a lot.
Have you listened to it? Ms. Oh's
voice recording is all over the Internet.
Let's get back to work.
I found out only a few days ago too.
All of this happened
since the day you disappeared.
- You're aware of that, right?
- Yes.
Have some remorse.
Did you hear it on the radio?
I was so shocked!
Of course I heard it! So funny.
My stomach hurts from laughing. Oh my.
So before Hae Young does something
crazy again, we should do something.
No matter how crazy she is
Hae Young isn't the kind of person
to harm another person.
If she were to kill someone, would she
publicly announce it on the radio?
She's not that stupid.
- She's right.
- What do you mean? She still said...
Hold on. Someone's calling me. Hello?
So tell people it wasn't that
Oh Hae Young! It was someone else!
So I think that did kind of
sound like our Hae Young.
But it could also not be her.
It's just--
Why are you so curious?
Even if you thought it was our Hae Young
why would you call our house
and ask about it?
Based on your actions, I can tell
how twisted of a person you are!
Let's just wait and see what kind of
misfortune comes your children's way!
Why even bother answering
these stupid calls?
That was my mom.
What is Hae Young doing?
The name "Oh Hae Young" is
all over the Internet!
People have sent me this "funny clip"
all day and all of them are sending me
her voice recording from the radio!
What are you going to do now?
Do you know how much pain
I'm in right now?
If I could, I would like to kill both
that man and Oh Hae Young!
I'm sorry, but didn't you say
you would like to stay anonymous?
Yeah. I've revealed her name. Not mine!
But you told us earlier that
you two have the same name.
- Same name...
- Hello?
Hello? Hello?
Why would you share this
to our group chat?
Go delete this before
Director Park checks it! Hurry!
Go! You bastard! Go!
Director Park... Could I see your phone?
Could you unlock your phone for me?
- I'll delete it.
- Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Bring me the recordings
that we did today.
Eat up.
It's fine. It's all good.
No one dies from something like this.
It's not a big deal. It's nothing.
It's okay. Eat.
Have something to eat
and just stay warm.
Let's just live our lives. Who cares?
If you had told me earlier
I would have sent them to jail!
I could have done something!
Why would you keep it a secret
from me and suffer by yourself?
Keep your head up and eat.
Mom.
I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry.
- Why would you be sorry?
We shouldn't have given you
such a common name.
We were too careless
when coming up with your name.
I told you we shouldn't use
the name "Hae Young."
We considered "So Ra"
and "Soo Bin" too! Why "Hae Young"?
Why are you blaming it on Dad?
It's some other guy's fault.
You just give up on that man.
No need to stay angry.
Just shut your mind down and forget it.
Stop thinking about it.
Just end things with him.
I heard you can get some monetary
compensation with a lawyer's help.
But what's the point?
Instead of constantly seeing his face
and being upset all the time
just be done with him.
If you take things further,
you'll become the ridiculous one.
If you take things further, people will
only point fingers at you. Not them.
So just shut your mind down
and be done with him.
Be done.
Why aren't you answering me?
Do you still have feelings for him?
Fine. You could have liked him
when you didn't know about any of this!
How could you like him after
you've found out about everything?
I could shred him into pieces!
I would hate his guts!
If you still like him after all of this
you are the biggest idiot
in the entire world.
You would be the craziest bitch!
You know?
I do know.
I know all of this.
But I just can't control my heart.
Thank god she didn't at least
reveal your name.
I was so scared the whole time
I was listening to it.
How could she make such a mistake?
My goodness.
Oh my.
Here's another woman
who is out of her mind.
I can't believe a day like this
has come in my life.
The day I'm disappointed
with Park Do Kyung.
Cheer up.
Hold on.
Why aren't you beating him up?
Shouldn't you kick him in the knees?
You used to beat the crap out of me
for petty things.
Why aren't you beating him up?
Are you favoring him over me?
You shouldn't yell at a person...
who has truly done something wrong.
It's because he's already in
a lot of pain.
I see.
So the things that I've done
in the past weren't
so terribly bad. I see how it is.
Fine. I'll do some really
bad things from now on. Okay?
How mean.
- Have you talked to that woman?
- No.
Were you the one who didn't call?
Or did she not answer your calls?
I didn't call her.
You're just so cruel.
Did you even like her? Genuinely?
How could you not call her
in a situation like this?
Out of everyone,
you should have called her.
- How could you do nothing?
- What would I tell her?
Would I ask her if she's okay?
Those words aren't worth saying.
I can't find a single word
to say to her.
"I love you."
- Wouldn't that be enough?
- That's for flattery.
That's just to calm her down.
Why do you always interpret
that phrase like that?
That phrase just doesn't fit
with this situation.
The phrase "I love you" is...
always the right thing to say.
[The Woman Next Door]
Please leave a message after the beep...
Hello...
How long will you
freeload off of them?
Who's freeloading off of whom?
He's our family.
You guys aren't even blood-related.
But we've grown closer
through all these years.
I'm closer to him than
my blood-related family.
Good morning.
Hello, ma'am.
- You live here too?
- Just temporarily.
I've done a lot of things wrong.
So this is my hideout place.
You let guests in all the time.
Yet you won't even let
your mom set a foot in here.
What brings you here so early?
I'm getting married tomorrow.
Again?
Soo Kyung couldn't even do it once.
But this is your third time.
Wow. That's so great.
I have so much respect for you!
Wearing a wedding dress at
that old and wrinkly age isn't
something to brag about.
I'm not going to wear a wedding dress.
At CEO Jang's 70th birthday,
he's just going to introduce me.
- You're not coming, right?
- No.
- That's what I thought.
- Should I at least--
- Only Do Kyung needs to come.
- Sure.
By the way, why isn't he
picking up his phone again?
You see...
It's because he's in a sticky situation.
- What sticky situation?
- You see--
We don't know the full story either.
He doesn't talk about these things...
Tell Do Kyung he doesn't have to buy
CEO Jang's gift because I've bought one.
Tell him to just send me money.
Seven million won.
He should at least give me that much.
I'll be bringing home a lot more.
You just wait.
I'll make a ton of money
and let you guys live in luxury.
Live in luxury? Who?
None of us are poor.
We all have jobs
and are doing fine with our lives.
You just worry about your own damn life!
Your face is getting worse
and worse as you age!
Quit drinking!
You look older than your mom!
I'm not saying you have to
get married three times.
But shouldn't you do it at least once?
Congratulations on your wedding.
Bye.
She's an embarrassment.
I'm so embarrassed that
she's my daughter.
Don't worry about her.
You know how she is. She always
says all these meaningless things.
Now that I think about it,
you and Do Kyung are nothing like her.
You two take after your dad.
Honest and genuine.
Where did you leave your car
after getting drunk this time?
You know.
I'm sure I'll find it somewhere.
Are you all right?
Oh my. Please open the door, sir.
Because this lady is embarrassed,
I think she should get off the bus.
Please don't stare.
Look away. Look away.
I'll give you a call if she's hurt.
Don't stare. She's fine!
My goodness.
I asked them not to stare.
Just leave. Just drive, sir! Go! Go!
Go!
Soo Kyung. Are you all right?
How could you sleep like that
and then trip like that?
- Son of a bitch.
- Don't curse at him though.
- I'm talking about you!
- Me?
What did I do? I was looking after you.
I thought you might be embarrassed.
I saw everything as
I was rolling down the bus.
I saw you holding onto your phone
and staring at me with awe
as I was rolling down the bus.
I'm not even asking you to
let me borrow your shoulder.
How could you stare with that kind of
expression as I was rolling down the bus?
With your mouth wide open! Huh?
Fine. I've got it. Get up.
Soo Kyung! Fine! I get it!
I've done wrong. Hurry and get up.
Soo Kyung! Soo Kyung?
Soo Kyung! Soo Kyung!
Shouldn't we take her head CT too?
She rolled down the aisle like this
and after she got off,
she slammed her head on the street.
I think something went wrong
as she was rolling down.
There's no need for a head CT.
You've been tired lately, right?
Yes! She drinks a lot.
- It's because of her liver, right?
- You should stop drinking.
See? It's because of your liver!
You're pregnant.
You have anemia from your pregnancy.
I'll prescribe iron supplements for you.
Make sure you take them. Congratulations.
Oh my goodness.
Sorry.
I think congratulations are in order.
This is something I should
congratulate you on, right?
Congratulations.
Gosh, I'm crazy. This is serious,
but I can't help laughing.
So it happened the last time
you saw him before he left, huh?
How could you be so careless
even if it was the last time to see him?
Let me see...
Has he gone to Brazil or not?
Call him now. What if he's already left?
What would you do
if he hasn't leave yet?
Gosh, seriously.
Gosh, you guys aren't even kids.
When you were involved in such an act
you should've been
more rational and prepared.
Look at me. Although I'm with
a different woman every night
I don't get myself in this situation.
Soo Kyung, this is completely his fault.
As a guy
he should've had protection
with him at all times.
Look at me.
See? Look at it.
I even have them here too. See?
I even have one in here. And there is...
Ah, there is another one in here.
I can't show you that in here.
Anyway, this shows
how responsible a guy should be.
Gosh, I'm sorry.
It's not the time to talk about this.
Why do you have to cry?
It's okay. Don't cry.
- It's okay.
- Get away from me, you bastard!
Go away!
This is a dream.
Soo Kyung, it's okay.
Jin Sang, shall we go
to a different hospital?
First, accept the fact.
Don't touch me.
- I will go get the doctor.
- Don't touch me.
Wait here.
Doctor.
I can't remember it.
Did we really do it?
Without knowing the whole truth
I fell in love with that guy.
I'm so mad that I want to kill everybody.
So badly...
You're all tangled together
in a ridiculous way.
I agree.
Isn't this something that could
make a headline in a foreign country?
By the way, how did
Hae Young fall for that guy?
Can't you guess?
She was deceived.
I'm sure that bastard was so nice
to her because he was guilty.
He was getting ready for the time
when the truth would come out.
- He made her fall for him.
- What did Hae Young say?
What can she say?
She's furious.
Tae Jin.
Go ahead.
Bye.
[Oh Hae Young]
The phone is switched off
and your call is being redirected...
Go bite his butt off.
It sounds pretty.
You had a delivery.
There was a knock on the door.
Aren't you going to ask if I'm okay?
You can't be okay.
No, I'm not okay.
I'm a total wreck.
I don't want to keep my eyes open.
But I can't sleep.
I can't sleep because I'm so mad.
At the same time, I can't sleep
because I miss you.
Now curse at me
and move on with your life.
Get together with others
and curse at me.
If you want to call and curse at me
I will answer your calls every time.
Call me any time.
You can torture me.
Do whatever you want to do.
Just...
Can you see me until I'm sick of you?
Not until I'm sick of you...
but until things become easier on me...
Now everybody knows
and it's right to end it now.
It's right to end it now, but...
I don't think I can do it.
If I break up with you now out of anger
I may suffer for a long time.
Can we just go out
for a bit and break up?
Let's go out secretly
for a bit and break up.
I'm sorry.
When I'm the only bad guy
it's right to end it.
Come out. I will drive you home.
I will take you home.
Get in. I will take you home.
- Congratulations, Chairman Jang!
- Congratulations.
Wow, this is good.
- Oh my, thank you.
- Congratulations.
- This is Mrs. Pang from Myungdong.
- Ah, hello.
- And these are her friends.
- Congratulations.
Hi, President Kim.
President Kim is in the wig business.
Hello there.
This is my father's fifth wedding.
This is your mother's third wedding.
My father beat her to it.
How was your second stepfather?
- He was nice.
- Was he really?
He was.
How do you think
your third stepfather will be?
Why does it matter to me?
Because money is involved.
You're pretending, huh?
My fifth stepmother
is the lousiest so far.
I'm too embarrassed to call her mother.
You've given up being a human being, huh?
Just listen.
When your mother is acting with a smile
you can't mess it up as her son.
Why are you drinking so much, Do Kyung?
What is it?
You think I'll make it
uncomfortable for your mother?
Why don't you congratulate me?
- Congratulations.
- Okay.
It's hard to make you congratulate me.
Young Joo, why don't you smile a bit?
Don't give me that look.
I told you not to be
bothered with my new wives.
No matter how many wives
come and go, I won't change.
You're the owner.
You also know that, don't you?
Smile, okay?
The light pink looks so good on you.
- Does it?
- I'm so happy now.
- Are you?
- It's a perfect day too.
- I agree.
- Don't you?
- Congratulations.
- Thank you. Please enjoy.
Thank you.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
You look so good.
I'm so happy.
- There you are.
- You smile too much.
It's a happy day, you know.
- Why don't you smile too?
- You know my father gets bored easily.
When he gets bored,
he sends the signal.
"Go give her a hard time.
I'm done with her."
Then I go give her a hard time.
And then we get into
a fight pulling hair.
And then she gets kicked out.
For some reason, I want to let you
know how it works this time.
I have a feeling that it'll be so easy...
for you to grab my hair
and get kicked out.
Although it won't be fun
when it happens.
What can I say?
I'm a woman full of charms.
It will take him a long time
to get bored with me.
I hear both your ex-husbands passed away.
And they had a lot of money too.
I spent it all.
I'm like a hippo that devours money.
You didn't get investigated
after they passed away, huh?
They both died so suddenly like that.
I would have investigated right away.
I'm a physician.
If my father should die
I would run all kinds of tests on him.
Don't even think about it.
I would kill you first.
See if you can kill me first.
Hello.
Get up.
- Don't be rude.
- Get up!
- I said don't be rude.
- Go apologize to her.
Let go of me.
- Let go of me!
- Come here.
- Let go!
- Apologize to her now!
What are you doing?
Don't do it, Do Kyung.
- What are you doing?
- Apologize to her.
- How dare you two!
- Apologize!
How dare you do that?
How dare!
- Hey!
- How dare you say such a thing?
- How dare you!
- What did you do just now?
- You stop!
- Hey!
- Let go of me!
Let go!
How dare you say such a thing?
How dare you!
Let go of me!
What were you thinking?
How could you do this?
Do you know how hard
it's been for me to get here?
How could you ruin everything?
Mother.
Let's not live this way.
Can we please not live this way?
We live once.
Let's not live this pathetically.
Unless I bring back
your late father's fortune that I lost
you won't treat me with respect.
This is the only way I know
how to bring back that fortune.
Isn't this the only way for me
to get that fortune back?
It's okay not to have that kind of money.
I hated the mother who always
wanted money all the time.
I didn't hate the mother
who didn't have money!
You bastard.
What will you do with that punk?
Will you leave him alone?
Calm down.
There is a way.
Thank you. We will do our best.
Thank you for trusting us, Chairman Jang.
I invest when I see the potential.
I pull out when I see otherwise.
Darn it.
We will work hard not to let that happen.
It's no fun to play by myself.
- Play with me.
- I will.
There you go!
- Go ahead.
- Set go.
- Wow!
- I did it!
What?
While President Han is trying
to expand his foreign market
his partner seems to be
messing things up.
He's increasing the sales by buying
his own merchandise on the web.
He's been getting
loans from different places.
But the sale volume
seems to be quite low.
How do you want to
pull out your investment?
Just pull it out.
No need to ask how.
Gosh, it's so annoying.
They are just a bunch of losers. Gosh!
I just got back.
I want to see Chairman Jang in person
and share this good news.
It's President Han.
- You didn't pull out our investment yet?
- We did.
- He will soon find out.
- Tell him not to come by.
No, tell him to come by.
I will make him pay for this drink.
How dare he tries to keep
my money for nothing?
You can come to the place
where you came last time.
When are you coming?
Hurry up. Hurry!
To succeed in anything
we should work with the right people.
Someone I can trust, right?
Cheers.
He's the one, Han Tae Jin.
He's getting married to Oh Hae Young.
Isn't he the one?
He was in Europe with Oh Hae Young
on the day of your wedding.
What are you, a saint?
If you go over and say
something to Chairman Jang now
you can have your revenge on him.
Why wouldn't you?
I understand.
I will do what you ask.
Don't worry.
I will pull out my investment.
You will know how loyal I am
if you get to know me better.
Who does he think he is?
Why would I pull out millions
just because he asks me to?
Go find out what Han Tae Jin is up to.
He must be dying to have his revenge.
- I will let him have it.
- Yes, Chairman Jang.
[The Woman Next Door]
Text me your account number.
I will wire your security deposit.
I was so easy when it came to you.
I came when you asked me to come.
I left when you asked me to leave.
I was that easy.
How can it be this easy
to break up with me?
How can you break up with me this easily?
I'm sorry.
I... want you to become very unhappy.
I... want you to cry every night.
Every time you think about me...
I want you to break down.
I wish I'd die of depression
thinking about you.
So...
I want you to feel guilty
for the rest of your life.
Let's go beg for
his forgiveness, shall we?
There is nothing Chairman Jang can't do.
Let's beg
for his forgiveness once, please.
Please, Do Kyung.
It's taken us longer, but...
somehow we've ended up
back with the right people.
My father is the owner of this house.
I heard you wanted to buy this house.
Do you perhaps still want to buy it?
Wow.
How does it feel to use the studio
your father used to use?
Have you heard from the woman
who used to live here?
Why would she call me?
How did you like your blind date?
- I didn't like her.
- You should see her again to be polite.
You can't tell anything
after only seeing her once.
One Oh Hae Young left the company.
The other Oh Hae Young
still works at this company.
Which Oh Hae Young
do you think has left?
do you think still works here?
I don't want to know.
Women don't badmouth
the men who left them.
We badmouth the men who were cheap.
Don't be cheap to anyone.
Why were you nice to me?
Because I felt bad for you.
You were dumped
the day before your wedding.
I couldn't stand watching you
tell everybody that you dumped him.
That's why I was nice to you.
Is it a crime?
- I'm sorry.
- Beg.
Beg.
Beg! Come back and beg!
- Are you seeing him again?
- Yes.
- You're so easy, huh?
- Yes, I am easy.
I'm starting to dislike you.
You bastard.
You're the cruelest man in the world!
You're the biggest coward.
Why wouldn't you let anyone in?
I'm sorry.
I love you.
I don't care if I die.
But I won't die with regret.
I will never die with regret.
I will go all the way
to where my heart takes me.
Good, Park Do Kyung.
I'm proud of you.
Go for it like a bull!
Be cool and go all the way!
Subtitles by DramaFever