Subtitles by DramaFever
[Another Oh Hae Young]
I don't care if I die.
But I won't die with regret.
I will never die with regret.
I will go all the way...
to where my heart takes me.
[The Woman Next Door]
Please leave a message after the beep...
[Episode 13: The Heart I've Understood]
- Hello. How have you been?
- Welcome.
- Hae Young wasn't picking up her phone.
- I see. She's in her room. Come in.
Let's go.
It's as if you knew I was coming.
You were all ready and everything.
You should dress nicely too
before you go out.
- We'll be back.
- All right.
Go somewhere far. Like the beach.
We might not even come back.
If you don't want to talk,
you don't have to say a word.
I can play some background
music for you, right?
I know that my tears
will be difficult for you to see.
I'm sorry.
All I can do...
What perfect timing.
These lyrics must
represent how you feel.
The me who was in love with you
and lost half of his mind
the me who dreamed of you
must have longed for you
to look back at me once.
There are times in my memory
I hope that there are days
when you'd hear news about me.
That you would notice my heart
tiptoeing around you
and that these hopes
and this foolish love would hurt you.
Once I was in my thirties
I thought I would be
living a wonderful life.
I thought I would be living in a studio
and driving my own car.
Traveling abroad once or twice a year.
I don't know why I thought
I'd be living that life in my thirties.
You probably thought
you would make a lot of money.
Maybe you thought
you would easily earn money.
I thought I would have
a fabulous love life too.
Yet I still stumble over
love like an idiot.
But I'm...
jealous of you,
someone who stumbles over love.
Because I've never done such a thing.
So you've decided to
end things with him?
Yes.
I got dumped.
I don't think you were
necessarily dumped.
It would have been hard to
work it out with him anyway.
Park Do Kyung has nicely
ended things for you.
He just wants to be the bad guy
and won't make you be the bad woman.
Hey.
That just means
he doesn't love me as much.
Hey.
It's not because he doesn't love you.
It's because he doesn't
know how to love.
Men just don't know
what's more hurtful for women.
Look at Tae Jin too.
Because he thought you'd wait for him
he dumped you, saying
those absurd things not to burden you.
Men just don't know whether
it's more hurtful for a woman
to wait for a guy who has gone bankrupt
or live for the rest of
her life all hurt and scarred
after hearing those painful words
from the man she loves.
For women, they're always
ready to take things all the way.
Right?
When will I finally get
to dump someone first?
Let's do it this time.
Dump whomever
you end up dating this time.
Should I?
Okay. I'll dump whomever
I end up dating this time.
If you won't, I'm going to follow you
around and tell you to dump him.
"This is your one and only
opportunity in life!"
"Dump him. Quickly! Dump him!"
- Should I just go around dumping people?
- Sure! Do it.
Oh my! Oh no! My hat.
- It's an expensive hat.
- Fine. I've got it.
Hae Young! Oh no!
Oh no!
If you got wet, you should've bought
new clothes, including underwear.
They don't cost that much.
Why walk around in wet clothes all day?
It hasn't been too long
since you got doused with water.
This is nice.
Your dad and I are moving.
Come with us.
You wanted to move to
the countryside, didn't you?
Let's move to Chung Joo
and live with Grandma.
I'm going back to work tomorrow.
No need to persist stubbornly.
Just resign.
After you resign,
come to Chung Joo with us.
It's more embarrassing to run away.
I just want to get back up. Right here.
Your daughter is strong. I won't get
knocked down by something like this.
I'm the woman who got dumped the day
before her wedding and survived it.
Stop. Don't say those things.
You can even search for me online.
If you type "Oh Hae Young Clip,"
you'll find me.
What an honor to our family.
Who is it?
I'll tell Hae Young to call you.
So you should go.
Hurry and go!
Run!
Whose hand are you holding?
- Don't take your clothes off.
- I won't.
I only do that with
people I have affection for.
I'm sorry.
I thought people's eyes don't lie.
But I guess I got fooled by your eyes.
I guess you can't judge
a person by their face.
A daughter who chased after
the guy who has ruined her life
without knowing anything.
A mother who fed that guy.
Both the daughter
and her mother are idiots.
I'm sorry.
I stayed quiet even though
I know where you live.
There is no use in cursing at
a person who is to be
completely cut out of your life.
That's why I didn't pay you a visit.
But I think I need to tell you this.
Nothing is free in life.
If you make someone miserable,
something even worse will come your way.
For ruining a perfectly fine couple
with a bright future.
For breaking
my precious daughter's heart.
You'll be punished for your wrongdoings.
Of course you should be.
My daughter has been
through hell because of you.
I'm sorry.
Hey.
- He's here.
- Huh?
I'm sorry.
What's the use in wishing
bad things for someone?
I would like to cancel
what I've just said.
I'll just punch him once and end it all.
Get back in.
From now on, you should keep your
eyes down when you meet someone.
Those big sad eyes of yours.
- I was going to curse at you...
- Go back in.
Let's go home.
Why do you keep blaming his eyes?
Let's hurry and get back in.
Let's go. Come on.
- Why are you here?
- Because I've missed you.
I'm sorry.
For being too late.
My goodness.
Just makes me wonder
what kind of man you are.
You didn't even budge when
I begged you in my worst possible state.
Now that you feel a little better,
here you are again.
- I'm sorry.
- We really weren't meant to be.
Our timing is just completely off.
It's all over now,
so don't come here anymore.
I've received the security deposit
and I won't say anything to
the owner of the house.
So you just need to pay rent on time.
Don't make him call me.
I've made mistakes.
I was wrong.
I won't ever act like a loser
in front of you.
I won't ever again go back and forth.
No matter what happens
I won't ever let you go.
I won't ever go back and forth either.
I've decided to let you go.
I've let you go already.
- I know you're mad at me.
- Do I seem like I'm playing hard to get?
When I like someone,
I don't play these games.
Or maybe you think I'm so easy that
I'll fall for you whenever you chase me.
You know that's not what I meant.
You know that I've unwillingly pushed
you away even though I like you too.
No need for you to do
such a thing anymore.
I won't ever go back to you.
If we ever see each other
on the street by coincidence
let's not greet each other.
Let's just go our own ways.
Instead of acting all cool and happy.
I'm not good at these things.
This isn't a tear. I have a runny nose.
It's not that I'm sad.
I just have a cold.
Don't take this the wrong way.
I'm grateful.
For letting me end things
by dumping you.
I just don't need a lamp anymore.
Let's go and beg him. Okay?
CEO Jang will do anything.
Let's go and ask for forgiveness.
Do Kyung...
Let's just beg him once.
Do Kyung.
It's all going the way...
It's taken us longer, but...
somehow we've ended up
back together with the right people.
The way I've seen it.
Like you've said
all the visions I've been seeing are
from the reminiscences before my death.
The regretful moments.
Visions that can't be changed
and are useless to see.
I wonder why I'm seeing them.
"We're just looking back on our lives..."
"that have ended already."
Whenever I feel like I'm wasting
my energy on something useless
this is the phrase I read to myself.
"We're just looking back on our lives"
"that have ended already."
What if our lives have already come to
an end based on a completed scenario
and this moment we know as present is
just the reminiscences of our souls?
You would feel futile, right?
And just live however?
But it's quite the opposite.
If you genuinely accept it,
you feel at ease.
You quietly start
looking into your heart.
In this situation
what is it that my heart wants the most?
Life is a scenario about your heart.
Don't try too hard to
change the situation.
From one moment to another,
just quietly...
relax and look into your heart.
To see what your heart wants to do.
I've never revealed my heart with ease.
To not get hurt
I've always done the bare minimum.
Less than the other person's kindness.
More than the other person's hostility.
My standards were always set
based on the other person's reactions.
I've never unraveled my heart's desire.
Not even once.
Once you acknowledge that
things are transient
you don't waste your energy
on useless things.
I'm now not afraid of dying at all.
I didn't give more love to
the person I could have.
I could've given her as much love
as I wanted, but I didn't.
The fact that there is this woman
who is suffering
because of my cautiousness...
That's what bothers me the most.
Hello. Hi.
Hey there.
Hello.
Hello!
Long time no see, eh?
- Aren't you guys getting on?
- We are. Sure. Yes.
I wanted to take more time off
but I've used up all of
my vacation days for the year.
My face looks
completely different, right?
I've lost two kilograms.
My waistline got slimmer too.
I should cause trouble one more time
to lose two more kilograms!
I'm fine! Truly. I'm fine.
So talk with ease.
- You're really okay, right?
- Yes!
She seems okay.
What's with the flowers?
I bought them. I thought it
might make me look less pitiful.
I'm really okay. Please laugh with ease!
Of course!
She's our Assistant Manager Oh!
I didn't know.
That my brother was involved in it.
I'm sorry.
Everyone is telling me,
"I'm sorry. I'm sorry."
This is my first time hearing
that phrase so often.
But it doesn't feel so great.
It feels like I've become a loser.
I'm sorry.
Never mind. Forget it. I'm not sorry.
Do Kyung is in a lot of pain.
Tell him not to be. It's all over now.
I guess I shouldn't even
tell him what to do.
It doesn't matter. I'm fine.
From now on, I'm going to live like you.
"I don't need a man.
Who cares about love?"
I'm going to live that kind of life.
As a cool, chic, and independent person.
But something must have happened
while I was taking some time off.
This is my first time seeing
you wear shoes without heels.
You see...
My feet were getting swollen...
You've put a mole on your face too.
What do you mean?
- A mole?
- Over here...
It's from some kind of snack.
You used to never eat
these kind of things.
My blood sugar level is a little low.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Now that everything was publicly
announced, I actually feel at ease.
It feels like I'm traveling
cross-country naked.
I have nothing left to hide
or be cautious about.
I'm just...
a woman worth this much.
I thought about resigning...
but if I quit now, I feel like
I could never make a comeback.
You're the pretty Oh Hae Young.
I'm the ordinary Oh Hae Young.
I felt like it would
stay that way forever.
While I was getting compared to you
during my teens
I think I just had this perception
that I was a sore loser.
That's how I feel right now too.
Whether it's through work or whatever.
By your side
looking at you...
I would like to overcome it.
You're still the same.
You always get over things so easily
and get back on your feet.
- I do?
- You used to when we were in school too.
You were sobbing your heart out
like a baby in one moment
and then in another moment,
you'd be smiling as if nothing was wrong.
You just made me feel awkward
for worrying about you.
You really won't get a drink with me?
Let's get a drink some other day.
When? When will you drink with me?
Some day.
I'll get going.
Park Do Kyung and I are completely over.
Good luck with him.
Okay. I'm done cleaning up.
Do Kyung and Hae Young.
They didn't break up
because they got sick of each other.
Or because they didn't like each other.
They painfully broke up even though
they still love each other.
That's what makes me sadder.
I'm not even Do Kyung's
most painful love anymore.
If we can't be in love again
I wanted to at least remain
Do Kyung's most painful love.
You're all done.
- I'm done.
- Keep going.
Your ears are all clean now.
Hello?
Yes. Yes, Producer Kim.
No. It's all right. I'm home right now.
Right now? Sure. Yes. That's fine.
Yes! Sure. I'll go right now.
- Sure.
- Who is it?
- Producer Kim.
- Is something wrong with your recording?
No. No.
She wants to work on my scenario.
Something is up.
If she approves, it'll be legitimate!
My god!
Have some of this before you go!
I just finished making
kimchi fried rice.
I've read it over again.
Your characters are nice.
Let's adjust them a little
and send your scenario to actors.
Once we find some good actors,
people will naturally invest in it.
Let's see. Firstly...
I should give this to Jung Min.
Never mind. Maybe a good-looking
actor will suit the role better.
A handsome man, playing a loser role.
That's it. That would work better.
I should show this to Jung Jae first.
By the way.
I've thought long and hard about it.
But doesn't this part
just seem a little off?
There is just something missing
in this action scene.
These scenes need to be good in order
for the actors to love the script.
Sure. As I was writing it, I thought
that part was a little lacking too.
- I guess it just wasn't working out.
- Yeah.
I will try to make it work this time.
Just give me one day...
Maybe two. Or three days?
Never mind. No. No. No.
I'll make it better in two days.
- She's not drunk. What's with her?
- I know. Right?
Excuse me.
Could you take me home?
I...
am pregnant.
Please take me home.
What to do...
So with that man?
He doesn't know he is the baby's dad.
He thinks it's someone else's baby.
Are you going to have this baby?
Didn't you say he has a lot of issues?
You said he jumps from
one woman to another...
That's not the only problem.
A rapist. A serial killer.
He's the infamous low-class attorney
who defends whomever will
pay him a lot of money.
He has no conscience at all.
That bastard who shamelessly
claims their innocence!
My baby is probably okay, right?
Objectively...
He's a piece of trash. Complete garbage.
But subjectively...
I like him.
Because I've slept with him.
Then you should ask him.
Who knows?
Maybe he'll want to get married.
Never. Not in a million years.
He'll probably pass out
not only when he finds out
I'm pregnant with his baby
but even when he hears
that we've slept together.
I've known him since
he was a 14-year-old kid.
He used to walk around naked
in front of me.
If he finds out
we slept together...
[Jin Sang]
Soo Kyung, I've just asked six men.
If a woman gets pregnant after
a one-night stand and comes to them
they all would never marry her.
They'd tell her to not have the baby.
Me?
I would immediately flee the country.
Who cares if she has the kid or not?
I would run. No matter what.
I would go to the countryside in England
change my name to William Sutherland,
and live there.
Yeah?
Okay. I've got it. Hold on.
Hey, listen up. Listen.
She would like to have the baby.
She's 44 years old. 44.
This may be the last pregnancy of
her life. Of course she would want to.
But the problem is, should she bear
this baby after she tells the father?
Or should she just have the baby
and quietly raise it by herself?
So here comes the question.
Would it be better for you to live life
without knowing of your kid's existence?
Or would you rather know?
Raise your hand if
you would rather not know.
I see. Two people.
Raise your hand if
you think you'd rather know.
Soo Kyung. It's two to four.
They'd rather know.
I feel the same way about this too.
Of course he should know.
Living life without the knowledge
of my own kid's existence is...
That's a little...
How should I put it?
It's as if there is a bomb
somewhere in the house
but I'm the only one
who doesn't know about it.
Make sure you tell him! Okay?
I think it's right to tell the truth.
When you want to raise
the baby by yourself
what would he have to say to that?
Tell him right away.
Call him up and tell him now.
I understand, so don't worry.
I will tell him.
I will... definitely tell him.
That's right. Tell him.
Shall we get something good to eat?
There you are. You came.
Why did you two tenants
make a deal about my house, huh?
Who do you think you are?
Why did you act
like the owner of this house?
You kicked her out by paying
her security deposit?
You desperately wanted
to get her out of here.
So you ended up kicking her out?
How cruel.
I happened to come by here
and saw it empty.
If I hadn't seen it
you would've made it look
like she was living here, huh?
How sneaky you are!
Didn't I tell you that
I wouldn't give it to you?
Miss, please listen carefully.
According to the contract, I will
return your security deposit in one year.
Until then, you need to pay the rent.
If not, I will start to take it
out of your security deposit.
He will send you the rent on time.
Did I rent this place to this punk?
I rented it to you.
I got the security deposit
from him, so I'm all good.
Why did you get
your security deposit from him?
I'm the owner of this house.
If that's how you're
going to handle this
why did you sign the contract?
Plus, your deal isn't valid.
I will see you in one year.
You can't use this place. Got that?
I don't want to come back
to this place in one year.
I want to end things right now.
I will give you
whatever amount you ask for.
What's the point of trying
to stop her from moving out?
Can you... just move back?
I'd like it if you moved back in.
- I will give you a ride.
- No thanks.
Hi, Tae Jin. I'm on my way.
[Han Tae Jin]
What's wrong?
I have a cold.
- Did you take some medicine?
- Yes.
Sorry I was wrong about you two.
I thought you
were seeing each other.
I thought he did that
to take you away from me.
I'm sorry.
Try. It's delicious.
I was planning to get my revenge on him.
It turns out that it was a waste of time.
- I can't believe it was a mistake...
- Can we not talk about him?
I don't want to hear about him.
I'm sorry. I'm just not feeling well.
Have some.
I have a runny nose
because of the cold.
Let's break up.
I think it's the right thing to break up.
Let's... just hang out.
There is no need to cut me out.
We will give it more time and...
if it still doesn't feel right,
let's break up then.
It's because I'm sorry.
I'm home.
- Did you have dinner?
- Yes, I did.
- Did you take your medicine?
- I did.
You don't look so good though.
What is it? Your fever hasn't gone down?
- It's better than yesterday though.
- You sound hoarser than yesterday.
Don't I sound sexy then?
Crazy girl.
Are you advertising that you live alone?
That punk had the change.
Didn't you say those were
too small and hurt your feet?
They seem to have stretched
out a bit. They're okay.
I will see you when I get home.
Boss, you have a guest.
Wow, your office looks good, huh?
Shouldn't you come by
to see me first though?
CEO Park Do Kyung.
Gosh, I was also a CEO once.
But that all flew out the window
thanks to a certain someone.
You better watch out.
You could be out of a job in an instant.
If someone makes up his mind...
I won't hide from it.
Do whatever you like.
You said this when you
ran into my car, didn't you?
It was a mistake that
you ruined my company.
It was a mistake that I made
your company bankrupt back then.
But I meant to do this.
You meant to run into my car.
You were already falling for
her then, weren't you?
You were mad that the woman
you like was hurting so much...
over what I said, weren't you?
Then you should've stopped right there.
Why didn't you stop right there?
Why drag it out until now?
Now everybody knows the truth.
What are you going to do?
There is no other way.
We will all have to go back
to our rightful places.
That has to happen.
If the public finds that
you stole my girlfriend
I wouldn't be able to survive
in this country anymore.
Depending on what you do
I could ruin you or let you slide.
So...
let's all go back to where we were.
You had a girlfriend
you liked, didn't you?
This whole thing happened
because of her, right?
I will assume that
you will do what I say.
Bye for now.
It's taken us longer, but...
somehow we've ended up
back together with the right people.
["Contender"]
Wow, this office worked on that film too?
He's worked on many famous films then.
I don't like to work.
- Bye.
- Who is he?
- I don't know.
Wow, he has charisma, doesn't he?
It didn't work, did it?
No. I tried, but I couldn't.
I guess it's too difficult for you alone.
- If you give me one more day...
- Let's...
make it work with me today.
- Get up.
- Pardon?
Okay...
Gosh, this one is stuck here.
I watched hundreds of action movies
to make it work.
It didn't work.
Gosh, I can't do this anymore.
I'm so tired that
I want to get some sleep.
Sure, I will get going then...
No, continue.
You should finish it today.
I will get some sleep briefly and get up.
Okay.
I'm so hot.
I will go change my clothes.
Man, why is she changing now?
Is she hitting on me or what?
Should I leave?
What should I do now?
Leave or not?
Should I leave?
Do you want something to drink?
No thank you.
What should I do?
[We have a problem!]
Take a break for now.
Hello? Hello?
Hi, Do Kyung. Ouch!
Are you okay?
Oh my, are you okay?
I'm okay. I'm really okay.
My cell phone fell, so...
where did it go?
Gosh, you thought
I'd make a move on you, didn't you?
You're crazy.
Gosh!
[Passionate Bottle Opener]
A passionate bottle opener.
The sound of this movie is awesome.
Listen to feel
how awesome your sounds are.
- Let's have dinner when you're done.
- Sure.
Let go! Let go of me!
Let go! Hey!
Hooray!
Park Do Kyung finally
has feelings for me!
Yeah!
Can we just see each other
a bit and break up?
Without letting anybody know,
let's see each other a bit and break up.
If I break up with you
out of anger now...
I may suffer for a long time.
Where are you going?
I told you not to act like you know
me if we see each other on the street.
I'm sorry that I acted like I knew you.
Change your shoes.
They sound uncomfortable.
Right now, I have some shocking news
that will make you
completely forget your suffering.
I can't tell you what it is.
I really want to tell you.
But I might get beaten
to death if I tell you.
But with this news,
you will completely forget everything.
I have a hidden card
that will shut you up.
If we had the same interests
I'd take you out for some fun.
Do you want me to take you
to a club, bar, and everything tonight?
Do you?
Why are you lying down there?
I'm tired.
Then go upstairs to lie down.
I'm too tired to go upstairs.
- I'm home.
- Did you have dinner?
I did.
What's wrong?
My feet are killing me.
I will sleep all day tomorrow,
so don't wake me up.
You still haven't
gotten over the cold yet?
Why isn't the medicinie working yet?
Do you want to get an IV tomorrow?
I'm okay. It's gotten better.
Hey, Assistant Manager Oh.
- I heard something.
- About what?
- Can you do this, please?
- Okay.
What is this?
If I walk around in my small
and uncomfortable shoes all day
I think about him less.
Because all I think about is my feet.
And I take the shoes off when I get home.
I become happy for only a brief time.
Because of the memories
of you that keep popping up...
In the least unexpected places...
I get so sad thinking about you
then I want it to hurt me
more and more.
Whenever I check my cell phone
when I wake up in the middle of the night
I'm trying to walk forward.
But my mind is crying
to try to go backward.
I want it to hurt me more and more.
If it hurts so I can't
even lift my fingers
or even be myself...
I get to stop thinking about him.
The higher the fever gets...
the less I think about him.
Even if I'm sick, I feel better.
[Oh Hae Young
Take three times a day]
Hae Young! Hae Young!
Hae Young. Hae Young!
Hae Young. Hae Young. Hae Young!
Hae Young. Hae Young.
Honey. Honey!
- Hae Young, wake up.
- Hae Young, open your eyes.
Are you okay?
- Open your eyes, will you?
- Wake up.
- Hae Young.
- Gosh.
Hae Young.
I see something that's not real.
Just because I'm a little better now
how can I possibly
think about him right away?
I'm angry.
Can I stop getting this?
- Why not? You should continue.
- I don't want it anymore.
Press it down, please.
Don't get sick.
I'm glad to see you!
It was unfair that I was
the only one who was sick.
I'm so glad that you're sick too!
If we could turn back time
I would ruin your wedding the same way.
I would make you move next door
and meet you that way again.
I'm sorry. I'm very sorry.
But I'm not sorry I ruined
your wedding, damn it!
I'm sorry.
But this is how I truly feel.
I got sick because I couldn't hug you.
Wouldn't it make her happier
if I left this world
after loving her as much as possible than
to have died without loving her at all?
I love starting my morning seeing you.
Ah! That dream.
Correct. It's a precognitive
dream about the baby.
Hey! You crazy punk!
I don't think it will work
to force them to separate.
You're sentenced for life,
which is to live with Park Soo Kyung.
- Sorry.
- You're making me a complete idiot.
But I care more about my love.