Subtitles by DramaFever
[Another Oh Hae Young]
You're like a drug, Park Do Kyung.
I feel all better now.
I don't have any fever either.
You've been through a lot.
Thank you for your efforts.
Both of us.
We've both tried hard.
If you hadn't chased after me,
we would have been over.
Thank you.
I thought you'd give me a half-hearted
apology and go your own way.
I thought about it.
What if I die?
If I'd look back on this moment as I die.
My conclusion was... it's all nothing.
No need to be cautious.
Let's go as far as my heart takes me.
Let's not hold back and just go.
I like that phrase.
"Let's go as far as my heart takes me.
Let's not hold back and just go."
All the men I knew were pitiful.
Men who would test the waters.
Me who would be cautious.
Men who would dump women because
they were ashamed of their failures.
I never had a man who would move me by
just fearlessly charging at me.
I was emotionless.
I'm insanely happy right now.
If I ever see you
being cautious from now on
- I'm going to kill you.
- Go ahead.
If you keep going back and forth,
I won't forgive you.
- I won't go back and forth.
- I will go back and forth.
Do it. You can.
[Episode 14: Silence All the Other
Sounds that are Not of Love]
Where have you been?
We checked the rooftop and staircase of
the hospital! We thought you were dead!
Where have you been?
I came home because
I was feeling all better.
You should have told us
you were going home!
I just came home because
I didn't see you guys.
Young people freaking heal quickly.
From the vision that you saw
you two broke up, and that was it.
But in real life,
it changed to you two dating...
Then it has changed!
It has changed! Hey! Do Kyung! Do Kyung!
Congratulations! Congratulations!
This is a victory of the human race!
You've changed your fate!
But what's with your expression?
You look too calm.
Shouldn't you be happier?
Rather than not loving her at all
I should love her as much
as possible before I leave, right?
That will make her happier, right?
Leave? Who is leaving?
Why would you die?
Things have changed! Why would you die?
In your vision, you let that woman go.
That's why you were regretful
as you were dying.
But you said you are with her now.
Then your fate has changed.
Your present has changed.
How could your future not?
That's why there are flaws
in predestination
and why some of prophesiers'
prophecies are wrong now and then.
They can't predict what
the heart will do. What love will do.
Love!
What's wrong? Are you worried?
For leaving behind the woman you love?
From now on, there's only
one thing you need to do.
Until your feet sweat
love.
I'm so jealous!
What are you up to?
I'm on my way to work.
I just left my house. How about you?
- I'm on my way to work too.
- Oh my god!
You scared me!
I love starting my morning seeing you.
Get in. I'll take you.
I think I could do anything.
I feel like I could even commit murder.
Keep it together.
Just pick a person for real.
I'll kill him for you.
Fine. I've got it, Mom. Don't worry.
Of course I won't.
Okay. I love you.
You're still a three-year-old.
No man dances the moment he wakes up.
- Ask me why I'm so happy.
- I'm too lazy. Just tell me.
I'm going to hit it big.
I just had this amazing dream.
Mom told me not to tell anyone...
Just keep this between you two.
Mom told me this is an amazing dream.
A great one!
I don't normally ever have dreams.
But this is the first time in my life
I've had such a vivid dream.
What was your dream about?
The stars in the sky
were shining brightly
as if they were covered in gold.
But all of a sudden, they started moving
and formed a fish shape.
And it was as if it was alive.
It kept on flopping.
As it was suddenly falling from the sky
- I hurried over and caught it.
- You caught it? You didn't drop it?
Of course! I caught it! Perfectly
in my hands. Don't ruin it for me.
Anyway.
As I woke up from my dream
and opened my eyes...
I felt...
very excited, yet serene.
It felt like I had heard God's voice.
"Your era has come."
- Sell it to me for 5,000 won.
- You crazy bastard.
Don't sell that dream. Don't sell it.
Not even for 100 million won.
Of course I won't!
I heard it means
I'll be the Minister of Justice.
Isn't it too early for this?
We should meet up for dinner.
I'll buy you something good.
There is this great steakhouse I know.
What would you do without me?
I always look after you.
So you should just hurry
and tell your family.
They'll all find out once you
start having a baby bump.
By the way, did you let
the baby's dad know? That guy in Brazil?
What's wrong?
Do you not even know his number?
Not even his e-mail address
or something?
That bastard.
Give me his biographical data.
I'll look him up for you.
- He's not the baby's father.
- What?
- What do you mean?
- It's not him. The baby's father.
But you don't have
any other man than him.
What's this? By any chance...
- It was from an one-night stand?
- Mind your own business.
Oh my god. It was really from
an one-night stand? Seriously?
I said mind your own business.
I'm going to raise the kid
by myself anyway.
Only I should know
who the baby's father is.
It's not that guy in Brazil.
So don't cause trouble for his family.
And don't go around
blabbing about the baby's dad.
Also...
- I'm going to move to another country.
- What? Why?
If I live in Korea
I'll get tired of being constantly
asked about the baby's father.
The kid will feel burdened too.
I should move to another country
and raise the kid in peace.
You can't raise a kid by yourself in
another country. You'd feel sad.
Just raise your kid in Korea.
You'll have Do Kyung and me.
We can all raise the kid together.
I won't ignore you once I hit it big.
Just raise the kid in Korea!
Where would you even go?
- Shut up. Forget it.
- No. You forget it.
I'm late. Let's go.
We have arrived.
Soo Kyung. I'll see you tonight!
Okay? Stay strong! Cheer up!
If I tell you I'm pregnant with
your baby, you'll probably pass out.
And things will get
really awkward between us.
I'll keep this a secret for life.
Raising the kid by myself
would be the right thing to do.
Let's just maintain
our sibling-like relationship.
Thanks for having
the conception dream for the baby.
I'll keep it in my memory.
The stars. The fish.
How funny.
You don't have to explain yourself.
A man and woman making up
and breaking up are like
the sunrise and rainfall.
We are not going to break up.
Don't break up. Ever.
Congratulations.
[1 out of 38 in class.
2 out of 500 in entire school.]
[Name: Oh Hae Young]
Oh my! Oh my! Oh my god!
Oh my! She must have gone crazy! Honey!
Hae Young must have gone crazy!
What is it?
She got first place in her class.
Second in her entire school.
She placed second out of 500 kids.
Of course!
She should go to University of Seoul.
Sure. I'll talk to you later. Bye.
- Who are you calling now?
- My sister-in-law.
- That's enough.
- What do you mean?
She's always bragging about
her daughter's academic success.
She has to hear me brag too.
She would've never guessed
this day would come.
It's me. Have you had dinner yet?
By the way, did you get
Seo Hee's report card yet?
Hae Young missed the top place in
the entire school just by a little.
I'll get the door.
I think our report cards were switched.
I'll give it to you tomorrow.
I'll give it to you in school tomorrow.
Could I...
get it signed before giving it to you?
Then I'll get it signed
and give it back to you too.
Ms. Oh, please come in.
Normally, I always place first
or second out of the entire school.
But I didn't study this time.
I just guessed on all the questions.
It seems like I'll be
getting a divorce again.
I want to get out of this house.
My stomach hurts.
That's what I thought. There's no way.
Number 27, Oh Hae Young.
B, C, C, B, D, D, D, C, D...
I was scared for a moment.
I thought Hae Young had actually
placed second out of all the students.
- Why would that scare you?
- Huh?
I... don't know.
I don't know why it did...
It's okay! Eat up!
Why would they put two girls
with the same name in the same class?
You should have picked up on it.
She usually places in the 200s or 300s.
How could you believe she came
in second in the entire school?
Of course their report cards
were switched.
Hae Young. Thanks to you,
I've had a good laugh.
[Oh Hae Young]
- So you're that Oh Hae Young?
- Yes.
Her eyes are too big.
It's fine! Grades aren't everything!
That's when I got this feeling.
The feeling that I would forever
come in second to you.
The feeling that I won't be
able to do anything
about the kids
who were raised with love.
This is buy one, get one free.
So you can take another one of these.
[Passionate Bottle Opener]
You thought
I'd make a move on you, didn't you?
Thank you. Bye!
Why do you seem so down?
I...
think I know why I can't be successful.
Why not?
I can't be a success...
because I love you.
Who is trying to seduce you?
Must be a powerful woman.
You're a bit like that. Must be nice
to be so quick on the uptake.
I have these special senses
all throughout my body.
My entire body is a tentacle.
I'm so proud of you.
It's hard not to be
seduced by a woman.
You didn't fall for her
even when she offered you success?
Good boy.
Here you go. Have a sausage.
Welcome.
If I could love you
and be successful...
What should we do? They're going to
mow the barley field tomorrow.
We're in a hurry to get
more filming done there too.
- When are they mowing it?
- Tomorrow morning.
You should've worked out
a better schedule!
I'm sorry.
What would you like to do?
It would be nice for us
if you could come
but I feel bad asking you to.
If you can get its sound recorded at
another location, that's fine too.
All right. Okay.
We should just go.
If not there, we have to
go all the way to Go Chang.
They're mowing that field next week too.
They should just leave it.
Why mow it? It looks pretty.
- They need to harvest it.
- Weren't they there for the view?
Can we get there and back by today?
When will you be back?
Tomorrow?
Tomorrow won't do!
So I can't see you until tomorrow?
I guess there is no other way.
Work comes first.
All right. I'll see you tomorrow.
If I'm still alive by tomorrow,
I'll see you then.
If I die from missing you too much,
I guess I won't be able to see you.
Let's see if I'm alive until tomorrow.
I'm hanging up.
- Yes. What do you need?
- I have a favor to ask.
What is it?
Let Assistant Manager Oh
work out of the office today.
- She can leave work from there.
- Don't be ridiculous.
- Can't you make it happen?
- No.
- Just this once.
- Forget it.
I'll be good to you from now on.
You son of a bitch.
He's being ridiculous.
She won't allow it?
Hello.
Who's buying these?
I am. I feel bad for
all the things I've done.
By the way...
If you'd like to hang out with me,
today is the only day.
I'm free today only.
Starting from tomorrow,
I'll be busy forever.
Until the day I die.
Good for you. Take this one.
And another one...
Hello, everyone.
Ms. Oh Hae Young?
This is her.
- Ms. Oh Hae Young?
- Yes. That's me.
We're from Seo Bu police department.
- Your phone number is 072-11...
- 1131.
That's right. Thanks.
It's 1131. Right?
- Yes. That's right.
- For violating the laws of
Information and Communications,
you'll have to come with us.
- Officer Go, arrest her.
- Huh?
Ms. Oh!
I think you have the wrong person.
I haven't done anything bad.
We know.
There are two Oh Hae Youngs here.
Do you know this too?
- Yes. We know about that too.
- I see...
Ms. Oh! Ms. Oh!
- Do you want another one?
- What is he doing?
What? I didn't do anything.
[Manager Kim]
- Hello?
- Ms. Oh, what happened?
I think someone did something bad
using my name.
- If I get my hands on them...
- Don't use your phone. Turn it off.
The more you use your phone,
the more serious your crime gets.
Every time you use your phone,
more money is getting leaked.
I'll call you back later.
[Power off]
Is money getting leaked even
when I simply pick up my calls?
Yes. It's leaking every time
your phone rings.
Since when has my phone been like this?
How much is my phone bill?
I'll be paid back for this. Right?
I won't have to pay
for everything, right?
If we report this,
I'll get paid back. Right?
Hold on! Hold on. You're so talkative.
This woman is noisy.
Just close your mouth like this.
- How dare she.
- Officer Go.
What's that? I think
the criminals are right there.
There they are. It's them.
The guy in the hat is the meanest one.
His personality sucks the most.
Hello.
We're late.
You guys should have hurried.
Which freeway are we taking?
- How did you guys get her out?
- We had our ways.
Good work.
- You scared me!
- Everyone except the driver, sleep.
What? Nonsense!
You shouldn't sleep either!
Even the wind is blowing.
We are very fortunate.
You know our movie has
only a few lines, right?
So the sound effects are very important.
I'm trusting you.
I'll get going then.
I'll see you at the next location.
Our next location is Manri-po Beach.
We don't have a lot of time. Let's hurry.
We'll go by ourselves.
Don't worry about it and have fun.
After we're done,
we'll come pick you up.
- All right. Good luck.
- Have a good time!
But isn't this a bad location
to leave them?
Maybe we should drop them in the city
where they could lie down and rest.
Wouldn't you prefer those places?
- You bastard!
- Your mouth!
Your mouth always causes trouble!
My goodness.
Let's go! Let's drive!
Let's go.
No one is around.
Let me hug you.
Here.
It's still daytime.
- Let's go.
- So what if it is daytime?
What? What have I done?
[C.E.O: Lee Chan Soo]
[C.E.O: Han Tae Jin]
You've been waiting long, right?
You should have called me first.
I had to go into customs
early in the morning...
The office has been expanded. Seems like
it's better off than when I was here.
They say the good comes with the bad.
Not long after that happened to you,
the European market starting buying.
After seeing that, all these banks
that couldn't have cared less
finally started making investments.
When we had begged them for loans
they didn't blink an eye.
What do you need me to do now?
What should I do?
Take your time.
You've just gotten out of jail.
Did you work things out with Hae Young?
Is it going smoothly?
We don't have anything to work out.
Of course I'll give you
your position back.
We've been through a lot together.
Look after Hae Young first.
Just hurry and get married.
Don't hurt her again by investing
all of your time in your work and stuff.
I think she should take priority.
Let's go. Let's get something to eat.
Please leave a message after the beep.
Appropriate rates may apply...
Is this Seo Bu Police Department?
Yes. We're looking for Ms. Oh Hae Young?
Oh Hae Young.
But they told us they were
from Seo Bu Police Department.
They took her with them.
- Those guys aren't our people.
- They're not?
Oh my...
Apparently, they weren't the police.
No. They weren't the police.
- You can zoom in on that car, right?
- Yes.
- These bastards are pros.
- Pros?
They've purposely hid
the license plates from view.
Then what should we do?
Excuse us. This is the police.
This is Ms. Oh Hae Young's house, right?
Ms. Oh Hae Young was kidnapped
by unidentified assailants.
So we're investigating.
There are two Oh Hae Youngs.
There is another Oh Hae Young
other than my daughter.
- Ma'am, wake up.
- Ma'am, are you okay?
Ma'am.
The barking of dogs
in the countryside in early evening...
I like that sound the most at this hour.
On a cold winter morning
I like hearing the sound of
shoveling snow under my blanket.
Around four in the afternoon
the sound of a little boy
running down a hill.
And...
the sound of a music box.
It sounds pretty.
And there is a sound I'd like to hear.
You saying my name.
You've never called me Hae Young.
Hae Young is still her, not me, huh?
I'm sorry I'm arguing again.
It's so petty of me.
It's quite okay.
It's the name you called
somebody else for a long time.
I thought you might think that way,
so that's why I couldn't call you that.
You might think
I'm calling somebody else.
I was afraid you'd think I call your name
thinking about the other Hae Young.
You may be right.
But my name is Hae Young, after all.
Just call me by my name.
I won't think about the other
Oh Hae Young when I look at you.
I hope you feel comfortable.
And call me by my name.
I want to ask for a favor too.
No matter what Han Tae Jin
does to me, don't get involved.
No matter what he does
it's right to take it all.
I've done so much wrong.
I even took you away from him too.
So whatever he puts me through...
don't get involved.
Don't think about Oh Hae Young
when you look at me.
And I will pay for my wrongdoing.
Let's do it that way, shall we?
Plus...
Stop putting distance between us
with how you address me.
What is up with that?
What should I call you then?
You know what it is.
- What is it?
- That.
What is it?
Honey.
Hae Young.
No more honey.
- Open your eyes.
- What?
I want you to look at the stars.
Shall we just die today?
I'd want to die when I'm happiest.
Park Do Kyung!
Why don't you answer?
I know you're there!
You're surrounded right now!
What kind of outrageous date is this?
You're in someone's barley field!
You've been here all day!
Why don't you wrap up
whatever you were doing?
Come out now!
I said come out now!
Wow, you do look like detectives.
You sure do.
The crime of impersonating a cop
and obstruction of justice.
You're in big trouble now.
Officer Park...
Gosh, we are in trouble.
Such bastards!
When they are so old,
how could they pull off such a thing?
You! I will break your legs!
I will lock you up in the house.
Otherwise, I will die
sooner than expected!
Of all the things,
you pulled off such a crazy stunt!
When you come home
you will die by my hands!
You bitch!
I'm sorry.
You keep her.
Take her.
Just let him take her.
Well...
- What do you think? Good, right?
- It's okay.
That makes me sad.
Do you know how much this is?
Are you crazy?
Don't you know not to eat pineapple
while you're pregnant?
You don't know much, do you?
You are a soon-to-be mom.
It's all theory.
Whatever it is, wouldn't it
feel safer not to have it?
I want to come over.
I haven't been able to do so,
because it's not good...
when there is
someone pregnant in the house.
Do a search on the Internet.
On what's allowed
and what's not during pregnancy.
Now you'll have a lot of time
since you won't be drinking.
Look who is here.
Excuse me.
What's going on?
How are they walking in together?
What are they doing here?
What are you guys doing?
What's going on?
Don't mind me
and take care of your business.
I just came here to eat.
She knows what kind of
human being you are, huh?
I do know. Carry on.
I saw your cell phone.
I wondered what you saved me as.
As your darling or just my name?
I was saved as Mon.
I wondered what Mon meant.
But then again, there were Tue, Wed...
Mon, Tue, Wed, Thurs, Fri, Sat.
Wait, there was no Sun.
Is it your day off?
How do you like seeing
us all at the same time?
I thought about how to end it.
It can't be fun to just end it, you know.
Six of us are thinking about
beating you up all together.
Wait, seriously?
We could talk about this.
Why are you doing this?
This is not the way, seriously!
Cuckoo. Cuckoo.
Don't touch him and walk away.
Why bother getting your hands dirty?
It's partially your fault that you
fell for him for his profession.
Why are you butting in?
Who the hell are you, old lady?
I'm Mademoiselle. I'm Miss.
I'm the one for Sundays.
He's with me on Sundays.
We live together.
- You're married?
- No, no. I'm not married...
I'll give you advice
as someone who's been there.
Don't focus on
appearance, job, or money.
Go out with a guy
for his personality.
Ooh-la-la.
Never mind.
You should have the right character
to be able to tell the difference.
Fine. Continue to focus on the outside.
Keep focusing on the outside
and meeting losers like him.
Fighting!
You seriously!
Ma'am, you're scaring me.
What was that about?
It was so girly.
Thank you. You handled it at once.
It's always better for a woman
to handle another woman.
Don't you think so?
How am I going to find
all different women for each day?
I'm sorry.
Jin Sang.
When I think about
how you were in high school
you were so adorable in every way.
You were adorable when you came home
crying when your principal passed away.
You were adorable when you pushed
the cart in the neighborhood...
for the old man who was picking up trash.
When you were studying with Do Kyung
you two waited for me
at the bus stop when I was late.
So when I saw you at the bus stop
you were adorable
and it made me happy.
When I think about
how you were in high school
you were adorable in every way.
Why did you change all of a sudden?
I'm sure only you know the reason.
Something must have happened, huh?
Jin Sang, by the way...
you're such a cool guy.
Why are you doing this all of a sudden?
You make me want to cry.
Stop blaming yourself.
Meet someone nice and marry her.
And...
Make sure you become
the Minister of Justice.
I won't tell the kid
that you're the father.
But I want the baby's father
to be someone worthy
even if he won't be around.
The father who is respectable and cool.
There are two men who
joined the company at the same time.
We will see the reaction
of the one who failed at his job.
- Too much.
- I'm full.
It feels good after a workout
during the lunchtime.
Excuse me, Na Sang Gyu.
Na Sang Gyu!
How can you sleep after lunch?
Manager, after lunch is
the perfect time to get some sleep.
You young fellow.
You always sleep after lunch.
That's what happened to your belly.
You should exercise like I do.
Crazy girl.
What are they thinking?
Just let them be.
I don't think it will work
to force them to separate.
- Your chicken is ready.
- Thank you.
- You don't deliver, do you?
- No. I'm sorry.
Well, if it's good,
it's never too far.
It takes 10 minutes by foot.
Thank you.
Thank you. Bye.
After I became an attorney
I never thought I'd have
to bail out Park Do Kyung one day.
What is it about her, huh?
He's completely in love with her.
I was with her today.
She was talkative.
- She was very talkative.
- He wouldn't like someone talkative.
She must have something
amazing other than that.
What is it about her that attracts him?
Ask him directly.
You think he'll tell us what it is, huh?
I told you not to drink it
out of the bottle, Dog Jin Sang!
My mouth isn't dirty like yours.
Dog Jin Sang, get a cup!
Get a cup!
- Get a cup! Get a cup!
- Nah!
Say it again.
Dog Jin Sang?
You're way younger than he is.
How dare you kick him?
How dare you add "dog" to his name?
What's gotten into you?
I've been doing that for years.
Because of his name, he already seems
more like a nasty piece of work.
How dare you add
"dog" in front of his name?
You're making him sound like
a more nasty piece of work.
Jin Sang is 36 years old
and will be 40 soon.
Will you still call him
Dog Jin Sang after he's 40?
After he's married with kids,
will you still call him Dog Jin Sang?
You've said "Dog Jin Sang"
more that I have now.
From now on, treat him with respect.
And he's being rude
when he's way younger.
Why are you letting him do that to you?
There is a difference
between being close and rude.
If he crosses the line
you should warn him.
You get treated well
only if you ask for it.
Don't let others treat you badly in life.
What's gotten into you?
It feels weird.
You're treating him badly.
It makes me uncomfortable.
So stop it.
You've been treating him
worse than we have.
- Why?
- I said stop!
I think I know why...
Oh my, I think I'm sensing things...
What is it?
Now what's wrong with you?
Please say no.
Say no. Please say no.
What are you two doing now?
Gosh, we never did it!
You've never done it with me!
No way! Such nonsense!
That dream!
You're right.
It was a precognitive dream
about the baby.
- No!
- You crazy bastard!
- No, it's not true!
It's not right. It wasn't me. Wait.
It wasn't me.
Hey, who is more miserable here?
Who is more miserable?
For the crime you've committed by
cheating on so many women all these years
You're sentenced for life,
which is to live with Park Soo Kyung.
You punk!
Hold him!
Hey!
- Hold him!
- Wait! No way!
You can't evoke the right
to remain silent, Dog Jin Sang!
No way!
Will it be too hard?
Will it work?
Hae Young.
Honey.
Yes?
Hae Young.
- Honey.
- Hae Young.
Honey.
Hae Young.
I'm sorry.
I know that I'm the crazier one
in this situation.
I won't ask you to forgive him.
I also won't ask you to forgive me.
I will take all the blame.
Seriously...
You're making me a complete idiot.
I'm sorry.
Do Kyung.
- Are you off somewhere?
- On my way to a blind date.
I'm so transparent.
I poured my heart out
for you not too long ago.
But this was arranged even before that.
Sorry.
I'm glad to know
you'll be on a blind date.
- I'm late for the date.
- Go ahead.
See you next time.
Let's get together for a drink
with Hae Young some day.
Sure.
The love that makes
someone want to die for the sake of...
can be the pain that makes
someone want to die for the sake of.
But I can't help
caring more about my love.
Okay.
Seriously?
- It's done.
- Is it?
This was amazing.
I want to call in to let
everybody know we're going out.
That we're going out...
Hello. My father owned this house.
I heard that you wanted to buy it.
Do you still want to buy it?
My father's passed away.
Let's go beg for his forgiveness.
It's taken us longer, but we've
ended up with the right people.
From the woman who used to live here...
- Isn't it courteous to meet twice?
- Oh Hae Young who has left...
Too hot!
I burnt my hands.
Luckily it's my left hand.
I was braising beef
and ended up spilling it all.
It always happens
when I try to do something new.
You haven't eaten, have you?
Ta-da!
Someone hurts themself
and someone dies.
So those things won't change, huh?
What's all this about?
Subtitles by DramaFever