This program is suitable
for viewers ages 15 and up.
Subtitles by DramaFever
I'm going to scan you.
- I'm tired.
- Don't put me down. Don't.
Stop moving. Look straight into my eyes.
If you're tired,
let's finish this quickly.
- Here. Look. Look at me.
- My senses are tingling.
My senses are tingling.
I see you haven't fallen for
that seductive woman.
Good boy. Good job.
Guys who look like delinquents actually
don't act like them. Don't you know?
- Let's go.
- Let's head in.
- I guess Do Kyung hasn't come home yet?
- No.
You look like a newlywed wife
waiting for her husband.
- So you've made some soup for him?
- Yeah.
I was just kidding.
That woman has lost it.
Are you crazy? How could you drink?
Have you given up on your life?
I'm pretending to be drunk.
- Because my body is bored.
- Oh my goodness.
- Hello.
- Let's head in.
- What did Jin Sang say?
He hasn't called you?
Move aside. Move!
He has run away.
I knew he would do something like this.
You must have done something wrong.
It must be something huge.
It really must be something huge.
Whatever. Forget it.
My goodness.
Oh my god! Oh my!
You scared me!
- Have you eaten yet?
- No. Not yet.
I've made you some soup.
[Episode 15: Those Past Days
I Couldn't Give You More, More Love]
Wow.
What does it feel like?
Using the workspace your father
used to use for yourself.
Wow. How does it feel like
to use the same workspace
your father used to use?
It just seems very fancy.
It feels like you're carrying on
the name of a prestigious family.
Could I ask you...
when your father passed away?
When I was eight years old.
So he passed away
when you were young.
Did he have an illness?
[Baek Il Mong - Do Kyung]
It was from an accident.
It happened when he went to
record some sounds with me.
It must have been very shocking for you.
If I think about it now, I think it's
better that it happened that way.
I'm glad I was there when it happened.
I didn't let him die by himself.
Wouldn't dying be less scary
if there is someone who could
hold your hand as you die?
You, who have come to me like a dream
on an early spring day...
- Who's singing?
- Me.
I thought it would last forever.
This is what my dad recorded for me
when I was six years old.
- The sand castle full of happiness.
- My sister is playing the piano.
It got washed away with a wave.
You may leave me.
You may forget about me.
I will have this one heart, only you.
Oh my god. It feels so weird.
I regret those past days.
- I couldn't give you more, more love.
- So this kid is the guy I like, right?
- It feels like he's alive right now too.
- He is alive. Right here.
The dream I can't wake up from.
The daydream.
Oh my. What to do?
He's so bravely singing without
even knowing what the lyrics mean.
I will love you
forever.
That beach on that summer night.
The sand castle full of happiness.
I was confused in the beginning too.
He looks perfectly normal.
But he kept on telling me
he could see these visions.
Then all those visions came true.
Wait. No. Not all of them.
Some of them didn't come true.
That's the problem.
Before dying...
I was thinking about that woman.
Since the moment I've first met her
I've regretted every moment.
Why couldn't I...
give her more, more love?
Because that remorseful
feeling is so strong
maybe it has pierced through time
and revealed itself
in the present.
Have you heard about
reaching enlightenment
at the moment of one's death?
Everyone clearly sees it
at their moment of death.
That they had nothing to fear.
- That's when you've realized it, right?
- Yes.
Human emotions can be divided
into two categories.
Love or fear.
One of them is genuine
and the other one is fake.
You've found out about what's genuine.
So your circumstances changed
when you decided to turn to love.
But why are you being hesitant?
Why are you ending our session so soon?
- You should have put him under hypnosis.
- It's all useless.
He knows which path
he's supposed to take.
He just came here
because he's temporarily scared.
He'll go down that path again.
But still...
Why do you think I've come
all this way to see you?
- Try some other place then.
- My goodness!
I regret those past days.
I couldn't give you more, more love.
Let's listen to it one more time.
- Let's listen to something else.
- Just one more time.
Why not?
Mother and older sister
let's live by the riverside.
- No way.
- That's right. It's Soo Kyung.
The shining, golden sand.
Wow.
Outside the back door...
This little girl.
Mother and older sister
let's live by the riverside.
Park Soo Kyung, who used to be so cute.
Where have you flown away to?
Smile! Put on a smile!
We look so pretty!
I'm sorry.
Welcome to our housewarming party!
Their bathroom is clean and nice.
- Where's the bathroom?
- Over there.
I would like to say just a few words.
In our house, you squat down and pee.
You'll die if you spill it anywhere.
Be careful.
Ta da. Look here. Over here.
Honey, you look so pretty.
You scared me!
I thought you would run away.
I'm surprised you came home.
You're more responsible than I thought.
I guess it's hard to ignore
your blood-related family.
Hey! You animal!
How did this happen between you two?
If I knew how,
that would mean my memory is intact.
If I did what I did
with impaired awareness...
then I'm a complete lunatic.
Maybe you go around causing
trouble like this everywhere.
Stop it. I'm more serious than ever.
Serious my ass.
I know you. You'll linger
for a little bit and run away.
- Run away?
- It's fine. I completely understand.
I'm not old-fashioned. I'm not going to
side with my family and all that.
I know how you feel.
It'd be too bad for you to end your life
because of Park Soo Kyung at your age.
You should try to make
some sort of an appeal.
Just do what's enough and leave.
Do what's enough and leave?
My sister isn't old-fashioned either.
She'll take what she deserves
and let you go freely.
Look at this rude bastard.
What would she take?
A kid isn't some sort of an object.
How could we make calculations?
Do you really want to talk like
a delinquent? About your sister?
A delinquent...
You're being ridiculous.
I was being considerate. How dare you.
What is it? Were you shocked?
Because I've read your mind?
I'm already mad enough.
- Would you like to fight me?
- Sure! Let's go! Come on!
- How dare you!
- Ouch. Hey! Hey! Hey!
This bastard.
I've been going easy on you.
Park Hoon!
You. Didn't I tell you I'll kill you
if you disrespect Jin Sang ever again?
It's just that he called me a delinquent.
I've done wrong.
You. Didn't I tell you to get
treated properly for your age?
You! You!
You are going to
kill this bastard today.
If they keep coming at you,
you need to kill them.
If you go easy on them,
they'll keep coming at you again.
Before they keep coming for you,
clearly finish them off!
Until you've killed this bastard
you can't leave this room.
Cleanly finish him off.
Die.
Brother-in-law.
- I've done wrong.
- Brother-in...
I'm not your brother-in-law!
I'm just like an older brother!
This isn't just horrible
and awkward for you.
It's like that for me too.
No need for you to get serious.
You and I could never
be a married couple.
You are aware of this. I am too.
You've been like a little brother
for the past 20 years.
And I've been like an older sister.
I'm going to move to another country
and you can freely
live your life just like now.
So stop lingering here.
Pack your stuff and move out.
Just move out. It's okay.
It's my baby.
You.
Could you ever kiss me?
I'll give you one day.
Think about whether
you could kiss me or not.
Then...
You'll have your answer.
- Oh my.
- Get out of my way!
- Do they both have to take a dump?
- Be careful. You might trip.
How gross.
[A Castle Within the Forest]
Why isn't he coming out?
- Are you creating your shit?
- How gross. What did he eat?
[May of 2014]
[Thank you for your love.
June 10, 2016]
I didn't think you'd actually come.
I thought you said it out of politeness.
This situation is just...
You can't judge a person
after seeing them once.
Thank you.
So I'm grateful to you right now for...
For being so pretty.
I'm probably the only one
who feels this way. I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Oh my. I'm sorry.
I shouldn't be checking my phone.
- Oh no. It's okay. Check it if you want.
- Should I turn it off?
Sure. It'd be nice if
you could turn it off.
I'll turn it off.
[Power Off]
Thank you.
- It feels refreshing.
- Park Hoon. Should I drive?
Who else would drive?
I'm not licensed to drive this.
Come. Hurry.
You're getting married tomorrow.
How do you feel?
I feel weird saying this, but my parents
are both extremely nervous right now.
Maybe I should break it off
like you the day before.
Be clear. I didn't break it off.
I was dumped.
I guess you feel fine about it now?
You're telling people you got dumped.
Of course I'm fine.
My friend who was supposed
to catch my bouquet
is upset and crying because she
and her boyfriend broke up.
Now I can't ask her to
catch my bouquet.
No worries. I'll catch it for you.
Huh? For real?
Are you coming to my wedding?
Of course. Why wouldn't I?
You're getting married.
Mom said you weren't coming.
Your mom said you weren't coming either.
Don't worry.
I'll go and catch your bouquet.
- Are you really going to come?
- Yeah. What's wrong?
I just don't want you to
feel uncomfortable.
Why would I be?
You know, about what
you said on the radio.
Everyone knows how strangely
your wedding was ruined.
The conclusion is...
I'm dating the man
who ruined my wedding.
- For real?
- Yes. For real.
So I'll catch your bouquet.
I'll be catching it, ma'am.
This is awesome.
I'm curious to know what he looks like.
All right then. I'll bring him
to the wedding tomorrow.
You'll be surprised, ma'am.
He's a keeper.
Even his hands are sexy.
Thinking about him
makes me miss him again.
Deok Hee. Is what Hae Young saying true?
Is she really dating that man?
I see you've read it!
Why won't you text back?
- You scared me.
- Bring him where?
You're bringing whom?
- What's wrong with it?
- Don't you know?
People will call you a crazy bitch
for dating that guy.
They'll curse at both of you! How could
you bring him to a family event?
Can't you just be on my side?
Even without you pointing fingers at him,
he's the one who feels the most guilty.
Can't you just tell me it'll all be okay
and pat me on the back?
I want to show him.
That no one in my family blames him
and he shouldn't be discouraged.
Just quietly date him
and break things off.
I'm not just going to date him.
What? Tell her I hate the way she eats?
Hey, you bastard!
How could you say that to a woman?
- Huh?
- Sir.
How could you make me
say that to a woman?
You should have advised me
to tell her the truth!
You said that woman backed off.
So then it was a success!
You come over here.
- Why?
- Come over here.
- You're dead meat.
- How come?
Come over here.
You bastard.
I was the crazy one.
I can't believe
I listened to a guy like you.
What's wrong? Do you feel regretful
now that you've dumped her?
Or does your heart ache like this?
Park Do Kyung.
What should I do with you?
Has Hae Young called you?
- To ask you to go to a wedding together?
- No, she hasn't.
Hae Young's cousin is
getting married tomorrow.
She wants to take you with her.
Because she's an idiot, she thinks
dating always leads to marriage.
But that's not quite true
for kids nowadays, right?
They may do some crazy stuff together,
but that's irrelevant to marriage.
Our Hae Young is already thinking
about getting married to you.
But you're testing the waters.
Right?
I like Hae Young.
You've left out some words.
"I'll marry her."
I'm sorry for being old-fashioned.
If she introduces you to
the elders at a family event
it means you two will get married.
If you tell people you two have
broken up after that
it's equivalent to
breaking a marriage off.
That's how the elders will take it.
Even if she asks you to just come to
the wedding and grab a meal...
you can't come to it
with that same mindset.
If you're determined that you'll
marry Hae Young no matter what
then you can come tomorrow.
If not, don't come.
If there is even the slightest thing
stopping you, don't come.
Hae Young's marriage
has been ruined once.
I can't just stand and watch
another one get ruined like that.
What did he say?
He's not the one.
[Hae Young]
- Hey.
- Why did you take so long to answer?
- I was showering.
- You were showering?
Sorry. What are you doing tomorrow?
I'm going to the countryside for work.
I'll be back in the afternoon.
Is that so?
I'm going to my cousin's
wedding tomorrow.
I'll see you at my house tomorrow
evening. I'll cook you something good.
Wow. Seriously? You know how to cook?
I'm good at it.
Don't eat too much at the wedding.
All right. I've got it.
- What do you like to eat?
- Everything.
I don't particularly hate
or love any type of food.
Should we get a drink tomorrow too?
I think it's been forever
since I've had a drink.
I think it's been over 10 days.
I've figured out why
I had been drinking so much.
It was because I wasn't happy.
Nowadays, I feel happy
all the time as if I'm drunk.
- Thank you.
- I'm more grateful.
Oh my god!
Why aren't you in bed?
Don't worry about tomorrow.
He can't come to the wedding anyway.
He has to work.
Are you looking for me?
Oh my god!
- Are you ready?
- No. I mean...
- Should we kiss?
- It's just that I have... You know...
It's not like that. No. Absolutely not.
Tell me when you're ready.
If you lack the confidence,
then give up.
Get ready for what?
How am I supposed to get ready for it?
This just isn't it from the get-go.
How could we?
Just throw it up high and far.
Here we go. Throw it!
Nice catch.
Is she getting married again?
You see... It's technically not "again."
- She didn't get married that time.
- So she's going to marry that guy again?
Mother, I'll tell you about everything
in detail when we get home.
Is she going to have another wedding?
I will tell you later.
We will do it one more time.
This time, throw it gently.
Ready? Throw it.
It was salty.
All buffets makes me thirsty.
- Here.
- I'm okay.
I haven't seen a very beautiful bride
yet at wedding halls.
I tell them
they're beautiful as a courtesy.
If someone tells me that
I'm pretty at my wedding
I will never be fooled.
Why did you come along?
You should've stayed home.
She's at home, you know.
Don't take too much time.
Make a decision.
Whatever decision you make
my sister or I won't resent you.
Do Kyung, can you
possibly kiss your sister?
- Are you crazy?
- That's how I feel right now.
Now you understand how I feel?
If the idea of kissing is possible,
the answer is right there.
I think I have my answer.
But I still feel that
I need to do something.
Gosh, I really don't know what to do.
What is it? Are you going to
cook for Oh Hae Young Two?
Can't you call her by the right name?
It's just that they have the same name.
In the order of when you met them...
Oh Hae Young One
and Oh Hae Young Two.
I'm sorry.
I said I'm sorry.
By the way, if you want
to cook for a lady
you should've asked me about it first.
Why would you buy such a thing, huh?
You know, I graduated from Stanford
with theadegree in cooking for women.
If a man wants to cook for a woman
it doesn't matter what's on the menu.
You have to choose the menu
that will make you look cool.
For example, you know a pepper grinder.
You know the one you twist, see?
This movement will
fascinate women, okay?
And squeezing a lemon.
When you squeeze
a lemon with one hand
your arm muscles pop out.
Women go crazy for it.
Or when you shake salt...
This is sort of too boring.
You might get criticized
for copying others.
So you'll have to pick food that involves
grinding pepper and squeezing lemons.
So it always comes down to a pasta dish!
Hae Young likes Korean food.
Did you just see me?
How excited I was talking about women?
How poor am I now?
Hey.
My sister likes melon.
Are you trying to mock me?
We have soy sauce at home.
Did you look for me?
Are you ready?
Shall we kiss?
When you're ready, tell me.
Get out of my way!
Wow, the way your dishes look
already passed the test.
Oh no, it doesn't come out right.
- Just eat.
- Hold on.
I don't usually take pictures of dishes.
But it's my first time
having what you cooked.
I will take a photo
and save it as a memory.
Wow, I got it.
Yeah, it came out well.
- Eat.
- Sure.
Let's see.
Wow. Not bad.
You made the broth separately, huh?
Impressive.
Is there anything you can't do?
You can't do cute, can you?
You can't say "How cute!"
squeezing my cheeks, can you?
I will do it later.
Let's hurry up then.
Slow down.
Aren't you going to tell me
that the way I eat is pretty?
Do you like hearing that
after you ask me?
That's pretty.
I'm so happy!
Soo Kyung.
24 hours have passed. Now leave.
Come on, Soo Kyung.
You now know that
we can't even kiss.
But how are we supposed
to live as a married couple?
It's just not going to happen!
Don't take any more time
and just get out of my life.
How am I supposed to
get out of your life?
How is that possible?
There is the baby.
It's okay. Don't feel pressured.
It's not entirely your responsibility.
I will raise the baby on my own.
And until I emigrate
don't come by.
Can you possibly kiss me?
I think I can.
Seriously?
Wait. Wait.
Don't get too aggressive.
Okay... I got it.
Jin Sang.
- Here.
- Okay.
Ta-da!
This is a letter for me
written by a high school boy.
It's so cute.
I found it while going
through my letters today.
He's so cute. Listen to this.
I won't get jealous
of a high school boy, okay?
Just listen to this.
"I saw you walking and sobbing
on your way from school."
"Seeing you sobbing,
my heart also broke down."
"I wanted to comfort you."
"But I couldn't interrupt
while you were crying."
"I just followed behind you."
"If you happened to collapse from crying"
"I wanted to give you a hug."
Who was this guy?
"What happened?"
"What was so bad
that made you sob like that?"
"When you said it was
because Chang Gook Young died"
"I suddenly hated Chang Gook Young
who made you cry."
"I was jealous of him
and wanted to be him."
Tell him that Do Kyung
wants to meet him.
"When I got home,
I ripped up all his pictures."
"I was furious."
Isn't he cute?
Come on, he's so cute.
What is it?
It's a love letter
sent to you in high school.
I knew right away that
this letter was meant for you.
I didn't want to give it to you.
It's okay. Grades aren't everything.
You grew up being loved by your parents.
I didn't want you to
have more love from a boy.
I felt like you were taking
something from me.
I've been throwing away
many letters all these years.
I just couldn't throw away this letter.
Because it wasn't meant for me.
I thought I'd be able to return
this letter to you smiling some day.
When I became good enough
to admit that I was jealous of you
I might be able to
return this letter to you.
That's why I haven't
been able to throw it away.
I'm not good enough yet.
I feel that I need to
return it to you now.
I should return it first
and focus on becoming good.
I am going to try.
I am going to go for it.
It took 13 years for this letter
to find its way back to you.
I'm sorry.
I also feel bad for the boy who wrote it.
I thought I was the one who
kept comparing myself to her.
She says she's kept
comparing herself to me.
Am I happy now that I know
how she's felt all along?
Is it comforting?
Why do I feel sad?
Bitch! Have a good life!
Perhaps the boy who threw
a rock at our window back then...
Hey!
I wonder if he had
feelings for me for real.
Yes. Lee Kang Yong?
Correct. Lee Kang Yong.
He might have been
in the class of seven or eight.
- Here he is.
- Can you take a photo and send it?
Okay.
- Let me see.
- No, no need to see it.
- Let me see who the punk is.
- No need to see.
- Give it.
- What are you going to do?
No, no, no.
- Let me see.
- Don't do it. No need to see.
Hold on! Wait!
What's up?
Where are you?
I'm at Hee Ran's.
I will stay over at her place tonight.
I'm serious that I'm at Hee Ran's.
Put her on the phone then.
Put Hee Ran on the phone.
Darn it.
I'm old enough to stay out.
Why are you acting this way?
You told him to take me.
Do you want me to come over right now?
Come home before you get dragged back.
You think it's good
as long as I come home at night, huh?
I can't do whatever just because
I have to come home early?
I can do whatever during the day too.
Can't you keep
your love life more private?
Why did you let
everybody know it all, huh?
You have no pride, girl.
If I ever catch you cooking for him
and going in and out of his place
- I will kill you.
- He cooked for me tonight.
Why did he have to cook for you?
Why would he cook for you
when you two are going to break up soon?
We have no food in our house?
How do you know that
we're going to break up soon?
Excuse me. Don't do this.
Come on.
I told him this.
If he ever wants to marry you
come to Suh Hee's wedding
and if not, don't show up.
That bastard didn't show up!
I'm sure he had his reasons.
Now all our family knows about you.
Not anymore.
Know that.
If you still want to see him,
see him secretly.
Why did you have to say that to him?
Why did you pressure him?
I don't have to get married.
If you weren't going to marry, why bother
planning to bring him to the party?
Because I thought it wouldn't
make you look as bad at the wedding.
I knew that everyone
would be talking about me
so I planned on it so you both
wouldn't feel so ashamed.
If he had come
you wouldn't have had
to feel so ashamed!
Hello?
What's wrong?
I cried.
How come?
My mom hit me.
Because I lied that
I was at Hee Ran's.
I'm too old to get beaten up by her.
Don't cry.
My mom is giving me
a dirty look now to hang up.
I will call you later.
When I'm about to die
if I think back on this moment
this will mean nothing.
This means nothing.
Let's go for it.
Soo Kyung, are you okay?
That's enough. Stop now.
Soo Kyung.
I'm sorry.
I've kissed so many women before.
- Honestly, with you...
- I understand.
Go.
Good try.
How can I possibly get out of your life
when you're carrying my child?
See what happens if you dance!
- Can I have one pitcher of beer here?
- Sure.
Gosh.
I had no idea about this chicken place.
Why beer and chicken during the day?
You seemed so happy that
you were on top of the world.
Now what happened?
Why do I always lower myself
when I'm in a relationship?
I was going to go for it
until I get rejected completely.
I didn't care if I loved him
more than he did.
- Now I feel differently.
- Are you still talking about that?
Honestly...
I don't understand why you think
Park Do Kyung will marry you.
Don't you have to take time
and see if he's the right one for you?
Love comes at once
when it happens.
It doesn't let me take
my time and think about it.
I want to hold his hands,
sleep with him, and marry him.
For me, it doesn't
always go in that order.
When I fall in love
in my head, I'm already sleeping
with him and being married to him.
- Is it just me?
- Yes.
- It's just you who thinks that way.
- I see.
[The Man Next Door]
- Why aren't you answering?
- I want to play hard to get.
Your call is being redirected...
[Provisional Seizure Notice]
[Decision]
By any chance...
Don't worry about this.
Is it a private loan?
He and I have
made deals many times before.
He's just doing this for no reason.
He's never said anything
when I was late with my payment.
He will lift the seizure notice soon.
Don't worry about it.
Don't think about getting
money elsewhere to stop that.
Just leave it.
Don't worry. I will handle it, okay?
I'm saying don't worry. Just leave it.
When I was little,
I'd kick a can on my way home.
I got so attached to that can
that I couldn't leave it outside.
I'm a can.
I told myself "I'm a mere can"
and went inside.
But I came out and took it inside.
That's cute.
Why didn't you answer my calls?
- Because I'm mad.
- Why?
I thought we both liked each other.
But it seems that I'm the only
one who feels that way.
If you like me
89 on the scale, not 100
then tell me so.
I will like you for the same amount.
I feel it's only 89 on the scale
when I thought it was 100.
Every time that happens...
I don't feel good.
So tell me so I can match that level.
It's 100 on the scale.
The 100 you're referring to
and mine seem different.
Mine is seriously 100 on the scale.
Because you're mad, you're
starting to call me "mister," huh?
- Go.
- Let's say bye after I give you a hug.
If I leave without one,
I'll be down.
I may get angry too.
Go now.
I will let you take away everything.
I will go down completely.
I will give you my arm if you ask.
I will give you my leg if you ask.
Just let me live.
Come inside. You will get
recorded by the CCTV there.
One sunny day...
I am walking in my favorite suit.
This guy suddenly kicks my knee.
So I ask him why.
Do you know what that punk tells me?
He says it was a mistake.
After he put me through so much
he says it was a mistake.
But that's not the end of the story.
It turns out that now
he's wearing my favorite suit.
He kicks my knee by accident.
And he steals my suit too.
What would you do
if you were me?
Spare my life.
[The Man Next Door]
I'm sorry.
I can't sleep.
I'm angry.
I miss you.
Come over.
Come over even if
you're 89 on the scale.
Come over.
I can't come.
Were you 70 on the scale?
Right before I was dying...
I was regretting that I didn't
love her with all my heart.
That's why I made another decision.
So here I am.
If I die this time
I will probably regret this moment.
When I'm not being honest.
When I couldn't be honest.
When I made her misunderstand.
When I hurt her feelings.
The same way Han Tae Jin couldn't
be honest and hurt her feelings...
Am I making the same mistake right now?
Should I tell her the truth right now?
I might die soon.
If I tell her the truth
would we still be
as happy as we are now?
If she knows that I may die soon
will she still be able
to smile at me like now?
Who did this to you?
Didn't you expect that
I'd get beaten up this much?
I expected this.
Compared to what I did to him...
I have to endure everything
including my business failure
and getting beaten up.
It's okay.
Don't you dare go see him.
I'm sorry that I didn't
come to the wedding.
I had my reasons.
Until I die
I won't leave you.
I'm 100 on the scale, not 89.
I wish Tae Jin's wounded heart
could be healed.
I wish we all could
have peace of mind.
I wish no one would be left
with an aching heart.
Not Tae Jin, me, or him...
I still want to see her smile.
I want her to be happier.
I still do.
[Many thanks to Woo Hyun,
Seo Joon Young, and Seo Ye Ji.]
Subtitles by DramaFever
Just tell her everything.
Han Tae Jin is pissed
and he will try to kill me.
What should you do?
The recording studio will be
repossessed in one or two days.
Han Tae Jin is playing badly,
unlike his build.
Am I allowed to have my heart flutter?
Now you should go home.
I may go somewhere
to have an exorcism done.
Why are so many Oh Hae Youngs
entangled in our lives?
Just relax and go with it.
I'm also curious about
how your life will end.