This program is suitable
for viewers ages 15 and up.
Subtitles by DramaFever
Who did this to you?
If I tell her the truth
would we still be
as happy as we are now?
If she knows that I may die soon
will she still be able
to smile at me
like she is now?
I won't leave you until I die.
I'm 100 on the scale, not 89.
I wish we all could
have peace of mind.
I wish no one would be left
with an aching heart.
Not Tae Jin, me, or him...
I still...
want to see her smile.
I want her to be happier.
I still do.
[Episode 16: Through You, I Live]
I'll drive you to work.
Sleep in for even 10 more minutes.
I'll come to your house.
Wow. I'm so touched. Got it.
I'm sorry. So sorry.
Are you all right? Oh no...
I must have scared you a lot.
I should've gone easier on you.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have done this
so early in the morning.
Your heart mustn't have
completely woken up yet.
I've scared you on top of that.
I was trying to impress you,
but this has turned out weird.
I can't stand up because I'm so touched.
- How long have you been waiting?
- About 10 minutes?
I told you I'll pick you up.
Why come all this way?
I felt bad for acting fussy yesterday.
I've come to you as a nice gesture.
Don't worry about
what happened yesterday.
I occasionally get mad and calm down
on my own over trivial things.
I know I shouldn't do that.
But I do, the more I like you.
- I'm sorry.
- You've done nothing wrong.
I have.
I'm not apologizing because I'm scared
you'd leave me for being fussy.
I'm apologizing because
I truly think I've done wrong.
This is how I am. I quickly apologize
for things that I've done wrong.
I don't know how I got so lucky.
Because I liked you first,
I snatched you up.
- Don't tell that to other people.
- But it's true that I liked you first.
I fell in love at first sight, chose you,
and made you mine.
Aren't you proud of me?
Thank you for falling in love
with me at first sight. Let's go.
I shouldn't try to
surprise you ever again.
Because you got so scared,
even I got scared.
Don't do it to another woman. It's
dangerous. Especially not to my sister.
She'd kill me.
I'd never do that to Director Park.
- Get in.
- I love it. This gesture.
Soo Kyung. Hold up.
Wait... I...
Soo Kyung. This isn't...
Oh my. What are you doing?
- Don't...
- Did you have a good time?
Freaking Park Hoon! You scared me!
I saw everything.
I saw you kissing Soo Kyung.
- You were kissing for quite some time.
- Keep your mouth shut.
Having a lawyer in the family.
That makes me feel stronger,
Brother-in-law.
Brother-in-law?
Do you really want to die?
You said you guys kissed.
Since you kissed, you'll get married.
If you get married,
you'll be my brother-in-aw.
You don't marry every woman you kiss.
I'd have married over a million times.
You're being so old-fashioned.
What is this? Then you won't marry her?
I'm already cornered.
Don't push me further.
Something really bad might happen then.
I'm using more brain power now than
I did when I was studying for the bar.
I'm trying to figure out
how to overcome this.
I'm trying hard to
be logical and rational.
If you keep making me mad like that
I might resort to drowning
myself in a bowl of water!
- Calm down.
- Get out of my sight.
- Barging into my room this early...
- Fine. I got it.
- Get out of my sight! Right now!
- All right. Fine.
Look at him! Look at him!
Idiot Jin Sang kissed
Park Soo Kyung!
- Park Hoon. Come out.
- I didn't disrespect him.
- I didn't say any mean things, right?
- Come out!
It'll be hard to drown yourself
in a bowl of water.
Take your time to think it over.
I'm done thinking about it.
Once you've made your decision,
we can each share our thoughts then.
What did you decide to do?
Let's talk once
you've made your decision.
So what decision have you arrived at?
Can't you tell me first?
I can't make a decision.
I never could.
Someone please make one for me.
Just tell her the truth.
About everything.
"I've seen my last dying moment."
"Because my feelings
for you were so strong"
"it has pierced time
and revealed itself in the present."
"So I've known about you
even before we actually met."
If she can't believe you,
I'll talk to her.
I'll say, "It might be hard to believe,
but this kind of stuff happens."
I'll tell her everything.
After that...
you can try to
formulate a plan with her.
Tell her, "Han Tae Jin is trying to
kill me because he is pissed."
"So what should I do?
The only way to save my life is this."
"Let's pretend thaht we broke up."
"Then he won't have
a reason to kill me."
"Let's pretend that we've broken up
and date again later."
What are you even saying?
We somehow need to save his life first.
Your logic makes no sense.
In his current vision,
he's broken up with that woman.
So even if they weren't dating,
that man would've tried to kill him.
- Is that right?
- Wait outside.
This is so hard.
I don't know what's right.
How do you feel?
I feel at ease. Very surprisingly so.
Then you're going down the right path.
Don't be nervous.
If you get nervous, you'll get scared.
Your current situations are all
consequences of your past actions.
You're facing the consequences of
neglecting those actions
out of fear and anxiety.
These circumstances will repeat
themselves until you turn to love.
Once you turn to love, because you've
learned everything you were supposed to
those similar situations will delete
themselves from your life scenario.
And that's why
your scenario is changing.
You've seen how it has changed, right?
Where are you going?
I told you to not greet me
when we run into each other.
Change out of those shoes.
Your footsteps sound uncomfortable.
Holding myself back from wanting to
embrace you has made me sick.
I'm sorry.
But this is how I genuinely feel.
If you turn to fear,
your scenario won't change.
Relax and go all the way.
I'm curious about your ending too.
- I'll see you again.
- All right.
Why are you trying to sway him?
He's going down the right path.
Is the drifting sound in sync
with the video?
I'll be there soon.
I'll take a look at it myself. Okay.
Here is what you've ordered.
Thank you.
You used to say carrying
a bouquet of flowers is embarrassing.
What's wrong with your face?
Are you okay?
It's nothing serious.
You also used to say
you hate a woman who cries.
But Hae Young cries a lot.
I get it. I know she's different.
A fearlessly honest woman like
Hae Young is perfect for you.
A woman who could love you
passionately and shamelessly.
A woman like that suits you.
You two are a good match.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
I'm purposely acting cool because
I want to be remembered as a nice woman.
I'm just kidding. Let's head up.
Don't you think Assistant Manager Oh
got so much prettier these days?
Assistant Manger Oh isn't that pretty.
- I mean she is pretty. But...
- Who's the prettiest?
- Let's not talk about this.
- Ms. Oh, you're the prettiest.
You always take things too far.
You always freeload on others.
What's with these flowers?
Can I let my heart flutter?
Usually...
if there are flowers on my desk, I think
"It has come to the wrong person again.
It should've been given to Manager Oh."
That's what I used to think.
But this one just feels like...
it's mine.
It doesn't even have a card!
If it was dropped off by a delivery man,
it should have a card!
If this was... If this was...
If it was dropped off by that man,
I could do anything today!
I thought you'd cause a scene.
So I'm just dropping the flowers off.
He came all this way!
He should've showed me his face.
I refuse your text reply.
I'm too embarrassed.
Aren't I better than Jang Gook Young?
So much better.
This bouquet of flowers is mine.
Wear your employee badge properly.
- Are you okay?
- Are you all right?
It hurts the most right now.
You know how this part hurts the most.
This makes me sweat.
So nice.
I want to enjoy this moment on my own.
- Let's go. Come on.
- I'm jealous.
His recording studio will be
seized today or tomorrow.
And what else?
Don't you have more stuff coming?
You're only taking
a building away from him?
His house isn't on the market yet.
You're so cool.
I heard your company hit big
once you lost your ownership.
So you just did all that work
for your partner?
Then you're done after
taking a building away?
You're so cool. That's fine then.
I can stop feeling sorry
for you now then, right?
If I hadn't taken my money away
after just listening to Park Do Kyung
you'd be driving
a nice car with a chauffeur.
You'd be living the life.
I just felt bad because
I thought it was all my fault.
So I tried to help you out.
But if this is enough for you,
then that's good enough for me.
Wow. You have such a big heart.
- I'll look further into it.
- No. Don't if you don't want to.
If you feel all better now,
then that's enough.
I'll look for something more.
Listen.
As a man
you need to knock the other man down.
Don't just jab at him.
Fly lightly like a butterfly
and sting like a bee!
Leave. I want to rest.
Let me be clear with you.
I didn't take my investments away
because you were up to something dirty.
I took them away because
Park Do Kyung asked me to.
Thank you.
You fool.
If you leave right now,
you'll run into Han Tae Jin!
He's not fit to run a business.
He's a scaredy-cat.
Quickly take your money
and make a run for it.
Run while you can.
I'm home!
We have rice.
We have carrots.
I thought we had stir-fried anchovies.
Here they are.
Let's see. Burdocks.
Mom, don't we have burdocks?
I need burdocks. Burdocks.
Let's see. We have dried seaweed.
How could we not have burdocks?
I don't get it.
Sesame oil. Here.
We have sesame oil.
I need a bowl.
A bowl. Here it is.
That's strange.
Why don't we have burdocks?
I just don't get it.
On May 22, 1985
a baby girl was born in this town.
Her first name is "Crazy"
and last name is "Bitch."
I hate her because she takes after me.
And I love her because
she takes after me.
Why do people with big hearts
always lead such sad lives?
How much are they?
Because she has such a big heart
that crazy girl will experience all
the hardships that I've been through.
That's why I hate her...
and love her.
At this crazy girl who
brings a can she's been kicking
into the house simply because
she couldn't throw it away...
I used to get so upset.
Then I would find it adorable.
Mom! Mom.
That crazy girl who is
pouring her heart out after falling
head over heels in love with this guy.
I don't know why it makes me tear up.
Would I feel less sad if I take
her side and cheer her on?
Instead of discouraging
and shutting her down
would I feel a little less sad if...
she had someone cheering her on?
That's why I'm sitting
next to the crazy girl
and doing this again today.
I'm almost there.
You came all the way to my workplace.
You should've showed your face.
- You're playing hard to get.
- You saw me in the morning.
What do you need?
- When are you coming home?
- Why do you ask?
I want to go home with you.
- I'll be late.
- We'll be there soon.
I made a lot of food
so that we could all eat together.
I've just heard everything! Everything!
I'll leave some food on the first floor.
Come in and have some.
But don't come up to the second floor.
You two just have lots of it!
I'm so freaking jealous! You bastard!
Hold on.
[Jin Sang]
- What's up?
- When are you coming home?
Is it because you feel awkward
being alone with Soo Kyung?
You two even kissed. What's wrong?
You go crazy over women in general.
If you treat my sister like that,
I'll be sad.
Just drink some soju in front
of a grocery store and go home.
Let's do that again.
Let's go.
It's not done yet.
Let me still look at it.
Come this way.
- Hello.
- Hey.
Is she the one? It is her.
What did you tell her?
Why is she acting this way?
Hey, kid. You don't have to look at me
like that. I don't care about your man.
He told me you tried to seduce him.
How could I ever ask you
to work together again?
You're getting angry. So it was true.
- How old are you?
- Hold on.
Hello? Yes. Director.
Talking about age will
put you at a disadvantage.
You're quite the talker. Keep going.
You know it'll just make you look funny
if you stop working with him now, right?
It doesn't seem like you tried to
seduce him because you needed a man.
I trust that you'll work with him
like a professional.
If you can't trust my Hoon
then come do work at
the coffee shop I work at.
From hearing you talk, it seems like
you're better than your boyfriend.
Sounds like you don't know
my Hoon very well.
But my Hoon is freaking good-looking.
How shocking.
You have a nice girlfriend.
I'll see you at the coffee shop!
Let's go.
Hey.
Soo Kyung likes melons.
You think you're Joo Yoon Bal?
Stop trying to act cool.
You do some crazy shit.
But I liked how you used to never smoke.
Did the results for
the bar exam come out?
I heard it's impossible to
pass that on your first try.
They'll have one next year too.
I've been drafted.
Perfect timing, right?
How could it come right after
I failed the bar exam?
If I try to study for it
after my service
I won't be able to.
I'd be stupid by then.
You can't postpone it any longer, right?
I must go.
Men have things that they must do
even if they don't want to.
There are things a man must endure.
So I'll serve.
But I was hoping
maybe this one cigarette would
make me feel a little better.
Don't breathe it in too deeply.
If a new smoker breathes in too deeply,
this might happen.
Jin Sang? Jin Sang?
I'm causing all this trouble...
but I just don't feel excited.
Because someone is helping me,
it's all going smoothly.
But I just can't get excited.
How could anyone feel excited
about ruining someone's life?
If it bothers you that much,
you should stop it.
Almost everyone who matters knows.
The fact that I went to prison
because of Park Do Kyung.
After getting released,
I see he even took my woman.
Everyone is waiting to see
what I'm going to do next.
But if I stop right here...
I want to get votes from everyone.
About what I should do.
I vote for stopping here.
Thank you for the meal.
It was delicious.
Leave it. They say it's heartless
to clean dishes right away.
By the way.
Where's my stand and music box?
Over there in the shopping bag.
Untouched.
It was childish, wasn't it?
Giving back your gifts.
It was just to show how mad I was.
I also thought they'd
make me think about you.
Did you have something to do
near my workplace today?
What were the flowers for?
You saw me in the morning.
Seeing flowers just reminded me of you.
Park Do Kyung is on a roll.
If you like me this much,
how were you holding back all this time?
I'm going to brush my teeth.
I'm going to go brush my teeth.
Brush my teeth.
As I was leaving work,
I felt bad leaving my flowers behind.
It felt like I was leaving you behind.
Just imagining it staying in
our dark office by itself
made me feel like you're the one
sitting at a dark desk by yourself.
How are you going to
look at it while it wilts?
Just imagining it makes my heart ache.
Don't take things too far.
I shouldn't.
By the way, you aren't still
addressing me correctly.
I'll call you by both names.
I just never had called anyone "Honey."
So gross.
Park Do Kyung, the good days are over.
Starting tomorrow,
there will be some trouble.
- Who is it?
- The driving service.
Come over here.
- The first, second, and third.
- Try it.
Second one...
Men who are good with machines
are always so attractive.
Why did you fall in love
with me at first sight?
How would I know that?
I don't know why.
People say you just recognize the person
you're going to fall in love with.
You don't fall in love with
that person just because
they were nice to you or something.
Just... At first sight.
You recognize it.
As soon as I saw you,
I wanted to barge into your heart
and spread myself out.
I wanted to remove anything
that was making you unhappy
and light up your heart with warmth.
I wanted to be
the only one sitting in it.
- Did I seem unhappy to you?
- Yes. Extremely.
From your head to toes.
So I couldn't just leave you behind.
- Like your cans?
- Cans are pitiful.
But you looked unhappy.
So you fell in love at first sight
with me because I looked unhappy.
I must have been unhappy too.
"I'm unhappy too."
"I'll make you happy."
"Let's be happy together."
But you played hard to get!
Is that what all good-looking men do?
Here you go again with
your handsomeness!
I wish you would age quickly
and become an old grandpa.
So that I'm the only woman...
who finds Park Do Kyung attractive.
So that no one even
looks in your direction.
And I wish you would get chubbier.
Should we?
I could get chubby
and you could get older.
Are you crying?
No.
What do you need?
What?
What's the matter?
What happened?
I asked what happened!
Hey.
Do Kyung.
- I'm on the phone. Get out.
- Do Kyung!
I said get out!
Hey, so Do Kyung already knew about this?
It seems that way.
He knew about it.
Take all four of them.
They are good at what they do.
Take all four of them, please.
I will give you all the equipment too.
Instead, you can't give them a pay cut.
Thank you.
You don't need anyone for the office?
It's you, isn't it?
You!
Is it our first time with a deal?
I've been late with my payments,
but I always paid you back.
- Why are you suddenly acting this way?
- Ma'am.
I was offered more,
so I had no choice but to sell it.
You sold my debt?
Whom did you sell it to?
The guy who was pissed off at your son
paid more and bought it.
So who is that guy?
- Is it CEO Jang?
- No.
He used to do so well with his business.
He went bankrupt and was sent to prison.
Your son did that to him
because of a woman.
I heard it was recently on the radio.
- Her name was Oh Hae Young.
- Oh Hae Young?
You came. Hey, Park Hoon.
They even placed his property
under distraint attachment?
Han Tae Jin is playing
badly, unlike his build.
Go do something to Do Kyung.
He's not doing anything.
We will appeal the decision first.
We will buy some time
and get money in the meantime.
Just leave it. It's the right thing
to get it all taken away.
- Do Kyung.
- You know what I did to him.
But you still need to do
whatever you can.
It seems that Han Tae Jin
and CEO Jang are working together.
CEO Jang has more power
than your legal advice.
So don't even try to help me out.
I deserve to die.
If I hadn't talked you into having
your revenge on him back then
things wouldn't have come to this.
I seriously deserve to die.
I'm sorry.
I don't know what to say.
If you hadn't talked me into doing that
I wouldn't have met Hae Young.
Thank you for saying that.
By the way...
you're the one who threw the dart.
What's the occasion that
you're taking me out to lunch?
Well, no reason.
I wanted to thank you for saving
my letter for 13 years.
You know that
I've moved around a lot, right?
I even went abroad.
I brought that letter every time.
Thank you.
- I'm sorry.
- About what?
I hated you for a long time.
When I think about it
you didn't do me any harm.
Because we had the same name
it was the boys' fault that
they praised you and put me down.
If we'd had different names
- we'd have been quite close.
- No way.
Pretty girls are friends
with only the pretty ones.
You're very pretty.
This is why I hate you.
Go ahead.
- Take this bacon.
- Thanks for the food.
Where did you buy those shoes?
- Those are designer shoes, aren't they?
- No, I got them cheap on the Internet.
- Do you want to know the website?
- Please.
I'm good at finding good deals.
You bitch!
How can you possibly
walk around with a smile on?
You ruined my son's life.
You walk around smiling?
What do you think you're doing?
Stop it before I call the police.
Call the police.
So I can have her arrested!
Once you're separated,
that should be the end of it.
Why did you show up again
to ruin Do Kyung's life, huh?
Do you even know the man you
almost married is ruining his life?
Do you know or not?
Go. Just go.
- Where do you think you're going?
- Stop it. It's not her.
- Just go.
- You bitch!
I asked you to stop.
- Who the heck are you?
- It's me, not her.
What? What are you saying?
[Oh Hae Young]
He thought this one was you...
So who is currently seeing whom?
Me and Do Kyung...
Then what's the relationship
between these two?
They have no relationship.
Now I understand.
Oh my goodness.
What's wrong with Do Kyung?
His taste in women is
getting worse and worse...
You don't look like your family is rich.
Did you do well in school?
You... are excited, aren't you?
You can't think straight
because two men are fighting over you.
Isn't that right?
Gosh, what are we going to do with you?
You should stick to your own league.
If your head gets too big
and you dare to cross over
you will get hurt.
What you're doing now
is in a different league.
Do you know what I'm trying to say?
I won't have to make a speech.
You don't look like someone
who will make it hard to forget.
So don't drag this out
longer than it should be.
Go back to the man you almost married.
Then everything will be taken care of.
Why aren't you answering?
Gosh! Seriously!
You must be one of those who don't talk!
If you really care about Do Kyung
it's right to just get out of his life.
Are you with him to watch him die, huh?
Even if the man doesn't say anything...
even if he says it's okay and to stay
with him because he loves you
the woman should be wise enough
to know at a time like this
and be the first one
to say goodbye to him.
Don't you watch movies?
That's what love is.
You call that man.
Tell him that you broke up with
Do Kyung and will come back to him.
Call him.
I said call him!
You'd better call him.
- What are you looking at?
- Isn't it time to quit?
This is not your place.
Why would his ex-girlfriend get involved?
Do Kyung is the most kind man.
Other sons would have left you long ago.
Crazy bitch. Hey.
I've been saying this all along.
Blood is thicker than water.
Plus, don't you feel guilty?
This whole thing started because of you.
I started half
and you did the other half.
Half and half?
I may go somewhere
to have an exorcism done.
Why are so many Oh Hae Youngs
entangled in our lives?
Mom used a private loan
without telling you, didn't she?
And she put you down
as a guarantor, didn't she?
It's not her fault.
Why are you acting this way?
- Why are you taking her side?
- It's seriously not her fault.
I spoke to someone at Sori Sound.
They will have you continue to work
on our project and give you jobs there.
- Bullshit!
- Seriously?
You think we're doing this
because we can't find a job elsewhere?
You thought we stayed
around here all these years
and were all happy about
working for such a difficult boss?
Because it was you, Park Do Kyung.
Even if it was very tough
in the beginning
I thought I'd learn more
because it's you.
I thought I'd learn more things.
And later, I started to like
who you were and stayed.
Should I cry now?
Whatever.
As much as we cared about you
you didn't care about us.
We can rent a place
and start over together.
I won't be able to work for a while.
You won't or you can't?
You go to the army.
Are you crazy?
Did you sleep with
a woman for the first time?
He's smiling.
He's not telling the truth.
Don't you know how I am?
You bastard, seriously.
How much did their check come out to be?
It came out to be 78,000.
Charge it 300,000.
I wanted to pay for your drinks.
I bet you don't have much money.
Enjoy.
- Thank you for the drinks.
- Thank you.
- Who is he?
- Sang Suk.
- Didn't he come by the studio before?
- I think he did.
I'm not getting a good feeling about him.
- Where are you?
- I'm still at work.
I'm working late in the office tonight.
Call me when you're done.
I will come get you.
Okay. See you later.
You're late.
Yes, I had to take care of something.
I had to find some information.
- Do Kyung's studio...
- I know.
Do Kyung called.
Come sit down.
I... still haven't made the decision yet.
Can we talk about it tomorrow?
I will tell you tomorrow.
By tomorrow...
I will definitely tell you.
Regardless of your decision
I will tell you my decision first.
Have a seat.
It's possible that
couples haven't kissed.
But no couple will sleep
with each other only once.
Couples who slept with each other
will be more likely to do it again.
But...
in our case, since that night
we haven't slept with each other.
We only slept with each other once.
It means that we won't
have a shot at being together.
We did it somehow the first time.
I can't do it again either.
It's not going to work.
Please go back to your place.
Get up.
I've seen you smoke
only twice in my whole life.
Once when you
received the draft notice...
And yesterday...
This isn't something you should
force yourself to handle as a man.
You shouldn't force yourself
to handle this. It's okay.
I was planning on raising the baby
without telling you.
You somehow found out.
So there is no need
to feel pressured at all.
Soo Kyung.
You and I have been
like family to each other.
It's impossible that we become a couple
over what happened one night.
As of now
I release you from the responsibility.
So don't look back and just go.
- I will kill you if you look back.
- Soo Kyung.
You've tried your best.
I have tried my best too.
It's been enough.
It's okay, so go.
Don't turn around.
Go now.
I said I'd kill you if you turn around.
Look straight ahead and go.
It's okay.
Go. Go! Hurry. Go!
Seriously...
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong with the way you walk?
Walk like a tough guy.
Left foot. Left foot.
Now! Left foot.
Left foot! Left foot! Good job!
Left foot. Left foot.
Left foot. March to the rhythm.
Left foot! Good job!
Change feet and keep walking.
Left foot. Left foot. Left foot.
March to the rhythm.
Left foot.
I have something to tell you.
- Come in.
- No, outside.
You think I might do something to you?
Let's talk out here.
I only have water.
The night before our wedding...
you told me that you couldn't
stand the way I eat.
That day...
you gave me a death sentence.
It was the same
as if I had to go kill myself.
I didn't want to open
my eyes the next day.
I wanted to die.
How should I kill myself?
I should make it
a pure accidental death.
Nobody should know why I died.
But I thought you'd tell everybody
when you came to my funeral.
Then I would be humiliated
again even after death.
I tried everything
in order to stay alive.
My heart had already
been broken into pieces.
Do you know how hard it is to
fear someone will find out about you...
so you walk around
as if nothing happened?
I felt as if my heart all melted...
and I was slowly disappearing.
I couldn't breathe.
I had to force myself to breathe.
Now you tell me that you did that for me?
You'd definitely have said
you would wait for me.
Yes, I would have.
You'd have gotten tired of waiting.
Why didn't you let me
get tired of waiting?
You chose to make me want to die instead?
I didn't want to put you through
a lot and pressure you.
You didn't want to pressure me,
yet you hurt me so badly?
You call that love?
You chose to hurt me badly
instead of pressuring me.
Is that really love?
To men, that's love?
Where did you learn how to love?
A woman hears something
humiliating from a man and...
gets dumped the day before her wedding.
Or she waits for the man
who has gone bankrupt.
Which do you think would
be harder on the woman?
Didn't you ever think about that part?
After hearing that you were in prison...
I felt so relieved.
It made me think that I wasn't
such an undesirable woman.
I felt like I was spared.
Don't say you're having
your revenge on him
because he took away the woman you loved.
You never loved me.
When I was struggling so badly...
he took care of me.
I was able to go on because of him.
I'm still alive today because of him.
Come to your senses.
Think clearly before and after.
He took care of you
because of what he did.
- He didn't do that because he liked you.
- But still...
But still I was able
to go on because of him.
I fell for him first.
I begged him to like me back.
I was the one who told him
that it was okay...
after learning that
he ruined your business.
You are crazy.
Why did you come here?
Why don't you leave now?
You can make him go bankrupt.
You can make him penniless.
It's okay to do all that.
Just don't hit him.
I'm begging you.
Please don't hit him.
It breaks my heart.
You're making me such a loser.
I'm sorry.
I'm begging you.
You... shouldn't have come here today.
I almost got used to your nagging.
Now you want to say goodbye?
He's telling me to get lost.
I can't go.
You can't do this to us.
I'm very hurt, seriously.
You all are saying goodbye
to Park Do Kyung now?
Why are you being so whiny?
I will go first.
- Where are you going?
- Where?
When will you be done?
Will it take long?
Wrap it up and come out.
I'm in front of your building.
Mister, can you drop me off
at the rear door?
Mister, can you open the door, please?
No, I should come in this way.
Please open the door.
Mister, please open this door.
Thank you.
Why didn't you call me earlier?
I'd have come out sooner.
Here.
You just don't get it, do you?
You brought two umbrellas.
Gosh, I worked all night,
so I'm very tired.
But I still want to beat you up.
I like us having our own umbrellas.
I'm not getting any raindrops on me.
My shoulder isn't getting wet.
What if that old man wasn't there?
We'd have walked all the way
holding our own umbrellas?
If so, you'd have been beaten up
with the umbrella tonight.
- That's enough.
- Why did you bring two?
Well, I knew it
when you called for the driver
in the middle of the night at the beach.
- Can I say something, please?
- Okay, go ahead.
Speak.
You don't have anything to say.
I love you.
I'm on top of the world.
The end of our story is a happy ending.
Let me be happy a little bit longer.
A little bit longer.
Subtitles by DramaFever