This program is suitable
for viewers ages 15 and up.
Subtitles by DramaFever
You just don't get it, do you?
You brought two umbrellas.
I'm very tired from working all night.
But I still want to beat you up.
I like us having our own umbrellas.
I'm not getting any raindrops on me.
My shoulder isn't getting wet.
What if that old man wasn't there?
Would we have walked all the way
holding our own umbrellas?
If so, you'd have been beaten up
with the umbrella tonight.
- That's enough.
- Why did you bring two?
I knew it when you called a driver
in the middle of the night at the beach.
- Can I say something, please?
- Okay, go ahead.
Speak.
You don't even have anything to say.
I love you.
I'm on top of the world!
You're finally telling me that now?
Took you long enough.
Aren't you going to say anything?
People usually respond in a certain way.
I wonder if I could
give you an answer here.
- I also love Park Do Kyung--
- That's enough.
What's wrong? I want to reply to you.
- I also love Park Do Kyung--
- That's enough. It's fine.
- Why not?
- Forget it.
I'm so pitiful.
I'm over the moon like an idiot from
hearing that one phrase "I love you."
It's because you haven't
been giving me anything.
I haven't given you a reply yet.
Could I do it here?
Forget it. Don't.
I love Park Do Kyung a lot too!
Park Do Kyung is mine!
[Episode 17:
I Could Die Today with No Regrets]
Lift it.
I don't want to go in.
Should we just go over to your place?
She's 32 years old.
Isn't a 32-year-old woman still a woman?
The world's biggest idiot.
You know, you did the same
thing when we used to date...
That's why she's the biggest idiot.
Thank you.
I've gotten prettier.
I've gotten prettier from being in love.
Sir, hold up! Wait! Wait, please!
I'm going to be late for work!
It's okay. I can just get yelled at.
Who cares if I'm late?
Love is what matters the most.
Wake up.
Wake up!
That scared me.
I got scared because I thought
I got drunk and went over to your place.
My god.
- You didn't go home?
- You know how it is at my place.
Women are constantly ringing my bell.
- Ouch. My head hurts.
- Get up. Let's go to a sauna.
I was being especially careful today.
I took my shirt off first
and put my pants on first.
I was trying to be considerate for you.
But it seemed like you didn't notice it.
Hey.
Please compliment me.
I need compliments.
I feel tired
and I can't even have fun
from playing all night long.
It feels like I'm walking around with
the word "bastard" on my forehead.
It also feels like that word is
stamped on my heart.
- Why did you even leave our house then?
- I got kicked out.
I didn't walk out on my two feet.
She even gave me a command,
ordering me to go without looking back.
"Left. Left. Left..."
I was going to marry Soo Kyung.
You know I'm not that much of a bastard.
But this is what Soo Kyung told me.
"You shouldn't force yourself
to handle this."
I got caught while I was smoking.
Since I smoked after failing the bar
and getting drafted...
That was the second time
I had smoked again.
She completely saw through me.
So freaking embarrassing.
I feel extremely sorry.
So embarrassing.
Do Kyung. Please give me a hug.
So embarrassing... I'm so sorry.
How's Soo Kyung doing?
Don't be lonely.
Although you may not have a father
you have a father-like mother
and a father-like uncle.
If you still feel like you need a father
I'll rummage through all the men
in this world if I have to
and find you the best father ever!
This is the analysis of the first
half of the next year's trends.
If I can't read it from
the very first sentence
it's not a proper analysis.
- Again.
- Bring me a cup of coffee.
- Sure.
- Insert the sound we recently recorded.
Don't worry about it.
You know how we are.
Even if the sky falls,
we'll get the job done.
I'll give you a call once
we move to a new studio.
Sure. Okay. Bye.
Joon Hee and Ki Tae are
looking for a studio.
Some cheap place in a basement
or something. I'm letting you know.
We're not going to another company.
Because people are always asking for you
I'm sure we'll reestablish
our company soon.
You're so awesome.
How can you get any work done?
- Go apologize to CEO Jang.
- That won't resolve this problem.
And let that girl go back to
where she belongs.
- That will put an end to all of this.
- Forget it.
Are you trying to punish me right now?
Are you trying to show me that
you've gone bankrupt because of me?
Are you trying to make me feel guilty
for all the things I've done wrong?
Is that it?
This all happened because of me.
It's not your fault.
What do you need?
Does Do Kyung...
have some health issues?
He's being weird.
I think something is up with him.
He won't get angry at me!
Something is definitely up with him.
Hurry and look into it.
You won't even wilt.
I'm so proud of you.
You're hanging in there to
not hurt my feelings, aren't you?
Don't get lonely and cry at night.
I'll come early tomorrow morning.
What are the flowers saying?
You shouldn't talk to flowers.
That's weirder than
sticking flowers in your hair.
- Let's go.
- Sang Joo says she'll buy dinner.
Really?
I want unlimited pork cutlet then.
I just finished work. What's up?
- Let's have dinner with Soo Kyung.
- With Director Park?
Tell him to forget it.
We told you we'd go pick you up.
Why would you drive back and forth?
We just took a cab instead.
You're not even alone...
There are two of you.
Of course we should go pick you up.
- Let's head in.
- Sure.
Let's go in.
I heard that woman's boyfriend
ruined our studio.
- I'm that woman's boyfriend.
- You've lost it, haven't you?
Don't say a word about it.
I'll kill you if you do.
You two look like a married couple.
How nice.
Our studio is...
Love is so great.
You two should head upstairs
and eat by yourselves. Why eat with us?
They can at least eat with us. They can't
do other stuff when eating anyway.
You always give me that look
whenever I say something.
Where's the fun if you can't
tease a lovey-dovey couple?
I won't get jealous. I have pride.
- Come and have a seat.
- Okay.
Take a seat. Let's eat.
Have lots.
Do Kyung told me you like melons.
I like meat and raw fish too.
There are a lot of things that I like.
Never reply to him if he ever
asks you if you like something.
He'll just buy that food for 365 days.
30 years ago,
when I was 14 years old
I told him I love melons after
having one for the first time.
Since then, he's been only
buying melons for me. Melons!
Let me just say a word.
Please give a lot of love
to our Do Kyung.
He's a pitiful guy.
Could I take and raise him?
- I'm just kidding.
- I took you seriously.
Take him and raise him.
Suffocate him with
your overwhelming love--
I will unless I die first from
my heart fluttering too much.
Wow. You won't even budge a little.
You must like him a lot.
Enough that I could
bungee jump without a harness.
Not by myself. The two of us together.
I think you're... a little crazy.
Don't take things too far.
Even though he's my brother
I can only cheer on
someone else's love so much.
All right.
By the way, that lawyer friend
must be late today.
If we look for him, we can find him.
He's probably in hiding.
Lee Jin Sang! Come out and eat!
- Lee Jin Sang!
- He's not here.
He won't come here anymore.
This dude...
ran away, didn't he?
He just went somewhere.
It seems like he has done
something really bad.
- What has he done?
- He did something.
- What did he do?
- I'll tell you about it later.
I'm so curious.
Why can't you just tell me?
I feel kind of hurt.
Everyone but me knows about it.
What would you like to listen to?
Instead of listening to something
let's sing and record that song
you sang when you were young.
"The Daydream."
I think it'll feel weird when you
listen to it later. When we're old.
Your voice as a six-year-old.
Your voice as a 36-year-old.
- I think it would be cool.
- Forget it.
Why not? Let's record it.
Sing it for me.
The voice of the man I love the most
recorded at the moment
I loved him the most.
I want to have it recorded.
I want to hear it. Sing it for me.
Please?
What's this? Is it a handcuff?
Do you like this kind of stuff?
I'm flustered.
This isn't an old thing of mine.
I bought it.
Am I going to die?
Why are you being so good to me?
I'm scared because
you're being so good to me.
I was just passing by.
It looked pretty, so I bought it.
I feel anxious.
I'm beyond happy,
but I'm also beyond anxious.
- Am I anxious from being too happy?
- Don't think too much into it.
I shouldn't be this happy right now,
but I am.
Then just be happy.
Then I'll just be happy.
And I'll brush my teeth.
Could I also take a shower?
I'll take you home.
Okay! Everybody, look! Come on!
Hey, everybody. Come on!
Jump! Jump! Jump!
Yeah! Yeah!
Are you trying to have fun all at once?
- You're going overboard today.
- Yeah.
Why haven't you been here?
I was a little... busy.
But from now on, I'm going to
have fun without feeling guilty.
Every day. Every night. Party, party.
Crazy party! Drink it! Cheers!
Brother-in-law!
You shouldn't live this way.
Think about the kid.
What has Soo Kyung done wrong?
That kid... Has he lost it?
It's nothing. Nothing.
He's a younger brother of my friend.
He just wants to mess with me.
He's taking things
a little too far though.
Have a drink. Here we go.
Let's go home, brother-in-law!
Even if Soo Kyung has freed you,
you shouldn't do this to her.
That bastard!
You bastard!
Park Hoon, stop right there!
Hey!
I'll kill you once I get a hold of you!
A married life without love
isn't necessarily bad!
You're crazy, aren't you?
Get out of my sight! Get lost! Leave!
Soo Kyung still loves you.
- Why can't you understand women?
- I can't! I don't know!
- You, come over here.
- Hey. Why can't you say it?
- Why can't you say that it's your baby?
- You...
Why can't you say that you have a baby?
You're a daddy!
What's freaking wrong with our family?
My brother has filed for bankruptcy
and my brother-in-law has left home!
What is this?
My goodness!
You're back.
That crazy kid. Crazy bastard.
He's just this guy I know.
But he follows me around
and causes a scene like that.
This must be fun for him.
Let's go dance.
You should go in.
Drive safely, okay?
That hurts, Hae Young.
If I look back on this moment as I die...
I won't regret it.
Whoever comes to my house
always asks for a favor.
Everyone just wants something.
I used to like you because
you never asked me for anything.
You're ultimately letting me down.
This all started because of me.
If Do Kyung's life crumbles,
I can't let go of him. I beg you.
I want to forget about him. Even if
that means this is what I must do.
Please help me out.
Take this vegetable away!
You're trying to starve
an old man to death!
You can leave.
Don't you think it's a little childish?
Forming a team against them?
Be honest.
Didn't you want those two
to break up more than anyone else?
Yeah. Perhaps.
But I haven't looked that
deeply into my heart.
Because I don't want to look into it.
Because I might actually feel that way.
So I'm doing something before
that resentment comes out.
"I really want them to be happy."
"I genuinely want them to be happy."
I keep saying this to myself.
You make life difficult on yourself.
I understand. That's how I used to
feel until about a few days ago too.
I used to feel so bad about
doing all this mean stuff to him.
So I tried to figure out
why I felt so bad.
It was because I was trying
to be half mean, half nice.
I was telling myself,
"I'm not completely a mean person."
"I'll just be half mean, half nice."
"So give in and bow out
right about now."
But the type of people
I hate the most in this world is...
those who are half nice, half mean...
and half rude.
Don't try to grudgingly do something
you don't want to do.
Just follow your heart.
And wish that those two break up.
That would seem cooler.
From talking to you, I can see why.
People say you truly get to know
someone once you break up with them.
After breaking up with Do Kyung
I saw how great of a person he is.
So I felt sad about our breakup.
But it seems like Hae Young won't
be sad over her breakup like me.
You come up very short
against Park Do Kyung.
Come in.
Director Park.
I hear the research and development team
has made a prototype. Let's go see it.
All right. Let's.
I think that product doesn't fit in
with the season very well.
Hey. Madam Park Soo Kyung.
- Let's go.
- That woman is just ignoring me.
In order to make it suit the season...
- Why won't you answer my calls?
- Leave. I'm at work.
Wearing high heels? Are you crazy?
You're a 44-year-old pregnant woman.
How could you wear high heels?
So? You haven't done anything to turn
me into a 44-year-old pregnant woman!
- But I did.
- Crazy bastard.
Since last night, I probably called you
over a thousand times.
So stubborn. How could you so
adamantly ignore my calls?
- Are you trying to fight me?
- I have no reason to take your calls.
When you kicked me out of your house
didn't that mean we could still
be like brother and sister?
How ridiculous.
How would that be possible?
Wow. I didn't know you were this uncool!
Cool my ass. Screw that!
Who in their right mind could
sleep with a man, get pregnant
do all this stuff, and still maintain
a brother-sister like relationship?
You said you majored in French, right?
What are they blabbering about?
I can't understand
a single thing they're saying.
Get lost.
Wow.
Fine then.
You don't even want to stay friends now.
Let's not ever see each other then.
I'm fine with that.
It won't be hard for me.
Hurray. Let's not ever see each other.
Don't you dare change your mind later.
What is it?
- Is something wrong?
- What is it?
What is it?
Let's give it another try.
I'm talking about the kiss.
Wow.
I know this word.
- Let's get off the elevator.
- We have to get to a meeting.
- Just get off.
- Why do we have to get off?
What was it? What did he say?
He asked her to kiss him.
Kiss?
He looked normal...
Plus, he looked way younger.
- Director Park is kissing...
- Wow.
- Director Park is kissing him...
- It's very cool.
They are good kissers.
- They're really kissing.
- You're cool, Director Park.
Wow, how charming. Wow.
Wow, Director Park knows how to kiss.
- Thanks.
- I've wanted to pay a visit anyway.
Thanks for asking me to do that.
Don't worry. Everything will be okay.
Thanks.
What's wrong?
He keeps seeing things.
It seems something is about to happen.
Can we hypnotize him? Please.
We can't just sit back and do nothing.
Are you okay?
Don't touch him.
White flowers are coming
down from the night sky.
What kind of flowers are they?
They look like cherry blossoms.
But I'm not so sure.
Someone has passed away.
He's a singer, Lee Byung Joon.
[Big sale in June 2016]
Was it exactly 2016?
Was it exactly June in 2016?
But cherry blossoms
don't make sense then.
First, leave for overseas. Just run.
He wouldn't come all the way
overseas to kill you.
Let's leave straight for the airport now.
Go home and get your passport.
I will drive you
to the airport. Let's go.
Hey, Do Kyung.
Do Kyung!
I have to tell her.
I have to tell her before it's too late.
[The Man Next Door]
Come out.
I will bring you back
before the sun rises.
In all these years
this is my second time that a man
called me out in the night....
since this senior guy
in college called me.
He wasn't my style.
But he seemed to like me a lot.
He met me
for the first time at our orientation.
He even remembered the seventh time
we ran into each other.
We ran into each other at the library.
It was the front gate the third time
and the fourth time was...
Do you remember where we first met?
How can I not know?
I first met you at the cafe with Hee Ran.
You made my nose bleed.
- It wasn't there.
- What do you mean? It was there.
We met before that... on the street.
You turned around.
Don't you remember?
Which street was it?
It was in front of
the post office in Ye Yi Do.
That's right. I went there.
What was that then? You saw me
for the first time on the street...
and fell in love at first sight
and remembered me all along?
No.
I knew you even before that.
- How?
- Your face kept popping up in my head
when we'd never met before.
And I saw you in person on the street.
And then I met you at the cafe.
How did I pop in your head
when we'd never met?
It was just...
It was like a memory...
I kept seeing you.
I saw you move into that room
even before you actually moved in.
I didn't see other stuff.
I saw only you.
At first, I thought
I was seeing the future.
I thought I had gained
some kine of superpower.
But I realized at some point...
what it was that I was seeing...
why I was seeing you.
Why did you see me?
In the future...
When I'm dying...
it is what I'll think about
at my last breath.
It was like a flash.
That's what I was seeing.
- In the future?
- Yes.
Right before I die.
Before I die...
you are all I was thinking about.
I missed you so much that...
those feelings crossed over time.
My doctor said it could happen.
My memory at the time of dying shows
we never got back together,
but went our separate ways.
You moved out of here and...
it was the end of us.
When I was dying
I was regretting that most.
I don't know why I wasn't
letting myself feel things.
Why was I always nervous
about such petty stuff?
To you...
I said things that were the opposite
from what I really felt.
I will give you whatever you ask.
What's the point of stopping one from
leaving when she doesn't want to stay?
Sorry I said hi.
Don't get sick.
What is it that I really want to say?
Forget the pride and all.
What is it that my heart wants most?
What is it that I truly want to say?
Can you...
just move back in?
I'd like you to move back in.
Sorry, but this is how I truly feel.
I got sick because I couldn't hug you.
That's how we got back together.
I've never really let myself
feel things, not even once.
I was taken aback
when you were forward.
Is it okay for a woman to be this way?
But...
I liked it.
I was touched.
If I died without experiencing such love
I'd feel very sad.
Now...
when I die
I won't regret anything.
Thank you.
If this is all true
it's such a cool story.
I guess you didn't get married then?
Considering that I was the last person
you were thinking about.
Probably not.
You didn't get married
because you couldn't get over me?
Should I believe that story?
You called me out in the middle of
the night and are telling me this...
So it seems quite true.
Is it true then?
Yes.
I will believe it then.
Do you know that
I keep a diary these days?
Because I'm touched every day.
It's the first time that the man
I'm crazy in love with...
crazily fills me with love.
So I write in my journal every day.
I feel I should save such moments.
I love every day. So I'd be still happy
even if I were to die today.
Thank you.
Me too.
Ask him to come in for breakfast.
What kind of fate is this?
When are you returning?
I will know for sure
when I get there.
I need to meet
with the Chinese in person.
It's too frustrating to keep
sending documents only.
When you're about to get on the plane,
why check the weather on the west sea?
Seize it all.
What's happened?
Lee Chan Soo took everything and fled.
He ripped you off too.
While you were overseas
working on the foreign markets
he faked our sales and received
investments from various places.
CEO Jang noticed
and pulled out his investment.
He didn't want you to find out.
That's why he got you out.
CEO Jang is too tired to see you today.
Damn it.
[Chan Soo]
Your call is being redirected...
Damn it!
This bastard...
Wait until I catch you.
Chan Soo, where are you going?
Hey.
Aren't you going to take your flight?
Chan Soo!
I really thought
our business was doing well.
I really thought our product
was selling like hotcakes.
Was it worth that much?
Did I ever want to have a business?
I just wanted to get the money and run.
- You're out of your mind, huh?
- I'm sorry, but...
Say it politely, you punk!
All right then. I'm sorry.
You talked the directors into suing me?
Was it you who sent me to prison?
You could've just stepped down as CEO.
When you were about to marry someone
why did you have to put up such a fight?
I was putting up a fight
because I was about to marry.
Plus, does it make sense that
I'm not the CEO of Tae Jin Corp?
CEO, my butt.
Did you really think
our product would sell well?
You're so slow that...
CEO Jang drags you around
for his errands.
What, you punk?
You and Park Do Kyung both
are being played by CEO Jang.
As if one of you is a white stone
and the other is a black stone.
He scored in love at least.
You're such a loser though.
Let's go somewhere today.
Today? I can't leave right away today.
Can we leave Friday night?
No, let's go today.
I got it. See you later.
- I'm just asking out of curiosity...
- Okay.
Do you know where I live,
by any chance?
Who are you? Why do you
keep popping into my head?
Why do I keep seeing you?
Did you eavesdrop on me?
Even if you did, you wouldn't
know who was who.
What is it?
I thought about
the possibility of me dying...
I told him this.
If he ever wants to marry you,
come to Suh Hee's wedding.
If not, don't show up.
That bastard didn't show up!
If I look back at
this moment when I'm dying
it means nothing.
No need to be cautious.
I will let myself go
as far as my heart wants.
I won't hold back
and will let myself go.
I'm sorry that I couldn't
come to the wedding.
I had my reasons.
Until I die
I won't leave your side.
I won't ask you to forgive me.
I'm sorry.
No. It can't be.
It won't be, Hae Young.
It won't be.
I fell for him first.
I begged him to love me back.
Just don't beat him up.
I'm begging you.
He scored in love at least.
You're such a loser.
You're no match for Park Do Kyung.
I recorded a song.
I love you.
We didn't get to take a photo together.
Like a dream on a spring day
you came to me.
I thought you would be with me forever.
At the beach in summertime
the sand castle was happy.
But the waves swept it away.
I'm okay if you leave me.
I'm okay if you forget me.
I will always think about you only.
Bastard.
Try to live.
Longer...
Like this...
continue to suffer...
[Lee Byung Joon suddenly
cancels his concert.]
I couldn't let myself love more.
I regret those days when
I still love you.
I love you forever.
Subtitles by DramaFever