This program is suitable
for viewers ages 15 and up.
Subtitles by DramaFever
As June passed by,
we didn't set foot outside the house.
The moment I could believe
everything he had said
I strangely felt at ease.
It felt like I had actually touched
destiny with my own hands.
The fact that this world
I didn't know of exists.
I can see isn't everything.
It felt strange and unfamiliar.
But it strangely felt
comforting and calming.
On an early spring day...
You, who have come to me like a dream...
I thought it would last forever.
Let's listen to this song
until we turn 100.
The summer beach.
The sand castle full of happiness.
Are you embarrassed?
It got washed away with the waves.
I don't have any
singing skills to brag about.
But my sensibility is
worth bragging about.
So I'm more suited for small concerts.
Wow. You're so modest.
Please say a word to our viewers.
What should I say?
I live because of you guys. Thank you.
Let's be happy. Cheers.
Only after June had passed
did we go outside.
So this is her.
The person you've been
seeing in your visions.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Park Soon Taek.
It's all true.
Seeing into the future is possible
but that doesn't mean
all of your visions come true.
It may follow the vision
or it may take a very different path.
An event can cause the vision to change.
- Do you still have visions?
- No.
I don't get any visions anymore.
So it's all over then, right?
As long as he's alive,
we can't say anything is over yet.
- Don't be so vague about it.
- How am I being vague?
So we don't have to...
worry about him dying
or anything like that, right?
I mean, everyone will die one day.
He's not a phoenix.
Just saying...
Let's live together.
I can't leave you by yourself.
I feel so bad thinking about how
you'd have lived in fear by yourself.
- Let's live together.
- I never lived in fear.
I wasn't scared.
I'm grateful to you for liking me first.
But don't say those kinds of words first.
I'll propose to you.
Carefully. Be careful. Hold on.
Hey, Park Hoon!
- Is this the last one?
- Yeah. Help us.
- Hold on.
- It's heavy. Help us.
[Do Kyung]
- Where are you going? Grab it!
- You bastard!
Hey. We're done.
I got it.
- Give it to me. Here. Here.
- Our studio is released from seizure.
- What did you say?
- It is?
For real?
Move everything out again.
He could have told us earlier.
We moved everything.
My hand is shaking. Look at this.
This is the first time my hand is
shaking from fatigue.
Park Do Kyung. That bastard.
He's hiding somewhere and watching us.
Now that we finished moving everything,
he figured now is the time to tell us!
Maybe he's looking at us with
a telescope. He is. For sure.
- He's so sick.
- Should I bring everything back out?
- Hire someone to do it!
- You're that someone.
You've done nothing wrong.
Live with ease.
And don't go anywhere near CEO Jang.
The 800 million won that you spent
buying bonds was wasted.
I'll get going then.
You shouldn't do business either.
You won't make it.
Those incompetent people
with talkative mouths.
- Get out of my way!
- You can't be like this.
- Don't you know who I am?
- Ma'am, you can't get in.
- Get out of my way!
- You can't. Please.
- You can't do this, ma'am.
- Get out of my way!
- These kids...
- You can't be here! Ma'am!
I heard that you were just
messing around with my Do Kyung!
Why do you live like this?
Hey! Get out of my way! Let go of me!
Hey. Who cares if
you have a lot of money?
You can't ever go outside!
You're always playing
board games at home!
And you encourage young
kids to fight against each other.
Hey. You shouldn't mess with this bitch
who has nothing to lose!
If I see that you're about to
mess with Do Kyung again...
Then I'll just...
put this body of mine to use.
Either you or I will die!
Let go of me! Let go!
You're always so full of energy!
- This is why I like you.
- Bullshit.
What?
Are you trying to flatter me right now?
You must be scared, eh?
The day I come back here.
You know what that day will be, right?
- Don't make me come back here, okay?
- Yes, ma'am.
If I had married her,
I wouldn't have survived a week. Right?
- Yes?
- I'm sorry, but could you get up?
Me?
[Yoga for Pregnancy]
- I'm pregnant.
- I see. I'm sorry.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
- Do you want me to carry your purse?
- It's okay.
Give it to me.
You heard that Do Kyung's studio
was released from seizure, right?
- Yeah. I heard.
- You did. I see.
You have pretty ankles.
My other parts are pretty too.
- The stars are shining so brightly.
- Yeah. They're so pretty.
When did they redo these streets?
It seems like they've
changed the wall too.
- Jin Sang.
- Yes?
You know...
Where should I grab?
Just anywhere...
- Over here?
- Sure.
Here.
- It tickles.
- I'm sorry.
- Aren't you tired?
- No. It's okay.
This feels weird.
I think we should...
- let go of each other now...
- Sure. You're right.
Let's let go on the count of three.
One, two, three.
- Good night.
- Good night to you too.
Soo Kyung.
- I just wanted to wish you a good night.
- Sure!
- Good night.
What kind of feeling is this?
Why is this so hard?
Seriously.
Oh my god.
Good night! Go to sleep!
Mom. I want to get married.
I just want to live with him.
I want to move into his house
and live with him.
Go live with him. Get out.
- Get up.
- Mom.
Leave.
You need to tell him!
That you've given me your consent!
If I tell him I just left home, he won't
live with me. He'll tell me to go back!
Come with me and tell him.
Tell him you've given your consent!
I can't leave him by himself.
Please come with me and tell him.
Get up.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
- Give it to me.
- I'll carry this one.
I've finally realized how I feel
about Soo Kyung today.
I respect her.
You feel respect toward
people like Admiral Yi Soon Shin.
So it means I'm dating someone like him.
Then what could I do
with Admiral Yi Soon Shin?
Could I put my arms around his shoulder?
Or around his waist?
Crazy bastard.
Still hasn't come to his senses.
To a woman who wants to live together
without even getting married
how could you say, "I'll propose.
I'll officially bring you home"?
To a woman you want to embrace,
sleep with, and wake up with?
Saying all these words you don't mean
and pretending like it's all for her?
How many times do you need to come back
from death to come to your senses?
- Me?
- Me!
What is he saying?
Don't get angry. With a smile.
Like you mean it, okay?
So that he doesn't feel bad.
Please? With a smile.
In my entire life...
I'm seeing possibly the most
ridiculous side of you.
- You're getting thrown away today.
- Don't say that.
[One Way Street. Do Not Enter.]
Hey. Look over here.
Do Kyung!
With a happier face. Nicely, okay?
I would like to marry Hae Young.
Please give me your consent.
Thank you for coming to us first.
We've given her our consent. Right?
We have.
Just live together from today on.
You guys are so madly in love.
It'll take too long to set
the date and get married.
Live together from today on.
I mean it.
Get up.
I wish you happiness.
Let's go back home.
Sir, could you open the trunk?
- We'll get going. You two should go.
- Bye.
Get your car out of the way.
Please look at me. Mom...
That guy must be ill.
That's why we need to let her go.
- I told you we should go somewhere nice.
- I like this place the most.
While I was living over there
I was so frustrated every single night.
How could you not come over to my place
when you knew very well
that I liked you?
I thought, "Should I seduce him?"
But it would have been extremely
embarrassing if I got rejected.
I got very angry every night.
And I thought
"How could this guy fall asleep?"
Do you really think I could have?
When should we get married?
Whenever.
Let's get married soon.
[Three minutes ago]
So how did...
My friend, I'm behind the couch.
Could you somehow let me quietly leave?
- You have a message.
- Forget it. Just leave it.
- Who is it?
- It's me.
Oh no!
What's wrong? We can just
tell her we're getting married
- and that we have your parents' consent.
- Let's tell her tomorrow, please.
We can officially tell her
tomorrow during the day.
This isn't the right time.
It feels like we got caught.
Let's pretend like
I'm going home right now
and tell her tomorrow. Okay?
- All right.
- You need to take your car key.
My legs.
- Hello.
- It's late.
Yes. I was about to go home right now.
What's wrong?
I was about to take her home.
- Is Jin Sang here?
- No, he's not.
But his shoes are here. Over there.
Let's go for a walk.
I have indigestion.
It wasn't my fault.
Hey, congrats. Congratulations.
For what?
Starting from today... I mean,
starting from tomorrow
they're going to do something.
- Do what?
- They have consent.
- For what?
- They're going to tell you tomorrow.
But not today. Never.
Don't you dare sneak into my room again.
I didn't sneak in! I've been here
since our conversation!
That doesn't mean I saw everything
from the very beginning...
I did. I saw it.
I saw everything from
the very beginning!
They were spinning from over here.
Soo Kyung, they were spinning
and they sat down. Stood back up.
They were laughing and everything!
They were pecking like chickens! Wow.
Let's go. I saw everything!
You just wait!
Anyway, thanks for saving me.
I was sweating so much.
I think I get it.
If something like this happens again,
you need to reveal yourself quickly.
If you wait longer,
it gets harder to get out of it.
You need to reveal yourself
within three seconds. Okay?
- Three seconds. Okay.
- Hold on. Jin Sang, stand right here.
I don't know what's wrong.
Hold still. You could get hurt.
Nice catch. Hold on.
Take a few steps back. Stretch it out.
Stop. Wait. Hold on.
Hey, Soo Kyung. Ouch.
- How nice. This is it.
- Soo Kyung, I don't think this is it.
- This is nice.
- Soo Kyung, I think this is dangerous.
- No, it's not.
- Soo Kyung.
He's here.
Espresso Con Panna.
Whipped cream made by hand.
Not whipped by a machine.
And with one additional shot, right?
Okay.
You're so quick on the uptake.
Hurry and come over. Quickly!
Take those tissues off your face.
You look pitiful.
There's still some left.
[Passionate Bottle Opener]
I don't have time to read all of this.
Explain it to me.
Let's see if you have the ability
to impress people with words.
Huh? In words...
Then I'll explain it to you in words...
There is this woman number three loved.
But this hillbilly goes
abroad for the first time.
To show people he was abroad
he buys a bottle opener
shaped like the Eiffel Tower.
One you can stick on the fridge.
So he gives it to that woman.
But one day,
he goes over to number one's house
and finds that bottle opener there.
Number three was always loyal to him.
The moment he sees the bottle opener
at number one's house...
He is disturbed.
It seems like it's about
betrayal and conspiracy
but, in truth, it's about his quest
to claim the bottle opener back.
It's a noir film featuring a pitiful man.
Sounds fun. Let's do it.
This kind of work requires energy.
And you seem to have a lot of it.
Same with your girlfriend.
Tell Producer Kim Hee Ran
that I've agreed to it.
Producer Kim Hee Ran is
good at what she does.
Thank you. You're a lifesaver.
A savior? Who knows?
Maybe you'll be my lifesaver.
- You're so awesome.
- I know.
I'll get going.
Bye!
Yes!
I'm planning on meeting with
his mother tomorrow. Are you available?
I've thrown you away.
Why would I care about
a girl I've thrown away?
- But you wished us happiness yesterday.
- Didn't you ask me to?
- Can't you be nicer?
- When were we ever sweet to each other?
Be nice from now on.
Since I can't go back home anymore
and see you once we fight over the phone
I feel bad if you talk like that.
Did that guy drive you
to work in the morning or not?
Of course he took me.
Why do you keep calling him "that guy"?
Stop calling him that.
- Then what am I supposed to call him?
- Call him son-in-law Park.
Bullshit.
Delete number two and three.
Then re-sync the first one.
Okay.
- Hello?
- It's me.
I'm your soon-to-be father-in-law.
Ah, yes!
Write this down.
Please go ahead.
- Milk vetch root.
[Milk vetch root]
White...
Sunroot...
[White balloon flower. Sunroot.]
Boil and eat them.
I hear they're good for your health.
[Effects of milk vetch root,
white balloon flower, and sunroot.]
The moment Oh Man Suk
walked into this place
I told myself, "Okay! I'm going to
work on him for a week!"
Just enough so that he doesn't
feel burdened, keeping him delighted.
Every day. Gently.
On top of that, my Hoon
wrote this amazing scenario...
You have such a great girlfriend.
I... would like to say
something a little embarrassing.
It's something really embarrassing.
I... love you.
I love you too.
- Anna!
- Park Hoon!
Cheers!
We're going to get married.
We're meeting with our mothers tomorrow.
- Congrats. Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Don't you have something more to say?
Before we get married,
we're just going to live together.
- Starting today.
- Enough. I might cut off our ties.
I'm your brother-in-law. You can't
cut ties off with your brother-in-law.
- The two of us are dating.
- You two are only going to date?
Put your younger brother in his place.
I... am pregnant.
It's okay.
She's going to be in our family.
She was going to find out soon anyway.
So that's why...
you stood outside every day
and couldn't come in.
Did your parents approve of
living together before the wedding?
- Yes.
- Wow.
- Good for you.
- You two are living together too.
Well, we're not exactly
living together yet...
By the way...
I know it's been tough for you two.
I wish you a happy life together.
Cheers.
Now we've said
"I love you" to each other!
What is she saying?
Hoon says he loves me.
Now that he says that L word,
it's time to fart in front of me.
If so, we're really in a relationship.
I can already fart in front of her.
There are steps to follow.
Farting openly comes
after saying "I love you."
You haven't said
"I love you" to each other yet?
- Have you?
- Of course we have.
How would I decide to move in together
without saying that first?
I never thought you were
capable of saying that.
Why haven't you yet?
It's not hard. I can do it right now.
You should say that
when you really feel it.
If you just blurt it out, you're dead.
There are a lot of things you two
should do with each other.
You should also speak
informally to each other.
- They're going to live together.
- What?
- We're going to get married.
They started to live together yesterday.
Let's go upstairs.
We will leave first.
Good night.
He's so on top of the world these days.
They're really living together?
Seriously?
So cool. You're so cool, honey.
Did you see these veins popping here?
What is this?
It was left at the front door.
[To my future son-in-law Park]
We should've had many
chances to eat together.
So I would know what you like
and what I should make for you.
We've only eaten together twice.
I just packed some things
I thought you might like.
I think people get married
not because they're in love
but because they're loyal to each other.
Marriage is knowing that one small thing
could cause you break up.
So I hope you stay together
for a long time.
Do you know your daughter lives
in my son's place right now?
I'm the one who dropped her off there.
Surprisingly, you're open-minded
about that, huh?
You don't look that way though.
They seemed like they were so in love.
There won't be many days of feeling
so in love for the rest of their lives.
And not many people
get to experience that.
I don't want them to worry about
what other people might say.
I want them to be
as happy as they can be.
That's why I dropped her off there.
But still that's not the way to go.
Especially since enough people
already know how they met.
They need to take even more
proper steps to get married.
But people will still find things
to say about them.
I asked her to move in.
But the woman shouldn't
just follow your lead.
I don't feel good about this.
I never thought my son would start
living with someone before his wedding.
There are proper steps to follow
when it comes to marriage and all.
Soo Kyung is pregnant.
Gosh, don't be ridiculous.
How can she be pregnant
when she's not even married?
I'm serious.
Congratulations.
Then.
Sure.
She seems so tough,
but she's nothing.
She's easy.
She shouldn't give you a hard time.
So don't worry about her.
- Go ahead.
- I will call you.
How could you say that
in the middle of it?
I'm sorry.
Is it true?
Is Soo Kyung pregnant for sure?
- She is.
- Who is the guy?
It's Jin Sang.
She hit the jackpot.
What is it?
Is the toilet clogged?
Is it number two?
Go unclog it then!
- I can't.
- I can't either!
Call someone to do it then.
Don't do that.
Should we just leave it then?
Let's move out. No one can get inside.
- You go unclog it, man.
- Are you crazy?
It's gross to see someone else's poop.
I can't even unclog mine.
Gosh, seriously!
I'm saying it's okay.
I will unclog it.
Do you seriously plan to move then?
I can do this. I can do this.
I can totally do this. I can do it!
It's been unclogged?
Wipe the toilet.
Spray some air freshener too.
It's okay. Everything is okay now.
I did a great job in there.
You should've seen me.
I'm saying it's okay.
We already made a baby together.
Can't I unclog the toilet for you?
- You came.
- Good that you came.
- This is the sound director.
- Nice to meet you.
- Have a seat.
- Sure.
Please have a seat.
My movie only has a few lines.
- True.
- The sounds will have to do the job.
They will help the audience
feel the scenes.
He was in charge of producing the sound.
I'm craving pork belly.
Let's have pork belly tonight, okay?
I almost forgot. You have
plans tonight, don't you?
Let's have pork belly next time then.
I don't want to eat it alone.
Enjoy your dinner
and I will see you at home.
- Long time no see.
- It is.
- Good to see you.
- So good to see you.
Say hi. This is the sound director.
Wow, the sounds were
really good this time.
Nice to meet you.
Director Yang, I will get going.
- Leaving already?
- Yes.
I'm sorry.
- Leaving already?
- I'm sorry.
Bye then.
- You said you'd be late.
- It ended early.
It's pork belly.
I will go change first.
Wow.
Pork belly tastes best
when I crave it.
Here it is.
Now again, I will do
what I have never done before.
Here. Eat it off my hand this once.
- It's okay.
- Please do it. It's not hard.
Say ah.
Please take it.
All you need to do is
open your mouth, seriously.
It was no big deal, wasn't it?
I hear you are pregnant.
Congratulations.
It might be the best thing
you've ever done for yourself.
I wanted to tell you first.
Jin Sang fooled around a lot
when he was young.
He's more likely to settle
down well after marriage.
If a man gets a taste of
fooling around after marriage
there is no solution.
So...
don't worry and be good to him.
But it's not romantic between us.
We haven't even held hands properly,
yet we sleep together just fine.
It's all chaotic.
Hey, how old are you?
Aren't you too old to ask for romance?
Plus, that should end
when you're pregnant.
Romance my butt.
But still...
We haven't even said
"I love you" to each other yet.
We haven't even held hands properly yet.
How? How?
- What?
- How?
How could he possibly touch my poop?
- Thanks for the food.
- Sure.
I love having a sister-in-law.
I get to borrow your delicious dishes.
Your mom is such a good cook.
Then.
By the way, was everything okay?
I heard you left the meeting early.
You were invited to a meeting
with famous directors.
It means that he thinks you're good.
Call him up.
Director Yang seems a bit mad.
- Get some rest.
- Will do.
Why did you leave so early?
You should've stayed longer.
You said you wanted to have pork belly.
Shall we download a movie and watch?
Sure.
Actually, I'm waiting now.
I can still continue to wait, but...
But for some reason, this moment
seems like our last time together.
Your concert went well.
Now what's the problem again?
You came by to keep
an eye on me at this hour?
Are you doing this to save me or him?
Both of you.
How have you been all day?
- How about you? Good?
- Yes.
I was busy today
recording for the weekend.
How about you?
I was so busy this morning.
I have a lot of patients in wintertime.
So I had Jjajangmyun delivered
and had it for lunch with Jee Hoon.
When I meet someone new later
how much should I come clean about this?
There is only one thing you
shouldn't say to your girlfriend.
I understand.
I'm sorry.
I think I was destined
to say that for your sake.
So you'd meet someone better.
The test results came out.
I see.
I wish you happiness.
I mean it. I'm serious.
It's true that
you were good to me, Tae Jin.
Thank you.
The results came out
sooner than expected.
What? You came and unclogged the toilet?
Quiet down, will you?
When a guy unclogs
the toilet after you go
he will stick around for life.
How could you unclog the toilet
when you haven't even said "I love you"?
It's almost the last step to
conquer between a couple.
They're following the steps in reverse.
They made a baby first
and now they're dating.
What? A baby?
Oh my.
You're a couple who follows
the steps in reverse now?
Wow, how cool.
- How is that cool?
- It is cool.
Usually, couples say "I love you" first
and start to speak informally.
And then they fart in front of
the other and unclog the toilet next.
And lastly, they make a baby.
It's reversed.
They made a baby, unclogged the toilet,
and farted in front of the other.
This means that they've seen
everything about each other.
And the last step
will be saying "I love you."
Wow, now "I love you" will
come at the perfect time.
Reverse! It's so cool!
It's very cool.
- Is that right?
- Absolutely.
When love gets created
at the end of the steps
"I love you" will be so sincere.
I'm so jealous.
- Let's eat.
- Sure.
Gosh, she thinks it's seriously cool.
My sister is that simple-minded.
Wasn't my acting good or what?
- What? A baby?
- A baby?
Here it is.
I came up with that. "Love in reverse."
- Wasn't it good?
- It was good.
Wasn't my acting good too?
- "Quiet down, will you?"
- Wow, it was so natural.
By the way...
it seems very cool to follow the steps
in reverse for some reason.
You're just kidding me.
- We can't have a baby.
- I wasn't kidding.
No baby.
I thought I wouldn't be able to drink
with you unless I was all happy.
I didn't want to drink with
you pretending to be okay.
But now I'm in a good place.
- Do you hate me?
- Yes.
I hated you for
all three years in high school.
And I also hated you until recently.
But you're the winner in the end.
Let's not decide
who the winner is on a guy.
It's embarrassing.
I... won't come to your wedding.
I think it's best not to.
And I will find another job too.
At a better company.
Let's see each other at the reunions.
I hope you two live happily ever after.
I mean it.
Thank you.
You have to be happy.
You have to be absolutely happy.
[Mom]
Hi, Mom.
Where are you?
I will come get you.
Don't come.
I think I should come home
by myself tonight.
See you at home.
Oh my, Jin Sang.
Wait. My knee.
- My knee...
- Are you okay?
Rooftop party. Rooftop party.
- That's not how you do it.
- Rooftop party.
I'm looking forward to
finding what the baby is like.
The video will show over there.
The woman should sit there
and you sit here.
You can signal with the cup
like this to start the video.
Okay.
Excuse me.
Yes?
- Where are you?
- I'm on my way.
I will be there in 10 minutes.
I don't know
why I'm getting all nervous
when I already know what you will do.
You can just toss me a ring.
Don't go too far, okay?
I know what you're like,
so don't try so hard.
Okay.
As if I was determined to be unhappy
I was living my life closed up.
And she flew into my heart.
As she put it,
I was incapable of emotions.
I was living my life not even knowing
if I was happy or unhappy.
I was that incapable of emotions.
I was stubborn and had a serious case
of being incapable of emotions.
That's why I might have to see
my dying moment beforehand.
What will I regret at my dying moment?
Even after being hurt that badly
she wasn't afraid to come running to me,
crying out and asking to love again.
As if her heart was malleable
so it can become something new
as I watch her come running
to me without fear.
Strangely, I felt relieved
and wanted to be with her.
I wished her energy
would come to me too.
Now it's my turn
to fill her with my love.
[Breaking news:
Singer Lee Byung Joon dead]
I let my guard down.
I... ended up lying like this.
The only difference is...
it's the blue sky
instead of the night sky.
And I think about her happy face...
rather than her unhappy face.
Hurry up and come hold my hand.
Before they die
they try to reach
each other's hands in this scene.
I could never understand
this frequent scene from the movies.
But now I understand.
The reason why they try so hard
to reach each other's their hands.
I might be going somewhere soon.
The fear of not knowing
where I might be going.
The fear of becoming absolutely alone.
At the moment of such fear
I desperately long for someone's hand.
The hand will assure me
that I won't be alone.
If she holds my hand
such fear will disappear.
The power of that hand
will make all fear disappear.
It may be your power.
It's okay.
I will be right there.
Just wait a little bit.
It's okay. It's not serious.
It's okay. It's okay.
Now I'm relieved.
Let's set the date for September third.
If we have the wedding
a week before Thanksgiving
people won't be happy.
If it's after Thanksgiving,
it may be too late.
Let's do it on September third.
If it's September third
it may be still hot.
Let's do it in October.
Sorry, but we should
have our wedding in October.
- Her stomach will show then.
- I'll have to see how the dress fits.
Then September third it is.
We will keep the wedding
presents for me simple.
What wedding presents for you?
What is it that you'd like to get?
An alligator purse and a mink coat...
- Come on.
- Ma'am, please.
What crime did an alligator
and a mink commit?
Why should we kill those two?
- Why are you getting all mad?
- How can I not yell?
Come to your senses.
What wedding present for you?
- Then no wedding presents for me?
- What wedding presents for you?
My Hae Young will be
the wedding present for you.
When my precious child is marrying
your son, what presents do you need?
Sorry to interrupt,
but we will sing the wedding song.
- We will sing the wedding song.
- Out of your mind?
Should I call what was going on
that day crazy or funny?
Everybody seemed like
they were out of their minds.
But I find that moment
relieving and comforting.
We went beyond the prayer
of asking to save his life.
We just assumed
he would be saved.
My mom was bluntly talking
about the next step.
And the rest of us knew
what she was trying to do.
And they all played along.
I was also sucked into this energy.
I will wear a pretty wedding dress.
[Lee Byung Joon has
regained consciousness.]
- Kiss her.
- Fighting!
- Good job.
After you have a near-death experience
you live your life differently.
Because you know what's important in life
your happiness is all that matters.
Right now, I'm as happy as one can be.
I'm grateful to everyone.
With him, the time we
spent crying and laughing
the times when it was bitter and sweet,
and we broke down and got back up.
I will probably look back
on those times when I die.
And I will say this.
Everything was just perfect.
[Please stay alive.]
[I'm grateful you're alive, honey.]
Subtitles by DramaFever