Subtitles by OnDemandKorea
- (Episode 10)
- I must find Soon-ok no matter what.
I have to find her! There's no time!
I'm sorry. You were in the
middle of a conversation.
No, it's fine.
You're the young grandma
I met last time.
Yes. Hello.
Starting from today,
she'll be working at our restaurant.
Oh, is that so?
Yes.
We troubled you last time and
didn't even get to thank you until now.
I'm sorry.
Things turned out well.
We'll see each other often now.
Yes. I'll do my best.
All right.
There are many people like her
who came from North Korea.
If Soon-ok is alive...
wouldn't I be able to bring her?
Of course, Elder.
So you must take care of your health.
All right.
It won't change?
But it's going to change soon.
How can it change when
there's something stuck on you?
Why? Is there a problem?
What's stuck on us?
Forget it! Let's go!
- What is it?
- Let's go!
- Why?
- Come out!
My goodness!
You'll be wasting a lot of your time!
Mom, wait! Did you just hear her say
that we'll be wasting a lot of our time?
She's a quack! A con-artist!
She's being ill-tempered because we paid
fifty dollars instead of a hundred dollars!
No, mom.
I suddenly feel anxious.
I think something is wrong.
What do you mean? What can go wrong?
It's strange.
The entire family's last name has to change,
so all of us should know about it.
Why hasn't anyone told us
anything yet though?
That's true.
This won't do, mom.
I need to check it out myself.
Mom, go home first.
Hey!
What if she gets in
trouble again? Hey! Hey!
Good-bye.
Where is my husband?
He's in his office.
Who is she?
She's Mr. Jo's wife.
Oh, I see.
Please hurry up.
And please find a trustworthy
broker in China for me.
Thank you for your help.
Honey!
I'm here.
What did you come here for?
I was just passing by.
What about father?
He had an appointment, so he went out.
Why are you looking for him?
Are you here to throw another fit?
If you do something
like that again, I'll just-
You'll just what? Divorce me?
I'd rather die than get a divorce.
All right. I'll throw a fit
at you only from now on.
Happy?
Stop being cheeky.
I don't want to talk with you
or see you for now, so get out.
He's so narrow-minded!
Hey, Jo Dal-ho! Stop being a show-off!
If it wasn't for father,
I would've dumped you already!
Why aren't you leaving?
Don't you have anything to tell me?
You woman.
What would I have to tell you?
Even if there was, I told you
that I don't want to talk with you.
Still, even if we have bad
and good times, we've
been a married couple
for almost thirty years now.
Aren't you being too harsh for me?
I'm your wife. Your wife.
Wife. Spouse. Life companion!
So what?
So what if you're my life companion?
Why aren't you telling your life
companion such an important thing?
Tell you what?
About being adopted as a son!
If you get adopted as father's son,
you're not the only one who will be effected.
If you become his son,
then I'll really become his daughter-in-law.
Our kids will become
Kim Hee-dong and Kim Hee-ra.
So why aren't you telling me about it?
What are you talking about?
Who said that's happening?
Father!
I definitely heard him tell you that he wanted
to adopt you as his son in the kitchen!
What?
Did you say no to him?
I'm busy.
Did you say no to him? Did you really?
Why not? Why not?
Damn it! What's so important
about being adopted as his son?
That's not the problem right now!
Then what is?
What's more important than that?
Do you know how
I've been living all this time?
I tried not to get on his bad side,
so I've been sucking
up to him all this time!
It was so difficult for me!
So you're saying
you were being nice to him all
this time because
you wanted his inheritance?
Then what about you?
Can you say you never felt
that way in the tiniest bit?
Yes! I never felt that way
in the teensiest bit at all!
Can you swear on
your dead father's name?
That you never felt
that way in the tiniest bit?
Did you already forget?
When we went bankrupt and had
to go to a motel, Elder came and
saved us. He did this much for us.
What more do you want from him?
You'll get punished for that!
Fine! I don't mind
getting punished at all!
I'll bear with all the
punishments, so hurry up and
go tell him that
you'll be adopted as his son!
What's wrong with you?
Fine. I know you're
a kind and good person.
But you can think of me just this once.
How many times have I told you not
to be greedy for Elder's inheritance?
If you want to keep
living with me as my wife,
you better throw those thoughts away. Got it?
Hey! Jo Dal-ho!
Hey!
You're a jerk!
You always make me
into a terrible person!
Ask anyone on the street if I'm the
terrible person or you're the awful idiot!
You moron! You fool!
I should slap you senseless
with rubber gloves on a rainy day!
I should beat you up!
Left! Right! Upper cut!
I should punch you and make you
bleed through both your nostrils!
You fool!
Damn you!
I feel a lot better.
I feel so fresh.
Take that, you jerk!
I should go home and cook.
(Leading lady??)
Darn it.
You should try dating, Mr. Jo.
Study women.
Excuse me.
Hello.
I'm a webtoon artist.
I'm someone who draws cartoons.
And?
You have the similar image
as the leading lady
of the webtoon
I'm currently preparing for.
If it's all right with you,
can you be my model?
I'll pay you, of course.
I'll think about it.
Yes, all right. Please think
about it and give me a call.
(Webtoon Artist Cleaning Man: Jo Hee-dong)
You'll clean hearts?
Fine. Go ahead and clean hard.
Hi.
A man?
What does he do?
He's a company employee?
He's a nice person?
No, thanks.
I don't date men who don't have money.
I don't care if
he's divorced or if he's old.
But he needs to be rich.
Who cares if he's a nice person?
Forget it.
(Owl)
They said they would
let me become a permanent
worker if I worked hard
for over two years!
Permanent worker, my foot!
They fired me overnight!
Does this even make sense?
They made me do all the work but
the dispatch company I worked for
won't even pay me my pension
because they said it went bankrupt!
So to sum it all up,
you were unfairly fired from the market
you worked at for over two years,
and you weren't paid your pension because
your dispatch company went bankrupt.
- Yes!
- That's right.
All right. I understand.
I'll use what you told me today
to try to find a way to solve this.
You two should find people
who will join you in your fight.
It would be very important to
make a team with a joint cause.
Then we'll leave it up to you and wait.
I'll do my best to make sure
there are good results.
- Please help us out.
- I will.
- Good-bye.
It's already so late!
Mi-poong will be waiting
for me without eating.
The person you are trying
to reach is unavailable.
Why isn't she picking up?
Oh! There it was!
Oh my goodness!
What's that?
What is this young lady doing here?
Look here, miss.
Miss!
What are you doing in
someone else's empty office?
How did you get in here?
I had some work to do,
so Jang-go told me I
could use this empty office
and watch over it.
He said I could use his computer, too.
You're really hopeless.
Even if he told you that you can use
his office, you should have said no.
How can you just
easily accept his offer?
How can you be so thoughtless?
I just-
What if the other people in this
building see you? What will they think?
They might misunderstand that there's
something going on between you two.
Do you have feelings for Jang-go?
Feelings? What do you mean?
Of course not.
You know the saying, "a boy and a girl
shouldn't sit together after the age of 7," right?
It seemed like you called
Jang-go out to drink last time.
Geum-sil will get angry
if she finds out about this.
You won't be able to live at
our house. Things will become chaotic.
I'm sorry.
I was thoughtless.
You probably know already,
but Jang-go is trying
to help you because
he pities your situation.
You should know your
boundaries though. This isn't right.
So be careful from now on so that
there aren't any misunderstandings.
Don't tell Jang-go I told you
this either. He'll get angry.
Do you understand?
Yes, I understand.
Then I'll be going now.
When I talk to her, she doesn't
seem like a strange person.
Do I have to tell Geum-sil or not?
If she finds out,
she won't let it slide.
What? Did she leave?
She should have told me she was leaving.
She's not even answering
her phone. What's going on?
Do you have feelings for Jang-go?
Of course not!
You should know your
boundaries though. This isn't right.
I hate the fact that you're hanging
around my son. It bothers me.
- Pardon?
- Jang-go has a lot of attachment like his father.
That's why he always has
to help poor people in need.
So I don't want you
to get the wrong idea.
(Jang-go)
Hi, it's me.
Kim Mi-poong, what happened
to you? You should've told
me you were leaving.
You didn't even answer my call.
I'm sorry.
I had it on vibrate mode,
so I didn't know you had called.
We were supposed to eat dinner together.
I was so hungry but starved myself
so that I could eat with you.
How can you do this to me?
I never promised to eat dinner with you.
I told you that I would come back
so that we can eat dinner together.
You assumed we would eat together.
We never promised that.
Hey, are you mad at me?
No.
I'm sorry.
I can't talk right now.
I'm hanging up.
Hey-
What's wrong with her suddenly?
(Jang-go)
She's not answering her phone!
What on earth is she doing?
Why isn't she home yet?
Did something go wrong?
Or did things go well and
they're celebrating without me?
- Oh!
- I'm back.
Dal-ho!
But why are you coming home alone?
Where's Chung-ja?
Pardon?
She didn't come home yet?
She went to meet you earlier,
and I can't get in touch with her!
Didn't you meet Chung-ja earlier?
Well, I did meet her, but...
Then did something happen
between you two?
Of course not.
She'll come home soon.
Don't worry and get some rest.
That indifferent fool!
His wife isn't home yet,
so how can he act like that?
My goodness!
It was a waste to make him
that brood hen a long time ago!
Chung-ja! Where are you?
Hello?
You just called this
cell-phone, didn't you?
Yes, but...
Pardon?
Where?
What did you say?
Mister!
Give me one more bottle of this!
No, no, no. That's enough.
I said-
Oh!
It's my mom!
Ms. Chun Gwi-ok!
Yes. I'm your mom Chun Gwi-ok.
What are you doing?
Jo Dal-ho will become
Kim Dal-ho soon, and you'll be hitting
the jackpot of your life.
So what are you doing right now?
That offer is off the table now.
What do you mean by that?
Mom, Dal-ho said he won't
be adopted as Elder's son.
What?
Are you serious?
Do you think that's all?
He's treating me like some thief
who is after the inheritance.
Why are you a thief?
It's not like you're forcibly
stealing Elder's inheritance.
This happened because
he didn't have any successors.
That's why that inheritance
should naturally go to you.
So how can you be a thief?
Why is that greed? It's not.
How could Jo Dal-ho
do this to me when he's the
only man I have ever
looked up to all my life?
Chung-ja, you have
nothing to worry about.
Even if Dal-ho isn't adopted as his son,
that inheritance is bound to be yours.
Even if Dal-ho says he won't
receive one penny of it,
all of that inheritance will
end up in your pocket anyways.
Watch what happens when it does end up
in my pocket. Jo Dal-ho, you just watch.
I'm going to pay him back
for hurting me today.
I won't give him even a penny!
Yes, Chung-ja.
Even half a penny is
wasteful on a fool like him.
Don't give it to him.
Don't give him anything.
- Mom.
- Yes, yes.
- I'll buy you an apartment.
- All right.
She's home.
The person you are trying
to reach is unavailable.
She's not picking up again.
Kim Mi-poong.
You still won't come out?
Are you okay?
It wasn't anything. It was just a bean.
A bean?
A bean.
I didn't throw it hard.
You're not hurt, are you?
How can you throw food?
Even immature kids don't do something
like that, but an adult like you did?
Well, you didn't answer your phone...
Same goes for earlier.
Do you know how baffled I was?
Of course we didn't make a promise,
but we had decided to eat dinner together.
So?
That's why you threw a bean?
No.
What I mean is...
you stood me up and
didn't even answer your phone!
I deserve to be mad! So I-
So you did something so immature?
Hey, Kim Mi-poong.
You're mad at me
for something, aren't you?
What is it? You need to tell me
so that I could know. Tell me.
What is it?
From now on, don't throw a bean
at my window to call me out again.
What would your family members
say if they saw you like this?
What else would they say? They would
assume that I'm talking to you.
Talking isn't a crime.
Why are you doing this to me?
Don't smile at me so sweetly like that.
- Aunt.
- Mi-poong, are you home already?
My mom and Yoo-sung are home.
What did I do?
Why is she being so cold to me?
I don't understand
women's capricious behavior.
Why did I have to throw a bean?
Lee Jang-go, you messed up today.
Here you go.
These dumplings are
from that noodle restaurant?
Yes. Mr. Kim gave it to me so that
you and Yoo-sung can eat them.
Hurry up and eat before they get cold.
Yoo-sung, is it good?
Yes, it is!
It's good?
What are you doing, Mi-poong? Eat up.
Mom, will you really be okay?
Working at a restaurant
will be very hard.
It's not hard at all.
The noodle bowls aren't heavy either.
I'm just grateful that
they gave me a job.
All the workers are very friendly,
and both Mr. Jo and Mr. Kim are very generous.
I'm going to work very hard.
From now on, I'm going to do
my best and make a lot of money.
Mi-poong,
let's save money and
move out of here quickly.
Okay, mom.
Grandma and aunt, are we going
to quickly become rich then?
Of course.
It'll be a while before the maid comes.
Why are they going to work late today?
My goodness.
It's salty!
It's so salty! What do I do?
It's so bland!
I need salt!
Mother!
Oh! It'll be done soon!
Go ahead and sit down, Mr. Kim.
Why are you cooking, Ms. Chun?
It must be tiring for you.
Grandma, where's mom?
Your mom is very sick.
She is?
She was fine yesterday.
It's all because of stress.
Grandma, the stew is overflowing.
It's hot!
My goodness! What do I do?
You should've been careful!
Ms. Chun, Dal-ho and I will eat out,
so don't work too hard.
No, no! It's almost finished!
Dal-ho, get ready for work and come out.
- Good-bye.
- Yes, Elder.
Oh, dear. It's all done though.
Chung-ja has fallen ill and is in bed.
Aren't you going to check up on her?
Your sweet words
are like medicine to her.
Why don't you check
on her before you go?
She's just sick from
drinking too much, so she
won't feel better just
because I say something.
- Good-bye.
- The point is that she's sick.
Why else would have
Chung-ja drank so much?
It's all because of you.
I know there are times
when you don't like Chung-ja.
But Dal-ho, who will be
next to you when you grow old?
Do you think it'll be Elder?
Or do you think your kids Hee-dong
and Hee-ra will be there for you?
That's all crap!
Nobody knows what
will happen in the future.
I have an important matter
to attend to, so I'll be leaving now.
Goodness! That idiot!
That indifferent fool!
That heartless fool!
Hold on.
"Nobody knows what
will happen in the future?"
What does that mean?
Is he saying that he might
not be living with Chung-ja?
Chung-ja! Chung-ja! Chung-ja!
Chung-ja!
- Hey, Chung-ja!
- What is it, mom?
Are Dal-ho and father worried
about me because they don't see me?
Worried, my foot!
I told them you were sick in bed,
and they have no interest whatsoever!
Really?
They don't ask where
and how much I'm sick?
Nope.
How did you stay married to
such a heartless man like that?
Mom, I told you I haven't told you
half the story of how I lived yet.
Anyways, stop protesting
and get up. This won't do.
I can't do that
because of my hurt pride.
Tell him to try living without me.
Do you know what Dal-ho said earlier?
I asked Dal-ho who would
stay by his side when
he got old, and do you
know what he said?
He said, "Nobody knows
what will happen in the future."
What does that mean?
Does that mean
he might not live with me?
Yes, it does.
Your husband is a
gold toad who is going to be
the successor of
Elder's inheritance later on.
So unless you're going to
divorce him, brush it all off and get up.
What are you going to do when
your gold toad hops off to another woman?
If that happens, it's all over for you.
What about my pride?
Your pride?
Just throw that little thing away.
Goodness! My unfortunate life!
- Hello!
Is it that late already?
I'm going to be late for
the logo contest deadline.
Where did it go?
It can't be gone!
Oh, where did it go?
I know I had definitely
made all of them!
Hey, it's me.
Two years ago,
there was a court case you did
against the Korean automobile dispatch workers.
Can you send me the documents for that?
All right. Thank you.
Okay.
This seems like
Mi-poong's logo contest drawing.
She drew it well.
It's not at home either! What happened?
I had definitely brought all of them
back from Jang-go's office yesterday!
Where did it disappear off to?
I don't have time to make it again!
(Jang-go)
Hello?
Hey, Mi-poong. I found one of your logo
drawings here. Do you not need it anymore?
That was there? I really need that!
What?
Isn't today the deadline?
Yes, I was looking for that right now.
I'll go to your office right now.
No, no, no.
If you come here, you'll be late.
I'll meet you in front
of the company right now.
All right!
Here.
- Thank you!
- Thank me later. Hurry up and go inside.
(Reception Desk for
the Symbol Competition)
- I'm not late, am I?
- No, you're not. You can give it to me.
(Application for Zishen Logo Contest)
Are all these the applications?
Yes. Today is the deadline,
so there are quite a lot.
It has been submitted.
When will the results come out?
They will contact you within this week.
I see. Thank you.
How did it go?
Thanks to you, I submitted it safely.
Thank you.
I'm glad.
I'm hungry.
Buy me food.
What?
Food?
Hey, I rushed all the way here
just for you. You can't just overlook this.
Okay. I'll buy you food.
What do you want to eat?
Is it black bean noodles today, too?
Black bean noodles? Not today.
Today...
Enjoy.
Is work okay?
Yes.
Hi, it's me.
Elder, I found Mr. Kim's address.
You did?
Where is it?
Gunsan.
I'm on my way over there right now.
If I meet Mr. Kim, I'll bring him to you.
You should have gone with me.
No, it's fine. It'll take some time,
so go on home first.
All right?
All right.
I wonder what's wrong.
He didn't even eat any of his noodles.
Poor Mr. Kim.
Poor Mr. Kim?
He's wealthy and successful.
So what? He has no blood relatives.
Isn't Mr. Jo his family?
Mr. Jo is just his distant nephew.
His real family members died
in North Korea a long time ago.
All of them?
All of them.
Not even one of them is alive.
Sometimes he cries while drinking soju.
It's so sad that it makes me tear up.
Good, right?
Is it that good?
Yeah. It's so strange.
Whether it's black bean noodles or spicy
rice cakes, whatever you buy is really good.
Eat a lot.
You're a different person today.
What do you mean by that?
Well, you were weird to me yesterday.
I told you to wait so that
we can eat dinner together,
but you just left.
You ignored my calls, too.
You were mad at me
yesterday, weren't you?
Was it because I threw a bean at you?
Yes, I was mad because
you threw a bean at me.
Really?
If you play with food like that,
you'll get punished after you die.
Sometimes, you nag on people so weirdly.
Kim Mi-poong, you're very scary!
Hey! Lee Jang-go!
Oh! Sung-sil!
Wow! It's been so long!
How have you been?
Wow. Is your company nearby?
I work for N&G.
The headquarters is right here.
But is she your girlfriend...?
Huh?
No way. She's like my little sister.
Is she really your little sister?
Wow! You have a lovely little sister!
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Bang Sung-sil.
By any chance, do you have a boyfriend?
Hey! How can you ask her that
when you met her for the first time?
Mr. Kang, aren't we going to go?
Yes, we are.
Anyways, let's catch up soon. You, too.
My name card.
Oh, dear. I didn't bring one.
Have this instead.
See you later.
- Bye!
He's so brazen. My friend is funny, huh?
Eat up.
It's delicious.
What is it now?
Why are you being like this again?
What do you mean?
You usually talk a lot, but you're not
even saying one word right now.
I'm wondering why
you're acting like this again.
Since you're not talking,
it's boring. Say something.
Am I a chatterbox that yaps my head off
anytime so that you won't get bored?
You're doing it again!
You're being aggressive again!
Why have you been
like this since yesterday?
You smile then frown.
You're happy then angry.
I don't know how to keep up
with your capricious behavior.
Why are you being like this?
We had a good time eating
spicy rice cakes. So what's wrong?
What did I do?
Then are you saying I'm doing
this for no reason at all?
Tell me what's wrong so that I can know.
Tell me.
Do you still see me as the little tadpole
who used to go to school with you in Macau?
You treat me like a little kid.
Hey, Kim Mi-poong!
Don't follow me!
What would your mom and
aunt say if they saw you like this?
My goodness.
We had a good time eating
spicy rice cakes, so what's wrong?
I really don't know.
Is she your girlfriend?
Huh? No way!
She's like my little sister.
To Jang-go, I'm not a woman.
I'm just his friend's little sister.
Jang-go is being good to me and helping
me out because he feels pitiful for me.
I was confused.
Jang-go wasn't the fool. I was.
I'll put my feelings away for Jang-go
while he doesn't realize them.
Yes.
I should have at least asked
for her phone number then.
- Here you go.
- Ma'am, that's the grandson of that old
man with the 100 million
dollar inheritance, right?
Yes, you're right.
- He is!
But why does his rich grandson
always go around like that?
He always wears sweatpants
and eats cup ramen.
Who cares when he's wealthy?
It must be because he's wealthy.
Doesn't he still look cool?
I guess. He has 100 million dollars,
so who cares?
Ma'am, what do you mean by that? The grandson
with a 100 million dollar inheritance?
Are you talking about that young man
eating ramen in front of the convenience store?
Yes, everyone in this neighborhood
knows that he's the grandson
- of that old man with a
100 million dollar inheritance.
- Nobody doesn't know that.
Oh, I see.
(Webtoon artist: Jo Hee-dong)
He's the grandson with a
100 million dollar inheritance?
Who is it?
Hello?
Is this Mr. Jo Hee-dong?
Yes, I'm Jo Hee-dong.
Are you...?
Yes, I'm the person you gave
your name card to at the
convenience store last time.
Do you remember me?
Of course I do!
I'm interested in experiencing the
modeling work you mentioned last time.
Is it still open?
Yes!
It's still...
open.
When should we meet?
Tomorrow?
Yes, I know that place.
Then I'll see you tomorrow.
Mother, where's Elder?
- He's home, right?
- Yes.
He's in his room.
Okay.
What is it? Why is he in a rush?
Mr. Kim is dead?
He died of an illness five years ago.
Don't be too disappointed, Elder.
This is just the beginning.
Dal-ho.
I can still hear Mr. Kim's voice.
I still can't forget it.
It's so vivid like it
happened yesterday.
The day he listed all of
my family members' names...
and said that they all died.
Yes, I feel the same way, Elder.
How he had said...
that Kim Soon-ok had also died.
If he had really lied that
a living person had been dead...
he would have gone to hell.
Since Mr. Kim died,
we can't know if he was
telling the truth about
your wife's death or not...
but this time, we'll find
a trustworthy broker who
knows well about the
situation in North Korea...
and I'll definitely help
you reunite with her.
Since you're going out
of your way just for me...
I should recover my strength
no matter what.
Yes...
Mom, what are you doing here?
Are you eavesdropping
on my father-in-law right now?
As soon as Dal-ho came home,
he rushed into Elder's room.
I thought something was weird,
so I eavesdropped, and
it seems like something
very serious is going on.
It seemed like he was crying.
Crying? My father-in-law?
Yes!
I think they were talking
about someone dying.
Why would he cry for
someone's death? There's no
one on this planet who
he would cry for like that.
Maybe someone had
taken a lot of his money!
Maybe.
Why is he crying?
- It's strange, right?
- Yes.
Honey.
Are you all right now?
Huh? Oh, yes.
From now on, she won't
cause any trouble for you,
and she'll only listen to you.
I see.
If you're feeling all right, I was hoping
you would make some porridge for Elder.
Why? Is he suddenly feeling unwell?
Something stressful happened to him.
What kind of stressful event?
Can't you tell us?
It's his personal matter.
He'll tell you later himself
after it gets solved.
A personal matter?
Perhaps his close friend died.
When you get old,
the most hurtful and bitter
thing is to lose
your friends one by one.
Do you think so?
Why are you just standing there?
Hurry up and go make porridge!
You need to
use this chance to
earn some brownie points!
Okay, mom.
Since there's no chance
of Dal-ho being adopted as
his son, I'm just going
to forget all about it.
Good idea. You don't need
anything else but the gold toad.
Just take care of your husband
Jo Dal-ho. Do you know what I mean?
Of course I do.
Yes. Mom is right.
The inheritance is the end goal.
We just have to inherit
father's inheritance no matter what.
It's hot.
Good, good, good.
What happened to you?
How can you pathetically be the third wheel
between your friend and her boyfriend?
Just drink coffee and go home.
If they ask you to go watch a movie,
you better say no.
I think I'm so blessed.
I don't know!
Hee-ra is here.
What an eyesore.
I need to use the restroom, too.
- Okay. Be safe!
- Okay.
Do you really want to do
that in a public place?
You two have been touching
each other ever since we met up.
It's not like you guys
are some seasoned meat.
I don't know.
He just can't leave me alone.
He said it's impossible not to touch
the woman he likes when he's next to her.
He said he likes everything
about me and wants to
touch me from head to tie.
What am I supposed to do?
You little brats...
Then you two should just meet up!
What did you call me out for?
Don't call me again. Got it?
You said you were bored to death!
You were the one who called me
first and wanted to meet up!
How could he not call me once
after going to the motel with me twice?
Am I really not attractive?
Am I not charming at all?
Yes. I need to meet with him myself.
Darn it.
Hello?
What do you want?
Right now?
You have something to ask me?
What is it?
Huh? Hello?
What's with this woman?
It's like she's playing around with me.
She always vanishes at the motel.
So what does she need to ask me about?
All she does is ignite fire
in a man's heart!
Where did it go?
Darn it! Did Jang-go wear it?
Grandma! Mom!
Grandma, are my tiger
print boxers there?
- Your tiger print boxers?
- Yes.
It's right here.
But what do you need it for?
For something.
Why is he suddenly looking for
his tiger print boxers at this hour?
What did you need to tell me?
Am I really not attractive? Really?
What are you talking about?
Am I really not charming
to you as a woman at all?
We went to the motel twice, not once.
How could you just leave me alone?
This was what you wanted to ask me?
Just answer my question. I need to know.
Am I really not attractive?
No, you are.
Then?
Then why are you just leaving me alone?
Because I want to protect you!
Because I like you!
Oh my gosh! I'm sorry!
But wait...
You're so pretty!
What's your name?
I'm Lee Jang-soo.
I'm Jo Hee-ra.
Now that we know each other's names,
we know everything about each other.
I'm sorry.
Get in here.
Oh my gosh!
You!
You didn't come home last night?
Mommy!
You're dead!
Open the door!
Mom, quiet down please! If Hee-dong
finds out, he'll beat me to death!
What? Did you really
cause trouble this time?
Did you really do something
you deserve a beating for?
Mom, don't get angry,
and just listen to me.
Mom, I have a man that I love.
I was with him until now.
I didn't cause any trouble.
What? A man that you love?
Fine! What does he do for a living?
I didn't ask him that yet...
You don't know
what he does for a living?
Oh my goodness.
Fine. What family is he from?
What do his parents do?
Where does he live?
I didn't ask him those yet either...
What? Then what do you know about him?
His name.
What?
You only know his name,
and yet you slept with him?
- You little brat!
- Mom!
Just die!
Mom!
- Mom, what are you looking at?
- You scared me!
Don't creep up on me like that!
Are you waiting for someone? What happened?
Did Jang-soo not come home last night?
Be quiet. If Geum-sil finds out,
things will get messy.
Goodness. It's not a secret.
This isn't the first time
Jang-soo stayed out all night.
Yes, I know that,
but he stayed out all night the
other times because
he was practicing his acting.
But last night,
I had a weird feeling about it.
What do you mean a weird feeling?
Last night, Jang-soo
looked for his tiger print
boxers and wore them before he went out.
Tiger print boxers?
Did Jang-soo go out to meet a woman?
That's what I'm afraid of!
Oh my god.
Why are all of you out here?
Were you waiting for me?
Lee Jang-soo, tell us the truth.
Where were you last night
and who were you with?
The thing is...
Fine.
Since things turned out this way already,
I'll just tell you everything.
Mom. Aunt. Grandma.
I have a woman I love.
That's why I spent last night with her.
What? A woman you love?
Lee Jang-soo, are you
still dating Ms. Song?
I just told you I have a woman that I love!
Why would you bring Ms. Song up?
I told you a hundred times that
I don't like a woman who left me behind!
Then are you saying
you got another girlfriend?
Yes, mom. She's super cute,
really pretty, and
extremely fashionable.
On top of that, she's so nice!
Oh my goodness. Oh, my head.
I don't know. I don't know.
I've been shocked enough times now.
I already saw you date a divorced woman
twelve years younger than you who has kids.
I have no interest in
your love life whatsoever,
so live your life however you want to.
Mom! Mom!
You need to know
about the new woman I love!
You little punk!
Why are you mouthing off when you didn't
do anything to deserve doing that?
We lost. We really lost.
Aren't aunt and mom being too harsh?
You little punk.
Men need to be careful of three things:
their mouth, their fist,
and their "down there."
But what are you doing?
If you have complicated women problems,
you'll be humiliating the entire family!
Grandma, I won't be doing
anything to humiliate
the family, so don't you
worry about a thing!
Grandma, don't you trust me?
Fine.
Who else would I trust besides you?
Grandma, I'm serious this time.
I really found my other half,
so don't worry.
Okay?
What am I suppose to do with him?
You're so cute.
Yoo-sung, will you really be okay
without me and your aunt?
Yes!
Goodness! You're all grown up!
You're going camping
with your school now.
Yoo-sung, you really can be good, right?
Yes, I can!
But will it really be okay
to send him off alone?
Come on, mom. All the other
children are going alone, too.
The teachers will take good care of him,
so don't worry too much.
Yoo-sung, be sure to listen to your teachers well,
and don't wander around alone.
Got it?
Yes!
All right. Let's go then.
Let's go!
Hello?
Yes, I'm Kim Mi-poong.
Excuse me?
I passed?
Are you serious?
Thank you! Thank you!
Mi-poong, what happened?
Mom, I passed the
logo contest I entered!
I'll get a prize, and I might be
able to work for the company!
Really?
- Are you serious?
- Yes!
Aunt, did you get an award?
Yes, Yoo-sung, I did!
Wow! You're the best!
Thank you! This is all thanks to you!
Yoo-sung! Mi-poong, you did well!
This is for table 13.
Yes, I got it.
Your cold noodles are here!
Enjoy!
Did something good happen?
My daughter won a contest and
got a job to work for a huge company.
That's great!
It's so hard to find a job lately.
Congratulations.
Thank you!
The weather is great.
Kang Mi-jung!
You!
What's your problem?
It's nothing. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry!
Why am I doing this again
when I decided not to?
You!
No!
It's you!
Hey! Stop right there!
Hey!
You wench!
Let go of me!
It really is you!
Yes! It is you!
(Blow Breeze)
Did you see a woman in a white dress
with long hair who just passed by?
You're trying to sell off your son! You brat!
What did you just say?
Are you done talking?
You won the contest!
You knew that, didn't you?
Where did you design that logo?
In my office, right? Using my computer, right?
Did you or did you not?
I'm sorry.
Can you leave me and marry another man?
Let's go to your house
and get permission!
When I think about it,
I think you're amazing.
To be honest, you were
a great strength to me.
Subtitles by OnDemandKorea