Subtitles by OnDemandKorea
(Episode 11)
You!
It's you, isn't it?
No! No!
Stop right there!
You wench!
Let go!
You awful wench! You horrible witch!
You damned vixen!
- Give me my money!
- Let go!
Let go of me! You got the wrong person!
- Lady, stop!
- Give me my money!
It's not me! I said it's not me!
Stop right there! Stop!
Stop right there!
Hey! Stop!
Where did this wench go?
Excuse me.
Did you see a woman with
long hair wearing a white dress?
Miss! Miss!
Did you see a woman with
long hair wearing a white dress?
No, I didn't.
You didn't?
Where the heck did this wench go?
She ran into the restroom.
Is there someone inside?
Kang Mi-jung. I was going to
catch that wench for sure today.
I got you today!
I got you.
Don't even move.
What do I do?
How can I get out of here?
Stay still!
Hi, mom.
Mi-poong! Seung-hee!
Hurry up and come here!
Hurry! I got Kang Mi-jung!
Hurry up!
What? You got who?
Don't move.
Open up!
Open the door!
You're a rat in a trap.
You're no better than a rat!
Fine! Try running away!
Where did all that money go?
Where is our money?
Money?
What money?
Our money that you stole from us!
Where is our money?
Did you see me steal it? Did you?
If there are any witnesses,
tell them to come out!
What?
Are you saying that
money belongs to you?
Isn't that the people's money?
So what right do you have
to throw a fit like this?
Open the door. I said open up!
Open up!
You little wench! That's the money that
my husband earned through his hard work!
Don't you dare lie.
I know it's money that
you sucked from the people!
It's money you stole from the people!
You're no better than a beast!
You're no better than a dog!
I dressed you, clothed you,
and raised you!
How dare you say
such atrocious things to me!
You!
Let go of me!
Let go!
That wench!
You.
You!
Mom! Your hand!
Catch her!
Your hand! What happened to your hand?
I'm fine, so catch that awful wench!
I'm fine, so catch her!
You must catch her!
How did they come here
without starving to death in China?
I should do plastic surgery
to change my face.
(Emergency Ward)
I can't forgive you, Kang Mi-jung.
I'll never forgive you.
Since we're in Korea,
we'll meet again someday.
I'll make sure to pay
you back a thousand times.
(My Rope)
(My Jang-soo)
Oh my god.
It's my Jang-soo.
It's me.
You answered right away.
I was just about to call you.
We must have
a telepathic connection now.
Are we a match made in heaven?
A match made in heaven?
Perhaps?
I really miss you, baby.
Baby?
Me?
Because to me, you're lovable,
sweet, and pretty.
On top of that, I feel like
you'll burst when I touch you.
Oh my gosh. You're embarrassing me!
Are you free tomorrow, baby?
Do you want to go to
an amusement park tomorrow?
Or is that too childish?
Not at all! I can go anywhere you
want to, even to the frozen Arctic.
Hee-ra, what are you doing?
Who are you talking to?
It's him, isn't it?
That Jang-soo or whatever his name is!
Hee-ra, who is that?
My mom!
- My mom...
- Don't talk to him.
No! No! Give me my phone!
I said give it to me, mom!
Hee-ra, what's wrong?
Did you get your phone taken away?
I don't know who you are,
but you better not call Hee-ra again!
I won't just stand by then!
Hello, mother.
I'm sorry for introducing myself
over the phone. I'm-
How dare you call me mother!
I warned you!
Don't call or meet Hee-ra ever again!
Mother! Mo-
Mom! My phone!
The person you are trying
to reach is unavailable.
What happened?
Is Hee-ra in big trouble?
Was it because
she stayed out that night?
Gosh. I can't even
get in touch with her.
If I had known this would happen,
I would've gotten her address.
What do I do?
Darn it!
What the hell happened to me?
How can this happen
when I'm supposed to meet him?
I have to meet him.
I don't have my phone,
so I can't even contact him.
Such bad luck.
They wouldn't still be there
trying to catch me, right?
Shin-ae.
Oh, my.
Why are you here?
Pardon?
Is this not the right place?
Two hours had already passed,
so I thought you had left.
We promised to meet,
so how can I just leave?
Oh my goodness.
I'm so sorry, Mr. Jo.
I made you wait for a long time.
No, it's fine. You came,
and that's all that matters.
I was reading a book
and looking at articles on my
cell-phone. It wasn't difficult
waiting for two hours.
Have a seat.
Okay.
Thank you.
But did something happen?
I couldn't get in touch
with you, so I was worried.
The thing is...
I was on my way to come see you...
but there was an
injured kitten that was crying.
Its cry was so sad that
I couldn't just pass by it.
I treated the kitten and
took it to the shelter afterward.
Oh, I see.
I'm sorry.
I was going to call you,
but my phone was gone.
I think I must have dropped it
while running with the kitten.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
That's why I wasn't able
to get in touch with you.
But I didn't think you would
have still waited for me.
Just like you said, we had promised
to meet, so I just came by just in case.
You have a scratch on your forehead!
Oh, this?
I was holding the kitten
and running with it,
but I think it was very hurt by people.
This is nothing compared to the hurt
the kitten received from other people.
I'm okay.
But what do I need
to do for the modeling?
Thank you.
Hi.
Look over here. Hello.
Nice.
Bark. Bark.
- What do you think?
- Looks good.
The color is very pretty.
- I'll pick one for you.
- Sure.
Wow! It's pretty!
It looks like you'll be
very good at magic.
- Weird, huh?
- No, you look like a very competent person.
Is this helpful?
Of course.
Hold on.
Can you delete this one, please?
It's so weird!
Hold on. I don't think
this one will do either.
You look very pretty.
- Want to take another one?
- The selfies came out great.
This is lemon tea.
What do you think?
I made it a while ago.
Is it good?
Yes.
It's very good.
It smells great, too.
Mom.
I know. Don't worry.
I won't be upset over
such a worthless girl anymore.
But after seeing her again today,
I realized she really is worthless.
Do you know what she told me?
She asked where is the
evidence that she stole our money.
She demanded if there were
witnesses that saw her stealing it.
She really said that?
Yes, and then she accused our money
of being stolen from the people.
She was very confident,
even though she stole our money.
She's a crazy wench.
That's what she said?
Yes.
We suffered so much
in China because of her.
If I think about that, I can't...
Later on, when I meet her,
I need to pluck out all of her hair.
That's the only way I'll be able to wash
away all the resentment in my heart.
Yes, mom.
When we meet her again,
let's pluck out all of her hair.
I'll pluck all of them out.
All right.
I'm alive right now
because I'm with you.
What would I have done
if you weren't here?
Mom...
Hi, Young-soon.
I was just about to leave now.
You're going to be late? How late?
Oh, all right.
We'll start first.
Okay. See you later.
Wait, Young-soon!
Chung-ja really isn't coming, right?
Okay! See you later.
What? Her family is opposing you?
She got her phone taken away,
and she's trapped at home.
They allowed her to be careless
like that, but now they're opposing you?
What idiots! My goodness!
Grandma, how can you say that?
Hee-ra and I are in love!
So why are you treating us
like we did something wrong?
Kids these days are so stubborn.
Goodness. I know. They're stubborn
as if they passed the bar exam!
It doesn't matter how much
the world has changed.
Does it make sense
that she got drunk and
followed a man she just
met at a bar to a motel?
How do you always meet such lousy women?
Lousy?
I can hold my breath for anything else
but not when you talk crap about Hee-ra!
If you're going to talk crap
about someone, talk crap about me!
Hey, Lee Jang-soo! You better tell them
that our family opposes her even more!
That you two can
never be together! Got it?
That's right! I'll never
let you two be together!
Gosh!
- Hold on. Mom...
- Yes?
Didn't Jang-soo say
his girlfriend's name is Hee-ra?
I'm not sure. Did he?
The name of Geum-sil's
friend's daughter who
Jang-soo went on a blind date
with was Hee-ra also.
I'm going out.
Where are you going?
To meet my friends.
Did you make up with
your 100 million dollar friend?
Am I crazy? Why would
I make up with her?
I'll be back, mother.
Bye.
They must be leaving
her friend out in the cold.
I guess so. Who would want
to be friends with someone who
shows off with their
distant relative's inheritance?
You better not go out
just because I did. Watch
what happens when you
meet up with that boy.
I'll tell your grandfather, dad,
and Hee-dong and
send you away to the
heart of the mountains!
I'll pretend I don't have a daughter,
shave your head,
and make you rot in
the mountains forever!
Got it?
Why would you do that?
Am I a child? Am I in middle school?
I just fell in love,
but you're going to shave
my head and make me rot
in the mountains forever?
How can you say that to me?
It's because you're my child.
If you were someone else's child,
would I do this? Am I crazy?
I definitely warned you.
Okay, mom.
I won't go out.
I won't go out. I'll stay home, so...
give me my cell-phone. Please?
Then you'll contact
Jang-soo or whatever his
name is. It'll be like
leaving a fish to a cat.
Am I crazy?
Don't talk about him that way!
He's a precious child
to his family, too!
Yeah, right!
Give me my cell-phone, you hag!
I'm going to go nuts!
Mom!
Oh, dear.
Mink is great!
Mink is perfect for winter!
Mom, you have to watch Hee-ra!
How can you fall sleep?
What are you talking about?
When I was sleeping?
I wasn't sleeping!
I was looking at this!
You don't know when she'll run away!
You know what to do
until I come back, don't you?
Watch for her like you're watching
money in your pocket!
I got it.
I got it, so stop with the lecturing.
What kind of strange boy is
Hee-ra dating for you to act this way?
Is he that bad?
I don't know. We'll talk later.
Bye.
Goodness. She's just like her mom.
What on earth is her boyfriend like?
Mom, where are you going?
To work, of course.
How can you go to work with that hand?
Tell them you can't come.
How can you work with that hand?
I just started working there.
I can't do that.
I'll be careful, so don't worry.
Mom, still...
And...
if I stay home, I'll be sick with anger.
If I go to work, I can forget everything,
so I'll be more comfortable. I'll be fine.
Then be careful. Don't work too hard.
Okay.
By the way, let's meet
after you're done with work.
It's your first day at work tomorrow,
and I need to buy you some new clothes.
No, it's fine.
I already washed the clothes
I'll wear tomorrow.
I want to buy you some clothes.
I'll come with Yoo-sung after I'm done
with work, so you better meet us.
Okay?
Okay.
Good.
Let's buy pretty clothes.
Geum-sil, is your son's office
settling down now?
Yes, it's just starting to.
Goodness. Already?
You're so lucky.
It's hard for a law office
to settle down, but
once it does,
you'll be sweeping in money.
No, it's not that well off yet.
And Jang-go isn't being
a lawyer just for the money.
But what happened between
Chung-ja's daughter and your son?
Let's not talk about that.
There's nothing to talk about anyways.
Hey! I'm here-
Young-soon, what happened?
You said Geum-sil wasn't coming today!
Chung-ja, enough already.
Goodness. We decided to
meet today to let you two
make up, so just bear with it for our sakes.
Chung-ja, come here.
It was good for a while. I feel like someone
threw a bucket of cold water at me.
Oh my goodness. You must
have been tempting someone else.
You were tempting me in order to somehow
make your son and my daughter get together.
Who were you using
that fake tactic on now?
What? Fake tactic?
That's right. Fake tactic.
Do you know what Geum-sil did?
She met my innocent daughter without me
knowing and told her to seduce her son.
Hey.
Are you done talking?
No, I'm not.
You're a crazy witch
who's trying to sell your son!
Geum-sil, hold back.
- Chung-ja!
- You need to know how scary Geum-sil is!
She kept telling me to
borrow money from her!
I thought she really was
trying to be a good friend!
But I found out she was
just trying to steal my daughter!
I'm speechless.
Save a stranger from
the sea and he'll turn
into your enemy.
You're worse than such a man.
What did you say?
Hey! I wasn't going to say this,
but did I let you borrow money
for no good reason?
You were begging for your life in
front of those loan sharks, so I let
you borrow money because I was
afraid something would happen to you!
But what? I was using a fake tactic
on you? My goodness!
You were smiling at me while saying
you would pay me back later. My goodness.
Oh, Chung-ja!
You're taking private loans?
Why?
That's not it...
Who cares if you'll get an inheritance later
when you don't have any money now?
She's all style and no substance.
Did you or did you not
call yourself that?
So you should earn money yourself instead
of bragging with other people's money.
- Cousin? He's your long distance relative...
- Hey!
You little!
- Stop it!
Let go of me!
Don't hold me back!
- About the broker you chose in China this time...
- Yes?
He's really trustworthy, right?
Yes, sir.
I must trust him. Yes, I do.
If he even knows the slightest bit of
how desperate I am to find my family...
he should do his best.
Yes.
He does business back and forth in China
and North Korea, so he knows the situation
very well and has a lot of experience.
He should have some good news for you.
- Mr. Yang.
- Yes?
I want to go to China
and meet the broker myself.
I want to greet him,
hold his hands, and beg him.
He needs to lie low until
he finds Kim Soon-ok, so
I think that's going
to be difficult to do, sir.
Really?
Is the situation
that terrible right now?
You know how unsettled things
are in North Korea right now.
That's why the border security
has been reinforced,
and it has become
a lot harder to find people.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
If there's any rumor that someone
is searching for someone, then
that information goes to the
North Korean government right away.
They could be on put on surveillance,
and if that happens, then the
person you are looking for could be
in danger before we find her first.
That can't happen!
That can never happen!
That's why you need to put your faith
in that Chinese broker for now.
He needs to do this secretly.
All right.
We'll be careful here, too.
Mr. Yang, please do your best.
I really hope we'll be
able to find her, too.
Mr. Yang,
please help me out.
Please.
- (Deokcheonok)
- Welcome.
Welcome!
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
Did you hurt your hand?
Did you hurt it here?
No!
I didn't hurt it here.
I hurt it while I was
going home yesterday.
Then you should have told us
your situation and stayed home today.
I just started working here.
I couldn't do that.
Still, you should go home right now.
Your hand has to get better.
No, Mr. Jo, I'm fine. I'm really okay.
You even made my schedule
flexible enough for Yoo-sung's
kindergarten hours.
So how can I be so shameless?
See? I'm perfectly fine.
Goodness. You're very stubborn.
Okay, then.
Since the end of your shift is
approaching soon,
just escort the customers.
That's okay, right?
Of course! I tried to
stop her from working, too.
Here you go.
Put the tote bag in the front
and shoulder bag in the back.
Also, bring out
more clothes in fall colors.
Welcome.
Can we look at some clothes?
Of course. Comfortably look around.
Shin-ae.
Where did she go?
Did she go to the restroom?
Whose clothes are you looking for?
For my daughter.
Tomorrow is her first day of work.
Will there be something suitable for her?
Of course. We have many office looks.
Come this way.
This is the most popular
outfit of this season.
I think it would suit you well.
What do you think?
How did they come here?
Did they come knowing I was here?
No, no, no, no.
If that was true, they wouldn't be
comfortably picking out clothes right now.
But why do we keep
running into each other?
Do they live around here?
Oh my goodness.
Oh! Hello!
Try both of them.
No, I'll just try on this one.
How can we just buy one outfit?
We need to at least buy two of them.
Try them on.
Come on, mom.
You can try both of them.
Yes. It's not like it
costs money to try them on.
Try them.
Where can I try them on?
The fitting room is back there.
Okay, thank you.
Aunt, some lady is in here.
Really?
Ma'am, are you done
wearing your clothes?
Yoo-sung, you shouldn't do that.
Go to grandma.
That little brat.
Thank you.
- Enjoy.
- Okay.
Good-bye.
I think you still have a customer
inside that fitting room.
Pardon?
I don't think so.
There wasn't anyone else.
There is a lady in there.
Really? I'll go check.
- Bye.
- Thank you.
Is anyone in here?
Shin-ae!
Ma'am...
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
I thought you were in the restroom.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Ma'am...
My grandmother collapsed.
Really?
You have a grandmother?
After my parents had passed away,
she had raised me until now.
Oh, no.
You should hurry up and go.
I'm here, so it's okay.
Can't I move to the branch
I was talking about last time?
Because of your grandmother?
That branch is close to
my grandmother's house.
I think I have to take care of
my grandmother from now on.
I won't be able to live if
something happens to her.
There's no other choice
since your grandmother is ill.
I can't work without you.
But now is not the time that
I should be holding you back.
I'll call that branch,
so don't worry about it.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
It'll be okay.
Thank you.
Mr. Lee, may I go home now?
Go ahead.
What about you?
I need to look up more data.
Okay. Good luck.
- See you at home.
- Okay.
Were the results for Mi-poong's logo
competition announced?
Should I call her?
No. It would be embarrassing
for the both of us if she had lost.
That's right.
(Announcement of Final Candidates)
I'm so nervous.
Let's see.
(First place: Kim Mi-poong)
What's this?
First place: Kim Mi-poong?
Mi-poong won first place?
That Kim Mi-poong I know?
Thank you for everything.
Thanks to you, I was able to
gain a lot of good experiences.
Of course. I knew things
would work out for you.
If you said you were going somewhere else,
I would have never let you.
I'm letting you go because
you're going to a good company.
Thank you. Please take care of yourself.
Mi-poong, if you happen to pass
by here, you must come and visit me.
Yes, I will.
I hope everything works out for you!
Okay!
- Good-bye.
- Do your best!
- Mi-poong, work hard!
I will!
Farewell, old work place.
I will succeed and come back.
What are you doing here?
I was just passing by when I realized it
was time for you to go home, so I came
to check just in case you were here.
What a coincidence we meet like this!
You're on your way home, right?
Well, yes...
But why?
What do you mean "why?"
We should go home together.
What? Aren't you going to go?
You must have something to tell me.
Something to tell you?
Come on.
Let's go.
What do I have to tell you?
Think about it carefully. There must
be something you want to tell me.
Yeah, right. There's nothing
I especially need to tell you.
Gosh, I'm disappointed.
Kim Mi-poong,
I'm really disappointed in you!
Disappointed about what?
I bought you black bean noodles all this time.
Are you acting this way because I bought you
spicy rice cakes instead of black bean noodles?
That was because you said you
wanted spicy rice cakes instead!
Are you really going to be like this?
What's wrong with you?
Stop beating around the bush
and tell me what's on your mind!
You won the logo competition!
It wasn't even for second or
third place. You won first place!
How can you not tell me about that?
Pardon?
You're not going to tell me
you didn't know you won, are you?
Oh... that?
"That?"
"Oh, that?"
Kim Mi-poong, I didn't know you were
like that! They say people change
once they succeed,
but you shouldn't be like this to me!
Is that something
you should be so angry about?
Of course!
Kim Mi-poong, half of that success
is due to me! Half of it!
What if I hadn't brought
your drawing to that
company? Do you think
you would have been chosen?
Do you think you could
have gotten first place?
And I didn't want to say this because
it would look like I was bragging,
but where did you prepare
for that logo competition?
You did it in my office
with my computer and printer.
Did you or did you not?
Huh?
I did.
You did, right?
Were you or were you not wrong?
I think I was wrong.
You think so?
I was wrong.
Right? You were wrong, right?
I feel a lot better now.
Shall we go?
But where are we going right now?
I don't think this is the way home.
Since you did something
very wrong today, all
you need to do is
stay quiet and follow me.
Don't move.
You should still answer me, Mi-poong.
Okay.
Good.
Kim Mi-poong, congratulations.
Thank you.
But this seems like
a very expensive place.
I told you to do as I told you today.
Still.
Again.
Eat up.
Hurry up and try it.
How is it? Good?
I think you're very amazing.
Why?
It must have been a very
competitive competition because
it offered, not only prize money,
but also a job.
It's not like you studied
industrial design, so
how did you manage
to get first place so easily?
When I was in North Korea,
I studied art.
If I hadn't dreamt of being
a dancer, I would've been an artist.
Really?
Anyways,
you won first place while you were
stressing over the housing issue,
working part-time, and taking care
of your mother and nephew.
Good job. You're admirable.
You're embarrassing me.
Why are you embarrassed
when I was merely stating the facts?
Anyone can do it with words,
but no one can actually do it like you.
Since you're so hard-working,
a good opportunity
was given to you. That's what I think.
Here.
Congratulations.
To be honest, you were
a big strength to me.
Thank you very much.
Lee Jang-go.
Oh, Sung-sil.
We meet each other frequently nowadays.
I know.
Hello. You remember me, don't you?
Hello.
What are you doing here?
Do you have a meeting?
Yeah, we're having a company dinner,
but no one is here yet.
I think I came too early.
But what are you doing here?
You said she's like your little sister.
So why are you
always with her? And what's
with this sappy atmosphere?
Stop joking around.
She won a logo competition.
So we came here to eat to
celebrate her victory and new job.
Oh, really?
Oh, congratulations, miss!
Thank you.
Mind if I join your celebration
before my co-workers come?
- What?
- I'll buy good wine to celebrate her win, okay?
Is it okay?
- Sit down.
- Okay.
Goodness.
Are you okay?
Please suggest a good bottle
of wine for us.
Hi, aunt.
Is it an urgent matter?
Hold on.
I need to make a call.
Go on.
So the market acquired a lawyer?
Yes. And do you know
from where? Janghaenggo.
Janghaenggo?
That means they won't do
any settlements.
I know.
Aren't they too much?
If they have money to spend on Janghaenggo,
they should just pay the pension.
They're not going to
make any exceptions.
What do we do?
What else? We need to fight and win.
Here. Cheers!
When Jang-go comes.
Come on. We'll do it again
when Jang-go comes.
Here.
I'm not a bad guy. I'm Jang-go's friend.
I want to read your palm for you.
I'm a pro at reading palms.
Wow!
What are you doing?
Forget it.
Your way of speaking is a bit...
You're not from around here, are you?
Are you from China?
No. I came from Pyeongyang.
No wonder!
Now I understand
why Jang-go friend-zoned you!
Jang-go is very old-fashioned!
Why does it matter where you came from?
But it's true when they say
handsome men are from the south and
beautiful girls are from the north.
You're a natural, aren't you?
Gosh, I don't care if you're
from the south or north.
Miss...
what do you think about me?
Why do you talk that way?
I have a name, too. It's Kim Mi-poong.
Okay! Mi-poong!
Since I asked you a question,
you should answer me.
Mi-poong, go on a date with me.
We'd be good together!
What are you doing?
"What are you doing?"
Why are you doing this to me?
"Why are you doing this to me?"
Wait. That's the Gyeongsang dialect.
Why are you being like this, miss?
I mean, Mi-poong. Can't you date me?
Not as friends or anything!
Why are you doing this?
Gosh. I heard North Korean
women love South Korean men.
You're really playing hard-to-get.
Have a glass of wine.
Just one glass.
Hey Bang Sung-sil!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hold on!
Lee Jang-go, are you crazy?
What are you doing?
What did I do?
You said you weren't dating her.
So why are you getting so angry?
What? You don't want to
date a North Korean girl, but
- you don't want to give her to anyone else?
- What?
Blood.
In a pig's eye. You better not act
like you know me again.
Trashy scumbag.
God!
Mi-poong.
Let's go.
I'm sorry, Mi-poong.
It's fine.
It's not like this is the first time
this happened to me.
I don't mind such low people.
It's his fault for being
disrespectful, not mine.
Keep being strong like this,
and never be discouraged.
If something like this happens again,
let me know. I'll...
I'll take care of it.
Don't be friends
with a low guy like him.
He's just an alumnus, not a friend.
It's late. Let's go home.
Okay.
No wonder!
Now I understand
why Jang-go friend-zoned you!
Jang-go is very old-fashioned!
Why does it matter where you came from?
Now I'll work and succeed for sure.
I'll make sure no one
can disrespect me again.
What did she say?
I'm a crazy witch
who's trying to sell my son?
How can she tell our friends
about my private loan?
I was begging on my knees for
my life in front of the loan sharks?
If I ever talk to you again,
I'll change my last name!
Watch if I ever talk
to that witch again.
You don't avoid poop
because you're scared of it!
Awful wench.
Cheap wench.
(Zishen Marketing Team.
Zishen Planning Team.)
Hello! I'm Kim Mi-poong!
This is Kim Mi-poong who will
be working with us from now on.
All of you know, right?
That she's the winner
of this logo competition?
Go ahead and say hello.
Hello, I'm Kim Mi-poong.
Please look after me!
- Hi!
- Welcome!
Your desk is right here.
Okay.
- It's nice to meet you.
- Same here.
Oh! That's...
That's the logo you made.
You're right!
How does it feel to see the logo
you made become the company's logo?
I'm so happy, and I can't believe it!
Thank you! I'll work hard!
Hee-ra!
- Hee-ra!
- Jang-soo!
Jang-soo!
Hee-ra, what happened? Do you know how much
I was worried about you and missed you?
Me, too!
My mom took my cell-phone away,
and I was trapped in my room!
But how did you get out?
And whose phone did you use?
I ran out while
my grandmother was asleep.
And I called you with
a middle school student's phone.
My mom took my card and wallet.
It's okay.
You have me.
My mom wants me to go on a blind date
she chooses and get married to him.
Hee-ra, can you leave me and
get married to another man?
No, I can never do that.
I can't live a day
without you now, Jang-soo.
Then let's go to your house
right now and get permission.
Right now?
You don't want to?
No! Let's go!
But where's your house?
Hannam-dong.
Which way is it?
- That way.
- That way?
- Let's go.
- Okay!
I need to get my bag first.
Chung-ja.
Let's eat spicy noodles.
Shall we? What is Hee-ra up to?
Why is she so quiet?
She was sleeping.
She's taking a long nap.
That brat.
Mom, it's me. Open the door.
Who is this?
It's me! Your daughter, Jo Hee-ra.
Mom, what happened?
She should be upstairs in her room,
so why is she outside?
I don't know!
I was watching her upstairs,
and you were
monitoring downstairs,
so how can she be out there?
Oh my goodness!
Oh, my! Hee-ra!
Hee-ra, when did you go out?
Mom, hold on.
That's not important right now.
Jo Hee-ra.
Who is this man? Who is he?
Hee-ra, is this your boyfriend?
Yes, grandma.
Say hello, Jang-soo.
This is my grandma and my mom.
Hello, grandmother and mother!
I'm Lee Jang-soo!
Lee Jang-soo?
Oh my goodness.
Who is this?
Are you Lee Jang-go's
younger brother Lee Jang-soo?
Is your mom Hwang Geum-sil?
Yes, my mom's name is Hwang Geum-sil.
Do you know her?
You're the lady who came
to my house last time!
Hey, do you know him?
Oh my goodness. Hee-ra.
It's not him, right?
This isn't your boyfriend, right?
Please say it isn't so. He's not, right?
No, mom. This is him.
This is the man I love.
Jo Hee-ra.
Jo Hee-ra!
(Blow Breeze)
Flowers that would suit
a kind, innocent woman.
- Here.
- Oh, my.
You thief!
Are we fated to become in-laws?
Kim Mi-poong.
It's so nice to see you, Jang-go!
Mi-poong!
She's my friend's younger sister.
Subtitles by OnDemandKorea