Subtitles by bioskopkeren
(Episode 12)
Hee-ra, when did you go out?
Mom, hold on.
That's not important right now.
Jo Hee-ra.
Who is this man? Who is he?
Is this your boyfriend?
Yes, grandma.
Say hello, Jang-soo.
This is my grandma, and this is my mom.
Hello, grandmother and mother!
I'm Lee Jang-soo!
Lee Jang-soo?
Who is this?
Are you Lee Jang-go's
younger brother Lee Jang-soo?
Is your mom Hwang Geum-sil?
Yes, my mom's name is Hwang Geum-sil.
Do you know her?
You're the lady who came
to my house last time!
Hey, do you know him?
Oh my goodness. Hee-ra.
It's not him, right?
He's not your boyfriend, right?
Please say I'm right. He's not, right?
No, mom. This is him.
This is the man I love.
Jo Hee-ra.
Jo Hee-ra!
- This can't be true!
- Mother!
Please don't do this, mother!
Please hit me instead!
You shouldn't hit my delicate Hee-ra.
Fine.
Fine!
You should get it.
Mom!
Why are you hitting him?
Why are you hitting him
when he did nothing wrong?
What did you say? You little brats!
Chung-ja! Chung-ja,
get a hold of yourself!
Calm down!
You...
Your mom knows about this, doesn't she?
You and your mom set this up, right?
You guys set this up, right?
Pardon?
Do you have something to tell me?
Are you going to
leave Jang-soo like that?
Then what else can I do?
He never listens to me.
That's true, but we need to know
what kind of woman he's dating.
This is a world where women
are scarier than men.
That's true, Geum-sil.
Ask him to let you meet her once.
We would feel safe if we knew
what kind of woman he is dating.
What's the point? It's obvious.
She drank with a man and stayed out overnight.
Would she be a proper lady?
That's why I'm saying this! I'm worried!
If she really is an awful woman,
then we can't let those two continue to meet!
If a man meets the wrong woman,
it'll be a matter of time
before he kicks the bucket.
Hey, Hwang Geum-sil! Come out!
What's that noise?
- Isn't that your 100 million dollar friend?
- Hwang Geum-sil!
- You con-artist!
- I think so. Why is she here again?
- Come out right now!
- She must be mad!
How dare she throws
a fit in our neighborhood!
Con-artist?
- I should just...
- Mom! Grandma!
What's this?
Isn't this Jang-soo's voice?
Mom, that is Jang-soo's voice.
- Oh my goodness.
- Come out!
You thieves!
Hwang Geum-sil! I said come out!
Jang-soo!
Mom! Grandma! Aunt!
Be quiet!
Ma Chung-ja!
What do you think you're doing?
What are you doing
to my precious grandson?
- Jang-soo!
- My goodness!
What's wrong with you?
What are you doing to my son?
How can you do this to me?
Were you that greedy for
your son to be my son-in-law?
You sent your oldest first,
and now it's your youngest?
It doesn't matter if you wanted
my inheritance or my daughter Hee-ra!
How can you cook up
such a devious plan with
your bum of a son
and do something like that?
What on earth are you talking about?
Jang-soo, what happened?
What on earth did you do to my friend
that made her treat you this way?
I didn't do anything wrong
but fall in love with Hee-ra.
- Oh my gosh!
- What? Hee-ra?
What are you-
Jang-soo, are you dating
this woman's daughter?
Hee-ra?
Yes.
- Oh my gosh.
- How can this happen?
This doesn't make sense!
You frightening wench.
You devious wench.
You set up this whole thing with your son.
Are you acting right now?
Hold on a minute.
Last time you wore
tiger print boxers and spent
the night with a woman
who happens to be...
her daughter?
Oh my goodness!
You wore tiger print boxers
and did what with my daughter?
How can you do this
to my daughter? How?
- Mother!
- Chung-ja!
Take her inside!
Oh my goodness!
Does she have a fainting disease?
How come she
always faints when she
comes to our house?
What on earth is going on?
But that woman looks like Mr. Jo's wife.
Mom, do it one more time.
Okay.
Oh, no. Chung-ja.
Oh my goodness. She woke up.
Chung-ja, are you all right?
Are you okay?
Geum-sil.
Geum-sil, how can you do this to me?
How?
What kind of ill-fated relationship do we have?
Chung-ja, it's a misunderstanding.
I really didn't know my son and your daughter
were in that kind of relationship.
"That kind of relationship?"
What do you mean by that?
What kind of relationship is that?
What do I do about my Hee-ra?
- What do I do?
- Excuse me.
It's not like Jang-soo forced
your daughter to like him.
Nobody died! Why do you keep crying?
Other people would think Jang-soo
did something horrible to your daughter.
What?
What do you mean by that?
What I mean is that
I really didn't know
that my son and your daughter
are dating each other.
How could you say
I set up this up with my son?
Your daughter already went
on a blind date with Jang-go.
She really did?
- With Jang-go?
- Yes!
Jang-soo, did you know Hee-ra was
my friend's daughter and dated her?
You really didn't know?
I didn't! I really didn't!
I swear to God!
You heard that, didn't you?
My son didn't know either.
Chung-ja, this happened
coincidentally like fate.
But how can this happen?
Maybe you and I are fated
to become in-laws.
What?
"Fated to become in-laws?"
You and me?
In your dreams.
You!
I dare you to meet my daughter again!
I'll kill you with my bare hands then!
Got it?
Mother! Mother!
- Mother, my foot!
- Why are you hitting him?
He did nothing wrong!
I'm so upset!
Why does it have to be her
out of all people?
It hasn't been long since
you broke up with Ms. Song!
Why are you bringing her up again?
Damn it!
Oh my gosh! My head!
I can't live! I'm going crazy!
Oh my god!
Oh my goodness! This is a hit!
How can this even happen?
Hold on a minute.
I don't think this is
such a bad thing after all.
Isn't this a good thing?
Jang-soo instead of Jang-go!
What do you think?
You may be right.
I raised Hee-ra like
she was made out of gold.
I put so much effort into raising her.
She was the apple of my eye.
What did they say?
My precious daughter! What do I do?
Lady!
Where did you put your head?
Open up the door!
Locking yourself up won't solve anything!
Mister, I'm sorry.
Mister, I'm sorry!
Mister, what do I do?
What do I do, mister?
How can this happen?
So she's the girl who Jang-go
went on a blind date with?
But like you said, it must be fate.
It would be difficult to pull
something like this on purpose.
Geum-sil, don't be
too harsh on Jang-soo.
It seems like he really likes Hee-ra.
I'm just afraid he'll get a bigger heartbreak
if he falls for her even more.
You saw what happened.
Chung-ja didn't even like
Jang-go who is a lawyer.
There's no way she'll accept Jang-soo.
She'll never let them be together.
Geum-sil, did you forget already?
You bought my phoenix dream.
That phoenix dream must have
been meant for Jang-soo.
If my dream is right, your friend will
never be able to handle Hee-ra.
That's right. Did you ever see a parent
overcome a child?
Have you ever overcome yours?
I guess...
So let's just let it flow.
Let Jang-soo deal with it.
Hold on.
I never thought Jang-soo would come upon
such luck! What good fortune is this!
What happens to Hee-ra and me now?
So the pathetic mama's boy
who hurt Hee-ra was Jang-go?
Mi-poong.
Yes?
Please take these
to the planning team.
Okay.
Yes, chief!
I got all the market research
for this season's
launching and the data
for the competitor's trend.
Yes, I'm on my way! Bye!
(Thump Thump Convenience Store)
You just changed
the romance in this, but why
does it feel so drastically
different now?
The chemistry with
the leading lady is great.
It's full of anticipation
and makes you curious.
- Really?
- Yes!
What is it, Mr. Jo?
Did something happen?
Of course not.
There's nothing.
Great! Let's sign the contract!
Really?
- Really?
- Really!
You're no better than a beast!
You're no better than a dog!
I fed, clothed, and raised you!
How can you say such
atrocious things to me?
Let go of me!
No.
There's no reason for me to run away.
What did I do wrong?
They lived well all that time,
so what else does
she want? Besides,
is that money really theirs?
But why isn't Jo Hee-dong
calling me yet?
Should I call him?
No.
If you call a man first, he'll run away.
It's a skill to make him
chase after you.
(My Rope)
Hello, Mr. Jo.
Do you have time today?
Today?
Something good happened to me, thanks to you,
so I wanted to buy you dinner.
Oh! Vichyssoise mousse with
croutons and white caviar?
Wow, I don't know what this is at all.
What would you like to eat?
Should we order wine, too?
Mr. Jo...
I don't think we should eat here.
Why not?
When I searched it up,
I heard the food was good here.
Do you not like it?
That's not it.
This place is too expensive.
Let's go somewhere else. Okay?
Come on, Mr. Jo.
Okay?
Hurry!
This place is better, right?
Yes, but I wanted to
buy you something better.
Oh, my. What's wrong with this place?
The food is great, and even if
we order a variety of things,
it's still less than a bowl
of salad from that restaurant.
You're so luxurious
and sophisticated that I
didn't know you
would like this kind of food.
Really?
I look luxurious and sophisticated?
Yes.
That's surprising! The clothes I wore today
are from Namdaemun and Dongdaemun.
I got this blouse for
fifteen dollars at Namdaemun,
and I got this skirt for
five dollars at Dongdaemun.
They don't look like that at all.
There's no use
wearing expensive clothes.
I think fashion has to do
with sense and philosophy.
It feels great to be outside
at night under bright lights.
What do you mean?
Don't you have lights at home?
No. My light bulb went out, but even if I go
on a chair, I'm not tall enough, and
it's hard taking off the case and putting it
back on, so I just live in the darkness.
Really?
That's not hard at all.
If it's okay with you,
can I do it for you?
Really?
We can go after we eat this.
It's too late tonight.
Can you come tomorrow
in the daytime and do it?
It's delicious.
Yes, eat a lot.
- Cheers!
Mi-poong, the first day
was hectic, right?
No, it was fine.
Oh, you must have
been able to handle it.
Now you're going to
have to run until you get
blisters on your feet.
You've been warned!
Come on. Aren't you
frightening her too much?
What are you going to do if she quits?
Is that true? Was I being too harsh?
- Just a bit.
- Go easy on her!
Okay!
No, I'm determined.
I'm going to work hard and
learn fast so that our marketing
team can become the
best team of Winner's Group!
I think we picked
the right new employee.
Good! Work with that
kind of confidence, okay?
We sincerely welcome you
to our marketing team.
- Me, too.
- Me, three!
Thank you so much for
welcoming me like this!
I will do my best
with actions and not words!
- You're good at talking, Mi-poong.
Should we drink one more time to that?
- Yes!
To our new employee Mi-poong and
to our marketing team! Cheers!
Cheers!
But Mi-poong, you have a dialect.
Where are you from? Gangwon-do?
No.
I'm from Pyeongyang.
Pyeongyang?
As in the Pyeongyang in North Korea?
Then you're from North Korea?
Yes, I'm from North Korea.
Eat. Let's eat. Eat up.
I sent a certification of contents
to the mart, but I don't think
we'll be able to arrive at
a conclusion with the settlement.
It seems like they're working
with Janghaenggo.
I think they're preparing a lawsuit.
Are you talking about
that enormous law firm that falls
within the first ten law firms
within the nation?
Yes, you're right.
I knew that would happen.
Those scumbags.
What will you do?
We're going to go through
with the lawsuit.
Even if we lose,
we're going to go until the end.
Hey, Ms. Kim Mi-poong.
Are you coming now? You're late.
How was your first day of work?
Was the work hard or was
anyone giving you a hard time?
You're too late.
Did they make you work until so late?
Why are you so curious?
You need to ask me one question
at a time in order.
How am I suppose to answer you
if you ask them all at once?
Then you can answer them
in order one by one.
Do you know how much I was worried
about your first day of work?
Why? Was someone giving you
a hard time? Or was the work too hard?
No.
I didn't have a hard time at all.
My chief and co-workers are all great,
and the work was manageable.
And I wasn't working all this time.
I was having dinner with my co-workers.
- Really?
- Yes, really.
Don't worry about this "little sister."
Worry about yourself.
Aww. I'm so proud of my little tadpole.
You're amazing!
Do you think I'm a kid? You always call me
"tadpole." I'm too old to be a tadpole!
Well, I just thought you were amazing.
And does it make you so mad
that I call you tadpole?
But you look like a tadpole.
You're getting mad just because I called you
a tadpole for looking like a tadpole.
Shut that mouth of yours before I rip you
into shreds and make you into soup, you fish boy!
What will you do
if I don't shut my mouth?
How will you make me into soup?
Explain to me.
Will you put bean sprouts
or kimchi in there?
Tell me how you'll make me into soup.
If you keep making me mad,
I'll change the order of your ribs!
What?
You'll change the order of my ribs? Huh?
Does that mean
you're going to break my ribs?
Yes!
Hey!
She's becoming more and more cruel.
Hey, Kim Mi-poong!
Kim Mi-poong, come back here!
One, two, three! You're dead! Come here!
Mi-poong, what are you doing?
Hurry up and eat this.
The grapes are very sweet and good.
Is Yoo-sung sleeping?
Yes.
He went to the museum today,
so he must have
been tired because
he fell asleep while eating.
While eating?
How was your first day of work?
It's just the beginning, so I'll have
to work hard and become acknowledged.
If you sincerely work hard,
they'll acknowledge you.
Even if someone disrespects you because
you're from the north, hold it in.
Don't worry about such a thing.
I'll work hard and become more competent
so that no one will be able to disrespect me.
That's right.
It's good, right? Mi-poong, do you know
what happened at the owner's house today?
What happened?
I saw something very amusing today.
What did you see?
The second son of the owner,
so Mr. Lee's younger brother,
must have gone to the motel
with his girlfriend.
But then he wore tiger print
boxers to go see her.
Tiger print boxers?
Why would he wear those?
You don't need to know why.
Anyways, because he wore tiger print
boxers and took
her to the motel, her mother came
and caused a scene.
She made a big fuss that she would never
allow them to be together and even fainted.
All of the owner's family came out
to the yard. What a fight that was.
Really?
Yes. It's the first time I saw something
so amusing after coming to Seoul.
If you were here,
we would have watched it together.
They're right when they say that watching
a fight is the most entertaining.
My goodness. It was fun to watch.
Come on, mom.
But Mi-poong, I think the
girlfriend's mom is Mr. Jo's wife.
Really?
You didn't see wrong?
Maybe.
I mean, tiger print boxers?
How humiliating.
Aunt, are you serious?
Yes.
Hee-ra's mom came and made a scene.
She cried and fainted. It was chaotic.
But it hasn't been long since he broke up
with that beauty parlor lady.
I know.
We were shocked into silence at first.
Your mom was shocked, too.
Nothing happened between you and Hee-ra,
but still, how could
Jang-soo be dating the girl that
your mom tried to set you up with?
(Princess Baby)
This phone is currently off,
so please leave a message after the tone.
I'm going nuts!
Hee-ra isn't getting
in trouble again, is she?
They shouldn't hit her delicate body!
Gosh! I'm going crazy!
Lee Jang-soo, we need to talk.
No. Don't say anything.
You don't deserve to say a word.
If you say something,
I'll just freaking-
"Freaking?" Freaking what?
What are you going to do?
Are you joking?
You turned the whole house upside down.
What I wanted to say was that
I don't want you to say anything to
me, worry about me, or criticize me
I just want you to trust me.
Don't bring up the past.
I know Hee-ra had gone
on a blind date with you.
Fine.
I did go on a couple dates
with Hee-ra, and I
know for a fact that
she doesn't suit our family.
She's not someone you can handle!
Why doesn't she suit our family?
Why can't I handle her?
And I'll be the one
who will handle her or not,
so don't talk about
my woman like that. Got it?
"My woman?"
Hee-ra.
Get up.
Get up and listen to me.
I know exactly how you feel.
When I was your age,
I experienced passionate love, too.
The only thing I could see was him.
I thought I would die if I didn't have him.
But if you're not meant to be,
time will make him disappear like bubbles.
It'll be nothing!
Don't lie.
Dad was your first love.
You loved dad, so you seduced him
and got pregnant with
Hee-dong and me. That's why
you two were forced to get married
Grandma told me everything.
Goodness! Why would mom
tell her such a thing?
You got to marry the person you love,
so why are you doing this to me?
I like Jang-soo!
What I'm saying is that...
you and that bum
Jang-soo aren't meant to be!
You need to date someone at your level
in order to be fated together!
So, Hee-ra, go to New York for no less
and no more than a month.
I'll get you a first class ticket
to New York.
You have many friends in New York.
Go hang out with
your friends and shop, too.
How about it?
And think very carefully about this!
What did his mom do to you?
She coaxed you to meet Jang-go!
You fell for that woman and her son's
trap because you're so innocent!
Because they want
your grandfather's inheritance!
No! Jang-soo isn't like that!
And I became Jang-soo's woman,
so I'll never fall for any of your tricks!
Whose woman did you become?
What does that mean?
Rather than becoming his woman,
you should just die!
- Die!
- That hurts!
Goodness!
Where's my passport?
Passport?
Are you going somewhere?
Yes. I'm going to China tomorrow.
China?
For what reason?
Elder is sending me on a business trip.
Here's your passport.
Okay.
What's wrong with your face?
Why? What about my face?
You're pale as
if you're going to faint soon.
Is something wrong?
Huh?
No, nothing is wrong.
Even if I go somewhere local,
you want presents,
and yet I'm leaving the country,
but you're not begging for presents.
All night long you've
been going upstairs. What is it?
Hee-ra didn't even eat dinner-
Did something happen to her?
Of course not. There's nothing
that would happen to Hee-ra.
Hee-ra was teaching me yoga to lose weight,
so I'm a bit dizzy from doing that.
Goodness. You can get hurt if you don't do
yoga properly. You should be careful.
Okay.
Hold on.
Do I need to take slippers, too?
Oh my goodness. That was close.
But why is Elder sending him
all the way to China?
Is he going to invest
into real estate in China?
Whatever. My head hurts.
I need to solve this matter with Hee-ra
before he comes back. What do I do?
Goodness! What can I do about her?
Oh my gosh.
I'll prepare lunch tomorrow,
so don't eat before you come.
About the broker you're going
to meet in China this time...
I wish I can go with you to meet him.
What can we do about it when
he refuses because it's dangerous?
It seems like things
got more intense nowadays.
There were many people
who were shot to death after
getting caught helping
North Koreans escape.
Still...
You're not feeling well these days.
I'll make sure to meet him and talk to him well.
All right.
I guess it isn't easy for
the broker to go into North
Korea disguised as a businessman
and try to find people.
Of course not.
The situation is pretty terrible,
but he decided to take on this
task because you promised to give him
more than the usual amount.
All right then.
Things can't go wrong
before they even start.
When you meet him yourself,
do whatever he wants.
All right. Don't worry, Elder.
Okay.
Dal-ho,
I'm so glad I could rely on you.
Thank you.
Father.
Have some hot jujube tea.
It's a bit chilly nowadays,
so I made some.
All right. Thank you.
You should drink some, too.
Okay.
But father, why is
Dal-ho going to China?
I'll get going now.
You still have some time
before your flight schedule.
Dal-ho, it's going to be a long trip.
So be especially careful
and come back safely.
Yes, Elder. Don't worry.
He'll find her.
He'll find her for sure.
Hello, Mr. Yoon!
Good morning!
- Did you go home safely last night?
- Yes, I did, but I must
have drank so much beer because
I kept going to the bathroom!
Same for me.
Beer is great, but that's the problem.
Yes, you're right!
Mi-kyung, did you hear
that the new employee in
the third marketing team
is from North Korea?
North Korea?
Then she's a defector?
Yes.
- What does she look like?
- She probably looks like us.
But isn't it a little bit weird?
Hello! I'm the new employee
Kim Mi-poong in the
third marketing team
who is from North Korea.
Oh, hello...
If you're curious about
anything about North Korea
or Pyeongyang,
go ahead and ask me anytime.
I look forward to working with you!
Wow. She's something else, huh?
That's how she was able to win all
those competitors and enter our company.
Hello!
Hello! I'm Kim Mi-poong!
I look forward to working with you!
(Kim Mi-poong)
Are you really going to take this case?
Yes. It's already been decided.
Why are you asking me again?
Janghaenggo is one of the
biggest law firms in the country.
A small office like us can't take it on.
It's obvious
they're going to destroy us.
Must you really do this?
We haven't settled down yet. If we lose
the case, it'll be more difficult for us.
Why do you think we'll lose?
There's a possibility
that we can win this case.
And if I work hard and overcome Janghaenggo,
it'll help us settle down faster.
All the other lawyers
gave up on this case, so why
are you trying to play
a game that we'll lose?
That's why I want to do it even more.
I can't ignore their situations.
You saw the file, so you should know
how hard they worked for the past two
years to become permanent workers
only to have their contracts broken.
Now they have nothing left.
I became a lawyer so that I can be
of strength on the side of the weak.
I want to do my best to help them.
I'm just worried about you having
to go against Janghaenggo.
Think how you would feel if lawyers
turned away from you in this situation.
It would be very difficult.
And this is one case I can fight.
I'm preparing hard for this,
and I gathered witnesses, too.
So don't worry too much.
I'm going out.
Goodness! Who can stop him
and his stubbornness?
Mom, how can I pay Geum-sil back?
Oh my gosh! I'm so upset!
Come on. Would she have really
set this up with her son?
Even if they had, it's Hee-ra's fault
for being stupid enough to fall for it.
Exactly! Who does she take
after that she's so stupid like this?
She rejected all those
great, wealthy guys!
Oh my goodness! I'm so upset that even if
I die I won't be able to rest in peace!
Who does she take after?
Of course she takes after you and me.
She was so blinded by love
that she didn't even
know that was fire and
was drawn to it like a moth.
Isn't it romantic?
Mom!
You better not tell Hee-ra:
"Your body will turn to dust anyways once
you die, so don't worry and become a moth."
Am I crazy? Why would I
say such a thing to her?
Hey, but why did Elder
send Dal-ho to China?
I don't know. I don't even want to know.
I went into father's room
with jujube tea this morning,
and they stopped whispering
to each other about something.
Dal-ho didn't even look at me
when he was leaving,
but he said good-bye
to Elder so affectionately that
it felt like they
were a separating couple!
I was so bewildered.
What kind of secret business
are they up to?
Like you said, Dal-ho is treating me
like I'm an empty shell!
Why would Elder make an investment into
China when there's nobody there to manage it?
If he has leftover money,
he should just buy a building in
Gangnam or land in Jeju.
Why would he go all the way there?
That's what I'm saying.
This is like prison.
Goodness. I feel so stuffy and sore.
Chung-ja, I can't stay
like this anymore.
I need to go get some fresh air.
Then what about me? What about Hee-ra?
You want me to
watch Hee-ra all by myself?
It's not my problem.
She's your daughter,
so you take care of her.
She has legs.
You can't watch her forever.
It's not my problem.
It's good, right? Eat a lot.
Okay.
Mr. Kim, this is meat broth
that was just made.
Have a seat.
Okay.
So how do you like working here?
I like it.
Everyone is so good to me like I'm part of
the family, so I'm not tired at all.
And when I get to talk
to elders from our home country,
I feel like I'm back in Pyeongyang.
That's why I really like working here.
Really? I see.
We can speak in our home dialect as much as
we want, which is why I come here often.
If I don't hear it for
a day, I get pretty sad.
I see. I think you would, too.
But which part of
North Korea did you live in?
I lived in Chung-guyok,
Changgwang Street.
Oh, Chung-guyok,
Changgwang Street?
I know that's a place
where wealthy families live in.
It didn't seem like you
had lived a difficult life.
I guess I was right.
Are your parents
still alive in North Korea?
I had a mother-in-law,
but she passed away a long time ago.
As for my son and husband...
while we were escaping...
Oh, dear.
I already heard what had happened
to your son and husband.
I was shameless to
bring up your family again.
Since I'm growing old,
I start talking a lot
once the topic of
our home country comes up.
No, it's fine.
It's gotten a lot better now.
Yes.
If you have a firm heart and work hard,
you will have a good future.
Yes.
It's fine. Feel free to answer it.
Hi, it's me.
Mom, I finished work near the noodle restaurant.
Should I go home with you?
Okay, sure. Come here then.
Okay, okay. I'm on the second floor
of Deokcheonok.
Don't get lost.
Bye.
You!
Why are you coming down?
Where are you going?
I'm going to the kitchen to drink water.
All right. I got it, so don't
you dare take one more step.
You better not come down!
Maid! Get Hee-ra some water!
Fill up a bottle up to
the very brim with water!
Forget it! I'm not drinking water!
I won't drink water or eat food!
I'll starve to death, so do whatever you want!
If I die, you can do
whatever you want with me!
Go ahead and sell me to a
congressman's son or a dermatologist!
That little brat.
What am I supposed to do with her?
Hee-ra, how do I look in this outfit?
Why bother asking? It must be difficult
to be such a fashion terrorist.
Really? Is it that bad?
Gosh, what do I do?
Today is an important day.
What do you mean what do you do?
Of course you
have to change into
something more fashionable.
Should I wear a trench coat?
How can you wear
a trench coat in this weather?
Hee-dong, do you remember
the brand-name cardigan
that mom bought for dad
last year for his birthday?
Dad's cardigan? Yes! The blue one?
That's right.
Ask mom to find that one for you.
If you wear that, you'll look very fashionable.
Okay.
Thank you.
You're pretty useful sometimes.
Hey! What do you mean "sometimes?"
Mom.
Oh, hi.
You know the blue cardigan you
bought for dad last year?
Can I borrow that today?
Of course you can!
But why are you trying to be
so stylish out of the blue?
There's something important going on.
It's been a while since you've gone out,
so I'll definitely find it for you.
Okay, thank you.
Jang-soo!
Hee-ra!
Don't cry.
If you cry, I'll cry, too!
Jang-soo, I thought I would
never be able to see you again!
If you hadn't contacted me today,
I would've confidently marched into
your home and saved you.
Of course we'll be
able to see each other!
Really?
Yes, really.
It doesn't matter if
they refuse to let me in
or spray salt on me.
I can handle all of that.
I'm not scared of anything
as long as I can see you.
Me, too.
Jang-soo, from now on, I don't think
I can live a day without you.
No!
I won't be able to live!
Hee-ra!
Yes, Jang-soo!
Then let's never be apart now.
From this moment on,
we'll be together forever!
Yes! Together forever!
Please do my hair and make-up lightly
so that I can look innocent.
As innocent as possible.
Yes, miss.
Hello.
Do you need something?
I need a gift.
What kind of flowers do women like?
Who are they for? What's her age?
She's in her late twenties.
I would like flowers for
a kind person with a pure heart.
Come in.
Excuse me.
Here.
Oh, my.
Thank you. You didn't
have to bring anything.
But...
is it this one?
Yes.
I need a chair.
I do have a chair,
but it's a revolving one.
It's fine.
Be careful.
Thank you.
Are you done?
Can you turn on the lights?
Sure.
Wow! The light came on!
Thank you!
- The case.
- Oh, yes.
I think it's done.
Thank you.
Oh my gosh!
Oh, my.
I'm sorry. I should have gotten
a better grip on the chair.
It's fine.
Thank you so much! It's so bright now! Wow!
Having a light makes people a lot happier.
It's nothing.
It wasn't anything difficult.
If you need help with something
like this again, let me know.
I will.
Oh, please take a seat.
I'll quickly prepare lunch for you.
- Okay.
Jang-go!
Jang Ha-yeon.
It's so good to see you, Jang-go!
Hey!
What are you doing?
I'm saying hello.
You're still tacky as ever.
How have you been, Jang-go?
Sometimes, I missed you a lot.
Didn't you miss me?
I was surprised.
Oh, Mi-poong!
Jang-go.
Who...?
She's my friend's younger sister.
Oh, your friend's younger sister?
It's nice to meet you.
Hello.
What are you doing here?
Did you come to see me?
No. I'm here for the noodle restaurant.
Jang-go, I'm a bit busy.
There's something I need to tell you.
Oh, really?
Let's go in and talk.
Bye.
Let's go inside.
I was surprised.
But why is she so quiet?
Hee-ra.
What happened?
I was monitoring from downstairs!
When I was finding
the cardigan for Hee-dong!
What do I do? Oh, if I catch her,
I'll shave her head bald!
Oh, dear! What's wrong?
Mom, did you see Hee-ra running away?
Hee-ra ran away?
I won't let this slide!
Chung-ja, wait for me! Hey!
So is Jang-soo still in bed?
He went out.
What? When?
I don't know. I just checked,
and he's not in there.
He said he can't get in touch with Hee-ra
because she got her phone taken away.
Maybe he went to meet her.
Jo Hee-ra! Hee-ra!
Hee-ra!
What's this noise?
- Jo Hee-ra!
- Oh my goodness!
- Hee-ra!
- Oh my gosh! How dare you come in here!
- Where is Hee-ra!
- How dare you throw a scene in here! Hey!
Nam-yi! Call the police and report that
a crazy wench barged into
our home with her shoes on!
Fine! Go ahead and report me!
I'll report that my daughter was kidnapped!
- Hee-ra!
- Ma Chung-ja! What's wrong with you?
You don't think I know
that you planned the whole
thing out with your son
to steal my daughter?
Why are you searching for
your daughter in my house?
Hee-ra!
Chung-ja! Chung-ja!
- Mom!
- Is it here?
- Yes.
- Is Hee-ra here?
- What?
- My goodness.
Look at this pathetic,
little house. Goodness!
My goodness!
Jang-soo?
Where are you right now?
Are you with Hee-ra right now?
Yes, mom. I'm with Hee-ra right now.
What? You're with Hee-ra?
Where are you? Where is Hee-ra?
Mother, I'll give the phone to Hee-ra.
I don't want to.
Hi, mom.
Hee-ra, where are you?
I'll come pick you up.
I'm going to be with Jang-soo.
Don't look for me.
Hee-ra! Hee-ra!
Chung-ja! Oh, my!
Get a hold of yourself! What do I do?
Tell that Dog Jang-soo
or Cow Jang-soo or whatever his
name is to bring Hee-ra
back at once! That thief!
Dog? Cow? Thief?
Are you talking about my grandson?
Yes! He's the thief!
You're all a bunch of thieves!
Oh, so Jang-soo is a thief?
Then your granddaughter
is a thief, too! A thief!
Mom!
That crazy woman! I should just-
I promise to never let go of
this hand that I'm holding.
Can you promise me, too, Hee-ra?
Yes.
I promise.
I will never let go.
That was very delicious.
Should we sit for a moment?
Sure.
Thank you for today.
No, I should be thankful.
All I did was change a light bulb,
but I got to eat your delicious cooking.
No.
I was very grateful
that you ate with me today.
To be honest, today is my birthday.
Pardon?
Birthday?
After both my parents passed away in
a car accident when I was in high school,
I spent my birthdays alone.
But when we were
eating seaweed soup together,
I felt so strange.
I felt so warm...
I'm sorry. What's wrong with me?
Kiss me. Kiss!
Don't just look at me. Kiss me.
(Blow Breeze)
I came to see you, of course.
You're Lee Jang-go's friend's
younger sister.
Hello.
I knew you would do this.
That phoenix is worth
at least 50 million dollars.
I'm going to marry Jang-soo.
I wish I can see you at least one time.
Sir, are you all right?
Subtitles by bioskopkeren