Subtitles by OnDemandKorea
(The staff sincerely wishes injured actress
Oh Ji-Eun will recover soon. Starting from today,
actress Lim Soo-hyang will play Shin-ae's role.)
- (Leading lady?)
- Episode 13
What do you mean a "100-million-
dollar grandson?" Are you talking
about that man eating ramen in
front of the convenience store?
Hello?
Is this webtoon artist Mr. Jo Hee-dong?
Yes, I'm Jo Hee-dong.
Are you...?
I would like to experience that
model work you offered me last time.
Is the offer still on the table?
Yes!
I'll prepare tomorrow's lunch.
Don't eat before you come.
Thank you for today.
I should be the thankful one.
All I did was change a light bulb,
but I got to eat your delicious cooking.
No.
I was very grateful that
you ate with me today.
To be honest,
today is my birthday.
Pardon? Your birthday?
Ever since both my parents passed away
in a car accident when I was in high school,
I spent my birthdays alone.
But when we were eating
seaweed soup together,
I felt so strange.
I felt so warm.
What's wrong with me? I'm so sorry.
Kiss me.
Why are you just looking at me? Kiss me.
I was happy to be with you, too. Really.
And I didn't just hug you now
because of momentary feelings.
So what I'm trying to say is...
that ever since I first saw you...
My goodness.
What a fool. Is he really a man?
I set up everything for him!
All he had to do was finish it up!
I liked you ever since I first saw you!
Shin-ae,
"Happy birthday-"
"-to you!"
He must have gone mad.
So this is his house, huh?
Fine. I'll make sure
to go into this house.
So you're saying that you won't
be able to accept our conditions?
What my clients want are the promised
reinstatement and proper compensation.
But how can you even
think of ending this whole
thing with just a small amount of money?
I knew you would do this.
Aren't you the one who doesn't want to
settle this matter more than your clients?
If you promise their reinstatement,
then we can settle with compensation.
Then we have nothing
to say on our end either.
Jang-go, you're going to regret
not doing the settlement today.
We'll have to wait and
see about that. See you in court.
Mi-poong.
Huh?
What is it, mom?
What are you thinking about?
You could get hurt if
you space out on the streets.
Did something happen at work?
No, nothing happened.
All right. Yoo-sung is waiting for us.
Let's hurry up and go.
Let's make hot tofu stew for dinner.
Tofu stew? Sounds good!
With a lot of dried red pepper powder in it!
It'll be delicious!
Hello?
You found Hee-ra?
Where is she right now?
Okay, all right.
Mom!
I think I ate too much.
I'm so full. Jang-soo,
what if my stomach comes out?
Come on. That's fine.
Goodness. How cute will my baby
be with her stomach popping out?
Just thinking about it is so adorable.
Oh, my. What's wrong with you, Jang-soo?
Who looks cute with
their stomach popping out?
You.
Oh my gosh! I don't know!
Hold on.
Here you go.
There's not enough money in here.
That can't be true.
It's fine, Jang-soo. I'll pay.
I can pay with my card.
This card has been suspended.
My card has been suspended?
Yes.
That can't be true.
Then I'll pay with cash.
I have $15.
I have $7.
I have some coins, too.
Is that the correct amount?
Yes.
- I'm sorry.
Let's go.
Thank you.
Chung-ja, this is
the correct place, right?
He said it was this restaurant.
Jang-soo, what do we do now?
Our cards don't work
and we don't have money either!
I'm so embarrassed!
Chung-ja! It's Hee-ra!
Hee-ra!
- Run, Jang-soo!
- Why?
Run away!
Get them!
Run!
I got you!
Grandma!
- Hee-ra.
- Don't move! You guys are surrounded now!
You guys are rats in a trap now!
- Run!
- Hee-ra!
- Rats in a trap!
Hee-ra, come here!
Mom!
- Mom!
- No!
Mom! Mom!
Yes! I got him!
Mother, I'm sorry!
Mom, I'm sorry!
- Hey!
- Hey, you brats!
Stop right there!
Hey! Stop!
My goodness.
What are we doing? It's not like we're
working out in the moonlight.
I lost Hee-ra because of you!
Why did you have to scream?
I'll get her.
I'm going to shave her head bald and
trap her in the deepest part of the mountain!
You don't think that I know
that you set this whole
thing up with your son
to steal my daughter?
What?
"Cow Jang-soo. Dog Jang-soo. Thief?"
The things she says!
Mother, why aren't you sleeping?
The more I think about this,
the angrier I get.
I couldn't just lie down and sleep.
I mean, how great are they to
be able to disrespect us like this?
Aren't they the thieves
for trying to steal
their father's distant
cousin's inheritance?
But how dare they call us the thieves?
It's all ridiculous talk,
so don't hold it in your heart.
We don't need such a woman, whose parents
treat him worse than a dog, for Jang-soo.
Make sure you tell them that
we don't want to be linked
with them even if
they're millionaires or billionaires.
Got it?
Yes, I got it.
Is it Jang-soo?
Yes.
Mom, I'm doing well with Hee-ra.
So don't worry.
Tell grandma not to worry, too.
Please be on our side, mom.
Out of all the girls in the world,
why did he have to fall for that one?
What do we do about Jang-soo?
Hey, Kim Mi-poong.
Did you just get off work?
Why are you coming home so late?
What about you? How dare a woman
like you roam around so late at night?
You're lecturing again.
I wasn't roaming around. I came to buy
milk for Yoo-sung to drink in the morning.
But were you working until now?
Yes.
I have an important trial tomorrow.
Lately I've been
so busy preparing for that.
But earlier...
Earlier?
Never mind.
What is it?
Why did you stop talking about it?
It's nothing.
What is it?
You're making me really curious.
Tell me.
It's not anything important.
About your female friend from earlier...
What kind of friend is she?
My female friend?
Oh, Ha-yeon?
That's not such a hard question.
Why hesitate to ask me that?
She's my college friend.
She's also the lawyer who'll be
fighting against me tomorrow.
Then you're going against your friend?
What kind of joke of a fate is that?
I know.
It just happened.
Oh! Your nose is bleeding!
What do we do?
Don't. You'll ruin your shirt.
It's fine. I can just wash it.
Oh, that's right.
Here.
Thanks.
I'm fine. I'm not bleeding much.
How can you work so hard to prepare
for your trial that your nose bleeds?
Is your friend that strong?
Rather than that,
it's because I have to win this trial.
If we lose this trial,
my clients will face a difficult time.
They're giving up
their compensation for this.
You'll do well.
You're usually a silly fool,
but when you work as a lawyer,
you're courageous and amazing.
On top of that, the strong one
doesn't win. It's justice that wins.
If you're on the side of justice,
you'll win for sure.
I guess you do know your stuff.
Of course! What do you take me for?
You look pretty with your hair down.
Well, my face is beautiful,
so whether I put my hair up or down,
I'll look beautiful no matter what.
Forget it.
Jang-go.
Sweet dreams!
Go in.
You're late.
Why are you so late?
I was preparing for my trial tomorrow.
Why aren't you sleeping?
Oh, I was about to.
Did you eat dinner?
Want me to fry rice cakes for you?
I'm fine. I won't be able
to digest if I eat so late.
That's true.
Then wash up and go to bed.
Okay. Good night.
Okay. Oh, and...
Jang-soo said he won't be able to come
tonight because he has acting practice.
Okay. Go to bed.
Good night.
What do I do about Jang-soo?
Chung-ja is against him.
I can't do this or that.
Oh, Ha-yeon? She's my college friend.
She's also the lawyer who'll be
fighting against me tomorrow.
I guess he met his friend
to talk about the trial.
You look pretty with your hair down.
Jang-go has good taste.
Jang-go.
Oh, Mi-poong.
You didn't go to work yet?
I had something to give you.
Something to give to me?
This.
What's this?
Can't you tell? It's a handkerchief.
Why? You think my nose will bleed again?
It's a four-leaf clover.
I thought you would need luck today,
so I spent all night stitching it up.
Do you like it?
It's a lucky handkerchief.
You spent the night stitching it up?
Hey. What's this?
You should have done it properly.
It's all crooked.
I spent all night making that.
If you're going to say something
like that, just give it to me.
I'll wipe Yoo-sung's nose with it.
I like it.
Thank you.
Make sure to win
the trial today. Cheer up!
Cheer up!
Jang-go, what are you doing?
Hurry up and go.
Okay.
Bye.
I'll drive today.
Okay.
I thought you would need luck today,
so I spent all night stitching it up.
We shall start the 2016 summation 21755:
the confirmation of the invalidity
of the dismissal and demand of payment,
in the Seoul Central District Court.
First of all, I would like to
thank you for coming out today.
Please introduce yourself first.
I'm the head of the personnel section
of Bang Bang Mart, Kim Doo-shik.
Witness, what did you say was the
reason that plaintiffs Baek Seung-hwa
and Shin Yong-cheol were unable
to become permanent employees?
Well, that's because they had to leave
before the two-year contract ended.
If they filled up the entire two years,
you'd have to make them permanent employees.
Isn't that why you intentionally
delayed their contract renewal?
I object.
That's the assumption of the
plaintiffs' lawyer. It's a groundless fact.
(Judge)
I acknowledge that.
That is all.
The defense side may
question the witness.
Can you please explain
the exact details of why
they were unable to become
permanent employees?
Yes.
As I said before,
the business went bankrupt
before they were able to fulfill the
two-year dispatch contracts and
was unable to renew their contracts
So in other words, Bang Bang Mart
didn't delay the contract renewal.
The company was just unable to do so
because of the bankruptcy.
Yes, that's right.
That means that Bang Bang Mart
has no responsibilities for their
dismissals or pensions because they
were only temporary dispatch workers.
Yes, we bear no responsibility.
That is all.
Your honor, I request
an additional interrogation.
Witness, who was in charge
of supervising the plaintiffs'
work schedule and allowing them
monthly and annual leaves?
Was it Bang Bang Mart
or the dispatch company?
Well...
we were.
Right?
At Bang Bang Mart, if the employees
are tardy or late, it makes them
write statements of reasons, gave them
a penalty, and docked their pay.
This shows that the ones
who personally managed the
plaintiffs was Bang Bang Mart
and not the dispatch company.
I submit the employees' schedule
of work as evidence.
Is Jang-go doing well?
Last of all, there is
no dispatch business allowed
in big markets.
Did you know that, witness?
Pardon?
If you look at the dispatch laws, it states
that food salesmen, cigarette salesmen,
clothing, shoes,
and accessories salesmen,
furniture salesmen, electronic device
salesmen, and books and stationary
salesmen are not
allowed to be dispatched.
Witness, what kind of work
did Baek Seung-hwa do?
Well, I...
don't know.
Baek Seung-hwa sold furniture
at Bang Bang Mart, and
Shin Yong-cheol sold electronic devices.
Therefore, their departments
are not valid to have dispatch
workers, so they can be seen
as illegal dispatch workers.
The plaintiffs must, of course be re-hired as
permanent workers at the Bang Bang Mart,
be paid for six months of unemployment, and be
separately compensated $30,000 per person.
That is all.
Jang-go.
Congratulations for winning.
Thank you. You did well, too.
See you around.
Sure.
I heard she's the daughter
of the head of Jang & Ko.
Yes.
Her expression doesn't change.
Is she spiteful or cool?
She's a lawyer,
but she's fashionable and pretty.
Let's go.
Mr. Lee Jang-go, please tell us how
you feel about winning today's trial.
Weren't you burdened that you were
going against Jang & Ko Law Firm?
People are comparing
this to David and Goliath.
- Do you think...
- Reporters, please don't do this.
Please ask one question at a time.
Tell us how you feel about winning.
Geum-sil, Jang-go won
that tremendous law firm Jang & Ko.
Look at this.
Jang-go totally became a star!
Here.
Oh my goodness.
So all these people here are reporters?
Oh, my.
Oh my goodness!
Jang-go is like some sort of celebrity
He hit jackpot!
Oh my gosh! Jang-go's
article is already up!
"David and Goliath."
"Lawyer Lee Jang-go
who won against Jang & Ko."
Look at this, Geum-sil!
- Goodness!
- Oh, my!
This is my son, Jang-go!
I can't believe this, Nam-yi!
Now that this article is up,
we'll get a lot of clients!
It would be so great if that happened!
You should have told me
he was doing such a huge trial.
He just talked to me last night
like it was no big deal,
so I thought it was
one of those pathetic trials again.
This was such an
important trial that I didn't
want to burden him,
so I was being careful.
And it was so chaotic
because of Jang-soo lately.
Let me see my son's article again.
Here.
- Oh my goodness!
- Mom.
Oh, my Jang-go! He's so handsome!
Who gave birth to him?
- Mother.
- Yes?
I gave birth to him!
Grandma! Mom! Aunt!
Who's that?
- Jang-soo!
- Lee Jang-soo!
Oh, that young lady is...
Hello.
Hee-ra.
Grandma, mom, and aunt.
Give us some food. We're starving.
Hee-ra.
Oh my goodness!
What are they doing while eating?
Come on.
It's delicious!
- It's good.
- Do they really want to do that?
Jang-soo.
But they're so cute.
Hey. When they're done eating,
tell her to go home.
And make sure to let her know
we're against this relationship, too.
Okay.
You want to separate them
when they love each other so much?
Hey, didn't you hear her mother call him
cow Jang-soo, dog Jang-soo, and a thief?
I don't want that kind of family
to be linked to ours anyways!
Mom, she's a phoenix.
Yet, you want to chase her away?
Are you crazy? You're supposed to
catch her even if she says she'll leave.
Nowadays, daughters have rights, too.
She's a phoenix worth
at least 50 million dollars!
Calculate before
you say something like that.
Anyways, call her mom and
let her know her daughter is here.
Imagine how she would feel
as the parent of a daughter.
I'm so frustrated!
We told him to study
to become a civil servant!
There's nothing
about him we can brag about!
They have every right to be upset.
Think about it in their shoes.
Jang-soo, open up!
- Is it good?
- Oh my gosh.
They have honey
dripping out of their eyes.
Oh, my.
- They're so cute!
- It's so good!
I'm so dizzy.
This little brat.
(Geum-sil)
Hi, it's me.
What did you say?
Hee-ra came to your house?
Yeah, she just came with Jang-soo.
I thought you had to know.
All right! Don't let her go anywhere!
Mom?
Mom! Mom!
So you two are saying
that you will never be able to
separate from each other no matter what?
Yes, grandma.
Even if we die, we can never break up.
I feel the same way.
I can't live without Jang-soo now.
Hee-ra!
- Hee-ra!
- Mom!
Are you okay? Nothing happened, right?
- Yes.
- Okay.
Then that's fine. Let's go.
Mom.
I can't go. I won't go.
What about Jang-soo?
Let's go! This is not somewhere
you should be! Let's go!
I'll go if you allow us to be together.
Please give us permission.
I'm going to marry Jang-soo.
What did you say?
What are you going to do?
- What did you say?
- Hee-ra.
How can you say that to your mom?
How can you say that after
you see what this house looks
like? It doesn't matter
if you're blinded by love!
- Let's go!
- I don't want to!
I said I don't want to go!
Hee-ra, what's wrong with you?
Hurry up and go with your mom!
- You...
- Your mother hasn't eaten or slept
because of you!
She's on the verge of dying!
That's why you should
just give us permission!
I love Jang-soo!
You won't come home with me?
Mom, please!
Then is it him or me? Choose one of us.
Is it me or him?
Can't you just understand us?
How can you tell me to
throw away the man I love?
So you're going to choose him
and betray your mom?
Goodness!
Get a hold of yourself, Hee-ra!
Jo Hee-ra.
I will ask you one last time.
If you don't come with me now,
that's the end of us.
What will you do?
Will you still stay here?
Yes.
I'm going to stay next to Jang-soo.
I promised I would
stay with him forever.
Fine.
Fine. I understand.
Starting from today,
you're not my daughter.
We're over.
Mom!
You terrible brat!
How can you betray your mom
who raised you all this time?
You and I are over, too!
You horrible brat! Chung-ja!
- Mom!
- Chung-ja!
Mom!
Chung-ja.
You can't just leave like this.
You need to lie that you'll allow them to
be together and take her away from here!
Are you really just
going to leave like this?
How can you still say that
after you witnessed everything?
That brat isn't my daughter anymore.
She's not my child!
She's not anything to me!
Her mom is very upset, but how could
she not even come out to see her off?
Terrible brat.
Chung-ja! Chung-ja!
Good work today. See you tomorrow.
- Good work!
- See you tomorrow.
Did Jang-soo's trial end?
What happened?
He probably won.
No. He might not have won.
Yes.
Hey, Kim Mi-poong!
Jang-go, what are you doing here?
Of course I came to see you.
Um...
about today's trial...
How did it go?
The trial?
Well...
I won.
Why did you do that?
You could have just told me you won
right away! You scared me!
You live to tease me, don't you?
How'd you know?
By the way, the handkerchief
you gave me actually worked.
It made me feel like I took a pill of
bravery when I was nervous.
Nice.
So you're saying you won
today's trial because of me.
Well, I guess you can say that.
Then you should buy dinner tonight.
That's why I came. To buy you dinner.
Let's go.
Let's go!
What do you think of this place?
Does it suit your taste?
Yes.
But it's such an expensive and
fancy place that I feel burdened.
Don't feel burdened.
From now on, I only want
to do good things for you.
Mr. Jo...
By the way, can you just
call me by my first name?
Then...
Hee-dong.
Like this?
Yes.
Like that.
Thank you.
Did you eat well?
I did, but I think I ate too much.
I think my stomach is going to explode.
What if my stomach explodes and I die?
You're fine. I never saw
anyone die because of that before.
Mi-poong, should we go over there
and digest our food?
Isn't this a place for little kids?
You are a little kid.
Let's go.
Try hitting it.
- You can hit with two hands, and I'll hit with one.
- Hit with this hand.
This one?
Okay.
Yes!
You're no match for me.
Did you just play games your whole life?
You can't win me.
That. Let's play that.
That one?
The loser has to buy coffee, okay?
You can't change your mind.
Don't worry.
You can't win that! I told you
I got special lessons!
I won, right? You surrender, right?
Yeah, you won.
Are you that happy?
Let's go over there.
It's suddenly raining.
I know.
I'm almost home now.
You can go now.
I'll go after I see you go.
I'll feel safe after watching you leave.
Then hold on.
Take this.
Bye!
Who are you?
Hee-dong.
Are you okay? Are you hurt anywhere?
It's okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
Hee-dong, can't you
stay until I fall asleep?
I'm so scared.
I'll stay by your side,
so don't worry and sleep.
Shin-ae.
Are you okay?
Did you have a nightmare?
Hee-dong.
Yes?
I miss my parents.
My parents...
It's okay, Shin-ae.
I'll stay by your side from now on,
so don't be afraid. It's okay.
It's okay.
It's me. Good job today.
Hey, Shin-ae. Call me anytime
you need that kind of help again.
My brother did well, right?
Yes.
I paid him well for that.
It's really nice.
The breeze feels nice,
and dinner was delicious.
We played games like little kids, too.
We're drinking coffee, too.
I feel great!
The food was delicious,
and the coffee is good, too.
This perfect day happened
because you won the trial, right?
I guess so.
Thanks to who?
Thanks to you! Thanks to you!
Thanks to the lucky handkerchief
you made me!
Happy?
Bingo! You got it!
Sometimes you take a lot of the credit.
Oh, my. You're the one
who takes a lot of the credit.
Did you already forget how much credit
you took because I won the logo competition?
Did I do that?
Fine. You can take the credit, too.
It's nice.
I'm very happy just
being with you like this.
It's okay if you don't look at me.
I'm just very happy that
I can look at you like this.
Chung-ja. Chung-ja.
Chung-ja! Hurry up and get up!
Mom, just leave me alone. Goodness.
Yesterday, my head felt like
it was going to break, and
today, my eyes feel like
they're going to pop out.
- I feel like I'm going to die.
- Dal-ho came back!
Dal-ho came back?
He's supposed to be back tomorrow!
Why did he come back already?
What if he asks me where Hee-ra went?
Tell him she went on a trip
to Hong Kong with her friends.
Hong Kong?
What about your dad?
Father went into grandfather's room.
Really?
This is his bag.
Oh, my. What's so important that
he went to see Elder right away?
I know.
Why did it take so long?
You couldn't even
tell me over the phone.
Why did you have to tell me in person?
Do you have bad news?
Elder, I talked with
Jo Kyung-sook on the phone.
What? What did you say?
Jo Kyung-sook?
Kyung-sook was alive?
Yes.
The Chinese broker in North Korea
helped me connect
with her, and she remembered
everything about you.
So... so did you ask her?
Did she really see my wife then?
Yes, she did.
She said she remembers it very well.
What?
Then Soon-ok...
was really alive?
She really saw your pregnant wife
after the Third Battle of Seoul.
She even remembered that
your wife's dress was a wooden color.
She was alive.
Elder, are you okay?
How?
How could this happen?
That means Soon-ok...
and my child...
might both be alive?
Yes, Elder.
Oh my goodness.
My goodness.
I didn't even know my child was alive.
Elder. Elder!
Elder, have some water.
Dal-ho,
they'll be alive, won't they?
Elder...
Goodness.
How can something
so unbelievable happen?
Even after I heard that they're alive,
I can't even find them.
I can't meet them.
How can this happen?
You must take care of yourself.
If you have your health,
you can fulfill all of your wishes.
I will.
That old man keeps murmuring,
so I don't know what he's saying.
Did you hear what they were saying?
No, I didn't.
I think I heard something
about father fulfilling his wish.
Wish? What wish?
What's his wish?
I'm not sure.
I think the only wish he has is a union.
What is it?
I don't know. What's the use
of knowing what his wish is?
We'll be in big trouble if
he finds out Hee-ra is gone.
Ms. Kim Mi-poong.
Yes?
Mi-poong, go to the store.
Say hello to the manager, examine
the sales, and comprehend the inventory.
Yes, I will.
- Hello!
- Hello.
I'm sorry!
No, I was the one who dropped them.
Are you...?
Hello.
You're Jang-go's friend's
younger sister, right?
Yes, I am.
But what are you doing here?
Oh, I work in the
marketing department here.
Oh, really?
I work here at the Jang & Ko Law Firm.
I see.
- It's good to see you again.
- Yes.
Let's have tea next time.
Sure.
Soon-ok, I'm sorry.
I made you give birth to our child alone,
and I made you raise him alone as well.
It must have been so difficult for you.
Do I have a son or a daughter?
I might have grandchildren, too.
Whether I have a son or daughter...
Whether I have a grandson
or a granddaughter...
I want to see them at least once.
Just for one day,
I wish I can live with them.
Are you listening to me?
Soon-ok!
Just please be alive.
Just please be healthy.
I will make sure to find you.
I will.
- You may go.
- Yes, sir.
After I'm done, I'll go home
on my own, so go.
Yes, sir.
Sir, are you all right?
I'm fine. I'm fine.
Go. Go.
Sir.
Hold on.
Sir!
Sir.
Drink some water.
Are you feeling better now?
I was going to buy medicine,
but I thought you shouldn't
take just any medicine,
so I just bought water.
I'm feeling better now.
Thank you.
I think you should go to the hospital.
Would you like me to take you?
I don't need to go to the hospital.
Miss, you must be busy. You can go now.
Then where do you live?
I'll catch you a taxi.
I'm really fine now.
Someone is coming for me.
Then take care.
All right.
Thank you, miss.
Mr. Kim!
I'm fine.
Here.
Hold on.
Jang-soo, if you wanted, I would
pluck you a star from the sky.
However, this is wrong.
Yesterday, you two said
you will never be able to
separate from each other
no matter what, right?
But the same goes for us.
We'll never be able to accept
you two like this no matter what.
Grandma! Mom!
Are you telling Hee-ra and me
to leave this house?
That's not what we're saying right now.
What we're saying that is that
it feels awkward to let you two
stay here when her parents
haven't even given their approval.
Hee-ra,
I understand your feelings for Jang-soo.
It's not like your mom
and I are strangers either.
If you really love Jang-soo,
get your parents' approval first.
She's right. We need
to do things in order.
If you try to do things forcefully,
they won't work out eventually.
Grandma!
If your mom gives
you permission, so will we.
Okay?
Jang-soo, take Hee-ra home.
Mom!
What can I do? I want to just accept you guys,
but I have no power in this house.
Good luck.
Go in, Hee-ra! Go in!
I'll always be waiting for you!
Don't you know how I feel?
Jang-soo!
Go inside.
My mom won't give us permission.
You saw my mom, too.
She told me she would shave my head
and send me to the mountains!
She really did?
Jang-soo, there's only one way
we can stay together.
One way?
What's that?
(Marriage Registration)
Hold on.
Are you sure you won't regret this?
What about you?
I won't regret it.
Me, too.
(My Princess)
Hi, Hee-ra. Where are you right now?
Are you back in Korea?
You have something to tell me?
Right now?
Mom, let's meet.
I have something to tell you.
Meet me at Some Restaurant
in the Swan Room right now.
I have to go and catch her.
My goodness!
Mother! Chung-ja!
Did you two come to meet Hee-ra, too?
Did you come because Hee-ra
asked you to meet her, too?
Yeah. I came because she said
she had something important to tell me.
I thought she only called me. I guess
she wanted to eat outside with the family.
Let's go in, mother.
Go in.
What's this?
I have a bad feeling about this.
Why did she call Dal-ho?
Did she call him
so he could give permission
for her to be with that
good-for-nothing bum?
This brat!
Hey, we don't know
anything yet, so be calm.
Let's go.
I'm sorry.
- Honey, I don't think it's here.
- You're right. It's not. Let's go.
Dad.
It's here.
It is?
But Hee-ra who is this man
and these people?
Jo Hee-ra, what are you doing?
Do you really want to see me go crazy?
What's wrong with you?
There are elders present!
- Anyways, let's go.
- Let's go, Dal-ho.
Mom and dad.
Jang-soo and I...
got married.
Chung-ja.
This is our marriage registration.
Jang-soo and I went to the borough office
and registered for marriage.
Oh my goodness.
What is she talking about?
Jang-soo, what is Hee-ra
talking about right now?
Come on. She said that they went to the
borough office and registered for marriage.
Let me see.
(Marriage Registration)
It's true!
Hee-ra.
Marriage Registration?
What are you talking about?
Hee-ra, what's this?
No, no! Don't listen to this crap!
This is fraud! This is invalid!
This is invalid!
Oh my goodness.
(Blow Breeze)
How much is all this worth?
I got a good one this time.
You're too much.
Is divorce a joke to you?
We have to break them up!
Is it you? The one who caused
trouble with Hee-ra?
Jang-soo!
I'm Kim Mi-poong's older brother.
Will you take responsibility
if I can't get married?
Okay, I will.
You will?
Subtitles by OnDemandKorea