Subtitles by OnDemandKorea
- (Episode 14)
- Let me see.
(Marriage Registration)
It's true!
Hee-ra.
Marriage registration?
What are you talking about?
Hee-ra, what's this?
No, no! Don't listen to this crap!
This is fraud! This is invalid!
This is invalid!
Oh my goodness.
Mother.
Grandma!
Hee-ra, why?
Why would you do something
like this without even telling me?
Are you an orphan?
Or do I mean nothing to you?
Dad, it's not like that.
I love you so much.
I didn't do this to disappoint you.
For the first time, I fell in love,
but mom won't acknowledge us,
and all she does is disrespect us
and disapprove of us!
That's why I did this.
Excuse me.
Since things already turned out
this way, why don't
you have a seat so that
we can discuss this?
Why would we sit down?
You thieves! You con-artists!
You did this, didn't you?
You planned all this, didn't you?
What?
You're too much.
Don't talk to Jang-soo's
mother that way!
She told us to do things in order
and get your permission first!
You don't know anything, so why
are you talking that way to her?
Jo Hee-ra!
Hee-ra, stop this madness!
Get a hold of yourself!
Both of you just stay still!
This doesn't make sense.
I can't acknowledge this.
Jo Hee-ra,
there's no need to discuss this.
This marriage without the adults
knowing is unacceptable!
Dad.
I'm twenty-nine, not nineteen.
I'm an adult, and Jang-soo
and I love each other.
So please understand me.
You want me to understand you
when you pulled something like this?
You disrespected your parents, and yet,
you want us to understand you?
You can't get married just
because you love each other!
I don't need a daughter who
disrespects her parents anyways.
Mother. Honey. Let's go.
- Dad!
- Father!
Hee-ra, how can you betray me like this?
Just pretend she died.
Enough talking. Let's go.
Chung-ja, let's go.
Mom! Dad! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry!
Hee-ra.
Jang-soo.
Because you would be so upset...
Because you would be so heartbroken...
I was trying so hard to solve
this before you had to find out.
Then this happened.
Solve this?
How? By making her leave the house
and get married without us knowing?
What did you to do her?
Dal-ho, how can you speak that way?
Are you saying it's
Chung-ja's fault that Hee-ra
got married to that good-for-nothing
bum without letting us know?
Hee-ra isn't such a horrible girl.
She did this because Chung-ja
had cornered her like a rat.
You're too harsh.
Do you know how heartbroken
Chung-ja is because of Hee-ra?
We catch her, and she runs away.
We lock her up, and she runs away again.
If you could open up her chest, you would
see her heart has turned rotten black!
Are you the only one who's upset?
I feel like dying right now.
You know how I raised Hee-ra.
She was going out with some good-for-
nothing bum. Was I supposed to just let them be?
God! Move!
What else can we do?
We need to accept them.
Yes, Geum-sil.
If we help them out a little, they'll be able
to work hard and move out on their own.
Are we a family that
can be so disrespected?
We worked hard and lived
without any shame until now.
Yes, yes.
But who is she to disrespect us?
We get on by, and we have a house, too.
You're completely right, and we don't
have anything to be ashamed about.
But she's treating us like
we're thieves who stole
her precious daughter!
How can she do that?
I completely lost interest
in Hee-ra, and
I don't want her to be
part of our family either.
Geum-sil, I'm furious, too.
But if you think about it
in their shoes,
I realize they have a right
to come out that way.
She's the apple of their eye,
and they even sent her
to study abroad.
How shocked they must be right now.
Just understand them.
If we chase them out,
they'll have nowhere else to go.
Let's allow them to stay here
temporarily, Geum-sil.
But where will they stay?
There are no more rooms.
There is a room.
You mean my room?
Hee-ra, here's water.
Jang-soo, I'm sorry.
Because I insisted
we register for marriage,
you were criticized.
So you regret it?
I'm not said because I regret it.
I'm sad because I hurt my parents.
Let's be happier then.
Eventually, they'll find out
you're a good person.
But it seemed like your grandmother,
mother, and aunt was really mad.
What if we get kicked out of here, too?
Hee-ra, don't you remember
how we came here?
My grandma dragged us here.
Would she have done that if
they were going to kick us out?
You're right!
Don't cry, Hee-ra.
Okay.
What a sight!
Close the door!
I didn't even give them permission to use
my room, but they already took over it!
I'm the greatest victim of this
marriage registration incident.
Their parents won't last long.
No parents win over their children.
I guess I need to sacrifice this
much for Jang-soo to become
the son-in-law of a 100 million
dollar inheritance household.
Later when Hee-ra gets her inheritance,
she won't forget me, right?
Goodness! Now isn't the time for that!
Goodness!
So immature.
My goodness.
- Bye, Young-ae!
- Bye.
- Bye!
- Bye. See you tomorrow.
Did Yoo-sung and
Mi-poong eat dinner yet?
Where did my cell-phone go?
Oh, my.
We locked the door, so why is it open?
Did they not lock it?
There it is!
You must have left something.
Oh my goodness.
I'm sorry. Were you very surprised?
No. I just didn't think
anyone would be here.
I should have at least
left the lights on.
It's okay. I left my cell-phone here.
But why are you drinking alone
without any snacks in the darkness?
Oh, I just wanted a drink.
Don't worry about me and go home.
I'll lock up before I go.
How can I just go when you're drinking
alone without any snacks?
Hold on.
I'm really okay.
Eat these.
If you just drink soju without eating
any snacks, you'll get an upset stomach.
I bothered you, Ms. Joo.
Nonsense. Seasoned acorn jelly salad
is the easiest thing to make in this world.
Try it.
I will. Thank you, Ms. Joo.
Mr. Jo...
I don't know why you're like this...
but there can't only be
good days in our lives.
Some days are sunny.
Some days are rainy.
It gets bright again and then suddenly
there are typhoons and landslides.
That's life.
Yes, that's true.
There can't only be bright days.
But after being hit with typhoons
and landslides out of the blue,
it makes me angry and wonder
if I lived a wrong life all along.
I'm having such a difficult time
and feeling so angry today.
Typhoons and landslides?
My daughter secretly registered
for marriage with
her boyfriend because
my wife disapproved of them.
She secretly registered for marriage?
Yes.
Her parents are both alive and well...
I never imagined my daughter, out of
all people, would betray me like this.
I can't forgive her.
This may be crossing the line,
but she's the daughter
of a great man like you,
I'm sure nothing will go wrong.
You should trust her.
She just has to live
a happy life, right?
Our children just have
to be healthy and alive.
Their mere existence should
make us feel grateful.
I'm sorry.
No, it's fine.
I shouldn't have brought this up.
No.
Well,
I didn't even offer you a drink.
Ms. Jo, have a drink.
Yes, thank you.
It's very hard living here, isn't it?
I would be lying if I answered no.
But because of people like you and
Mr. Kim who help and encourage me,
I'm very lucky.
Thank you very much.
This is quick service.
(Equity List)
(Basic Equity List)
Samseong-dong building.
Jongno building.
Jeju-do ranch.
How much is all his inheritance worth?
Is he really the inheritance
of 100 million dollars?
He's so lucky. He'll be getting such
an inheritance from a distant relative.
I got a good man this time.
Hello?
Yes, I'm Lee Jang-go.
Oh, hello.
Right now?
(Jang & Ko)
What are you here for?
The president here called for me.
Jang-go.
Oh, Ha-yeon.
You're here to meet my dad, right?
Yeah.
I came because he called for me,
but what is this about?
Do you know anything?
How about you hear it from him yourself?
Come on.
You mean you want to scout me?
Why are you so surprised?
I've been keeping an eye on you
before Ha-yeon told me about you.
I liked how you defeated
my temperamental daughter in this trial.
Must you really bring
that up in front of me?
You're mean.
What do you mean? It's true you were
completely defeated this time.
Did you lose to him on purpose?
Dad!
I was kidding.
People think that all lawyers
need to do is memorize the law.
That's nonsense.
Actually, it's a fight of
passion and principles.
I'm scouting you because
I see that kind of passion in you.
But this is such an unexpected offer.
Naturally, you will need
some time to think about this.
But don't think about it for too long.
I really hope we can work together.
You'll never regret it.
Not anyone can work in our law firm.
You know that, right?
Anyways, thank you for the good offer.
I'll answer you after I have
thought about this thoroughly.
That's right. Isn't Mi-poong's company
in this building, too?
(Jang-go)
Hi, Jang-go.
Hi. How many people work in your office?
Why are you suddenly asking me that?
What will you do with that information?
Come on. You just have to answer me.
How many people are there?
There's my chief, Mr. Ha, Min-cheol,
Young-ju, and me. So five people in total?
But why are you asking that?
Five? Okay.
Jang-go!
What on earth was that about?
Ready for the meeting?
- Yes!
- Yes.
Should we go to the meeting room?
Hello.
Who are you?
Why are you here?
The thing is...
I'm Kim Mi-poong's older brother.
Oh, I see.
Oh, that's right. Here.
What are these?
Can't you tell? Coffee.
I left my sister in your care,
and I didn't get to greet you until now.
I had some work to do nearby,
so I stopped by to say hello.
I'm Lee Jang-go.
Please take care of my sister.
Don't worry.
Mi-poong is doing very well.
But you two must not be real siblings.
Your last names are different.
Mi-poong's last name is Kim,
and your last name is Lee.
Yes. She's actually my friend's younger sister,
but she's like my sister, so please be good to her.
But Mi-poong is from North Korea, so how
did you become friends with her older brother?
Maybe there will be a chance when
I can tell you that story in the future.
I took up a lot of your time
when you should be working.
It seems like I should get going now.
Oh, that's right.
Here. This is my card.
Call me anytime you need my help.
I'll be going now.
Thank you for the coffee.
- No problem.
- Good-bye.
- Mi-poong, walk him out...
- No, no! I'm fine!
Don't come out. Work hard.
Bye.
Good-bye.
- Bye.
Wow. He must be a lawyer.
Oh, yes, he is.
Mi-poong, be honest. He's not your friend.
He's your boyfriend, right?
No! We're just friends!
She said he's her friend,
not her boyfriend.
Now, now. Should we have
a fun meeting while eating
the cookies and coffee that
her friend bought for us?
- Yes.
- Let's go.
Hee-dong, it's me.
Hi, Shin-ae.
Do you want to eat dinner tonight?
Shiitake mushrooms are good lately, so I was
going to make shiitake mushroom rice.
Oh.
I have something to do today.
I'll call you later.
Okay then. We'll eat together next time.
What's wrong?
How can he reject me?
Jo Hee-dong, I thought
you had fallen for me.
What's going on?
Is that man your older brother?
Hee-dong is angry!
Jang-soo, never fight him, okay?
Hee-ra, don't worry!
My legs and arms are long!
I'll protect you so that
he can't do anything to you.
Is it you?
The punk who caused trouble with Hee-ra?
Yes, I am!
But you're being too rude
when it's the first time we meet!
"Trouble? Punk?"
Are we middle school students?
Bite down, you punk!
You punk!
Hey! Let go!
I can't! I won't!
Jang-soo!
Jang-soo, get a hold of yourself!
Oh, no! Jang-soo!
Who are you to hit my Jang-soo?
Who are you?
Stop it!
So in other words, the two of you
didn't just do this thoughtlessly.
Yes, Hee-dong.
I really love Hee-ra.
Fine.
I'll trust your words.
But if you make Hee-ra cry...
I'll come back here again.
I'll make sure you never
have to come here again!
I promise you, Hee-dong.
Hey, Jo Hee-ra.
You did do wrong to our parents,
so you better get on your knees
and apologize. Got it?
Okay.
Then I'll get going.
Hee-dong.
I'm going to live well, so don't worry.
And...
I'm sorry.
Jang-soo, are you all right?
I'm fine.
But is he usually like that?
No.
He's usually a stupid, gentle baby.
An extremely gentle baby.
He only does that
when he's really angry.
Really?
But he turns like that
when he becomes furious.
It's the first time I see him
do a spinning kick today.
Oh, no. Are you okay?
- I'm sorry.
- The spinning kick...
Let me see.
- That spinning kick...
- I know.
- You got sand on you.
- I was so scared.
I protected you though, didn't I?
Thank you.
- Just trust me.
- Okay.
Hi.
Mr. Jo, hurry up and come to my office!
You know the outline you showed me
last time? Did you modify it?
Bring me that! Hurry!
Why out of the blue?
I think there's a T.O on a zoisite.
Really?
Yes! It's information
I just got right now!
Let's put this in before
someone else fills up the spot!
You need to start
publishing series now, right?
I'll come right now!
It can't just end like this.
I can't give up on my daughter.
(Ma Chung-ja)
Hi, it's me.
Right now?
I have to talk to you
about our kids, so come out.
I don't want to see you.
I'm begging you.
What do you need to tell me?
Geum-sil.
No matter how much I think
about this, this is wrong.
Why must our kids go
through such a marriage?
My husband said he would
never see Hee-ra again.
We shouldn't cut off ties
between parents and children.
People must live rationally.
Your son and my daughter are quite old,
but they're still immature.
That's why they caused
such a great incident.
We learned that nothing good
comes out of living
irrationally and cutting ties
off with our family.
Do you think our kids will be happy?
That's why we should support them.
Why should we support them when this
was a wrong marriage from the beginning?
This isn't rational!
Then what are we supposed to do
if we don't support them?
Either chase Hee-ra out,
or if they can't separate,
chase both of them out.
You want me to kick the
kids out of my house?
Yes.
Our kids are both jobless, so they
won't be able to last a long time.
Hee-ra lived with money, so she won't
be able to survive a week without it.
So do that for me, Geum-sil.
Then I'll break them up no matter what.
So are you saying you want them
to have a divorce before
their ink dries up on
their marriage registration?
Is that it?
That's why we need to take care
of this before the ink dries up!
Goodness.
Hey, Ma Chung-ja! You're too much!
They didn't receive our permission
to register for marriage,
but they're still a married couple by law.
Do you think divorce is that easy?
Is divorce a kid's joke?
I can never do that.
Hwang Geum-sil.
Oh, now your true colors come out.
What?
"True colors?"
Yes! True colors!
Are you secretly happy that
our kids registered for marriage?
But don't even dream about it!
If Hee-ra won't divorce your son,
then we'll cut off ties with her!
She's not my daughter,
so she won't even get a penny!
You wench!
What do you think you're doing?
You awful wench.
How can you do this?
Are you really a parent?
What? It's rational to make
our kids get a divorce?
I will never make them get a divorce.
I'll take care of that daughter
you threw away like she's mine,
so you go ahead and live well
with the inheritance your
distant relative leaves behind,
you terrible wench!
Horrible wench!
Fine!
I'm going to watch how long you
can last with my penniless daughter!
I...
Witch!
This blouse was so expensive!
You're back.
Yes.
How is Mr. Park doing?
Goodness. It's his homesickness again.
I heard he was being discharged today.
I'm glad it's not a severe illness.
So did Mr. Yang contact you?
No, not yet.
I guess. Only a few days have gone by.
But is something wrong, Dal-ho?
Well, Elder...
Um, I have something to tell you.
I think you should know about it, too.
All right.
Tell me.
Hee-ra...
left the house.
Hee-ra left home?
What do you mean?
Goodness.
They're not orphans.
How can they register
for marriage by themselves?
What's going on?
It's all my fault.
This happened because
I was lacking, father.
I'm sorry, father.
Since things already
turned out this way,
shouldn't you get them
officially married?
Pardon?
Marry?
If Hee-ra marries him,
her life will be worthless!
How can I let that happen
as a parent? How?
Those kids already became
a married couple by law.
Do you really want to separate
them when they're in love...
and make Hee-ra into a divorcee?
Yes! That's better!
Until this day, I never went
against your words,
but even if you give them permission,
I won't be able to this time.
I will never acknowledge
them even if I die!
Elder, I can't forgive
Hee-ra yet either.
I'm sorry.
Just leave this matter up to us.
I understand.
Hee-ra is your child, so it's only right
that you decide what to do with her.
Instead, tell me if you ever
need my help, Dal-ho.
I'm sorry.
Are we just going home?
I don't know. Tell me what you want.
Should we get beer or soju today?
Beer!
Hey, Kim Mi-poong!
He came again.
- Go on.
- I don't think we can hang out today.
Lucky.
What are you doing here?
Did you wait for me all this time?
No, I didn't.
I had some work to do nearby,
and it was time for you
to go home, so I decided
to pick you up. Get in.
Gosh.
What's up with you today?
You got in without an argument.
Hurry up and drive.
Why? Is someone following you?
Just go!
All right.
What is it? What's wrong?
People keep misunderstanding us
if they keep seeing us together.
I thought it was something else.
Just tell them I'm your friend.
I did say that.
But people keep misunderstanding us.
They ask me what our relationship is.
I wonder why they're
so curious about that.
Fine. I'll go to your office
tomorrow and clarify that
I'm just your friend so that
they won't misunderstand.
Forget it.
What do you mean? I just don't
want to cause trouble for you.
So what if you say that a hundred times?
If there's weird rumors of me because of you and
I can't get married, will you take responsibility?
Yes, I will.
You will?
Yes. I'll take responsibility and
send you off to marry a great guy.
Hey, there's no guy like me out there.
Fine.
I'm so grateful.
Then be good to me, and don't complain.
You fool. I'm so curious how
you managed to pass the bar exam
when you're so dense that
you don't know a woman's heart.
What now?
It's nothing.
I'm the fool for liking
such a clueless fool.
Jang-soo!
What do you think
about your new bedroom?
- Grandma!
- Yes.
Hee-ra, my mother-in-law and I prepared this
as quickly as we could. Do you like it?
Mother.
Grandma.
What's wrong? You don't like it?
No, no!
I like it so much! I love it!
Hey, aren't you going to give me a hug?
I picked out all the colors.
Grandma!
Goodness. Yes, yes.
I know you guys wanted
something fancier, but what to do?
You two registered for
marriage out of the blue,
so even if you feel
disappointed, live well.
Rather than wedding gifts,
it's better to live a happy life together!
Yes! We'll have a happy life, grandma!
Thank you!
My goodness. I'm so dizzy!
Aunt, what's this?
A gift from me.
Can I open it?
Go ahead.
It's so pretty! I love it so much!
It's so cute! Right?
Lee Jang-soo.
Lee Jang-soo! Come out.
Let's have a beer party.
A beer party? I love beer! Hooray!
Hooray!
My goodness.
Go out, mother.
Mom, let's go!
Here. A toast to Jang-soo's
happy honeymoon life!
Cheers!
Lee Jang-soo, congratulations.
- Thank you.
- Congratulations.
Thank you, brother-in-law!
Look at her. She's like someone
who's been married for over one year.
She says brother-in-law so easily!
Goodness!
That's Hee-ra's charm!
To be truthful and lively!
Thank you for knowing
my charming points, mother.
She talks so smoothly with the
whole "brother-in-law, grandma,
and mother" talk. She even
drinks her beer so smoothly!
Are you a heavy drinker?
I'm not a heavy drinker.
I'm just someone who loves beer.
I love beer so much.
That's how I met Jang-soo.
I drank beer with Jang-soo, ended up
getting drunk, and went to a motel with him-
- What?
- Good for you!
Come on, Hee-ra, stop there.
What do you mean stop there?
Tell us everything while you're at it.
- Should I? Anyways, so what happened was...
- No! Stop! Stop!
Aunt! Hee-ra!
Come on.
She's going to spill everything!
Let her be!
How did you two meet?
So we decided to just drink one bottle
of beer, but there was this game-
- Hee-ra, stop right there!
- Why? They're family anyways.
- Aunt!
- Keep spilling it!
While you're at it, spill everything!
- I'll finish it after I drink this.
- Sure, go ahead.
One shot! One shot!
- One shot!
- Cheers!
I think this family is in big trouble.
Oh, my.
So spill it.
Come on, Nam-yi! Stop it!
Seems like the owner's family
is having a blast.
Something good must have happened.
Did Jang-go's brother get married?
The girl's family was against it.
I think they just decided
to live together.
I see.
Even though they didn't
officially get married,
it's nice to see that
their family accepted them.
Mom, what's wrong?
I remember when
your brother got married.
I think about his dead wife who died
while giving birth to Yoo-sung, too.
Your sister-in-law was a very pretty
and sweet person.
You remember her, don't you?
If she hadn't died while
giving birth to Yoo-sung,
he would have had a mom, too.
Yoo-sung...
My poor Yoo-sung...
Mom.
Yoo-sung has you and me.
I'll be like a dad and a mom to him.
So don't worry, okay?
I promise.
Are you going to live
taking care of us forever?
When you meet a good man,
you need to get married.
I will never marry a man who doesn't think
of you and Yoo-sung as part of his family.
I'd rather be single forever.
Goodness.
Don't ever say something
like that again.
Yoo-sung has me,
so don't worry about it.
When you meet a good man and
get married, I'm going to be so thrilled.
Don't think about it for too long.
Are you going somewhere?
I'm going to exercise.
All right.
Did Yoo-sung leave?
Yes, he was so happy
to go with his teachers and
friends that he didn't
even look back at me.
The weather is so nice today,
so they'll have a fun time.
Yeah. I'm going to get ready and
go to work, so stay home and relax.
Oh, my! What's this?
Mom! Mom!
What's wrong?
The money for my logo competition
must have been deposited! Look at this!
- Oh, my!
- (You have received $8,321.40 in your account.)
How much is this? $8,321.40?
But wasn't the prize money $10,000?
Why was only this much deposited?
Is it a mistake?
Was this deposited
after tax was deducted from it?
Tax?
They take tax from prize money?
Why did they take so much?
That's too much! They shouldn't have
said the prize money was $10,000 then.
Mom, this is still a lot though.
You're right.
Even if they take the tax, we should be
grateful they're still giving you the money.
This is so great.
I was wondering when this
money would come in.
But Mi-poong, about this money...
You want to give this
to the owner, right?
Yes. We lived without giving them
any money all this time.
We're getting our security deposit
next month, but I still feel too bad.
You and I had the same thought
at the same time.
Let's do that.
Okay.
Mi-poong, here.
Give it to her with this money.
What kind of money is this?
It's the money you made from your part-time jobs
and the money I made from working.
If we add these up with your prize money,
it'll be about $10,000.
But Mi-poong, I think it would be best
for you to give the money to Jang-go.
His mother doesn't like seeing us.
Okay, I'll do that.
Goodness. I feel so much lighter knowing
we can at least give that much to her.
I was on pins and needles until now.
Good job.
Hi, Mi-poong.
Jang-go, tell me your account number.
My bank account number? Why?
It's not much, but I want to send you
a part of the security deposit.
Security deposit?
You really came.
Why aren't you telling me
your account number?
Why did you make me
come all the way here?
Take this.
It's $10,000.
$10,000?
Gosh, I said it's okay.
Sit down for a moment.
Where did you get $10,000?
I got the prize money
for the logo competition.
Also, my mom and I combined
the money we made so far.
Then save up this money.
It made both my mom and me uncomfortable
to live without paying the security deposit.
Of course, it's not much,
but please accept it.
Mi-poong,
do you think I would feel uncomfortable
accepting this money from you?
When you get your security deposit back,
give it to me then-
It's not much, but please accept it.
Fine. I will.
Then I'll give this money to my mom.
Thank you.
This is just temporary.
I haven't decided the title yet.
- ("Thump Thump Convenience Store")
- They meet in the convenience store.
The man is actually very passive.
- What's this?
- It's good, right?
I really like it.
When will you be able to finish this by?
Well, I'll have to finish it
by the end of this week, right?
Yes, yes. Okay.
(My Rope)
The person you are trying
to reach is unavailable.
Why is his phone continuously off?
What does this mean?
Does it mean he wants
to end things with me?
Did I make a mistake?
Or did he find out who I was?
No, no. That's impossible.
Then what's the problem?
Does he have another woman?
It's me.
I want to ask you for a favor.
Oh my goodness! What are you doing?
Mister, don't do this!
Thief! Thief! Thief!
There's a thief!
Are you all right?
He just left.
Are you hurt anywhere?
Where do you live? I'll take you there.
Here?
Let's go.
- He must have left, right?
- Yes.
Mom!
- Mom!
- Oh, dear!
What's going on?
I was about to have my bag
snatched in front of the house.
What? Snatched?
Yes.
If it wasn't for this young lady,
I don't know what would have happened.
Oh, dear. She saved you?
Oh, I didn't save her.
All I did was scream.
I came over and hit him with my bag,
so he just ran away.
Goodness! How grateful!
- Come in.
- Yes.
Oh, no. I was on my way somewhere.
You saved my daughter,
so how can we just let you go?
Come in!
Yes! I have to pay you
for saving me. I'm so grateful.
Give me your phone number.
Oh, no. It's okay.
I just did the right thing.
It seemed like you were very shocked.
Take care.
Thank you.
- Good-bye.
- Bye.
My goodness.
How can there be such
a brave young lady?
She's pretty, too.
Oh, the grocery! Maid!
Oh, mom.
Seeing that Hee-dong didn't
come out, I don't think he's home.
What the heck is going on?
They'll never forget my face, right?
I had a good view of my future house.
Mom.
What kind of money is this?
Is it the money you got
from winning the trial?
No.
Mi-poong gave you that to pay
partly for the security deposit.
They must have felt bad
for not paying anything.
What kind of calculation is this?
They should calculate properly. How can
that back house be worth only $10,000?
My goodness!
Mom, that's not it.
Mi-poong's mother felt bad, so she wanted
to give this to you to pay partly for it.
She'll give you the rest once
her security deposit is returned to her-
She boasted about leaving the house
once she gets that money back.
How dare she try
to continue living here?
Mom! Where are you going?
Where is your mom?
Tell her to come out.
She went to work, so she's not here.
Let me ask you something.
Did you give this money to
Jang-go to pay for this house?
Yes, I did.
You did?
Oh, my.
You and your mom both
don't have any conscience.
How can you think of staying here
by just paying merely $10,000?
And you should have given this
to me personally.
What is your ulterior motive for
giving this money to my son?
Ulterior motive?
There's nothing like that. I just-
I don't want to hear it. When your mom
comes back, make sure you tell her.
This is far from enough.
And tell her not to
even dream of living here.
Make sure you tell her to move out of
this house once you get your money back.
Why are you crying?
Did I hit you?
Did I pinch you?
Why are you crying when
I haven't done anything to you?
No, I'm sorry.
Mom!
What are you doing to Mi-poong?
I already told you
what this money means!
- Come out.
- What's wrong with you?
- Let's go.
- What did I do?
Let go! Let go of me!
What's wrong with you?
Let go!
Lee Jang-go, what are you doing?
Let go of my arm!
Mom.
Aren't you being too harsh?
How am I being harsh?
They're the ones being too harsh!
Mom.
Don't you remember how we used to live?
How did we live
after dad's business failed?
I was young back then,
but I remember everything.
We worked a day to live a day, and
we worked the week to pay the rent!
Why are you bringing up the past?
You should know better
than anyone how hard Mi-poong
and her mother worked to
come up with that $10,000!
But how can you say
such hurtful words to Mi-poong?
Her mother was the one
who first broke her promise!
She was so prideful as she boasted
about leaving this house!
And now she's slyly trying to stay here!
It's not like that.
Mi-poong's mother said
she would look for another house
once they get
their security deposit back.
But they're not sure when
they'll get their money back,
so they were trying to pay
a part of it because they felt bad!
Was that something
they should be criticized about?
Hey. It seems like you were
too harsh this time, Geum-sil.
Just accept it with a good heart.
You're already stretching
the rule for them anyways.
Mi-poong.
Mi-poong!
Kim Mi-poong!
Where did she go?
(Jang-go)
So this is where that
North Korean family lives?
Yeah.
Did you talk to them? Aren't they scary?
No, I haven't even seen them yet.
I guess you haven't seen them yet
because there's another gate here.
This is nice.
- Right?
- Yeah.
Once the family moves out,
we'll re-do the wallpapers and
fix everything. It'll be a really
cozy place for us to live, right?
I love the idea!
- It's nice!
- It's nice, huh?
How are you doing?
I came here again because I missed you.
What are you doing?
What are you pulling out
from the garden?
Or...
are you looking towards the southern sky
while you're thinking of me?
Father.
How are you doing?
Mom, Yoo-sung, and I are doing well.
Father,
you're watching me now, right?
I miss you so much.
Where are you and Yeong-cheol right now?
Are you two still lying down
in Amnok River?
Even if you're tired, don't go
anywhere else and just stay there.
That way...
I'll be able to go find you later.
It'll get cold soon.
I need to put a blanket over you.
Father.
Look here.
Aren't you the young lady
from last time?
Sir...
(Blow Breeze)
I'll be able to see you
again if I come here.
- I'm Kim Mi-poong.
- I'm Kim Deok-cheon.
Jang & Ko's president?
He wants to scout Jang-go?
This is better than the
100 million dollar inheritance.
- Does she like Jang-go?
- No. They're just friends.
Mi-poong? Your friend's younger sister?
She must go to your house a lot.
Did something happen to Mi-poong?
What? She's missing?
They'll take care of it.
No, I have to go.
Jang-go!
Subtitles by OnDemandKorea