Subtitles by OnDemandKorea
(Episode 2)
That's the bus to the city. Run, Seung-hee! We have to get on that!
Oh, my! He's so manly!
Wow! It's so beautiful!
Jang-go?
What is it? Were you that touched by a headband?
I think I'll have to marry you later on.
What? You'll do what with me?
Well, in my country, you have to marry the person who gives you a headband.
That's the law of our country.
Oh, really?
Then I'll wear it.
Now I don't have to marry you, right?
How can you take back what you just gave me?
That's a girl's headband!
Give it to me!
I'll give it to you if you can catch me.
Give it back to me!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Why can't you do it?
Like this! How many times do I have to tell you to slide your feet like this?
Yeah, like this.
Jang-go, you're a stupid pumpkin head!
Hey, I'll show it to you properly.
Watch carefully.
Like this. Like this.
What happens if...
my friend's father-in-law passes away before his cousin does?
Then I...
I mean, my friend's family becomes distant relatives with his cousin.
Then they can't receive the inheritance?
In that case, they can still legally receive it.
I shouldn't be doing this right now.
Hee-dong.
Hee-Ra!
My precious babies! I cheer up just looking at you two!
Grandpa, have some porridge.
You, too, grandpa.
Oh, it's delicious!
Grandpa, have one more bite.
Oh, that sly fox!
Good job, sweetie!
Thank you.
It's delicious!
You're such a good dancer!
Good job, Hee-dong!
Here.
Here's five dollars.
Thank you, mom.
I'm going to go home and study.
Okay, sweetie! Do your best!
Do you best!
Okay.
You did a good job, too.
I'll give you ten dollars for being very cute!
Mom, this wasn't what you promised.
Come on. Your brother was happy with five dollars.
I don't have much money lately.
You don't have money when you go to those expensive
plastic surgery hospitals and dermatology clinics?
And if you keep breaking your promise like this, I can never do this for you again.
I have to be able to trust you.
You annoying brat!
I wish I could just hit her once!
Why? You want to hit me just once?
Why would I want to hit my pretty daughter?
Here.
The fifty dollars I promised.
I'm going to go watch a music program with my friend. I'll be late.
-You better not be!
- Cheer up!
That little brat!
Did our twins leave?
Yes.
Honey, look at this.
Elder finished his porridge. So did father.
You saved them both.
Thank you. You're the best!
Did you just realize that?
And Elder said he would help us out again. Everything is solved!
Really?
Yes.
It's all thanks to you!
To be honest, I was so scared that something might happen to them!
Dal-ho.
Honey, I'll make sure nothing bad ever happens to father!
I'm going to think of your father as mine and
do my very best to make sure he lives a long and happy life!
So don't worry!
-Chung-ja.
- Dal-ho!
Dal-ho, honey, you need to live with me forever, okay?
Okay?
-Yes, well...-Dal-ho!
I love you!
Oh, my.
Why is my heart beating so fast?
I'm sitting right next to Jang-go. I might get caught.
Gosh! Stop thumping!
A girl should have some pride!
Kim Seung-hee, you idiot!
What's wrong? Are you sick?
No, I'm not sick.
Why are you staring at me like that?
You're not sick, but why do you look like you just ate poop?
Poop?
I ate poop?
What does that mean?
How can you say that to a woman?
Forget it then.
And what? A woman?
You're not a woman. You're a tadpole.
Then am I a man?
Fine. You're a woman. Happy?
That's right. Now I know.
My heart is thumping because I like Jang-go.
It's not a heart disease.
I wonder if Jang-go's heart beats like this, too, when he looks at me.
Then that means he likes me.
I can't even ask him.
Oh! I know who I can ask!
There's a story about that music room.
If two people who are not destined to be together are inside the music room,
a ghost appears at exactly 9 o'clock to harass them.
Then what happens if there are two people who are in true love?
You'll hear music with fantastic melody.
Yes. I'll have to find out if Jang-go likes me, too.
If Jang-go likes me, too,
I'll be able to hear a melody that he's the boy fated to be with me.
What's wrong? We still have a long way to go.
I'm in big trouble! I left something important at school!
I have to go back to school!
School? At this time?
It'll be getting dark soon.
That's why you have to come with me.
Hurry!
What on earth did you come to find here?
I left an accessory for a a dress that I'll have to wear for the school festival.
Hurry up and find it. It'll be getting dark soon.
Okay.
Where did I put it?
Mother, what did the teacher say?
There was no group studying today.
Then Seung-hee lied to me?
She told me she would be going to a group study.
Nothing would have happened to her, right?
Of course not. If something had happened, we would have gotten a call.
Mother, I'll go look for her.
Why isn't Jang-go coming home?
Did something happen?
Of course not.
Don't be ridiculous.
That's why I said you should buy us cell-phones.
A call would do the trick.
Forget it.
Don't even dream of having a cell-phone.
Jang-go has never been this late without telling us before.
You still haven't found it?
Maybe you left it somewhere else.
No, I really left it here.
Oh, my. It's not here either.
Is it over there?
You already looked over there.
Why are you in such a rush?
We still have a lot of time. I'll take my time.
Maybe it's over there.
Yes! It's finally nine o'clock! The fateful time has come!
But why can't I hear anything?
What's this? Then is Jang-go not meant to be with me?
That can't be.
Oh my gosh! Jang-go! Jang-go!
It's a ghost. It's a ghost!
It's me! Are you all right?
Jang-go, there's a ghost!
It's me! It's not a ghost! It's me, Lee Jang-go!
What's this?
Jang-go?
Did you wear a ghost mask?
It wasn't a real ghost?
Sorry. Were you that scared?
How can you do this to me?
I really thought you were a ghost!
I hate you, fish boy!
I'm sorry.
But Kim Seung-hee, tell me the truth.
You didn't come here to find something, did you?
Then did you come here to check the legend?
Well, the thing is...
I wanted to check if we were meant to be.
Seriously?
What do I do with a little tadpole like you?
Hey, do you think this makes sense?
My friends told me it would work!
That's why you're a tadpole and not a woman.
It's all a lie. Let's just go.
Your family will be worried.
I don't want to! I can't go!
I'm not going to go until I hear music!
Then you're going to spend the night here because of that superstition?
Fine. You stay here by yourself.
Don't look for me when a ghost appears.
-It's a ghost!
- It's a ghost!
Save us!
Hurry!
Jang-go, what do we do?
What's wrong with this?
It was open, so why is it locked?
The ghost did it so it could eat us up!
What?
We're stuck in here!
Open the door!
But wasn't that the melody of fate?
No way!
That was-
Oh my gosh!
-We're stuck here! Open the door!
- There's a ghost here! Help!
Open the door for us!
Jang-go, we need to speak in English!
Oh, that's right!
- We're inside!
-  Help!
- Please help us!
-  Please open the door!
We're inside!
Help! Please help us!
Please!
Open the door! We're inside!
Your father isn't even here. What do we do?
Something definitely happened.
Seung-hee never did this before.
I talked to her friend Jessica who told me that Seung-hee said
she had somewhere important to go to and left by herself.
This won't do. I need to call the police.
Hello?
What?
Seung-hee was where?
The music room closet?
She was in there with who?
Jang-go, you're old enough, so how could you fall for this little brat's trick?
Are you out of your mind?
Mom.
You're being too mean.
I'm not!
Do you know how shocked I was after getting the phone call?
Nothing happened.
How would I know they would've locked the doors?
You're being so audacious after you scared me.
You little brat. I dare you to trick him like this again.
Then you're going to get in trouble by me!
Hurry up and go.
We have to wait until Seung-hee goes home.
She'll go home on her own.
Her mom said she would come pick her up.
But still...
how can we leave her alone here?
I don't want to see her mother.
Seung-hee!
What do you think you are doing?
Were you about to slap my son?
Let go!
Let go? Let go?
What did you do to Seung-hee?
How dare a young man like you act so indecently?
You piece of garbage!
You're a crazy woman.
Why are you trying to hurt my precious son?
What? A piece of garbage?
Were you saying that to my son?
Yes!
You piece of garbage!
What did you do to Seung-hee?
Mom! I was the one who asked him to come with me!
Jang-go didn't do anything wrong!
So why are you saying such rude things to him?
What?
What did you say?
Did you hear that?
Your daughter made my son come here because she has a crush on him!
Isn't that right?
Tell your mom the truth!
My friends said that you would be able to hear music if
you're in the music storage room with your fateful partner!
That's why I lied to Jang-go and brought him here.
What?
Hey, you should get hit, too.
Mom!
Mom, let's go! Let's go!
Is hitting others all you people know how to do?
Why did you try to hit my precious son?
Stop showing off and educate your child properly, you obnoxious woman!
What a devious little witch! How dare she try to seduce boys with lies!
Mom, stop it! Let's go!
-Let go of me! What's wrong with you? I have a lot to say!
- Let's go!
Let me ask you again.
Did you really ask him to go with you first?
Yes. How many times must I tell you?
How dare you!
No matter how immature you are, how can you be so fearless?
What would you have done if he had tried to do terrible things to you?
What terrible things?
Jang-go isn't a terrible boy!
How dare you talk back to me! I dare you to do that again!
Didn't you say you met father when you were my age?
You said you married father because you liked him ever since you were my age!
But why can't you understand how I feel?
What?
I like Jang-go.
He's so cool, and I keep thinking about him.
Is it wrong to like him?
What? Hey! What did you just say?
Don't ever say something like that again.
How can you like a South Korean boy?
If you say something like that again, I'll tell father
to send you back to North Korea by yourself! Got it?
Do whatever you want!
Oh my goodness.
What will I do with you?
Ms. Joo.
I'm Mi-Jung.
Kang Mi-Jung.
Oh Bok-soon's daughter.
How did you come here?
What about your mother?
My mother...
starved to death.
What?
My mother told me that I wouldn't starve to death if I go to you.
She told me to live with you.
My goodness.
She must have starved for days.
Mother, is she really a kkotjebi?
-(Kkotjebi: Homeless kids who go around looking for food.)
- A kkotjebi?
Then she's a very pitiful girl.
Quiet.
My clothes fit you well.
Mi-Jung, do you want to use this?
If you need anything, just let me know. I'll help you with everything.
I'm so angry!
I should have hit that little brat on the head!
I think I'll be too angry to sleep tonight!
Mom, that's enough.
Aren't you angry after suffering through that?
If you think from Seung-hee's mom's point-of-view, she has a right
to be angry. It was still my fault for sending her home late.
Is that your fault?
It's her fault!
I'm just saying.
Yes, he's right. She can think that way since
she's raising a daughter. It's different from us.
That's why I told you not to be close with those North Korean kids!
You told me to be friends with them.
I told you to pretend you were friends! Not to
stick around with them! This is why this happened!
From now on, don't even act like you know them. Got it?
I'll take care of that.
Oh my goodness! Where are you going at this hour?
That's enough. Let him be.
Who are you?
You're a thief! Thief!
Thief!
How dare you steal from us!
Mom.
I brought rice.
Mom, wake up.
Mom, wake up!
Mom! Please wake up!
Mom.
At least eat this before you go.
Mom, it's rice.
Mom!
Mi-Jung...
my daughter...
if something happens to me,
go find my friend Young-ae in Macau.
-You must live no matter what.
- Mom.
I love you.
Mom!
Take a bite of this before you go!
Mom, wake up!
Mom!
Right this instant?
Why all of a sudden?
Mother is in danger.
And...
I was commanded to return. Plans changed.
Okay.
How can this happen?
Shouldn't I at least say good-bye to my friends?
You and Yeong-cheol should go back to North Korea by yourselves!
Fine.
Then live here by yourself.
Fine!
I can live alone!
I'm sorry we have to leave you here, but we have no choice.
Find a different way to live.
Ms. Joo, I have nowhere else to go!
Please don't throw me away!
I'll do whatever you want me to!
So please take me with you.
Ms. Joo!
I don't want anything else!
So please just feed me!
Ms. Joo!
Mother, Seung-hee is gone!
You didn't come here to find something, did you?
Fine. You stay here by yourself. Don't look for me when a ghost appears.
-It's a ghost!
- It's a ghost!
Hurry up!
But wasn't that the melody of fate?
My friends said that you would be able to hear music if
you're in the music storage room with your fateful partner!
Hi everyone!
Good morning everyone!
Hey Jang-go. Did you hear?
No, what?
Yeong-cheol went back to Pyongyang. He dropped out of school.
Seriously?
Yeong-cheol's mother called today and said he's going back to Pyongyang.
Seung-hee!
Jang-go!
What happened?
Are you and Yeong-cheol really going back to North Korea?
Kim Seung-hee!
What are you doing here? Get in the car!
Mom, wait! I need to say good-bye to Jang-go!
I said you to get in!
Jang-go, we'll meet again!
You heard that music in the room last night, right?
So never forget about me!
Got it?
Seung-hee.
Good-bye.
Leave.
Seung-hee!
(2015 Seoul)
Hello, Mr. Kang!
Hello.
Did you prepare what I ordered?
Yes, it's ready.
-Hold on.
- Let me see.
It's right here.
Here you go.
My goodness! It looks very nice!
Lawyer Lee Jang-go.
(Lawyer Lee Jang-go)
Gods of heaven and earth,
our eldest son Lee Jang-go has opened up a law office.
Please look after him so he can succeed.
I pray for good luck.
Who is this woman?
The highlight of today's opening ceremony!
There will be a celebratory performance from our family's cutie!
-Lee Jang-soo!
- Hey!
Oh my goodness!
Hey, Lee Jang-soo!
You're crazy!
Crazy wench!
Mom! Not a crazy wench. A crazy jerk!
Jackpot! Jackpot!
-He's out of his mind!
- You're crazy!
Whatever!
All right, fine! Let's strike jackpot!
-It's jackpot!
- Mother!
Yes! Yes! Jackpot! Jackpot!
Honey.
After I lost you in a car accident,
I really didn't know how I would survive.
Our Jang-go played your part as the head of
the household and became an amazing lawyer.
Honey.
Are you watching right now?
Mom! Come here, mom!
Okay, fine! Our son hit jackpot!
(Seoul Law Office)
Father!
Father, please wake up!
I can't let you leave like this!
Father!
If you care for us, you can't leave like this!
Father, we can't live without you!
Father!
Please gain strength! Father! Have strength!
Father! Father! Father!
This isn't it.
Father!
Why does it have to be father and not Elder?
The heavens are so cruel.
If he lives a bit longer...
If he endures just a little more...
he would be able to live a happy life with us and the kids.
He suffered all his life.
How can he have such bad luck?
Why isn't Elder coming yet?
He needs to come so they can solve everything before father dies.
Elder, over here.
-Eok-man!
- Elder!
I'm here.
Eok-man.
Open your eyes.
What happened?
What's wrong with him?
To be honest...
we went bankrupt, so we lost everything, including the house and company.
Father collapsed because of the shock.
Bankrupt?
What are you talking about?
Then you should have come to me!
He felt bad for asking you,
so he told us to never tell you.
That's why...
Elder!
There's nothing I feel wasteful towards you.
I'll fix everything, so wake up.
Hurry.
Deok-cheon...
-Father!
- Father!
Eok-man.
Get up.
We lived a hard life all this time.
You can't just go like this.
Deok-cheon...
I'm sorry....
that I troubled you all this time.
Don't say that.
Don't say such things.
If you can live, I'll do anything.
So, Eok-man...
Eok-man!
My children. Dal-ho...
Don't worry about the kids!
I'm here.
Your kids are my kids.
Dal-ho, take care of Deok-cheon.
Be a good son to him.
Father! Father!
Father, don't worry about Elder.
We'll serve him as our father.
Eok-man, you can't go. Wake up.
Deok-cheon...
thank you.
I'll go...
home first.
Deok-cheon.
Please live...
and go back to our homeland.
No, Eok-man!
-Father!
- You can't go alone, Eok-man!
Father!
-Eok-man!
- Father!
-Father!
- Eok-man!
- Father!
-Father!
- Eok-man!
-Eok-man!
- Father!
Father!
-Dad!
- My daughter!
Wow! It's been so long!
-Good work!
- Thank you. Let's go.
Are you Joo Young-ae and Kim Seung-hee?
Welcome to the Republic of Korea.
We're glad you're here.
Mom!
You must tell us exactly what happened while you were escaping.
So?
You came to the Amnokgang with your husband Kim Dae-hoon leading the way.
Behind him were you and then your daughter Kim Seung-hee in that order?
Then...
there was my relative Kang Mi-Jung...
Kang Mi-Jung...
My son...
was the last one to follow us.
But at that moment...
What's that?
Stop right there! We'll shoot if you move!
Run!
Yeong-cheol!
Yeong-cheol! Yeong-cheol! Yeong-cheol!
Do you want Seung-hee to die, too?
Seung-hee, take Yoo-sung and run!
Focus!
Listen to me carefully.
This is my mother's ring.
When you go to South Korea, make sure you find my father.
My father's name is Kim-
Father...
Hurry up and run!
Hurry! Hurry up and run!
Seung-hee, don't look back and just run forward.
No matter what you hear,
don't ever look back.
Just run forward.
Got it?
Ms. Joo Young-ae!
-Ms. Joo Young-ae!
- Call for an ambulance!
Please wake up. Can you hear me?
Ms. Joo Young-ae!
Your mother Joo Young-ae told us that Kim
Dae-hoon's father, so your grandfather, is alive.
Do you know about that?
What? My grandfather?
She said your father told her while you guys were escaping.
No. My father never said that before.
That can't be true.
Joo Young-ae collapsed. Ms. Kim Seung-hee, you must come with us.
My mother?
(Repossessed)
Father.
Honey, we're in trouble! Hurry up and come out!
Let go of that and go out!
Father.
Hee-dong.
How can you still be here? We told you to move out a long time ago.
We had a death in the family.
No one in our family is in their right mind because my father-in-law passed away.
Father.
Can't you give us a few more days? Please?
That's why we let you stay here until now.
We can't give you anymore time.
Let's start.
-Make them leave.
- No, please!
We'll leave! I said we'll leave!
Father! Father!
Father.
You awful bastard.
Why were you in such a rush that you had to leave alone?
You said you wanted to hold hands with me and go to our homeland together.
Bastard.
You should have told me when something like this happened.
Look at you guys.
Hurry up and get up. Let's go to my house.
I only have you guys now.
So Dal-ho,
from now on,
let's live as if we're biological parent and child.
Elder.
Father.
We only have you now.
We'll take care of you very well from now on.
-All right.
- We'll really, really be good to you.
Elder.
Honey.
(Emergency Center)
Where are we?
Mom.
This is the hospital.
Are you okay?
Are you awake now?
Mom.
But what were you talking about?
You said my grandfather is here in South Korea.
My grandfather is our country's hero.
You said he died during the Great Nakdong Battle.
I don't think that's true.
Your father told me that we had to find your grandfather in South Korea.
Your father said your grandfather's name, but
I couldn't hear it because of the gunshot.
No matter how hard I try to remember, I can't.
What do we do?
Mom.
Why do you keep talking about that?
No! I definitely heard it!
Seung-hee, if we find your grandfather, we won't have to suffer here.
Let's find your grandfather.
Mom, please.
Seung-hee.
The bag.
Where is the money?
The bag your father gave us. With that money, we don't have to worry!
Mom!
That dirty wench Mi-Jung stole that money!
Mom, what's wrong with you?
Get a hold of yourself.
If you do this, what about Yoo-sung and me?
Mom, this is Seoul.
This is not Pyeongyang but Seoul!
South Korea!
-Mom, our names changed now.
- (Kim Mi-poong)
You said that we can live in a tiger's den as long as we focus.
Mom, I'll work hard.
So let's please not do this!
Seung-hee.
Mom!
Seung-hee!
Stop.
Seung-hee, you look graceful here. Practice that.
Wait for us!
You're beautiful!
-(Pyeongyang Art University)
- Seung-hee!
A mass of male students chased after me again.
It's so bothersome!
What if there are rumors of you being a flirt?
Even if such a rumor spreads, you have me, so don't worry about it.
Father, you're the best!
Look at her.
You're all grown up, but you still act like a baby.
Seung-hee is still a baby to me.
Geez, father.
I'm not Kim Seung-hee anymore.
I'm going to have a new life here as Kim Mi-poong.
-(2016 Seoul)
- From now on, the 2016 case 9-82033 for the
cancellation of the pay of the deceased family will be decided now.
Yoo Bok-Nam passed away on April 12, 2016 due to septic shock.
The plaintiff Ji Hyun-soo who was in a relationship with Yoo Bok-Nam
has deemed his death had been due to professional
negligence and applied for survivor's benefit.
However, Korea Workers' Compensation and Welfare Services has denied her of that.
Ji Hyun-soo had merely been his caretaker.
Because it is difficult to prove her relationship with Yoo Bok-Nam,
that's why we have declared it is difficult for her to apply for survivor's benefit.
We will submit her bank account that shows she received monthly payments
as evidence that they were nothing but a patient and a caretaker.
Your honor, I call for a witness.
You are the nurse who worked at the hospital Yoo Bok-Nam was in, correct?
Yes, that is correct.
I heard he has been ill in the hospital for a long time before he passed away.
How did it look to you?
Were Yoo Bok-Nam and Ji Hyun-soo merely a patient and a caregiver?
At first, they were just that, but before he passed away,
they called each other "honey."
Anyone could see that Ji Hyun-soo was sincerely helping him out.
Was there anything else besides the pet names?
For example, something they can prove their relationship?
Before Yoo Bok-Nam passed away, he wanted to have a wedding,
so our hospital did a small wedding for them.
I have a photo from then.
A photo?
Your Honor, I submit that wedding photo as evidence.
Your honor, this photo here is undeniable proof
that the two of them had been in a relationship.
On top of that, plaintiff Ji Hyun-soo
has taken care of Yoo Bok-Nam with love and care ever
since he got into an accident and until he passed away.
There's even a witness for that.
There is no stronger evidence than this.
Therefore, I strongly demand Korea Workers' Compensation and Welfare
Services to cancel their decision to not pay her survivor's benefit.
Hello, mom!
Of course I won!
I totally won!
That's great!
You better get paid properly for this one.
Nothing like sesame oil or old pumpkins.
This is just the beginning for you.
Geum-sil!
I'm at a high school reunion. I'll see you later at home.
Did I come to the right place?
Yes, it's here!
This is Chung-ja's house?
Yes.
Did she win the lottery?
You didn't know about that?
Are you serious?
It's not that kind of lottery.
You wouldn't know about it because you didn't come out to our reunions.
Don't get shocked. Chung-ja became the heiress of a 100 million dollars.
What? A 100 million dollars?
Yes.
Kyung-sook! Hee-Jung! You came!
Hello!
It's good to see you!
You got prettier!
Welcome!
Oh, aren't you Geum-sil?
Yes, Chung-ja. It's nice to see you.
It's been a long time.
-It's good to see you, Geum-sil.
- Mom!
There are guests.
This is my daughter, Hee-Ra.
Say hello.
Hello.
Hi.
I'm going out.
Good-bye.
Subtitles by OnDemandKorea
(Blow Breeze)
This is my husband, Jo Dal-ho.
He's not acting as a single man, is he?
I want to marry Joo-ri.
Aren't you over forty years old?
How dare you, you crazy bastard!
Joo-ri!
This house will be auctioned now.
This is our house under my name!
For how much longer will you call him Elder?
Call him father. Father.
Are you worried that I'll spill the reason why you're being so good to that old man?
Please help me get my security deposit back.
Lawyer Lee Jang-go? Jang-go?