Subtitles by OnDemandKorea
- (Episode 23)
- Your son and his family passed
away a few years ago while they were escaping.
However, your granddaughter is alive.
What did you just say?
Who is alive?
Your son's name is Kim Dae-hoon.
Everyone but Kim Seung-hee passed away
while they tried to escape a few years ago.
Kim Seung-hee?
My granddaughter is alive?
My granddaughter?
Chung-ja! Chung-ja!
Chung-ja!
Kim Dae-hoon? Kim Seung-hee?
Is he talking about Kim Mi-poong?
No! No way!
Are you okay? Get a hold of yourself!
Chung-ja!
- Mother.
- Don't touch me!
Get out of my face! I don't want to see you!
Get up. Get a hold of yourself.
Goodness. Chung-ja.
Dal-ho, get the airline tickets immediately!
Let's go to China right now.
I need to go find my granddaughter!
- Elder!
- Mr. Kim!
Elder, I'll get the airline tickets and
prepare everything, so please calm down.
- I have go right now!
- Goodness!
Mr. Kim, even if you go right now,
it'll be useless.
Your granddaughter disappeared and
we don't know where she is right now.
What do you mean by that?
Do you mean you don't know where my one
and only granddaughter is right now?
The only information I have about her is
that she's alive and somewhere in China.
I don't care how much money it takes. Mr. Yang,
please find her using any means you can!
I'll do my best.
Dal-ho...
what on earth happened?
I thought we would be able to
meet one day if they're alive.
Elder...
No.
I must get a hold of myself.
I must!
That way, I'll be able to
find my granddaughter.
My granddaughter!
Elder.
I'll do my best to find her.
Elder!
Bring me some water and Cheongsimhwan.
We have Cheongsimhwan, don't we?
What's going on?
What do you mean his granddaughter is alive?
Were you searching for his blood relatives
behind my back all this time?
How could you not say one word
to me about this? How could you?
That's not important right now! Elder fainted!
Father, here's water.
Oh, thank you.
How can his granddaughter be alive?
Mom, if his granddaughter
comes back, what will happen to us?
What else?
Everything will be over.
She'll be the owner of this house,
and you'll just be the distant relatives.
You guys will be on your own now.
- Goodness.
- Chung-ja! Let's go to your room.
Get a hold of yourself!
He should have told me he was
looking for his blood relatives.
Then I wouldn't have lived so foolishly!
I served him with devotion
like I was his biological child!
How can he search for his family
in North Korea behind my back?
How can he do this to me?
Dal-ho is the worst one!
Even if Mr. Kim wanted
to find his family, Dal-ho
should have just said he couldn't find them!
Right?
I really don't want to live with him anymore!
I'm going to divorce him!
Go ahead.
If Mr. Kim finds his granddaughter,
Dal-ho won't have any rights
over the inheritance, so what's
the use of staying with him?
Divorce him!
This is so unfair!
According to grandmother,
if the granddaughter comes back,
she'll become the
new owner of this house.
Kim Dae-hoon. Kim Dae-hoon.
Kim Seung-hee. Kim Seung-hee.
That can't be.
His granddaughter is in China.
Take this.
What is this?
It's money.
No way.
Come in.
I did everything you told me to do.
Already?
Yes.
I organized all the proposals within the past
five years from all the
market teams by seasons.
Wow! You're really good at working!
You're very skillful!
If I had known you would've been
so good, I would've made you
organize all the proposals
from the past ten years instead.
Excuse me.
May I go home now?
It's way past closing hour.
No way.
I, the boss, haven't left yet, so how
can you, my secretary, leave first?
All right.
Ms. Kim!
When was the last time you did
a big clean-up around here?
A big clean-up?
The cleaning lady vacuums every morning,
and I wipe down everything now and then.
Really?
I grew up sheltered, so
my respiratory system is very weak.
If there's even a tiny speck of dust...
What are you doing?
Get a wet mop and wipe everything.
Yes, sir.
Do you think I'll let you go so easily?
Not a chance!
Yes. Let's hold it in.
I came this far.
Kim Mi-poong, hold it in.
Yes.
Over there.
Here, too.
Good. And over here.
That's right.
I already wiped this spot.
Come on.
How dare you question your boss.
If I tell you to wipe it, you wipe it.
Hurry.
Why aren't you coming out yet?
Did something happen to you?
Is Sung-sik bothering you?
I'm in front of your office right now.
Do you want me to come inside?
That's from Jang-go, right?
How dare he send a private
message during work hours.
Jang-go has no manners at all.
Ms. Kim, put some strength into
your hands. Scrub it nice and hard!
That's it! Use all your strength!
You're doing great!
That's it.
Mi-poong.
Bang Sung-sik, what do you
think you're doing right now?
It's already past closing time, and
yet, you're still making her clean.
You're a funny one!
Mi-poong is my secretary, not yours.
Why would you care if I make
my secretary clean or not?
Mi-poong, give that to me.
It's past closing time.
If someone needs to clean up, you do it.
Let's go.
Jang-go, just wait outside for a little bit.
You don't have to listen to him.
Let's go.
Hey!
Ms. Kim! Mi-poong!
Prepare to quit! I'm going to fire you!
This wasn't what I had in mind...
Who is it?
Ms. Joo...
What are you doing here at this hour?
It's barley tea.
It's nice because it's warm.
It's similar to grandfather's ring.
No. I think it's the same.
But I don't see the character for
"Cheon" on it. Maybe I'm wrong then.
Why did you come here? No one will welcome you.
You didn't come out to the restaurant.
I was worried about you.
Why would you worry about me?
You were upset because of
my mother-in-law, weren't you?
I heard what happened.
You must have come here because you were scared
I would reveal your identity and harm you.
You don't have to worry about such a thing.
I really didn't come here because of that.
I just missed you, and I kept thinking
about how I hurt you and Seung-hee.
You came to your senses now.
Why?
Is your mother-in-law giving you a hard time?
She seems to have a terrible temper.
You got married to him because you wanted to.
What else can you do but endure it?
I'm okay.
I just feel like it's all my fault
that you're living like this.
The more I think about it, the guiltier I feel.
When I make money in the future,
I'll be sure to pay you back.
Are you all right?
Are you okay?
Your mother-in-law must be
giving you a really hard time.
By any chance...
did you get kicked out? Is that why
you're here at such a late hour?
No.
I'll be going now.
She must be having a really
hard time with her in-laws.
Kim Seung-hee, the granddaughter
he's looking for, is actually Kim Mi-poong?
That's impossible. Impossible...
Mi-poong.
Don't be mad. I said I was sorry.
Do you want me to stand by and do nothing when
I witnessed you being mistreated by Sung-sik?
Still, that was my work, and it was
something I should have handled on my own.
What am I supposed to do if I really get fired?
Let's use this chance to find
a different company for you.
How about it?
Where?
After I came to South Korea, I struggled
until I came into this company.
I couldn't even dream of
becoming a permanent worker.
It was a miracle I got into
this company. I can't quit on my own.
Sung-sik will keep on bothering you.
Are you going to put up with that?
I am.
To my family and me,
this company is like our lifeline.
I'll provide for you.
No.
Why not?
I don't want to give up my work
just because I like you.
Fine! Fine!
Instead, if Sung-sik
bothers you again, you better
not hide it and tell me right away! Got it?
And I'll meet Sung-sik separately on my own.
I'll take care of Mr. Bang on my own.
When the two of you meet up,
the situation gets worse,
and you guys end up
beating each other up!
Just let me handle my own issues.
Jang-go, you trust me, don't you?
Fine.
Mi-poong, you haven't
forgotten what I said, right?
No matter what happens, you can't be swayed.
Okay.
Where are you going?
You can go in through the front gate here.
I can't go through here.
Of course you can.
It's okay if you go in with me. Come on.
Come on.
Are you disrespecting me?
I told you several times
not to go through this way.
Did you think I was joking?
Get out. Get out at once!
Mom.
- Why are you just standing there? Get out!
- Mom!
What's wrong with you?
Lee Jang-go, what are you doing?
I'm sorry.
- Mi-poong.
- Lee Jang-go!
Mom!
Why are you guys shouting in the front yard?
If you have something to say,
come inside and say it!
What do you think you're doing
yelling at me in front of her?
Was it so wrong of her to use the front
gate when we live in the same house?
Don't you think you're being too harsh?
How am I being too harsh?
I didn't want to see her,
so I told her not to go through there.
Isn't it her fault for
not listening to my words?
Mi-poong is the woman I like!
She's my girlfriend!
What?
The woman you like?
Girlfriend?
What's wrong with you? What about Ha-yeon?
Mom, stop talking about Ha-yeon!
I'm through with her!
Jang-go, Ha-yeon is still waiting for you.
Ha-yeon isn't angry at you anymore!
Are you going to mess things up again?
Mom, please! Stop talking about her!
Jang-go, what's wrong with you?
Lee Jang-go, aren't you being too much?
How dare you talk back to
your mom who raised you all this
time! Are you sure you're
the eldest son in this house?
Up until now, you never worried me!
Seriously, what's wrong with you?
What do we have?
I want to make you a shade
you can be protected in!
How can you not understand my feelings?
Jang-go.
I don't know whose side I need to take.
Then grandfather's huge inheritance...
belongs to Mi-poong?
Why?
God.
God, if you're there, answer me.
Does someone like me not deserve to be happy?
God, if you're there, answer me!
- (My Rope)
- It's my rotten rope.
Hello?
Shin-ae, where are you right now?
I came to meet my friend.
What is it?
Something big happened at home.
Hurry up and come home. Hurry.
I heard you were home when it happened.
I can't believe my grandfather's biological
granddaughter is alive! Isn't it dramatic?
Dramatic?
My grandfather lived his whole life missing
his wife and family in North Korea.
Everyone else passed away, but I hope
he can find his granddaughter.
How can he say something so ridiculous?
Everything is being taken away from him,
and yet, he's really okay with that?
That's why I'm going to China
tomorrow with my father
and grandfather to help them
find his granddaughter.
I won't be here for a while. Will you be okay?
But Shin-ae, what's wrong?
Are you sick?
No, I'm just tired.
I'm going to wash up.
Sure. Since you're tired,
I'll pack my travel bag by myself.
Honey,
am I wrong?
Tell me.
I'm not, right?
I'm growing older, and I want to make a
sturdy windbreak for Jang-go and Jang-soo.
That's why I want Jang-go
and Ha-yeon to be together.
Later on, Jang-go will definitely regret it.
Don't you want to see Jang-go
and Jang-soo turn out well?
Can't you help me so that
Jang-go can change his mind?
I went to the temple and asked
your father what I should do about you.
No matter how much I think about it,
there's only one way to solve this.
Lee Jang-go,
think very well before you answer me.
Choose.
Choose either me or Mi-poong, that brat.
- Mom.
- No need to waste words.
Just answer me.
How can you ask me to
choose between you and her?
Both of you are equally precious to me.
We're equally precious?
So you're saying that you'll never
give up on Mi-poong, right?
Yes. I'll never give up on her.
Then I'll choose.
If you can't give up on Mi-poong,
I'll give up on you.
Mom.
Jang-go, get out of this house.
- Mom!
- Get out at once!
Mom!
Geum-sil! Geum-sil, what's wrong with you?
Geum-sil, are you seriously
kicking Jang-go out?
Geum-sil!
Lee Jang-go, get out!
Get out at once, Lee Jang-go!
Don't do this, Geum-sil!
Mother, Jang-go isn't my son anymore.
You just lost your eldest grandson, too!
What are you doing? Get out!
If you won't give up that brat,
I'll give you up!
Go ahead and live with that girl!
Do as you please!
You're not my son anymore.
I don't need a son like you!
Get out! Get out at once!
You horrible brat!
Are you happy cutting off our ties?
Fine! I'm going to watch how happy you
live after destroying our family like this!
Awful brat.
Mother, go in. Nam-yi, you, too.
- Go in! Go in!
- Okay!
Jang-go, go and beg for forgiveness. Hurry.
Mi-poong, I'm sorry.
Ms. Joo, I'm sorry.
Mi-poong, come here!
Mom.
Why are you making things worse?
How will you deal with cutting off their ties?
Do you think you and Jang-go will be
happy if you two get married like this?
This is why I opposed this!
Jang-go says he likes you now,
but how long will it last
after he threw his mother away?
No child can ever throw their parents away!
On top of that, Jang-go is the eldest son!
And even though Jang-go
turns his back on his mother,
you two will never be happy!
This is wrong, Mi-poong.
All you have to do is make up your mind!
Why are you being so foolish?
Why are you being like this, too?
Then what will you do?
What will you do when
his family is reacting this way?
Still, I can't give Jang-go up.
I promised him.
What?
Mr. Kim, have a safe trip.
I will pray for good news.
Yes, thank you.
Good-bye, father.
Be safe while I'm away. I'll call you.
Mom, you can't give my wife
a hard time while I'm away.
Then I'll fly back from China right away.
- Bye.
- Honey! Sweetheart!
If there is any news, make sure you call me.
You must!
I told you I would so many times!
Bye!
Have a safe trip!
Bye, father.
The granddaughter you're looking
for is right next to you in Korea.
You're going all the way to China though.
How pitiful.
What do we do now?
Now that father directly stepped in, it's only
a matter of time before they find her!
All my efforts are about to go to waste!
Mom, what if we have to leave this house?
Come on. China isn't a small country, you know!
It's hard to find anyone
in the streets of Seoul.
How will he be able to find her
in such a wide piece of land?
It'll be difficult for him to find her
in his lifetime, so don't you worry.
Your efforts won't go to waste so easily.
You're right, grandmother.
She might not be in China either.
Hee-dong says he hopes grandfather finds her.
This is all your fault!
Why else would his granddaughter
appear out of nowhere?
This happened because bad luck
like you came into the house!
Get out! Get out right now!
Goodness, Chung-ja!
What's wrong?
Why are you being like this to her?
No matter how angry you are, you shouldn't
be so rude to kind Shin-ae! Stop it!
Kind Shin-ae?
You don't know how frightening she is!
She's a defector! She's from North Korea!
But she lied to us that she was from
Sokcho and came into our home!
She lied to us all!
A defector from North Korea?
- Oh my gosh!
- Yes, mom!
Get out, you unlucky wench!
Blood! Blood!
Here.
I'll leave.
I'll leave!
Is it such a big crime to be a defector?
How dare you disrespect me when
you're living off of this house, too?
Even a worm will turn once it's stepped on!
And you keep calling me a defector.
We're from the same land
and speak the same language!
You shouldn't be like this!
And even if you beg me to live here,
I won't, so don't worry!
I don't have a bit of lingering
feelings for this house!
Is she out of her mind, mom?
Am I crazy?
I don't know if I want to stay here
even if they're nice to me.
I won't be a maid here any longer.
Why doesn't she realize that Hee-dong
will be the one to suffer if I leave?
Hold on.
Why should I just leave?
Even if I leave, I need to get my share.
If I find his granddaughter for him,
I can get five million dollars.
Won't I be able to get
at least five million dollars?
Yes!
That's it!
He'll be able to pay me five million
dollars for his granddaughter!
Yes.
If I want to sell his granddaughter
to him, I need definite evidence!
Goodness! This feels warm and nice!
Coming here makes my day!
I feel comfortable here, too.
If I'm home, all I get is a headache.
Geum-sil has an unhealthy taste for money.
Or maybe she's so tired
from raising Jang-go and
Jang-soo on her own
after her husband passed away.
She isn't her old self.
How can she be so brutal to him?
It's because she covets Ha-yeon so much.
I think Jang-go is being too harsh.
His mom really wants this.
Would it be so hard for him to marry Ha-yeon?
It's mind over matter.
Hey, you can't get over love so easily.
Why do you think there is such a thing as being
lovesick? People can die when they're in love.
But why is Mr. Kim late today?
He said he's single.
Is he a bachelor or a divorcee?
I should've asked him.
I think he's a bachelor. He's very neat.
Nam-yi, by any chance, do you...?
Hello.
- Hi.
- Hello.
But who is he? Your nephew?
No.
He's my son.
Son?
Won-bin, say hi.
Hello. I'm Kim Won-bin.
Hi.
What?
You were kicked out of the house?
Yes.
They found out I was a defector.
Still, how can you pack
your things and leave the house?
You should've asked for forgiveness!
You were wrong for lying anyways!
I tried to endure it, too, by being their maid
and doing everything they wanted me to.
What? Maid?
Yes.
But they won't treat me like I'm a human.
They purposely take the curtains
down and make me wash
them with my hands and
make up chores for me to do.
They disrespect me like I'm some
kind of criminal and hit me.
What? They hit you?
Is that true?
They beat me like I'm some kind of dog.
Look.
What's all this? How can
they do this to a person?
That's why I left home.
But I didn't have anywhere else
to go, so I came here.
As a woman, I couldn't go to a motel by myself.
Ms. Joo, please allow me
to stay here for a few days.
I don't have anywhere else to go!
Did you eat?
Wait a little bit.
Ms. Joo, I'm going to use your bathroom.
The bathroom is outside.
One of them belongs to Yoo-sung. Then
one of those two must belong to Mi-poong.
Ms. Joo, this won't do.
I'm going to go out for a moment.
The food will be ready soon. Eat before you go.
My back hurts so much.
I'm going to the hospital.
I'll eat when I come back.
Why? Does it hurt a lot?
Do you want me to go with you?
No.
I'll go by myself.
No matter how much they hate her, how can they
make her sick like that? Those terrible people!
What's going on? Why is Hee-dong's
wife coming out of that house?
Why would Shin-ae visit those
North Koreans who live behind our house?
- Hello.
- Hi.
Ma'am, do you know that woman
who came out of your house just now?
Why?
That woman who came out of
your house just now is my brother's wife.
Why is she coming out of your house?
How do you know my sister-in-law?
This is my grandfather-in-law's.
One of these belong to his granddaughter.
You can do a DNA test to find out if this
person is his real granddaughter, right?
A DNA test for a grandfather and
his biological granddaughter?
Yes. I want to find out if
she's really his granddaughter.
I'm sorry but that cannot be
found through DNA testing.
What do you mean it can't be found?
If you were looking for a biological grandson,
we can detect if they're related or not.
But in the case of a granddaughter,
we can't find out
if they're of blood relationship or not.
Are you serious?
Are you sure that
DNA testing can't prove
if a grandfather and his granddaughter
are related or not?
Yes. For women, we are unable
to find their biological grandfathers.
So what does it mean when
they can't prove a grandfather
and his granddaughter
are related through DNA testing?
Does that mean that anyone
can be his granddaughter
as long as she has
a different kind of evidence?
Yes.
That ring!
As long as I have Ms. Joo's ring,
I can be his granddaughter, too!
I can be grandfather's granddaughter
and the heiress of Winner's Group!
Oh, my head!
I must have gotten shocked after
Shin-ae left like that. Oh, my head!
But what will you tell Mr. Kim, Dal-ho, and
Hee-dong when they ask you where she went?
Goodness! I don't know!
That's not important right now!
Hee-dong will be so shocked!
Mom! Mom! Mom! Mom! Mom!
- Mom!
- Goodness! What is going on?
Big news!
Your grandma and I have a headache already!
Don't open your mouth! I'm tired already!
Mom, Shin-ae is a North Korean defector!
She's from North Korea!
What's this?
What's wrong?
Did you two know already?
Am I the only one who didn't know?
But why didn't you tell me this?
Am I really not your daughter anymore?
Where did you hear that anyways?
Is there a rumor
going around that she's
a North Korean defector?
It's not a rumor. A North Korean family
lives in the back of my in-laws' house.
But Shin-ae was there a while ago!
Your mom chased her out
after she got caught for lying to us
about the fact that she
was a North Korean defector.
Really?
No way!
Does Hee-dong know about this?
What about grandfather and dad?
They don't know. She deceived all of us!
Only your mom and me know.
This is totally a fraud marriage!
This witch! How can she fool my kind brother?
If Hee-dong finds out, he'll be shocked, and
he might try to jump off the Han River Bridge.
So don't blabber anything and keep your
mouth shut until I take care of this issue.
Poor Hee-dong!
That witch seduced your brother because
she coveted our family's inheritance.
Goodness!
We're about to go under
because of that unlucky witch!
This bitch!
I won't let her get away with this!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Mom, why did she have to come, too?
I know.
Oh my god. I'm so scared imagining what will
happen to us once father
finds his granddaughter!
I don't know what his granddaughter
is like, but imagine what
will happen once she gets married
and lives here in this house!
If she tells us to leave this house,
we have no choice!
Yes, you're right.
I really hope he won't be able to find her.
No! I wish she was dead and gone!
Wait a minute, Chung-ja.
Let's go find out if he will really
find his granddaughter or not.
Go where?
Is it true that she's alive?
That old man's granddaughter is really alive.
She really is?
Then is it true she's in China?
She's not in China. She seems to be nearby.
She's nearby?
Nearby where?
China is near here, too.
China is closer to here than America.
She's revolving around here.
Tell them to come back!
Their efforts are fruitless!
Their efforts are fruitless?
Is that true?
That's what I wanted! Fruitless efforts!
Whether she's near or far, please make
sure my father won't ever be able to find her!
Please! Please! Please!
Isn't there a charm that makes
sure they will never meet?
Is a charm not enough?
Do we need to have an exorcism?
Hey, you bitch!
- Hee-ra!
- Don't call my name!
What are you going to do about my nice brother?
How can you deceive us all
and come into our house?
Did you covet our inheritance so much?
What are you going to do about Hee-dong?
- What are you doing?
- Let go of me!
Goodness! What are you doing? Stop it!
If something happens to
Hee-dong, I'll kill you!
How can you downright lie
and marry my brother?
Go inside.
Hey. What's going on? Huh?
She deceived my entire family
by hiding the fact that
she's a North Korean defector
and married my brother!
What?
Your sister-in-law is from North Korea, too?
She got kicked out of our house,
so she's not my sister-in-law anymore.
Why aren't you eating?
I am.
No, you're not.
You're not swaying already, are you?
That's not it...
Both of our mothers are so upset.
You're not able to go home either.
Everyone is having a hard time.
I told you we have to endure times like this.
You can't become weak, okay?
Things will get better once time passes by.
But are you really not going to go home?
You should still go home.
Okay, I will. I was going to anyways.
- Jang-go.
- Yes?
Do you really have the
confidence to not regret this?
Regret what?
You quit Jang & Ko because of me.
If you go back to working in
a small office, you'll struggle again.
Mi-poong, I can settle down by myself.
Don't you trust me?
It's not that.
- I'm just worried you'll have to struggle again.
- Of course it'll take some time.
But it's meaningful for me
to settle down by myself.
I'll never regret this, so don't worry.
Aren't you going to eat?
I'm going to eat it all then.
Okay, I'll eat.
(Director Bang Sung-sik)
Is it Sung-sik?
Yes, it's him.
I didn't go to work today.
Will you really be able to handle him?
Go in first. I'm going to stop by the market.
Okay.
Mi-poong, get in.
Why?
I have something to tell you.
Let's go talk somewhere.
I don't have anything to say to you.
If this doesn't have to do
with work, please leave.
You're driving me crazy.
You're not the only one who can say
something. I have something to tell you!
Then tell me at work.
Good-bye then.
Kim Mi-poong, do I look easy to you?
Just get in and stop talking!
Don't do this!
Bang Sung-sik?
Kim Mi-poong!
Stop the car.
I said stop the car!
Bang Sung-sik.
Get out.
Mr. Bang, why are you doing this?
Why are you bothering me by
forcing me to come with you?
You made me like this!
Why do you keep making me
into a strange person?
You don't pick up my calls
or answer my messages!
I'm doing this because you're disrespecting me!
Who are you to make me
so pathetic? Who are you?
Mr. Bang...
I'm sorry for yelling at you, but I really
want to be a gentle man to you.
I don't want to yell at you.
If you knew how I felt,
why would I act like this?
I don't want to listen to this anymore.
I'll see you at work tomorrow.
You're not going anywhere!
You can't move one step
until I say you can leave!
What's your reason for
stomping on my feelings like this?
What am I lacking compared to Lee Jang-go?
Do I not have as much money as him
or am I not as good-looking as him?
And do you know how much this ring costs?
You're the first woman
I bought such a ring for!
But why can't you realize my feelings?
Don't do this, Mi-poong.
Take this ring back, please?
I don't want to.
What? You don't want to?
You still don't realize my sincerity?
Do you think you'll ever be able to
receive such a ring in your lifetime?
Like you said, I'm a woman who has nothing.
Don't like a lacking woman like me.
Find a great woman who suits you.
Bang Sung-sik!
- Jang-go, don't do this!
- What are you doing?
Go ahead and hit me, you jerk!
I'll just be beaten to death!
Hit me!
- Mi-poong!
- Jang-go!
I'm not going to forgive you! Damn it!
What's this? It's blood!
Gosh, Bang Sung-sik,
why do you keep getting hit?
Mi-poong!
How will you be able to face
Sung-sik at work tomorrow?
God, I'm already starting to worry.
I'll deal with it tomorrow.
I'm going to protest for him to
send me back to the marketing team.
What? Protest?
Are you serious?
Yes, I am.
Or I'll at least make him
sign a contract that
he'll never pull a stunt like
the one he pulled today.
You're so brave.
All right. As long as you think like that,
he won't be able to mess with you.
Cheer up, Jang-go!
Cheer up!
Eat a lot. You need to eat a lot
to be healthy to overcome this.
Yes. I'm fine. You should eat a lot.
I will.
Yoo-sung, you eat a lot, too.
Okay, aunt!
Should you call me aunt or auntie?
It doesn't matter.
He can call you whatever he wants.
I want to call her "aunt."
You do?
Sure, you can call me that.
Seung-hee.
Mom, what are you doing right now?
Well, I called you, but you didn't pick up.
I'll explain everything to you.
What are you up to?
No shame, no honor. How dare you
come here! Do you even have a conscience?
Aunt, what's wrong?
Grandma, Aunt Mi-poong is scary.
It's all right, Yoo-sung.
Mom, how can you be eating dinner with her?
Mi-poong, come in.
She's in a pitiful situation.
Her mother-in-law found out
she was a defector and
treated her harshly before she got kicked out.
How can I just let her go?
Mom, did you already forget what she did to us?
I didn't forget it, but what's the
point of remembering it again?
On top of that, she begged for
forgiveness and is trying to live a new life.
So Mi-poong,
let's understand her a little bit, okay?
No, I can't do that.
It's her fault for lying and getting married!
Why do we have to help her out?
How can you be so spineless?
Why would you let her inside the house?
She had no choice but to come to us!
She was trying to endure it,
but her mother-in-law
beat her! Her whole body
is covered with bruises!
I feel bad for her.
Fine. Do whatever you want.
Instead, she can only stay for one night.
You must send her away tomorrow.
No. If I take the ring like this,
they'll suspect me.
How will I be able to
take that ring off of her?
How?
I need that ring to grab the golden rope again!
Is that bean paste soup? It smells delicious.
It's soybean paste soup
with dried radish leaves.
Come and taste it.
It's hot. Be careful.
Is it good?
The seasoning is just right. It tastes great.
Mom, I'm going to work.
Why? Is there an emergency at work?
Aren't you going to eat breakfast?
I don't want to eat with her.
Mi-poong.
Don't ever come back to our house again.
When I see your face, I think about
how much we suffered in China.
I'll be back.
Seung-hee, I'm sorry. I was wrong.
If you're sorry, don't come back here again.
Don't resent Mi-poong.
Okay?
I won't. I hurt you and Mi-poong.
Serves me right.
Do you have a place to go if you leave here?
I should go back home.
I'm going to live as if
I'm going to die in that house.
Yes, you should.
Ms. Joo, thank you.
No problem.
Even if they treat you poorly,
if you act sincerely,
they'll recognize you one day.
On top of that, Mr. Jo is a good person,
so endure it for him and your husband.
Yes, I will.
What can I do? What can I do
to take that ring off of her?
Hold on.
This...
is for you to buy your mother-in-law's
favorite fruits before you go home.
It's fine. You can use it.
I want to give it to you, so accept it.
The bus is here.
Ms. Joo!
Thank you.
I either die or live.
Ms. Joo will live without that ring,
but if I don't have that ring, I'll die.
Mister, you can't lose that bus.
(Hiring)
Please don't let him find her.
Chung-ja, let's stop doing this!
I'm so tired! I can't do this!
Please fulfill my daughter's wish!
- I'm so dizzy.
- Please don't let him find her.
Goodness! My leg!
Oh, no! I forgot to buy your medicine!
I'm going to go buy medicine
before the pharmacy
closes. You can stay home by yourself, right?
Yes, grandma.
What can I do? What can I do
to take that ring off of her?
(Blow Breeze)
Isn't that a person? Her head
is bleeding! I think she's dead!
No! No! The ring wasn't
swept away by the rain, right?
I have to find that ring.
Tonight, my fate can change.
I've committed a grave sin!
Do you remember this place? I promise to
always make you happy and comfortable.
I'm Jang Ha-yeon. Who are you to call my name?
Ha-yeon!
Subtitles by OnDemandKorea