Subtitles by OnDemandKorea
No! No! No! No!
Wasn't gym class so annoying?
Hey, isn't that a person?
- Oh my gosh!
- What do we do?
Oh, no!
Mom, someone must have fainted!
Oh my goodness! Is that an unconscious person?
There's an unconscious person here!
- Excuse me. Ma'am.
- Her head is bleeding! I think she's dead!
Ma'am!
Oh my gosh! She's the woman
who lives behind our house!
- Mom, she lives behind our house!
- What? Oh my goodness!
Young-ae, open your eyes!
- My goodness! How can this happen?
- We'll call for help.
There must be CCTV around here, right?
Hello? Is this 119?
The ring...
Please remain there until I come back.
(Episode 24)
Hi, it's me. What are you up to?
Are you done yet?
No, not yet.
How did Sung-sik hold you back this time?
I heard he skipped work today
because he didn't want to see you.
Is he giving you tasks over the phone?
I'm organizing the market proposals
from the last ten years.
What? Ten years?
You did the ones from the past five years
last time. Now it's from the past ten years?
Gosh, that ridiculous scumbag.
So this is how he's paying you back, huh?
It's fine. I'm learning something,
and it's not tiring at all.
And don't call my director names.
What?
Geez. You're siding with him
because he's your boss.
Fine.
Tell me when you're done. I'll be waiting.
She's too nice.
Hi, aunt.
Mi-poong's phone number?
Why do you need that?
What? Her mother?
Mi-poong!
Let me do it.
She'll be fine. Don't worry.
Hurry up.
Okay.
Oh, dear. You woke up.
Can you see me?
Where am I?
Oh, you're Jang-go's aunt and grandmother.
Goodness, just stay down.
You got hit in the head.
You must be in a lot of pain.
Pardon? What...?
What are you talking about?
I got hit?
You don't remember anything?
Nam-yi and I were so shocked
to find you unconscious
and bleeding from your head on the streets.
Did you lose anything?
You didn't have anything with you.
What? My things?
What about my wallet? My wallet wasn't there?
Did you have a lot of money in there?
No...
I had about thirty dollars.
They made you like this
just for thirty measly dollars?
Whoever they are, they need
to be locked up behind bars!
I was on my way home
after getting Yoo-sung's medicine...
Oh, no!
Yoo-sung is home alone!
- Wait.
- Don't worry. We'll call someone for you.
Is that true?
Yes, it's true.
When I think about how she hid the fact
she was a defector and seduced my brother,
flames of anger burn in my chest!
It seemed like Hee-dong genuinely loves her.
Those people who live in the back are the
same as her. They all have black hearts!
Mi-poong seduced Jang-go, too, and
made him fall crazily in love with her!
Mother is right about everything!
Don't be so pessimistic.
Mi-poong seemed like a nice person to me.
Nice, my foot. How would you know that?
There's a saying that goes, "If you want
to know what he's like, look at his friends."
Those women in the back are the same
black-hearted women as my sister-in-law!
All right. You win.
You don't understand me.
Oh, it's my aunt.
Hi, aunt.
What did you say?
Okay, I got it.
Grandma!
Aunt!
Don't cry!
You're Yoo-sung, right?
Yes, I'm Kim Yoo-sung.
I live in the owner's house.
You've seen me before, haven't you?
Your grandma just called me.
She said something came up,
so she wanted you to
play with me at my house.
Really?
Let's go.
Hee-ra.
Yoo-sung.
Hee-ra, take him inside our bedroom.
I'll bring some snacks.
- Okay. Let's go inside.
- Go inside.
Jang-soo, what are you doing? Why are
you bringing that kid here at this hour?
Ms. Joo was attacked by a stranger.
She's in the hospital right now.
So how could I not watch over him?
What? Attacked?
Oh my gosh. Who did that?
I don't know.
Aunt Nam-yi and grandma were
coming home when they found Ms. Joo
unconscious on the streets
and took her to the hospital.
Your aunt and grandma?
Yeah. Aunt called me to tell me to watch
over the kid since there's nobody home.
So please understand, okay?
Goodness! What kind of terrible
person would do such a thing?
Hold on.
Jang-go didn't follow Mi-poong
all the way over there, did he?
Mom!
Mom, what happened?
I'm fine.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm fine.
Jang-go's aunt and grandmother saved me.
Thank you so much.
Besides getting five stitches on the head,
your mom is fine, so don't worry too much.
It's a relief that you didn't
suffer worse injuries.
I was so shocked that my heart
is still beating fast right now.
Aunt, what happened?
I think she was attacked by a stranger.
It's a relief that we happened
to be passing by at that time.
If she remained there, it wouldn't
have ended with just five stitches.
Thank you so much.
Goodness. You don't have to thank us.
We only did what was natural as your neighbors.
What's up with you, Jang-go?
What do you mean?
Someone could misunderstand you
as this family's son-in-law.
You could have just passed
on the news to Mi-poong.
What did you come here for?
What if your mom found out?
Aunt.
What? Did I make something up?
Anyways, since your daughter
is here, we'll be going now.
Take care.
Yoo-sung is playing with Jang-soo right now,
and he'll be sleeping
with me tonight, so don't worry
about a thing and just focus on getting better.
Thank you so much. I don't know
how I'll be able to pay you back.
Thank you so much.
Aren't you going with us?
I'm going to leave a little bit later.
Don't worry about him! Let's go!
Mom, what happened?
Well...
while I was coming back
from buying Yoo-sung's medicine,
I knocked out, and when
I woke up again, I was in the hospital.
I don't remember what happened.
Did you lose anything precious?
I don't have anything precious.
I just lost my wallet
that had thirty dollars inside.
What about your ring?
Did you leave that at home?
My ring? Where did my ring go?
They must have taken my ring! What do I do?
Mi-poong, what do I do about my ring?
Ring?
What kind of ring?
It's a silver ring.
My husband gave it to me
before I came down to South Korea.
It's very precious to me.
It's not expensive, but I must find that ring!
- Mom!
- Ms. Joo.
Where exactly did the accident happen?
Excuse me. Hold on.
Yes?
What are you doing over there?
I lost my earring, so I was looking for it.
Go home quickly. It's dangerous here.
Why? Did something happen her?
A lady was attacked by a stranger here.
So don't wander around by
yourself at night and be careful.
Oh, all right.
Thank you.
I think we can check the CCTV over there.
Can we check it?
You couldn't ask for worse timing.
It broke a few days ago.
It is being requested to be fixed.
Then can we check the CCTV that starts
recording from the pharmacy over there?
I think we'll be able to
find out something from that.
I think it's this punk.
The body figure looks like it belongs
to a woman rather than a man.
A woman?
No way. It looks like a skinny high school boy.
Women can't do such daring things.
Can you zoom in?
It was captured from too far away.
I can't zoom in any further.
And I think he thought the ring was a
good ring and took it so he could sell it.
If he found out it was a silver ring,
he would have tossed it away.
Then it would be impossible to find it.
(Little Tadpole)
Hey, Mi-poong.
How can it be raining? The ring couldn't
have been washed away by the rain, could it?
Is it here?
Yeah, it's around here.
Your mother was found unconscious here.
Here?
I have to find that ring.
It means a lot to my mom.
Mi-poong, it won't be here.
He would've found out it wasn't
a gold ring and just thrown it away.
What can I do?
It'll be fine. Don't worry.
Why are they just standing
there and not leaving?
That ring can't be washed away...
Please stop raining. Stop raining.
Mom, please stop the rain!
Mom!
He's adorable.
I know.
Kids are the cutest when they're sleeping.
You two should have a baby, too. Whether
it's a son or daughter, it'll be adorable.
Hee-ra, let's try harder!
Try harder?
You two don't know what shame is.
Mom, forget about that ring now.
If you keep thinking about it,
you'll just be upset.
How can I forget that ring?
It's the last keepsake your father left me.
Whoever did this will be punished.
If he needed money, he should have worked
for it. How can he do this to someone?
But Mi-poong, don't you think this is strange?
It's not an expensive gold ring.
It's a cheap silver ring.
Since it's night, he thought it was a
gold ring and took it so that he can sell it.
When I had that ring on,
I felt sturdy.
Now that I lost it,
I feel so empty.
I feel like I lost all hope.
Why would you lose all hope?
You have Yoo-sung and me.
We're your hope.
That's right.
I'm just glad you weren't severely injured.
Let's forget about it. From now on,
only good things will happen.
Yes, you're right.
Oh, my baby.
It's still there.
It's over. It's over now.
Lie down in the room. I'll set the blankets.
Goodness, no. I lied down all this time
in the hospital. My head hurts now.
Will you really be all right?
Of course I'm all right.
Mi-poong, go bring Yoo-sung.
He needs to go to kindergarten.
No, no. I'll go. If you go and meet Ms. Hwang,
she won't have any nice words to say to you.
- Yoo-sung.
- Grandma.
- Hello!
How are you feeling?
Thanks to you, I feel a lot better.
You had a hard time sleeping
with Yoo-sung, didn't you?
Goodness, no. We slept well and woke up well.
I feel so bad for troubling you, ma'am.
It's no trouble at all.
Don't say such a thing.
- I'm going to take Yoo-sung to the bus.
- Okay.
Yoo-sung, say bye to grandma.
Bye, grandma.
- How cute.
- Say good-bye to her, too.
- Bye.
He's adorable.
- Ma'am, it's shabby, but please sit down.
I'll make you a warm cup of tea.
- Oh, no.
I don't need tea. I just...
Speak comfortably, ma'am.
I would like to apologize on behalf
of my daughter-in-law who wrecked
your home last time.
Geum-sil isn't such a spiteful person.
She's just worried since
this concerns her son's future.
She did something she shouldn't have.
Young-ae, I'm sorry.
It might be difficult, but I hope you can
understand her from a mother's perspective.
Thank you for saying that, ma'am.
I heard you were going to move out soon.
Forget about all the awful things that
happened here and live a happy life.
Yes.
I made pine nut porridge.
I don't know if you'll like it though.
- Try it.
- Thank you so much. I'll enjoy it.
What? You're coming back
because father is sick?
Tonight?
They're coming today?
Oh, all right.
I'll call Dr. Yang.
Bye.
Is Mr. Kim coming back already?
It's not easy finding his granddaughter
over there. He's so distressed that he's sick.
I guess buying those charms and
bowing before Buddha worked after all!
Of course! We bowed until our knees
fell out, so they must work!
You better act like you don't know me later on.
Of course I won't.
I do feel bad for Mr. Kim though.
He should just take you guys
in as his children since
you served him all this time.
Don't you think so?
That's what I'm saying!
I can just be a hundred times nicer to him than
his biological granddaughter will ever be!
Anyways, is Shin-ae really gone?
There's no news from her ever since then?
She's probably contacting Hee-dong right
now so that she can come home with him.
Are you going to accept her again
as if nothing happened?
Are you crazy? Of course not!
If she acts without a conscience
again and tries to come home with
Hee-dong, I'll reveal all her lies
and officially kick her out of here!
What if Hee-dong forgives her and accepts her?
Then I'm going to kick both of them out!
Father and Dal-ho won't
forgive her this time either!
Only father and grandfather
are coming back today?
Didn't my mom tell you?
My father told her earlier.
I'm at the market right now.
But grandfather must not
have found his granddaughter.
Yeah, he didn't find her yet.
It'll take some time to find her.
Really?
He can't find his granddaughter
over there when she's here in Korea.
But what do we do? I miss you so much, but I
think I'll have to stay here
for the time being.
Oh, really?
I have something to tell you.
Something to tell me? What is it?
Never mind.
Since you're away doing something important,
I'll tell you when you come back.
Shin-ae, is something wrong?
Tell me if there is.
No, it's nothing.
You're doing something important
over there, so focus on that.
So grandfather is coming today, right?
Why is my heart racing so fast?
My fate can change tonight.
No.
No matter what happens, I will change my fate.
I will become his granddaughter
and the heiress of Winner's Group.
But what happened to Ms. Joo?
She won't be suspecting me, will she?
What if the police is looking for me?
Why is it so quiet?
Did Ms. Joo die?
Oh my god!
Why are you so shocked?
You came out so suddenly.
What are you doing here again?
What? You went back to your in-laws?
Yes, I think my mother-in-law
calmed down a bit.
That's why I came to thank you.
I bought beef, too.
Make some seaweed soup with it.
Thank you for worrying about me.
You chose good apples. Have some.
Here.
Thank you.
But what's wrong with your face? Are you sick?
No.
To be honest, I was mugged on the streets.
Mugged?
Who did that?
If I knew, I would feel a lot better.
He hit me from behind, so I feel so upset.
Didn't you report it to the police?
There are CCTVs everywhere nowadays.
You might be able to catch him in no time.
But the CCTV in the park happened to be broken.
The CCTV was broken?
I didn't lose much, so the
police just wants to let it go.
But I must find that ring.
I don't understand why they
stole such a cheap silver ring.
Ring?
Yes.
It was a ring my mother-in-law used to wear.
It was the last thing my husband
gave to me before he died.
It's a relief you weren't seriously injured.
Just forget about it.
Yes, I should.
Mi-poong told me to forget about it, too.
This neighborhood won't do. It's too dangerous.
Something terrible happened to you.
You should move away from here.
We already decided to move.
We already signed the contract.
Really?
You made a good decision.
The CCTV broke and they're going
to move away from here, too.
My mom is helping me from heaven.
Sung-sik, we need to talk.
Hurry up and say what you have to say.
Why do you want to talk outside
when the weather is so cold?
Sung-sik,
I don't want to fight with you anymore.
Let's stop.
Is that why you wanted to see me?
I think you're done talking then.
- I'll be leaving first.
- Wait a minute.
Then let me ask you something.
Why are you bothering Mi-poong so much?
I'm not bothering her. I like her.
You like her?
Yes.
I like her. I sincerely like her.
Sincerely?
Hey.
If you sincerely like her, how can you
talk about "sticking a flag" in her?
Fine. At first, I said I was going
to stick a flag into her.
But I said that when
I didn't know her very well.
To be honest, the strong resentment
I had against you influenced me.
What do you mean? Strong resentment against me?
It's true. We're friends, but you punched
because of one woman?
If you were me, would you
be able to forgive you?
So that was what it was about?
Fine. Let's do this.
Punch me once and let's end this.
Leave innocent Mi-poong alone.
Sung-sik, Mi-poong and
I genuinely like each other.
So hit me once and give up on her.
I'm begging you.
Don't regret this.
Okay.
Bite down.
Forget it, you jerk.
I'll be leaving first.
Lee Jang-go, I dare you
to mistreat my nice Mi-poong.
I'll definitely take her heart then.
Got it?
Bye.
This is to let you know that...
you have been transferred from the secretary's
office to the third marketing team today.
What's this?
Then I'm going back to
the third marketing team?
Mr. Bang...
the personnel division contacted me that I'm
being transferred to the third marketing team.
I understand.
I didn't want to see you. That's great.
Good-bye, Mr. Bang.
- I wanted to say...
- Thank you for everything.
You don't have to say
such heartless words to me.
Just pack your things and go.
- Welcome back!
- Congratulations for coming back!
Mi-poong, you're not going
back to the secretary office again?
Yes, I'll never leave the marketing team again.
Ms. Kim, don't we need to have
a party for Mi-poong's return?
Then let's have a party this Friday.
It's on me, so all of you have
to be there or be square!
- Ms. Kim! Ms. Kim!
- That's enough! Let's get to work.
Mi-poong, congratulations for
going back to the marketing team.
Don't make any plans tonight.
It's my mother's birthday today.
Let's go and officially greet her.
This won't do. Let's go back to the mall.
Why?
I don't think giving her a scarf
for her birthday is enough.
Let's buy her facial cream, too.
It's fine. It's the thought that counts.
It took us a long time to pick this one.
My mom will like it.
- Are you sure?
- Of course. It's fine.
What now?
No matter how much I think about it,
I think you should just give her the gift today,
and we should go greet her together next time.
Next time? When?
Today, I'm going to officially tell
my entire family that we're dating.
That you're my girlfriend.
To treat you nicely
because you're the woman I love.
Just stay by my side.
Let's go.
Here.
Hee-ra, what are we doing here?
I was thinking we should give mother
a washing machine for her birthday.
I didn't even bring any wedding gifts.
A washing machine would
be a nice birthday gift.
Besides, the one we have is too old.
A washing machine?
Why? Don't you have money?
If you don't have cash, you can pay with card!
- Well, I guess so.
- Look! Come here!
Wait up.
Jang-soo, what about this one?
It looks so stylish and nice!
I like it, too. It's nice!
Right? Shall we test it out?
- It works?
- Of course.
Squeeze. Squeeze.
Wow! It's going around and
around and around! Awesome!
Jang-soo, our backs and
knees won't hurt anymore!
Mother will love this! Let's get this one!
What do you think?
Sure. Let's get this one.
It's going around and around and around!
That's right. It should work like this.
Excuse me.
Please spread news about us!
Thank you! Good-bye!
You had so many customers
that you couldn't even eat until now.
Hurry up and eat.
I get full just thinking
about raising the sales.
Goodness. People will think this is your store.
Your boss's wife won't even be
able to work as hard as you do.
Shouldn't your boss give you a raise?
He said he would give me
a bonus if the sales increase.
But what should we buy for Geum-sil?
I was thinking of buying her cosmetics.
What about you?
I already bought it on the way here.
You bought long underwear again, didn't you?
How'd you know?
You bought it for the past two years.
You always buy long underwear!
Long underwear is the best during winter!
Hello!
Oh, hello! You're just on time!
We were eating kimbap.
Come and sit down.
- I feel so bad for troubling you all the time.
- Goodness, it's no trouble at all!
- Won-bin, come and eat with us.
- Okay!
But...
is Geum-sil not here today?
Oh, it's her birthday today, so she went
to eat lunch with her friends.
- It's her birthday today?
- Yes.
If you had told me beforehand,
I would have prepared a gift!
What? Why would he buy her a birthday gift?
Goodness, Won-bin, you eat very deliciously!
Does this kimbap suit your taste?
Yes, it's very delicious!
It tastes like the kimbap
my mom used to make for me!
Kimbap your mom used to make for you?
Doesnt she make it for you anymore?
No. She can't.
She passed away.
Who can it be?
Is Dr. Yang already here?
I don't know.
What are you doing here? Why did you come back?
Mother...
What? Mother?
Who is your mother?
Get out of this house this instant!
I'm sorry about what happened last time.
Please forgive me, grandmother and mother.
What are you trying to do now?
You threw a tantrum before you left! How dare
you come here now and try to sweet talk us?
I was having such a hard time, so I talked
back to you then, but I'll never do it again!
Please forgive me this once, mother!
You unlucky brat! Why are you
trying to stick around here again?
Get out! Get out of this house at once!
Mother!
Didn't you hear her tell you to leave?
Get out at once!
I don't want to see an unlucky brat
like you for another second!
- So get out!
- Get out!
Get out!
Shin-ae!
What do you think you're doing right now?
What's going on?
Honey. Father.
Grandfather! Father! I have committed
a grave sin! Please forgive me just this once!
What is she talking about?
What did she do wrong this time?
Father...
she's a North Korean defector.
She deceived all of us and married Hee-dong!
What?
A defector?
She fooled us all, Mr. Kim!
Dal-ho, she played with us!
Shin-ae, is that true?
Yes, it's true.
I'm sorry, father.
She lied to us about her name, age,
and hometown! They're all lies!
How can you do this to us?
We treated you so nicely!
I'm sorry, father! Please forgive me, father!
Grandfather, please forgive me this one time!
Hold on.
Shin-ae, get up for a moment.
Grandfather...
Get up. Let me see your hand.
This ring...
Grandfather...
It's the same!
Elder, what's wrong?
You...
Shin-ae...
Where did you get this ring?
This is my ring.
It's my ring that my grandmother
passed onto me.
This was your grandmother's ring?
Yes.
Then what's your grandmother's name?
My grandmother's name is...
Kim Soon-ok.
What did you say?
Kim Soon-ok?
Yes.
Then what is your father's name?
My father's name is Kim Dae-hoon.
Kim Dae-hoon?
Are you sure his name is Kim Dae-hoon?
Yes.
Shin-ae, you...
Then what's your name?
I'm Park Shin-ae.
Is that your real name?
You said you lied about your name, too.
What's your real name?
What's your real name that
you used in North Korea?
Seung-hee.
Kim Seung-hee.
What? Kim Seung-hee?
Kim Seung-hee. Kim Seung-hee.
Kim Seung-hee.
Kim Dae-hoon.
Kim Soon-ok.
What on earth is going on, Dal-ho?
- Grandfather!
- Father!
- Elder!
- Oh, no!
- What do we do?
Chung-ja, what do we do?
Jang-go.
What's wrong?
I don't think this is right.
We'll greet her next time.
I don't think I should be there today.
If my mom says something mean to you,
we'll just run away together.
This is something we have
to go through anyways.
Let's have courage.
You can do it, right?
Ha-yeon...
This is super expensive! It's a mink coat!
Geum-sil, try it on!
I don't know if I can accept
something so expensive...
Of course you can! Try it on!
Try it.
Mother, you look like a rich madam!
I know! They say clothes
make the woman. My, my.
I'll buy it for you on your birthdays, too,
randmother and Aunt Nam-yi.
Really?
Goodness! For us, too?
Why isn't Jang-go coming?
I know.
- It's so pretty.
- He's here.
- Jang-go!
- Hi!
- Hello.
What are you doing here? Who invited you here?
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
We came to congratulate you for your birthday.
- Congratulate me?
- Yes.
Let's go in.
This is a present from Mi-poong.
A present?
Your present to me is to disappear.
Your present to me is leaving Jang-go's side.
Mom.
- Aren't you being too harsh to someone
who came to congratulate you?
- Congratulate me?
Is her way of congratulating me forcing
her way to my birthday party and ruining it?
Do you have a brain or what?
You're so stubborn.
Just a few days ago,
you got a ring from a wealthy man.
How dare you show up here with Jang-go!
- Mom!
- What?
Did I say something wrong?
Everyone listen carefully.
The woman I love is Mi-poong.
So don't call Ha-yeon to events like this one.
Hey, Jang Ha-yeon, this is wrong, isn't it?
I hope you won't make anymore
uncomfortable situations like this again.
Lee Jang-go!
How can you be so rude to someone I invited?
Fine.
We weren't invited, so we'll leave.
Happy now?
Jang-go, wait.
This is the last time I'm going to say this.
If you leave this house with her,
we're really over.
You won't have another chance again.
A chance?
What chance?
Ha-yeon, you must think you
have something great.
But that might be nothing at all.
And if I don't want it, it's not a chance.
Got it?
Let's go.
Lee Jang-go, stop right there!
Ms. Hwang, I can't do this anymore.
Good-bye.
Ha-yeon! Ha-yeon! Ha-yeon!
What do I do?
What's going on?
Seems like she still  can't give up
on that wealthy family's daughter.
Shin-ae is Mr. Kim's
one and only blood relative?
Right?
No, mom! That'll never happen!
Such a bat-like witch can't be
father's granddaughter!
Then what's with the ring?
The ring is fake! Everything is fake!
Fake! This can't be true!
But why haven't you been
wearing that ring all this time?
Pardon?
If you had been wearing that ring,
he would've recognized you at once.
Last time, you found his ring for him, too.
Why didn't you notice the ring then?
I just thought it was a similar ring.
I never imagined that such
a deep story was behind it.
And even if I wanted to wear it
every day, it's too big for my finger.
That's why I didn't wear it all this time.
To be honest, this ring
was too big for me that
I left it in my suitcase and
forgot about it all this time.
But then mother found out I was a defector.
When grandfather, Hee-dong, and you were
all gone, she told me to leave the house.
I was packing my things when I saw this ring.
Seeing this ring...
made me think of my grandmother and father.
I thought of my mom and
big brother, too. That's why I wore it.
I just asked you
because I was fascinated by the
unexpected turn of events,
so don't be offended.
But...
why is your name Park Shin-ae?
Your name isn't Kim Seung-hee.
Your last name isn't Kim either.
Oh, that?
Well... my father was in
a high position in North Korea.
If I use my real name, I could be
in danger, so he told me to never use it.
Dal-ho.
Yes.
From now on...
we'll never use that name.
Many North Koreans live in South Korea.
Something...
terrible might happen...
so we'll all forgot about it.
It'll be better for us to live that way.
Yes, sir. I understand.
You must have had a hard time
coming down here and living on your own.
Grandfather...
Yes, my granddaughter.
My one and only blood relative.
Honey. Sweetheart.
How can you tell she's father's
granddaughter with just one ring?
This is wrong. This is ridiculous.
There's DNA testing.
Shouldn't you do that first?
Tell father to do the DNA testing first!
Don't just believe her right away!
Do you remember this place?
Do you remember what you said here, too?
What I said here?
You said it was the first time you felt like
a Seoul citizen after coming to South Korea.
You said it was the first time
you felt relaxed and happy.
You said Yeong-cheol would be thankful to me.
Mi-poong, I'm sorry about today.
I was thoughtless.
I was supposed to take you
after being blessed by my family.
Just wait a little bit.
Instead, I'll make sure you'll be happy and
relaxed by my side for the rest of your life.
Jang-go...
I'll get blessings from both our mothers...
and then...
Let's get married.
You'll marry me, won't you?
Give me your hand.
It's pretty.
Who is this?
Hello?
I'm Jang Ha-yeon.
Ha-yeon...
What is it?
You told me that you would stop liking Jang-go.
Are you drinking right now?
Hey.
Just answer my question.
Did you or did you not say that?
Ha-yeon...
Come here right now.
Come and give me an excuse or an explanation.
Hey! Why aren't you answering me?
Come right now!
Where are you right now?
Give it to me.
Jang Ha-yeon, if you have
something to say, call me.
Put Kim Mi-poong on the phone.
You're very drunk.
Go home.
Jang-go, how can you just hang up on her?
You don't have to answer. She's really drunk.
Hi, Ha-yeon. It's me.
All right. I'll come right now.
Jang-go, go home first.
I'm going to go see Ha-yeon.
Then I'll go. It'll be better that way.
Ha-yeon.
How ridiculous.
She's really pissing me off.
Did I tell you to come?
I won't let her get away with this.
Hey. Get a hold of yourself.
How dare you touch me!
Ha-yeon.
Don't say my name.
Who do you think you are?
Let's go. I'll take you home.
Lee Jang-go.
Where are your eyes?
How can you have such low taste for women?
You think you're so special
because I like you, huh?
Don't make me laugh.
I hate you now.
But the heartbreak you gave me...
I'll always remember that.
I'll never forget it.
Ha-yeon.
- Ha-yeon.
- Let go!
I have no business with you!
I need an explanation from Kim Mi-poong.
I won't let her get away with this.
Ha-yeon!
- Please prepare a CT scan.
- Hurry!
Hurry! Hurry!
Dad! What do I do?
Let go of me!
My legs won't move!
Let go! Let go of me!
- Dad!
- Ha-yeon...
My legs! My legs won't move!
Let go! My legs won't move!
(Blow Breeze)
I want to marry Jang-go.
Eventually, Jang-go will do
what his mom wants him to do!
Please don't tell Jang-go.
Can't you return my legs to normal?
In three months, it'll be my world.
She either stole that ring or made it!
When are you doing the DNA test?
DNA test?
Did your grandmother ever talk to you about me?
- Sweetie.
- Grandfather, I'm sorry.
It was all a lie?
I'll give him a divorce
if that's what he wants!
Subtitles by OnDemandKorea