Subtitles by OnDemandKorea
(Episode 25)
Doctor, what's wrong with
my daughter? She's okay, isn't she?
You said her exam results were fine.
As I said before, her MRI test and
electromyography results came out fine.
Due to the accident, she seems to
be suffering from spinal cord injury.
We'll have to wait and see, but she
may be paralyzed from the waist down.
What do you mean she might
be paralyzed from the waist down?
Do you mean she won't
be able to walk again?
We'll have to wait and see.
- Geum-sil, that way.
- What on earth is going on?
If my daughter's life ends, so will yours.
I won't let you get away with this.
Jang-go, what happened?
What do you mean Ha-yeon got
into an accident because of you?
Lee Jang-go, say something!
Mom...
What do we do about Ha-yeon?
What's going on?
You were fine when you were at my house
a few hours ago! Why are you like this now?
- My legs...
- Geum-sil.
My legs won't move.
I can't feel anything!
Mother, what do I do?
Ha-yeon, don't cry.
It's times like this you need to get your
head on straight and conserve your energy.
Mother, how will I live now?
It would be better to die rather
than to lie down like this all my life.
I can't feel anything. I can't walk.
So what's the point of living?
Ha-yeon, you will get better.
You will be able to walk.
You will be all right!
That's right, Ha-yeon.
You just have to get treatment.
You'll be fine.
Jang-go, get out. Get out!
I don't want to show
this side of myself to you.
I said get out!
Yes, Jang-go. Go outside.
He's not answering his phone.
He's not home yet.
Perhaps...
No. Nothing happened.
Jang-go, I came home right now.
What happened?
I can't get in touch with you.
Are you still with Jang Ha-yeon right now?
Call me as soon as you get this message.
Why are you so late?
Here. Have some hot ginger tea.
Thanks, mom.
Where did you get this ring?
Did you get this from Jang-go?
Mom, Jang-go proposed to me.
I promised to marry him.
What?
Marry?
His family is against you!
Do you think you can still marry him?
Did you forget how his mother treated you?
Give that ring back to Jang-go immediately!
Mom, even though it'll be tiring
for me, I want to marry him.
Jang-go said he would get permission.
Permission?
Do you think that'll happen?
His family will never be able
to give up on Ha-yeon.
Mi-poong, get a hold of yourself! In the end,
Jang-go will do what his mom wants him to do!
No.
I trust Jang-go.
Even when I'm holding your hand,
I can't tell if I'm dreaming or not.
Tell me about your grandmother.
About my grandmother?
Did she ever talk about me?
I only saw Seung-hee's grandmother
once when I was little. What do I do?
What's wrong? Does your head hurt again?
I'm okay. It's bearable.
Shouldn't you go to the hospital?
When I think about the times before I escaped,
my head hurts, and I get dizzy and nauseous.
When you escaped?
We arrived safely at Amnok River.
All we had to do was cross that river...
but we got caught by the border guards.
Bullets rained down on us.
When I came to my senses again,
my dad, mom, and brother were all dead.
After that, I don't remember
how I crossed the river by myself.
Since then, I can't remember the past.
You lost your family right
in front of your eyes.
So how can your mind be sound?
My poor baby.
Grandfather.
I think I was alive all this time
so that I can meet you.
So, sweetheart, from now on,
don't worry about anything, okay?
Good.
The only evidence he has is that ring,
but it's like he found
his biological granddaughter already!
What's wrong with him?
I know.
What is he going to do if they do a DNA
test and she's not his granddaughter?
I know!
But mom, if she really is
his biological granddaughter,
then what happens with her and Hee-dong?
I have no idea what is going on!
If that's true, then don't
they need to get divorced?
Cousins up to three times removed
can't get married to each other.
Shin-ae and Hee-dong are exactly
cousins three times removed!
Mom, is that true?
Yes! That's what our country law states!
Mom, aside from everything else,
what do we do about Hee-dong?
Poor Hee-dong!
How can you believe that she is father's
granddaughter with just one ring?
There's DNA testing.
Did you contact Hee-dong?
Yes. He'll be coming back today.
Don't tell Hee-dong.
I'll talk to him when he comes.
When he comes, I'll tell him myself.
All right.
It might be better for you to tell him.
But father, when are you
going to do a DNA test?
DNA test?
You know, the test that lets you
find out if you're truly related
to each other or not by using
things like hair and nails.
Yes, father. That would
be the most efficient way.
Forget it.
I'm sure she's my granddaughter,
so why would I do a test?
What can be better proof than the ring?
No, grandfather. Let's do the test.
I'll feel more comfortable that way.
Yes, Elder, I think that would be best.
Yes. Let's do that, grandfather.
All right.
If it's what you want, we'll do it.
Sure. Let's do that.
Grandfathers and their
granddaughters can't be checked
if they're biologically related to each other?
Why not?
In this case, Shin-ae's father
would need to come
and be tested to check if
he's related to Mr. Kim,
and then we can
connect their relationships
to check if Shin-ae and Mr. Kim are related.
But with just these two people,
we can't prove if they're related or not.
My father can't come here.
He passed away.
This doesn't make any sense!
What do you mean their relationship
can't be determined if her father isn't here?
Please do something about this!
As I have just explained, it isn't possible.
Shin-ae, let's go.
Okay.
Honey, this is ridiculous!
How can a grandfather and his
granddaughter not be able to be checked?
Even if they can't prove their
relationship through DNA testing,
is father still going to
accept her as his granddaughter?
No, right?
That's enough.
That's up to Elder to decide.
This is ridiculous!
Why can't I get in touch with him?
Something must have happened.
Okay, I'll just look around!
Excuse me.
Are you talking to us?
Yes.
I can't get in touch with Jang-go. I was
wondering if something happened to him.
Did Jang-go call home last night?
- The thing is...
- Jang-soo, stay quiet.
How is that any of your business?
You have nothing to do with Jang-go.
And don't come into our yard.
I'll get in trouble if
my mother-in-law finds out!
- Hee-ra, come on.
- Did I say something wrong?
- What's going on? Are you two fighting?
- Grandmother! No, we're not!
Goodness.
Why didn't you contact us?
How is Ha-yeon doing?
Is she okay?
No, she's not.
Poor Ha-yeon. She may
never be able to walk again.
What? Is that true?
Goodness. What is going on?
Why did she have to
get into an accident
right in front of Jang-go?
I know.
Which hospital is she at? I'll go visit her.
Hatsal Hospital.
But mom, it's better
if you don't go right now.
Ha-yeon and Geum-sil
were crying all night long.
Jang-go is out of it, too.
Goodness. What is going on? What do we do?
Go in. It's cold.
Go inside.
All of you must be shocked and in disbelief
because Shin-ae suddenly
became my granddaughter.
However, if you doubt her as my real
granddaughter and hurt her again,
I won't forgive you.
Do you understand, Chung-ja?
Yes, father.
And Dal-ho...
Yes.
Now that Shin-ae is my granddaughter
and your daughter-in-law,
wouldn't it be better for you
and me to become in-laws?
Of course, Elder...
I mean...
Mr. Kim.
I'll explain this matter to Hee-dong well,
so don't worry about anything.
What does he mean he wants to be in-laws?
And why is Dal-ho calling him Mr. Kim
like we're complete strangers?
Come on! My arm is about to pop out!
Why are you so strong?
Your arm is not the problem right now!
What does he mean he wants to become in-laws?
It's like he wants to become strangers
with us! And yet, you say okay?
You should've said no!
How can relatives become in-laws?
Do you think that makes any sense?
Well...
And can we become in-laws just
because he wants to be in-laws?
Even though his word is law in this house,
there's something called the
Family Registration Act! This is impossible!
Honey, calm down and listen to me.
Honestly, I was going to tell you
last night, but I thought it would be
best if I told this to you when
Hee-dong was here, so I didn't tell you.
No! I'm not going to
be in-laws with him!
I'll make those two divorce if I have to!
I'll never become his in-law!
To be honest, in-laws are
complete strangers. We need to be
distant relatives so that we can
have the right of inheritance.
But you want us to give that up?
Distant relatives, my foot!
Right of inheritance, my foot!
We're not related to Mr. Kim by blood at all!
What are you talking about?
You keep calling him Mr. Kim!
Because we're not related at all!
We're not related at all?
How can we not be related at all?
He's cousins with your late father!
He's not!
My father...
The truth is...
he was adopted.
He's not my grandfather's biological son.
That's why we're not distant relatives at all.
What?
Your father was adopted?
That's why I was telling you
not to be greedy all this time.
We should just be grateful
he treated us like his relatives!
Don't even think of getting one bean from him!
Now do you understand
why I couldn't tell you the truth?
We were complete strangers?
So what?
We're living off of our in-laws?
Hee-dong is living in his wife's home?
If Shin-ae decides to divorce Hee-dong...
we'll become beggars.
Ms. Jang, you shouldn't do this!
Please calm down!
Let go of me! I don't have
a reason to live anymore!
Why do I have to suffer through this?
What did I do so wrong?
- Please stop her!
- I hate this!
- Ha-yeon!
Calm down.
Ha-yeon.
Can't you return my legs to
the way they were before?
You got a lot of nerves
showing up your face here.
Do you know what happened because of you?
Jang-go and Ha-yeon's bright
future is ruined because of you!
- Mother.
- Oh, I see how it is. Did you come to see how
Ha-yeon is after she got into
an accident because of you?
Fine.
You came all the way here. You should
go and see what you just caused!
Let's go see poor Ha-yeon who
became half-paralyzed because of you!
- Let's go see her!
- Mother, it's not that!
I'm sorry.
That's why you should have
broken up with him when I told you to!
Why are you sticking to my son like
a leech and creating all this chaos?
If it hadn't been for you,
they would've been in
England by now, and none
of this would've happened.
This is all because of
your greed! It's all your fault!
You horrible wench!
How much more of this
frozen time has to pass by?
In your arms, in my heart
You used to live
I loved and wanted you
Because I live inside your memories
In the memory that spreads inside of me
You always protect my side
Forever
Father, are you going somewhere with Shin-ae?
Yes, I am.
But Chung-ja...
Yes, father?
You must have heard everything from Dal-ho.
Now that we're in-laws,
change the way you address me.
Oh, yes, father...
I mean, Mr. Kim.
Good.
Understand that this is all for
the best for Shin-ae and Hee-dong.
From now on, be careful.
- Let's go.
- Yes, grandfather.
Good-bye, mother.
My goodness!
How can he tell you to
change the way you address
him just because he found his granddaughter?
How can he be so cold? Oh my god!
Chung-ja!
Chung-ja.
Get up and drink this.
Here. This is honey water. Here, here.
Goodness. You need to keep up your spirits.
You don't know how that old man will change!
What's the point of keeping up my spirits?
There's nothing I can do now.
I can't believe my late
father-in-law was adopted!
We're not distant relatives anymore!
That's why Dal-ho should have grabbed the
chance to become Mr. Kim's adopted son!
This problem wouldn't be happening then.
I know!
I hate Dal-ho more than father-
I mean, Mr. Kim!
The fortune-teller was right!
I was making fruitless efforts all this time!
Goodness. But would
he really chase you out after
all these years you've been living together?
Anyways, Hee-dong is the husband
of his one and only granddaughter!
I guess.
All you can do now is to be good to Mr. Kim so
that Hee-dong and Shin-ae live well together.
If they get a divorce, then you'll
really be holding onto false hope!
So what now?
I have to serve two people now.
Now I have to serve my own daughter-in-law.
Mom, how did I end up this way?
Soon-ok.
My son Dae-hoon whom I've never seen before.
Are you watching?
I met Kim Seung-hee- I mean Park Shin-ae.
So don't worry.
I'll live a long time so that I can
set up a good place for Shin-ae.
Grandmother.
Mom. Dad.
I met grandfather.
Don't worry anymore.
I think he's completely
acknowledging me as his granddaughter now.
Thanks to this lucky ring.
- Look who it is.
- Mr. Kim!
- Hello.
- Hi.
It's been a long time!
But did you come here
because something awful happened?
No! I took the bus and somehow ended up here.
Oh, I see.
Did you come alone today, too?
No. Today I came with my granddaughter.
Oh, with your granddaughter?
She went to the restroom right now.
When she comes back, let's go
to the coffee shop and drink coffee.
Oh, no! You came with your granddaughter.
You can buy coffee for me next time.
It's fine!
- Have you been doing well?
- Yes.
Isn't that Mi-poong? I mean, Seung-hee?
What's going on?
How are my grandfather and Mi-poong together?
How do they know each other?
Mi-poong won't be able to
recognize grandfather's ring, right?
What's wrong, Shin-ae?
What?
Grandfather, I don't feel well.
Hurry up and come.
I'll be inside the car first.
You're not feeling well? Okay.
Oh, no. My granddaughter is feeling sick.
I'll buy you coffee next time.
- Sure. Good-bye, Mr. Kim.
- Bye.
- See you next time.
- Okay.
Grandfather said "Shin-ae"
in front of Mi-poong.
She wouldn't have realized it was me, right?
Shin-ae, are you very sick?
Let's go to the hospital right away.
Where did my driver go?
He went to the
convenience store to buy hot tea.
Goodness, Shin-ae. Where does it hurt?
I was dizzy and shaking earlier,
but I'm feeling better now that
I'm sitting in the car with the heater on.
I think I didn't dress warmly enough.
From now on, make sure you dress warmly.
Yes, grandfather.
Goodness.
I saw you talking with a woman earlier.
Who is she?
I met her here coincidentally.
While escaping like you, she lost her father
and brother. I think she suffered quite a bit.
I see.
I guess she doesn't have other family members.
While we were talking, she did mention
she has a mom and another family member.
I see.
I don't think he knows that Mi-poong
and Ms. Joo are in the same family.
What can I do about this?
I barely chased Ms. Joo out of the
restaurant, but he knows Mi-poong as well.
Everything will be over
if she recognizes this ring.
My ring fell.
It always falls out like this
because it's too big.
What if you lose it somewhere?
Grandfather, now that our rings are together,
how about we save them in a frame?
Then your ring and grandmother's
ring will always be together.
Yes.
I almost lost my ring several times, too.
How did you come up
with such an incredible idea?
Let's do that. That's a great idea.
Now your ring and grandmother's
ring will never separate.
That's right.
Why? What's wrong?
Are you sick?
I want to hurry up and go home.
Hurry up and drive!
What shall we do?
We can't do this or that.
- Your cell-phone is all charged.
- Thank you.
(Little Tadpole)
Sorry, Mi-poong. Where are you right now?
Mi-poong!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm so happy to see you.
I missed you.
You were worried because
you couldn't get in touch with me, huh?
The truth is, Ha-yeon got into a
car accident when she was with me.
That's why I couldn't contact you.
I feel like she got into
an accident because of me.
If only I had stopped her,
she wouldn't have become like this.
No, this is all my fault.
I shouldn't have answered her
phone call. I should've gone to see her
even though you insisted on
going instead. I should've gone to see her.
This isn't your fault. It's my fault.
Why do you think that? It's not
your fault. Don't think like that.
What do we do about Ha-yeon?
What did the doctor say? Will she be okay?
Well...
Yes.
They said she'll be okay.
But right now, her condition isn't so great.
She's very shocked.
That's why I have to be
at the hospital with her.
So, even if you can't get in touch with me,
don't misunderstand and don't worry.
You trust me, don't you?
Hold on.
(Madame Geum-sil)
Hi. It's me.
Where are you? Hurry up and
come back. Ha-yeon is looking for you.
She's anxious without you.
Okay. I'm coming.
I have to go.
I'm fine, so go on.
I'll call you often, so don't worry.
Bye.
Grandfather, they're so pretty.
Now that they're together,
it feels like I met your grandmother
again. I'm so touched.
Grandfather, leave this here,
and look at it in the
morning and evening,
like you're admiring artwork.
What kind of artwork would make
my heart flutter more than this one?
Shin-ae, when I die,
put this frame into my coffin.
Why would you say such a thing?
You have to live with me
until you're 200 years old.
All right. I will live a long time for you.
Father- I mean, Mr. Kim. Here is ginger tea.
All right.
Did you put a lot of honey in there?
Yes.
If you drink this and get a good
night's sleep, you'll feel much better.
Hurry up and drink it.
Good girl.
Yes. More. Good.
They went to Imjingak Pavilion by
themselves. What are they doing now?
They're treating each other like
they're the apples of their eyes.
Of course they would be doing that.
He's been searching for his
blood relative his whole life,
and now he finally found her.
But why doesn't she feel
like his granddaughter to me?
She feels like an imposter.
Goodness! He'll hear you!
Do you want to be kicked out by her?
She wouldn't dare!
I'm still her mother-in-law!
Goodness! Now she's the
top-dog and we're the underdogs!
From now on, you need to look
good to her in order to live here.
If Hee-dong says he'll divorce her,
I'm going to leave this house with him.
Can you really do that?
No.
I can never leave this house.
It would be too unfair.
I can't leave because of all the years
I dedicated my life to this house!
Anyways, how much did you tell Hee-dong?
Dal-ho just told him that
we found the granddaughter.
If Hee-dong finds out Shin-ae is
the granddaughter, he'll be so shocked.
Still, they got married because
they love each other so much.
Aside from everything else, I just
want those two to live a happy life now.
Thank you.
Father.
What do you mean Shin-ae is the
granddaughter grandfather has been looking for?
We found out on the day
we returned from China.
The Kim Seung-hee he had
been looking for is Shin-ae.
But Hee-dong,
since your late grandfather isn't
really relatives with this grandfather,
there are no problems.
So all you two have to do now is live happily.
You two can't live without each other.
You two love each other.
Shin-ae,what's going on?
Even if they explain it to me,
I don't understand.
Hee-dong...
Then everything you told me
so far has been a lie?
I did that because-
She did that because she loves you so much!
She really didn't want to lose you!
I heard that, and my heart broke!
She loved you so much that she had to do that!
Hold on.
Hee-dong.
I need a moment to think.
- Hee-dong! Hee-dong! Hee-dong!
- I'll go after him. I'll talk to him.
Oh my goodness. Hee-dong.
What is going on? Oh my goodness. Hee-dong.
Hee-dong!
Let's talk.
About what?
What are you going to lie about this time?
Hee-dong...
The fact that your hometown is Sokcho.
The story about your parents
passing away in high school.
The memories with your grandmother
who passed away two years ago.
All those things you told me while
you were crying were nothing but lies.
Yes.
They're all lies.
I made them up.
Why would you do that?
I don't know who you are.
It's like you're a different person.
You have no idea how I lived in
Korea after escaping North Korea.
People are smiling on the outside,
but they actually disrespect me.
I thought if I told you
I was from North Korea,
you would be distant from me,
leave me, and not like me.
That's why I did that.
No.
Not everyone is like that.
Shin-ae,
I would've liked you no matter who you were.
My feelings towards
you would've never been shaken.
I thought you would know my sincere feelings.
I thought our sincerity connected,
so I don't know
why you would need to
make up such lies between us.
Hee-dong, I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have lied for whatever reason.
Forgive me, Hee-dong.
I'm still so...
Everything is so confusing.
He must have genuinely liked me...
As each day passes, I'm here in this place
Since I lost my mom's ring, I feel like
all of my ties to her disappeared.
You have me by your side now.
Thank you, Hee-dong.
Hee-dong, cheer up.
All I have is you now.
Hee-dong, no matter what happens,
you'll never throw me away, right?
At least that way my heart will be at ease
I'll do as you want
Thus, I may hurt more
I may have a harder time, who knows
If I do and you come to me, that's enough
Why isn't he coming? I can't even call him.
Fine.
If he wants a divorce, I'll give it to him.
It's his loss if we get a divorce.
No.
We got married even though
his mother was against us.
If I divorce him so easily,
they'll doubt me for sure.
Until I become grandfather's
legal granddaughter, I need him.
I can't divorce him.
Hee-dong.
I was so worried about you.
Are you...
telling the truth right now?
Yes, I am.
Did you really lie to me...
because you love me?
I thought you would leave me
if you knew the truth about me.
I can't live without you, so...
I'm nothing.
A cartoonist like me is nothing.
Hee-dong.
I'm sorry for not realizing
your feelings and lying to you.
No.
Lying is a hard thing to do.
When I think of how hard
it must have been for you,
my heart hurts.
Hee-dong...
Is there anything else you haven't told me?
If there is, tell me now.
No. There's nothing else.
Really?
Really.
Then it's fine.
We're okay now.
She got hurt that badly?
Jang-go didn't say that,
but I think her legs are paralyzed.
Mom, I feel like this is all my fault,
and I don't know what to do.
Why is that your fault?
You didn't push her. Neither did
you curse her to get into an accident.
Why would you say such a foolish thing?
It just hurt my heart to see
Jang-go having a hard time.
I should have stopped him from going.
All I can think about is that.
Mi-poong,
listen to me carefully.
This happened because you
and Jang-go aren't meant to be.
Do you understand?
That's why you shouldn't say it's your fault.
You should be stronger
in these kinds of situations.
Got it?
Ms. Kim, did you hear the rumor?
What rumor is it now?
Gosh! Jang & Ko Law Firm is a mess right now!
The daughter of the president
of the law firm got into a car accident
and became paralyzed
from the waist down.
That's why they're in total panic right now.
Really?
Oh, no. That's so sad.
- But Young-ju...
- Yes?
Now you're bringing gossip
from over there, too?
It's not that!
The important thing is that there
was a man there when she got into
the accident, and the man happens
to be Mi-poong's lawyer friend!
- Mr. Lee Jang-go?
- Really?
Then what's going to happen?
Her friend has to take
responsibility for that woman's life?
Oh, no. It seemed like
Mi-poong was dating him.
Oh, really?
But if he was there when she got into
an accident, it's not going to be easy for
him to avoid responsibility. On top
of that, she's the daughter of a lawyer.
Would he let Mr. Lee get away with it?
That's true. If he leaves
the handicapped woman,
he'll be labeled as a jerk his whole life.
Gosh. This situation is very ironic.
Then what about our poor Mi-poong?
Mi-poong, you're here?
- Hi!
- Good morning!
Good morning!
Grandfather, will I change
my last name to yours now?
Of course! You must change it!
A Kim cannot live as a Park.
I see.
How long will it take for Shin-ae
to become my granddaughter?
She needs to officially change her last name
and file for a change of family registry.
It'll take about three to six months.
Six months is too long!
Do it as quickly as you can!
What if I die while I'm waiting?
Grandfather.
Yes, sir. I'll do my best.
Drink your tea.
Mom, all we have to do now
is make sure Hee-dong
doesn't lose that spot
as his grandson-in-law, right?
Of course. Of course.
When one door closes, another one will open.
If I just wait three months,
grandfather's inheritance will be all mine.
So nothing has to happen until then.
In three months, it'll be my world.
- Mom.
- Yes?
This is really South Korea?
Yes, this is the South Korea
you always wanted to come to.
Goodness, you lucky girl.
Let's go!
- Please spread the word about us! Bye!
- Thank you!
Goodness! There were so many people today!
I didn't even have time to sit down!
Won-bin, I did well today, didn't I?
You got much better,
but why didn't you explain
to the woman in her forties
how to use the mat?
I didn't?
That was because she knew how to use
the mat, so I didn't have to explain it to her.
Still, all the mats can be differently used,
so you must explain the directions to them.
Didn't my father tell you?
Not to be dull?
He did.
I hate dull things, too.
That's why our family motto is,
"Don't live dully."
We should put the motto here, too.
Won-bin, you need to go to
the academy. Hurry up and get ready.
Yes, sir.
- Were there a lot of clients today?
- Yes.
We hit jackpot today!
There were about fifty people today.
People kept going
in and out of here.
I didn't even have time to rest!
- Dull.
Well...
Yes! There were exactly
fifty-two people today! Look here!
Good job.
I hope you will continue
to be exact from now on.
Father, I'm ready to go.
Go outside and wait.
Yes, sir.
Here.
Give it to Ms. Hwang.
My sister-in-law?
It's her birthday present.
I heard it was her birthday last time.
Why would you buy a birthday gift for her?
Why else? It's the birthday of
my employee's family member. So as your
boss, I should definitely
get her a birthday gift!
I'll be going now.
What's going on?
Is he interested in Geum-sil, or is he being
nice to my family
because he's interested in me?
Hello, Mr. Jo.
- Anything unusual?
- No. Welcome back.
Ms. Joo is still not coming out?
Yes, she got another job.
I see.
Still, I can live, I am happy
Life is just a one-time playground
Though it's hard, our lives
are always sparkling, it's livable
Let's go.
Mi-poong, aren't you going home?
Go ahead first. I'm going
to do some more work.
Okay then.
When you have a lot on
your mind, work can be medicine.
Good job today.
- Cheer up.
- Keep up the hard work.
Bye.
Please stop her!
- I hate this!
- Ha-yeon!
Calm down.
Jang-go...
That's why you should have
broken up with him when I told you to!
Why are you sticking to my son like
a leech and creating all this chaos?
If it hadn't been for you,
they would've been in
England by now, and none
of this would have happened!
Jang-go.
Yeah?
I want to sit up.
Sure.
That's enough.
Thanks.
Do you want something to drink?
No, I don't want anything.
Do you want to go outside?
It's a bit chilly though.
Jang-go.
You don't have to make an effort anymore.
I can't hold you back anymore.
Ha-yeon.
It's the truth.
I lost you even when my legs were normal.
You must hate me more now.
Since you're next to me...
I feel more pathetic.
I'll get you some warm water.
Mom.
Go home and rest. I can be here alone.
How can I go home
when Ha-yeon is in that state?
She said I'm taking place of her late mom.
Give that to me. I'll get the water.
I'm going to get some fresh air.
Sure.
Ha-yeon, are you walking right now?
Since when did you start walking?
Since just now.
Is this a dream or not?
I was so worried you would
never be able to walk again!
Oh my goodness, Ha-yeon! I'm so happy for you!
Oh my gosh! I should tell
Jang-go the good news! Jang-go!
Mother!
Please don't tell Jang-go.
Mother, you'll do that for me, won't you?
This isn't for me. This is all for Jang-go.
Mom.
What's wrong?
Don't go in there right now.
Ha-yeon is crying.
She doesn't want to show you this side of her.
I feel so bad for her.
She used to smile so happily,
so how did she end up that way?
Jang-go, can't you stay by Ha-yeon's side?
Stay by her side.
Be her strength to live again.
If you can't do it,
I'm going to stay by her side.
I meant it when I said
I think of her as my daughter.
I really wanted to do that.
But Jang-go, do you
really have the confidence to
live your life without being
concerned about Ha-yeon?
Can you really do that?
I feel so bad for her, Jang-go.
What do we do, Jang-go?
Poor Ha-yeon.
What can we do?
When my chest feels stuffy, I close both eyes
Into the wind, I whisper your name
Though time passes for me,
The memories remain
My heart that is stuck on you
Mi-poong, it's me.
Let's meet up.
I have something to tell you.
Wind, sunlight, memories
I can't forget that beautiful day
You still remain in a corner of my heart
Even if you blow into the wind
My heart that wasn't conveyed, you can't know
Mi-poong...
No.
I'll go first.
I know what you're going to say.
Jang-go...
let's break up.
Let's do that.
You're not throwing me away.
You're not breaking your promise to me.
I...
I just want to stop here.
No matter how many times I think about this,
I think our relationship ends here.
Do this for me.
Don't worry about me. I'm fine.
I'll live well.
Wherever you are, I hope
you'll be healthy and happy, too.
I did not know that your heart would change
I really did not know
I lived only trusting in you alone
(Blow Breeze)
My goodness! You have such a great figure!
Anything looks good on you!
- Who is she?
- I can't believe this!
You met your grandfather!
Seung-hee's family is all dead.
So why can't I do this?
I think if you come with me,
it'll be a big support.
I'll do that. Let's go together.
Why is he getting engaged to
a woman whose legs are paralyzed?
To the future of Jang-go and Ha-yeon!
I'm sorry.
I'm going to marry Mi-poong.
Subtitles by OnDemandKorea