Subtitles by OnDemandKorea
When my chest feels stuffy
Jang-go, let's break up.
You're not throwing me away.
You're not breaking your promise to me.
I...
I just want to stop here.
Waiting for you
Wind, sunlight, memories
I can't forget that beautiful day
You still remain in a corner of my heart
Even if you blow into the wind,
Hi, it's me.
Where are you?
I want to discuss something
with you about Ha-yeon.
I'm in the lobby. I'll be up there soon.
Bye.
Johns Hopkins?
- (Episode 26)
- It's a famous hospital in America.
Ha-yeon's father came earlier and told us
he got in touch with a professor from there.
She can get a complete medical
examination over there to find out the
reason why her legs are paralyzed
and find a way for her to get better.
So how about you go with her?
Me?
You're the only one who can help her.
No, mother. I'm okay.
You're not okay.
How can you go somewhere so far by yourself?
Jang-go, will you be okay with this?
If you go with me, I won't be nervous,
and I think you'll be able to support me.
Is there really a possibility
for you to get better over there?
I want to do anything if there's hope.
Even if the possibility is only one percent.
Of course! You should do anything you can!
Jang-go.
All right. I'll do it.
Let's go together.
Really?
Are you serious, Jang-go?
You made a good decision, Jang-go.
Engagement?
Why would he get engaged to her when
she's paralyzed and can't even get up?
Ha-yeon wants to get treatment in America,
so Jang-go decided to go with her.
That's why it'll be better for them
to get engaged before they go.
Did Jang-go say he would go?
Yes.
Geum-sil, are you out of your mind?
You want Jang-go to get married to someone
who might be handicapped her whole life?
Ha-yeon will get better. Don't worry.
Are you a doctor?
Are you God?
There's no guarantee that she will get better.
You want to give our precious
Jang-go to such a woman?
She got hurt because of Jang-go,
so how can we just ignore her?
If you saw how much pain Ha-yeon is in,
you wouldn't be able to say this.
It's not like Jang-go pushed her into the car.
She was drunk and got hurt on her own.
Why should Jang-go
have to take responsibility?
Do you hate Ha-yeon that much?
Why are you twisting my words?
When did I say I hated her?
I like Ha-yeon, too, but to me,
Jang-go comes before her!
Are you really a mother?
Even if Jang-go said he would do this,
you should've stopped him.
Do you care more for that family's son-in-law
position than your own son's happiness?
Mother, you're being too harsh.
I'm doing this for a reason.
I would never do anything that
would damage Jang-go's life.
- Stop it. You guys are going to fight at this point.
- What?
What? Damage?
Are you using Jang-go for business?
So you're going to sell Jang-go for money?
You've gone mad for money!
Yes! I've gone mad! All I see is money!
What do we have?
We don't even have the
ability to buy them a house!
That's why you shouldn't
meddle into my affairs.
Whether I sell my son or not,
it's up to me. He's my son!
- What? Are you talking back to me?
- Grandma!
- Hey! You despicable wench!
What do you take me for?
- Mom, what's wrong with you?
Let go of me! You despicable wench!
Is that all you have to say?
You! You! Get out of this house right now!
- Mom!
- Grandma!
- You horrible witch!
- Mom, go to your room.
- That wench!
- Mom, I told you to stop it!
Goodness! And she calls herself a mother?
No.
I can't get weak now.
When time passes, they'll understand me.
You broke up with him?
Good job.
Time will heal everything.
Mi-poong,
you should take off this ring now.
Not yet.
I'll take it off a little bit later.
I can't take it off right now.
Okay.
As time passes by,
you'll naturally take it off.
You can keep it on.
Hee-dong.
Why are you sleeping here?
I was just going to take
a break, but I fell asleep.
It's already this late? I have to
meet someone. I'll be back.
What about lunch?
I can eat outside.
I'm going shopping with mother today.
Do you need anything?
I'm not sure.
I don't think I do.
Then I'm going to choose for you.
I like anything you choose for me.
I'll be back.
- Hee-dong, are you going out?
- Yes, I  have plans.
- Bye.
Are you ready? Let's go out.
You can go out first.
I'll be out after I get ready.
Sure.
I'll go to the car first and
turn the heater on! Take your time!
Oh my goodness! You have such a nice
figure that it looks good on you, too!
- Really?
- Yes.
That will look good on you, too.
How can everything look good on you?
You have a call.
Please take my phone out.
Here.
(Grandfather)
Hi, grandfather.
I'm shopping with mother right now.
I bought a nice cardigan and
tie for you, so come home early.
Bye.
Goodness. Did you guys go shopping?
Yes, mom. Shin-ae said she had
a lot of things to buy.
But why are you carrying these for her?
Are you her servant?
It's not like that, mom!
Shin-ae, you said you were tired, right? I'll
take these up for you,
so go upstairs and rest.
Yes. My feet hurt.
I think I should do that, mother.
Go ahead.
Stop right there!
"I think I should do that?"
What's wrong, grandmother?
What are you doing to your mother-in-law?
I see. Are you playing the top dog now?
Grandmother...
- Mom, what's wrong?
- You stay put!
They say a no good person acts up!
Are you using your mother-in-law
as your servant now?
How dare you act so rudely!
- How dare you!
- Mom!
That's enough!
Chung-ja,
what is going on?
Shin-ae, you tell me.
What's going on?
Grandfather...
It's nothing.
Shin-ae.
Chung-ja, what are you doing?
Even before they got married,
you hated her,
so you opposed her,
scolded her, and ruined her face.
Do you still hate Shin-ae so much?
No! It's not like that!
You know better than anyone
what Shin-ae means to me!
You can't even treat her warmly like she's
your daughter! How can you do this to her?
Mr. Kim, it's not like that.
What happened was-
You shouldn't act like that either!
If your daughter did something wrong,
you should talk to her.
How can you play along with her?
I beg your pardon?
I was really treating Shin-ae
like she was my daughter.
There was a misunderstanding!
Forget it!
How can we live under the same roof
when you hate Shin-ae so much?
If you hate her, you should
move out of this house.
I'll live with Hee-dong and Shin-ae.
No! I don't hate Shin-ae!
You horrible people.
How can he change so much
after he found his granddaughter?
How can he do this to you when you served
him like he was your parent all this time?
He told me I'm playing along with you!
Mom! Mom!
Jang-go, just carry Ha-yeon. The wheelchair
can't go over the high doorstep anyways.
All right.
Careful.
Be careful.
Are you that happy to be
invited to your friend's house?
Yes, I'm so happy!
Listen to the adults. You know you
shouldn't run around in their house, right?
Aunt, don't worry.
I have that much common sense.
What? Common sense?
Where did you learn that word?
Kids these days use that word.
"Kids these days?"
Oh my gosh! You're adorable!
Then have common sense when you play
with your friends until I pick you up later.
Okay. Aunt, we're going to be late.
Okay.
Jang-soo! Nam-yi! Mother!
Yes, mom!
Hello.
We can see you at the engagement.
Why did you come here?
She must be heavy. Go in, Jang-go.
- That's right. Jang-go will be tired.
Go in. Jang-soo, take these.
- Sure, mom.
Be careful.
Take the wheelchair.
Be careful when you go inside.
Aunt, what's wrong?
It's nothing. Let's go.
This is Chinese quince tea.
I made it. Drink it.
Thank you, mother.
I'm sorry I'm the only one sitting like this.
You don't have to be. It would've
been nice if we had a stand-up table.
Should we put a sofa in here
and change the interior?
You're not feeling well.
You didn't have to come all the way here.
No, I'm a lot better now.
And if we get engaged and go to America,
I won't be able to come here often.
We should be grateful she came to visit us.
I hope you get better over there.
Get well soon.
Yes, I'll get well.
That's why I'm going.
Yes. If you go with such a mindset,
you'll be able to get better.
I don't feel very well,
so I'm going to go rest.
Have a good time.
Okay.
She doesn't feel very well.
What are you up to?
Is that kiwi juice?
Yes. Shin-ae likes this.
What?
You're going to give this
to that devious witch and
not your mom who is dealing with constipation?
I told him that she's like a daughter
to me. What else can I do?
I have to pretend to be nice to her.
How can you do this after you
went through that? You're too nice.
I already feel upset as it is,
so you don't have to add onto it!
I want to spit into her drink!
Mom, what's that?
Mom, what did you put in there?
Constipation medicine.
I need to get my revenge this way at least!
Shin-ae, what are you doing?
No, don't get up.
What's this?
It's gold kiwi juice.
It's good for preventing constipation
and making your skin healthy.
I felt bad about yelling at you when
I could've just talked nicely to you.
Is that why the two of you
came in here together?
You didn't have to.
My mom suggested I make this
for you. I made it myself, so drink up.
Thank you.
Okay. Drink up.
My stomach hurts.
Mother, you should just drink this.
No, no, no. I brought this
for you to drink. You drink it.
No, thank you. I appreciate
your efforts, but I think
I'm going to get
a stomachache if I drink this.
I must have ate too many cold foods today.
Mother, drink it.
Sure, I'll drink it!
Chung-ja!
Chung-ja...
Chung-ja, I'm sorry! I'm so sorry!
My poor daughter!
It's me.
I'm in front of your house right now.
I brought someone you would be happy
to see. Hurry up and come out.
Someone I would be happy to see?
Who is it?
I came with Yoo-Jin.
Aren't you happy to see her?
Yoo-Jin, say hello.
You know auntie, don't you?
Hello, aunt.
Are you really going to be this way?
Look here, Kang Mi-Jung.
I have to send Yoo-Jin to school.
I want to send her to a nice school here.
Why do you look so upset?
Are you really going to be this way?
Leave here! Go wait somewhere
for me! I'll be there soon!
Shin-ae.
Why are you outside?
Grandfather.
Who is she?
Hello.
The thing is, grandfather...
she's the woman who gave me a lot of
help when I was having trouble in China.
Is that so?
She has a child with her,
so why is she standing outside?
They're visiting Korea and just
dropped by. They were just leaving now.
She saved you. You can't just let her go.
Come in. I'm grateful to you
for helping my granddaughter.
You should at least have
a cup of tea before you go.
Granddaughter? Not granddaughter-in-law?
What's going on?
Come inside.
What's your name?
Kang Yoo-Jin.
Kang Yoo-Jin?
I see. Come on. Let's go inside.
You can't call me Kang Mi-Jung.
Shin-ae, why are you just standing there?
Escort the guest inside.
Yes, grandfather!
- Do you have a place to stay?
- I'm staying somewhere nearby.
I see.
Thank you.
Isn't she the woman from last time?
But why is she inside our house?
Does this woman know her weakness?
How old are you, baby?
I'm not a baby.
I'm seven years old.
Oh, really?
That's right. If you're seven years old,
you're not a baby.
I'm sorry for calling you a baby.
But you don't look like your mom at all.
I look like my dad.
Your dad?
Where is your dad?
I separated from her dad a long time ago.
I see.
Grandfather, drink your tea.
You drink your tea, too, aunt.
All right.
Thank you so much for
helping my granddaughter out
when she was going through difficult times.
We must help each other as fellow countrymen.
Shin-ae is this old man's granddaughter?
What on earth is going on?
But how do the two of you know each other?
Oh, us?
Well, we knew each other in
North Korea, but we met again in China.
You knew Shin-ae when she was in North Korea?
Then do you know Kim Soon-ok's son
Kim Dae-hoon as well?
Kim Soon-ok's son Kim Dae-hoon?
Oh, you mean Seung-hee's father?
Yes, he's my son. He's Seung-hee's father.
What on earth is he talking about?
"Seung-hee's father?"
Do you remember my father?
What's this?
Is she pretending to be Seung-hee?
Well, I do know him,
but it's been much too long.
Still, I'm happy to meet someone
who knows my son's name.
I just thought she was
this family's daughter-in-law,
but she turned out to be your granddaughter.
It hasn't been long since I found her.
I met her as my distant
relative's daughter-in-law.
But I found out she was my granddaughter
whom I've been searching for.
The heavens helped us meet.
Goodness! Goodness! Goodness! What a miracle!
Oh, Shin-ae, I'm so happy for you!
You got to meet your grandfather!
Hey, Kang Mi-Jung!
You're pretending to be Young-ae's
daughter Kim Seung-hee, aren't you?
Why are you glaring at me
when you played along with me?
You've got some nerves!
Aren't you scared of the
heavens after deceiving blood ties?
Seung-hee's family died,
so why can't I do this?
Grandfather gets to be happy
with his granddaughter.
Thanks to that, I can live
a decent life in South Korea.
Yoo-Jin and you will be
able to live a carefree life
from now on. So is the heavens
a big deal right now?
Yes, yes. Who cares if you're Kang Mi-Jung,
Park Shin-ae, or Kim Seung-hee?
As long as you give me money,
I'm happy. Right?
Take this, and don't contact me
until I contact you first.
Do you understand?
But Shin-ae, hurry up.
I need money urgently. Got it?
Yoo-Jin, let's go!
Yoo-Jin, let's go eat something yummy!
This is all I have right now!
If they find out I'm a North Korean defector,
it'll be the end of us!
That woman clearly threatened
Shin-ae to get money from her.
But why is she calling that woman "aunt?"
Something is strange. Something is fishy.
Who on earth is Shin-ae?
What are you mumbling to yourself about?
Is Shin-ae really father's granddaughter?
I really feel like she isn't, honey.
You woman! What are you talking about?
Do you know how hard it was to
find out the name of Elder's son?
Do you know how much money we spent on this?
We barely found out, and yet,
Shin-ae knew it right away!
On top of that, she said her grandmother's
name and she has the ring, too!
What more do you need to know?
They can't be checked through DNA testing.
And my instinct keeps
saying she's not the one.
But why are you getting so angry?
How can I not get angry?
Elder spent his whole life searching for his
blood relative, and now he finally found her!
Can't you see how Elder is smiling
every day because of Shin-ae?
Goodness. You look like an evil granny!
What? An evil granny?
Hey! Jo Dal-ho!
Jang-go, hold on.
I want some fresh air.
Can we walk around a bit?
Yes, Jang-go.
Ha-yeon must have felt frustrated
in the hospital room. Go on and do that.
It's a bit chilly.
- Will you be okay?
- Yes, I want to do it.
Mother, go inside first.
All right. I'll go in first,
so you two have a good time.
Okay. See you tomorrow.
See you tomorrow.
- Jang-go.
- Okay.
Yes. Jang-go will develop feelings
for her if he keeps being with her.
- Here?
- Right there.
It feels great!
But Jang-soo, what do you do at the theater
that you always have to put on patches?
It's not like you're building sets every day.
Well, there's something wrong
with the set, so we have to rebuild it.
When will you be able to succeed
from being a stage actor?
Just wait a little bit longer.
My baby, you said you would understand me.
Fine.
But Jang-soo, don't you
think something is strange?
What is?
I'm talking about Ha-yeon.
If I was in her shoes,
I'd want to die, but she's too normal.
Jang-soo, what if she's purposely
lying when her legs are fine?
Come on, Hee-ra.
Forget it! I was just saying!
Still, how can you say such a thing?
She must be so tormented inside.
Watching her purposely
hide her true feelings and act
so cheerful actually
made me feel sorry for her.
Right? No one in this world
would make up such a lie.
- Of course.
- Right?
- Yes. So don't think like that.
- All right. I'm sorry.
Here.
It's warm. Thanks, Jang-go.
There aren't many days we can spend in Korea.
It'll be difficult for us to come back
to Korea for a while, huh?
I think so.
I didn't know there was such a place
in your neighborhood. It's so nice here.
The smell of autumn! It's so nice!
I loved and wanted you
Because I live inside your memories
Jang-go, do you want to smell this, too?
In the love that has already passed
I need to fill up my tired heart
Jang-go, what's wrong?
You'll catch a cold. Let's go.
But where are you?
Grandma.
Go ahead and sit down.
Do you have something to tell me?
I don't feel right about this.
Do you really want to get
engaged to Ha-yeon tomorrow?
Huh?
If you don't want to, tell me the truth.
After the engagement, you won't
be able to change your mind.
If you have someone else in your heart,
but you're doing this because
you have no choice or because
your mother wants you to do this,
tell me that this is an engagement
that you don't want.
Then, no matter what I do, I'll make
sure this engagement won't happen.
No, grandma.
I was the one who decided
to do this engagement.
Are you sure?
Have you really decided to do this?
Yes.
If you think so, then there's
nothing I can do about it.
My goodness.
After I send you to America, how will I live?
Jang-go,
you need to keep this in mind.
Whatever you decide to do, I'm always
on your side. Don't forget that.
Got it?
Mr. Lee and Mr. Jang's daughter
is getting engaged today?
How can he leave Mi-poong behind
and get engaged to another woman?
I was hoping things would work out for them.
Poor Mi-poong.
- Ready?
- Yes.
What's wrong with the atmosphere?
Let's start the meeting.
- Okay.
First of all, I would like
to thank Lee Jang-go...
for deciding to be with
Ha-yeon even though her future
has become unclear
after her car accident.
And I would also like to thank his family for
allowing him to go through with his decision.
Jang-go, thank you.
Please be good to Ha-yeon.
Please say a word, Ms. Hwang.
I believe Ha-yeon will get well.
I know she'll return healthy
after getting treatment in America.
I hope Ha-yeon, who is like a daughter
to me, and Jang-go will live happily together.
Then let's make a toast to bless their future.
To Jang-go and Ha-yeon's future. Cheers!
Cheers!
- Let's congratulate them.
- Sure!
Jang-go, congratulations.
Ha-yeon, congratulations.
Thank you.
Congratulations, Mr. Jang.
Oh, no!
Oh, no.
Hey.
- Ha-yeon, you can walk?
- What happened?
You can walk, but you lied?
No way!
The thing is...
Ha-yeon.
You could walk?
Mother, what do I do?
So the thing is...
You knew about this, too?
Let me explain everything.
Jang-go!
Don't go.
Please.
Jang-go, I'm sorry.
But I wanted to hold you back.
Can't you understand
my feelings just this once?
Jang-go, we didn't have bad intentions.
Do you think I would have done
this if things hadn't been so terrible?
Don't get angry, and listen to me. Please?
So...
the two of you set this up to fool me?
Mom.
I hurt the woman I love to go to Ha-yeon.
You two won't have any idea how I felt.
But that was all a lie.
Mom, how can you do this to me?
Don't hold me back.
You! If I had been younger
and had more energy,
I would've kicked you out of this house today!
And you call yourself a mother?
How can you drive a nail into
your own child's heart?
How can you do this as his mother?
Do you think I lied because I wanted to?
It's because I'm his mother!
I did it because as his mother,
I wanted to make him
walk on a path of flowers!
Oh my goodness.
How can you be so immature?
There's no such thing as a path of flowers!
I dare you to plant as
many flowers as you can.
Do you think it'll turn
into a path of flowers?
You have to walk in thorns and
weeds before you get to walk in flowers!
I don't want my son
to walk in a path of thorns!
I don't want my son to suffer
and die just like his father did!
Why do you keep bringing up my dead son?
My son lived a nice life!
Why do you keep blaming my son, huh?
My son lived the best that he could!
That's why we have
this house for us to live in!
Who are you to disrespect my son?
- My son had a good life!
- Mom, what's wrong with you?
She keeps blaming my son!
When did I say that? Fine! It's all
my fault! I'm the one who deserves to die!
Yes, you are!
Goodness! You don't even
deserve to be a mother!
You drove a nail into your child's heart,
so of course you don't deserve
to be a mother! You have
no right to be a mother!
You better not try to interfere
with Jang-go's life again!
If you do, we'll both fight until we die!
- Mom, stop it!
- Got it?
Grandma.
Oh, Jang-soo. Jang-soo.
I'm sorry.
If I can't take you out,
I'll have to love you
Just like this, stay this way
I'm sorry.
Stay this way
I'm going to marry Mi-poong.
Yes.
Go ahead.
You're really going to marry her?
Think about this carefully.
Aren't you rushing?
Aunt, I already thought about it carefully.
Lee Jang-go.
Is marriage a joke?
You quit the law firm.
With what money will you marry her?
Fine. Let's say you'll have a simple wedding.
Where will you live?
You keep your mouth shut.
The eldest son in our family
is going to get married.
What right do you have
to say anything about it?
Since you seem uncomfortable
with her, mother, we'll move out.
And I can't make her throw
her mother and Yoo-sung away.
That's why we're going
to live with her family.
Lee Jang-go, you're so-
Nam-yi, unless you're going to
help him pay for a house, shut your trap.
Mom.
Jang-go, you're the eldest son of our family.
If you move out of this house with Mi-poong
just because we're uncomfortable with her,
there will be no chance for us to get closer,
and we'll just become strangers in the end.
That's wrong.
Grandma, but...
If you decided to marry Mi-poong
and make a family with her,
then you have to make an effort for
all of us to become one family.
So just stay here until we become
closer and then move out.
That way, we'll really become a family.
But if all of us live here together,
the population density will increase.
- It's already so difficult to use the bathroom, so...
- Hee-ra!
Oh, okay.
Jang-go, I think grandma is right.
- We need to live together to get closer.
- That's right.
Let's do that.
We'll let Mi-poong's mother and
Yoo-sung continue to live in the back house.
Let's do that, Jang-go.
Let the kids get married.
Ma'am...
Our family has already
decided to let them get married.
Let's forget all the horrible feelings
and comfortably get them married.
Well...
I'm very grateful for
your words, but we need to
move out, so we don't
have any money for a wedding-
We don't have any money either.
Let's just think of it
as combining two families.
Mi-poong will be moving into
Jang-go's room. Just think comfortably.
Goodness. But still...
I didn't bring much with me
when I got married either,
but I'm still living pretty well to this day.
- Ma'am...
- It's all mind over matter.
If you think it won't work, it won't,
but if you think it'll work, it'll work.
And you don't have to move out.
Jang-go wanted to move out, but I stopped him.
If you move away, we won't be able to see
each other, and we'll become strangers then.
We'll become a real family
once we live together.
Just think comfortably.
How will Mi-poong be able to live
after sending you and Yoo-sung away?
Ma'am, this isn't right.
We already signed the contract to move
into our new house by the end of the month.
Ms. Joo.
Do as grandma says.
Mi-poong and I won't be able to live comfortably
if you and Yoo-sung leave like this.
Don't trouble yourself and
let's just do it this way. All right?
Jang-go said he was going to move out
with Mi-poong, but I told them to stay here.
Think about it in their shoes. It would be
heartbreaking and lonely for Mi-poong to leave
her mother and nephew
when they came from North Korea
and have no other family member here.
That's why I told them to just live here.
I'm talking to you,
but how can you just lie there
like that? Where did you learn your manners?
Goodness! Your daughters-in-law
will learn great things from you!
Mi-poong, you're going to
get married to that lawyer?
Yes.
Congratulations!
We were actually worried about you.
But how could that female lawyer
do such a thing? She's terrible!
Mi-poong, tell us what you need.
We'll get it for you as a wedding present.
Really? Thank you so much!
Mi-poong, I heard you're getting
married to Jang-go.
Yes.
I sincerely congratulate you.
I hope you'll be happy with Jang-go.
Thank you.
Mi-poong.
Thinking about it now,
I never apologized to you.
All this time, I bothered you, gave you a hard
time, and annoyed you
just because I liked you.
I'm sorry.
Next time, I'm going to
the headquarters in America.
Headquarters in America?
It's not because of you.
I just want to go somewhere else
and get more experience.
That's why I don't think
I'll be able to go to your wedding.
Have a safe trip.
Thanks. Be happy.
If Jang-go doesn't listen to you,
call me anytime.
Thank you, Mr. Bang.
Shall we say our good-byes?
- Nothing unusual happened?
- No.
But Mr. Kim...
Go on.
I won't be able to come out next weekend.
There are many customers
on the weekends. It'll be busy.
I know that, but it's my nephew's wedding.
My sister-in-law's son.
Geum-sil's son is getting married?
Young Geum-sil had such an old son?
Mr. Kim, why are you calling
my sister-in-law "Geum-sil?"
Be careful what you say. And Geum-sil is old!
Really?
I thought the two of you were
just a couple years apart.
What did you say?
And I called her that because she seemed
friendly and sweet like my older sister.
If it offends you,
I won't call her that anymore.
Lock up the doors well before you go home.
How annoying! That jerk!
How bad is his vision? He wears glasses, too!
What? Geum-sil and
I only look a couple years apart?
Darn it! How annoying!
Yoo-Jin, let's eat ribs until we explode!
Really?
Can we really eat until we explode?
Of course! Excuse me!
Yes?
Please give us four servings of pork ribs-
I mean four servings of cow ribs.
Wait a minute.
Aren't you Kim Soon-boon?
Aren't you Young-ae?
Soon-boon!
Oh my goodness! Young-ae!
So, Dae-hoon and Yeong-cheol
died while you were escaping,
and only you and Seung-hee survived?
Shin-ae said that Young-ae's family died.
Does she really think they're dead?
Or does she know they're alive and
is still pretending to be Seung-hee?
Do you have a place to stay?
I'm staying at a motel right now.
Young-ae, I'll pay you,
so can I stay here for a few days?
You don't have to pay. While you're
in Korea, you can stay here.
Thanks, Young-ae.
I have an important phone call.
What kind of phone call is it?
I told you I would pay you back. I can
pay you back by the end of this month.
I told you I would pay you back!
Why can't you believe me?
Do whatever you want! Come here
and take my liver or kidneys if you want!
- Who...?
- Oh...
Are you Seung-hee?
Who are you?
Me? I'm your mom's friend.
Hello. Why aren't you coming inside?
- Go in first.
- All right.
So Shin-ae stole Seung-hee's spot, huh?
She's that old man's real granddaughter.
Should I tell her or not?
No.
If I just keep my mouth shut,
I'll be able to keep getting money.
The weather is great.
I can't believe I'm getting married
to a little tadpole like you.
I can't believe it either.
The hideous fish boy is becoming my husband.
What? Hideous?
But if we get married,
do we have to call each other
"honey" and "sweetheart"
like other married couples?
Of course!
I think that will be too cheesy for me!
Why?
What's so hard about that?
Honey.
Jang-go, don't do that! I feel like
I ate 100 spoonfuls of butter!
How could you say that, honey?
- Please don't say that!
- Honey!
Mi-poong!
How can you fall down like a little kid?
Honey, are you okay?
- Stop that!
- Honey, are you okay?
Do you need to go to the hospital, honey?
Wow! You're so beautiful!
- Congratulations!
- Congratulations, Mi-poong!
You look so beautiful!
Hello, girls!
Hi, Chung-ja! Nice to see you again!
These are my friends. Say hello.
- Hello.
Your daughter-in-law looks better than before.
I guess you don't give her
a hard time nowadays.
Come on!
When did I give her a hard time?
- Let's go to Geum-sil.
- All right.
What's going on?
Why is Ms. Joo standing there?
Mi-poong is the bride
who's getting married today?
She's going to be Hee-ra's sister-in-law?
What's wrong, Shin-ae?
It's nothing. I'm going to use the restroom.
Sure.
- Welcome.
- Congratulations.
Thank you.
Say hi. This is my son.
It's been a while.
Yes. Congratulations.
- Where's Shin-ae?
- She went to the restroom.
Geum-sil, brighten up. Why do you
look so unhappy on such a joyful day?
Is it because you can't get
a lawyer daughter-in-law?
Yeah, brighten up.
Don't think of it as losing your son.
Think of it as gaining a daughter.
But your in-law is so pretty like a flower.
I know. It makes you get compared to her.
What the heck? It's that gold digger
who used to work at our restaurant!
Then what's going on? Our daughters
are going to be sisters-in-law?
Oh my god! No way!
Chung-ja, let's go inside.
You guys go ahead.
I'm going to use the restroom first.
- Let's go inside.
- This way.
How cheap! I can't believe our daughters
are going to be sisters-in-law!
How the heck did Geum-sil
get such a daughter-in-law?
Mom, Mi-poong looks like
an angel who fell from the sky.
You think so?
Yes. Since you're marrying a lawyer, you'll live
well even if you don't find your grandfather.
Shin-ae has to be that old man's
granddaughter so that Yoo-Jin and I can live.
(Bride: Kim Mi-poong)
Yoo-Jin, let's take a picture!
- Yay!
Please take a pretty photo!
What's going on? Why is that woman here?
Is she out of her mind?
Hey, it's pretty busy at the wedding hall-
We need to talk.
- Why are you here? What are you doing?
- Come with me!
It's that woman from last time!
What is it?
Be gentle! Why are you so strong?
Why are you here? What did you tell Mi-poong?
Are you scared I told her that
you're acting as the fake granddaughter?
You must be scared after all.
You knew Kim Seung-hee was alive, huh?
You'll be damned to hell!
If you do this, you won't even get one penny!
What? Fake?
Fake granddaughter?
(Blow Breeze)
You two just have to live happily.
- What's wrong?
- Mother!
Are you making her make
breakfast all by herself?
- Please do the dishes for me.
- How dare she order me around!
Pretend this marriage never happened then!
You con-artist! You thief!
It's all over when I tell him
you're an imposter!
It'll be the end for you, too!
You need to give me money
for me to live in China.
This is the only method we have, mother!
- How about we have a baby?
- A baby?
- I'll come get you.
- Mom!
Since when did you know that I was your mom?
Subtitles by OnDemandKorea