Subtitles by OnDemandKorea
(Episode 28)
What if one day, she appears
out of nowhere and
declares that she's the real granddaughter?
I'm so scared!
What will happen then?
Grandfather, you were so awesome today.
All the board members looked at you with
trust and respect. It made me so proud!
Really?
Yes.
Congratulations, grandfather.
Thank you.
Hello, Mr. Kim.
Who's this? It's Kim Mi-poong!
But what are you doing here?
I work in the marketing team here.
Is that so?
You're an employee of Winner's Group?
She works in our company?
Yes. But...
It's been a while, Mi-poong.
But how do you know my grandfather?
Your grandfather?
Hold on.
Do you two know each other?
Shin-ae is my granddaughter.
She's my biological granddaughter
I found recently.
Pardon? She's your granddaughter?
Yes.
But how do you two know each other?
The thing is-
We knew each other in Pyeongyang.
Oh, is that so?
No wonder!
When I met you at Imjingak for the first time,
you didn't feel like a stranger at all.
What a coincidence!
Oh, yes. But...
See you later, Mi-poong.
- Grandfather, let's go.
- Sure.
See you again, Mi-poong.
Sure.
Bye.
How can we run into each other here?
Is that the Kang Mi-Jung I know?
Mom, it's me. Did you know that Kang Mi-Jung
has a grandfather in South Korea?
What are you talking about? She has no family.
She didn't have anyone left
after her mother died,
so she came all the way from North Korea
to Macau to look for me.
Right? I thought so, too.
But she was with her grandfather
whom she found recently.
Really?
This is something new. Did she have a
grandfather in South Korea I didn't know about?
All right. I'll hang up now.
Grandfather will be going to
the company every day now.
What if he keeps running into
Mi-poong at the company?
It'll be the end of me if he finds out the
name she used in North Korea is Kim Seung-hee.
Shin-ae, is there a problem?
No.
What kind of problem would I have
when you're right next to me like this?
That's right.
Tell me if you have any problems.
I'll solve all of them for you.
Grandfather, let's go on a date
before we go back home.
We can eat broiled grills for your health
and drink coffee at a coffee shop, too.
Sure.
Let's do that.
No.
This won't do.
How would Shin-ae know
if Geum-sil's daughter-in-law
Mi-poong is searching
for her grandfather or not?
What will I do if I just sit by
and get stabbed in the back?
This must be it.
Why do they have to
stay here out of all places?
I'm a nervous wreck!
What are you looking at?
Oh my god!
Why are you peering into my in-law's home?
You're like a ghost! You scared me!
I'm asking you, what are you doing here?
I was just passing by, and I was
curious how Hee-ra was doing.
At your son's wedding,
I couldn't even talk to you
because I had to leave early
with a stomachache.
That's why I was dropping by.
I was curious how North Korean
people lived, so I was checking it out.
What?
You don't even acknowledge
Jang-soo as your son-in-law, but
you came because you were
curious how Hee-ra was doing?
The things you say!
How can I not be curious
when she's my daughter?
You'll give me some tea, right?
I brought those traditional sweets you love!
Geum-sil!
Try them! There's one with pumpkin,
one with red bean, and one with fruits.
I bought a variety of them.
You love these traditional sweets.
I can see right through you.
See...?
What do you mean you can see right through me?
I heard everything.
Your Elder found his biological granddaughter.
Your family and the Elder
are not even distant relatives.
Now that you're broke,
do you finally notice Jang-soo?
Didn't you come here to
give the kids a wedding?
Geum-sil, this isn't about our kids.
We're friends, right? That's why I came.
And I'm not broke!
It's true that I have no right to
inherit Elder's inheritance anymore,
but his one and only heiress
became my daughter-in-law.
What?
My daughter-in-law will inherit everything,
so it'll be the same thing, right?
It's like a golden calf came into our family.
And my daughter-in-law is so nice to me.
She bought me this.
And aside from everything else,
my daughter-in-law can't go against my son.
They love each other so much!
You were giving her a hard time because
she hid the fact she was from North Korea.
You really wear your heart on your sleeve.
Anyways, it seems like you and I are
deeply connected to North Korea.
We both have North Korean daughters-in-law.
You were upset too, right?
Ask your daughter-in-law if...
she has a grandfather or
any other relatives in South Korea.
Who knows? She might have a wealthy
grandfather, like my daughter-in-law.
How can you say that when you saw their house?
Goodness.
Wealthy grandfather, my foot! She brought two
burdens with her: her mother and her nephew!
She must really not know
that she has a grandfather
here, or else she would
have looked for him already.
But where did your daughter-in-law go?
I don't see her.
She went to work.
Really?
I heard your son was fired from the law firm.
It's a relief your daughter-in-law
is working at least.
But where does she work?
At the marketing team in Winner's Group.
What?
Where?
Winner's Group?
Are you serious?
Yes.
But why are you so surprised?
Oh my god. I totally forgot I had plans.
See you later!
Isn't she curious how her daughter is living?
She didn't even check her room!
All she talked about was my daughter-in-law.
Hold on.
Did she come here to
show off her daughter-in-law?
My goodness!
Oh, no. How can she be
working at Winner's Group?
How can things become so messy like this?
What if she bumps into Mr. Kim,
and they recognize each other?
They're blood relatives, after all!
Oh, my!
Welcome back, father- I mean Mr. Kim.
Did you go somewhere, too?
Oh, yes.
Did the board meeting go well?
Yes, mother.
Grandfather became the temporary chairman.
Really? Congratulations!
It's only until the company becomes stable.
Good job today, Shin-ae.
Go and rest.
Okay. You should rest, too.
I will.
We're in big trouble! Come here!
What is it?
You tell me first.
Why? Do you have something to tell me as well?
What is it?
You go first.
The thing is... oh my gosh.
We're in big trouble.
Mi-poong works at our company!
What? You knew about this, too?
I just found out a while ago.
She works in the marketing team.
Grandfather and I were leaving the
board meeting and ran right into Mi-poong.
Oh my goodness! Did Mr. Kim see her, too?
Grandfather and Mi-poong already know
each other. They met at Imjingak before.
What? Is that true?
Oh my goodness! What do we do?
Mr. Kim is going to work at the company, too!
Then he'll be able to see her often!
If they keep bumping into each other,
the secret will be revealed!
If Mr. Kim asks her...
what her father's name is and
what her name was in North Korea...
then it'll be over for us!
We need to separate them to
make sure that never happens!
How?
Mother, I should go work in the company.
Yes! Do that!
Work there and chase her out!
Come in.
Grandfather, have some chrysanthemum tea.
All right.
The both of you came in together.
Do you have something to tell me?
Yes.
Shin-ae wants to work at the company.
You want to work at the company?
Yes, grandfather.
I want to work.
Before I got married, I used to work
at one of Winner's fashion store,
and mother suggested I work as well.
Yes. I can do the housework.
I think it would be a huge loss
to the company, society, country,
and the world if my skillful
daughter-in-law stays stuck at home!
Why is she overreacting?
Grandfather will become suspicious.
Well, this company might become yours
one day, so you should learn the business.
Thank you, grandfather.
But since when did the
two of you become so close?
It makes me very happy to see
the two of you getting along.
Shin-ae is so kind, father- I mean Mr. Kim.
Hello. I'm Lawyer Lee Jang-go.
I have an interview with the president.
I see. Please hold on.
Sir, Lawyer Lee Jang-go is here.
All right. I understand.
He said he'll call you next time.
Pardon?
I'm so sorry, Jang-go.
It's fine. You don't need to feel sorry.
- Jang-go.
- Yes?
I think I should tell you this.
What is it?
Jang & Ko Law Firm is acting low because you
broke off the engagement with Jang Ha-yeon.
- What?
- Mr. Jang has a wide circle.
Time will bury what happened, but for now, it
won't be easy for you to enter a law firm.
You know this industry is small.
Cheer up. Let's get a drink soon.
- Okay.
- Call me.
Thank you.
Ha-yeon, eat up.
Thank you, Ms. Hwang.
But I don't know if it's okay
for me to be here or not.
It's fine. No one's home right now.
That's why I asked you to come.
I would feel more comfortable
if I made you your favorite noodles
one last time before you left.
Thank you.
You're leaving for England tomorrow?
Yes.
I thought you were going to end ties with me
because you ended ties with Jang-go.
Thank you for calling me.
I should be the one grateful
to you for inviting me like this.
You know how I feel, don't you?
I really thought of you as my daughter.
It really would have been nice if we had
become mother-in-law and daughter-in-law.
I'm so upset.
I shouldn't have said that.
I'm sorry. Eat up. Here.
Did someone come?
Oh, my. Who is this?
Geum-sil, what's going on?
Ha-yeon is leaving for England tomorrow,
so I invited her here to have some noodles.
Ms. Hwang, I'll be going now.
No, Ha-yeon, eat before you go.
No, it's okay.
Good-bye.
Ha-yeon, eat before you go. Ha-yeon!
Ha-yeon.
Ha-yeon!
Is she saying good-bye to her lover?
Why is she being so mournful?
Ha-yeon.
I'm so sorry.
No, Ms. Hwang.
Don't come out. I'll be leaving now.
Forget about everything here and live well.
I will. Thank you.
Why am I tearing up?
Don't skip your meals and don't get sick.
Got it?
Thank you for everything.
No, I'm grateful to you.
Ha-yeon,
in our next lifetime,
let's meet as mom and daughter.
Ms. Hwang...
- Ha-yeon.
- My goodness.
- What on earth is going on?
- What's wrong with her?
Oh, no!
Ms. Hwang, I'll be going now.
It's cold, so go inside.
- I'll see you off.
- No, it's okay.
Ha-yeon.
Grandmother and aunt, I'm back.
I'm saying this because you might understand,
but we really didn't know she was here.
It's the truth! My mom and
I didn't know! We just came home!
I'm going to change my clothes first.
Geum-sil is being too harsh.
How would Mi-poong feel right now?
What on earth is going on?
Hey. What are you trying to do?
What? "In our next lifetime,
let's meet as mom and daughter?"
How can you say that when you
have your own daughter-in-law?
And how dare you invite Ha-yeon to our house!
Are you crazy? Do you have dementia?
I thought of Ha-yeon as my daughter.
But was it so wrong of me to call her over
and give her a bowl of noodles?
Am I doing this because of noodles?
And if you wanted to feed her noodles,
you could have met her
outside and bought her some.
I can't invite someone I like to our house?
Do you think what you did was right?
Fine!
If you like Ha-yeon so much, no need
to push this into the next lifetime!
I'll buy you a plane ticket to England.
Go and be her mother there.
- Mom!
- Ask anyone on the streets what they think!
They'll say you're crazy!
Goodness.
Yes, I think you were
wrong this time, Geum-sil.
I'm almost always on your side,
but this is really wrong.
Would I do this if I had any other choice?
I wouldn't have such lingering attachment
if Mi-poong was from a normal family!
Do you know how I feel, Nam-yi?
You never had a kid before,
so how would you know how I feel?
Geum-sil, are you done talking?
No matter how upset you are,
you shouldn't act like this to me.
Do you think I didn't have
a kid because I didn't want to?
I got divorced because I couldn't have
a kid, so how can you say that to me?
Oh my gosh!
So don't say anything to me!
Do you know how I feel right now?
What's all this about?
Mom, did you invite Ha-yeon to our house?
Yes, I did!
Ha-yeon is leaving for England tomorrow,
so I told her to come here
so that I could see her
one last time, you jerk!
Mom!
Jang-go, I gave her an
earful already, so don't do anything.
Kim Mi-poong.
The onions are making me cry.
Go over there. The onions are spicy.
I'm sorry.
You were upset, huh?
No, I'm fine.
So don't say anything to mother. Okay?
Okay.
I'm going to wait.
Mother will realize
my feelings one day, won't she?
I have hope, so I'm okay.
Yes, she will.
My wife is so adorable.
- Good-bye.
- Bye. Go home safely.
Excuse me.
Mr. Jo!
- You're done with work, right?
- Yes. But what are you doing here?
I have something to tell you.
To me?
What is it about that
you came all the way here for?
Oh my goodness! Oh, no! Your jacket is ruined!
It's fine. I can just wash it.
Thanks to you, I'm fine.
It's cold outside. If we stay here, we might
get wet again, so let's go inside and talk.
If it's okay with you, I was hoping you
would come work at Deokcheonok again.
That's a bit...
Ms. Kim suddenly said
she wouldn't be able to come out
because she had to
take care of her pregnant daughter.
So can you work with us again?
Ms. Koo and Ms. Choi would
like you to come back as well.
If it's too difficult for you,
how about for only a month?
I thought of the people at
Deokcheonok often as well.
All right.
You helped me so much.
To pay you back, I'll do my best.
Thank you, Ms. Joo.
But the restaurant I'm working at
right now will need to hire someone else,
so I think you will need
to give me some time.
Of course! Take your time
finishing up your current job.
Yes, I'll do that. Thank you.
Hi, it's me.
Mr. Kim?
Okay. I'll be there soon.
I was hoping Dal-ho could do the job,
but I can't do anything without him.
Shin-ae said she wants
to work at Winner's Group.
How about you start
working with her, Hee-dong?
Yes, Hee-dong. You should help
Mr. Kim with his business now.
I'm sorry, but I like
the job I'm doing right now.
Hee-dong, you shouldn't reject Mr. Kim.
You must accept it.
No, no. This is something
we can't force him to do.
I won't be able to come
to work every single day,
but I'll be able to help make the company
newsletter while doing my own job.
That's a great idea.
You can start with that then.
Yes, thank you. I'll do that, grandfather.
That idiot!
He should be taking a position as a director!
Newsletter, my foot!
Hello, Mr. Kim.
Who's this? It's Kim Mi-poong!
Yes.
But what are you doing here?
I work in the marketing team here.
That brat!
Why does she keep getting in my way?
I need to enter the company
and chase her out somehow
to make sure she can't
bump into grandfather anymore.
What's on your mind?
Huh? Oh, nothing.
I'm just a bit nervous
about going into the company.
But we were going to have a baby.
Won't it be difficult
since you're going to work at the company now?
If I get pregnant, I can just
take a break from working.
Our baby is more important than work.
I wish we can have a baby soon.
I want a daughter who is just like you.
I want a son who is just like you.
Kim Mi-poong.
What's all this? What are you
doing when you should be sleeping?
I'm preparing some things
for breakfast tomorrow.
I think I'm going to be too busy getting
ready for work in the morning.
Will our family die of
starvation if you don't cook?
How will you go to work tomorrow like this?
No. Come in and sleep.
I just need to make the radish shreds.
Then I'll be done.
Okay then. Give it to me. I'll do it.
Go in and sleep.
How will you make the radish shreds?
I was part of the kitchen police
when I was in the army.
What do you think you're doing in the kitchen?
Go in first. I'll quickly
finish this up and go in.
You make me so happy.
What do you want me to do? Stop doing
the radish shreds? Should we just go in?
Go in.
- I'm good, huh?
- Yes.
This soybean stew is so delicious!
How did you make this?
Is it North Korean style?
That's right! It's delicious!
I don't need any other
side dishes because of this.
If you make soybean stew the wrong way,
it can get brittle and have a bad smell.
But this is very delicious.
My wife made all of this.
Keep that in mind as you eat.
All the men in our family
become fools when they get married.
You must have gone through a lot
of trouble to make breakfast, Mi-poong.
Thank you for enjoying the food.
But I need to go to work...
Yes. You'll be late.
Go and get ready. I'll give you a ride.
No, the subway is faster.
But what about the dishes?
Leave them! Hee-ra isn't
doing anything, so why worry?
Hurry up and go to work.
Yes, grandma.
What? "Hee-ra isn't doing anything?"
How annoying!
I'm getting compared because of her!
(We are currently examining and fixing it.)
What's this, grandpa?
It's a car, of course.
It's my gift to you
for your first day of work.
- Grandfather, thank you!
- You're welcome.
He gave her a credit card to use freely
and even bought her a new car. She's lucky.
Drive carefully. Don't speed. Be safe.
Yes, grandfather.
- I'll drive you to work.
- Sure.
No! It's dangerous!
No, it's fine.
My granddaughter said
she'll give me a ride. I should accept.
Let's go, Shin-ae.
Yes, grandfather.
- Bye, mother.
- Bye.
Good-bye.
That fox has nine tails.
No. She's not a fox anymore.
She's my treasure now.
Yes. I couldn't wish for more if
she just lives happily with my Hee-dong.
Hello, Mr. Kim.
That's our new chairman, and the
woman beside him is his granddaughter.
Oh my gosh. Then is that woman going
to be the owner of Winner's Group?
Yup!
Mi-poong, aren't you coming?
That elderly man is Winner Group's chairman?
Yes.
Mi-poong, you can't call him that. You need
to call him chairman. Chairman Kim. Let's go.
Mi-poong.
What's going on?
I can't even believe
he's Shin-ae's grandfather.
But her grandfather is the chairman of
our company? How can this happen?
Ms. Kim! Ms. Kim! Ms. Kim!
We have a new director!
- Another one?
- Yes.
This is your new director.
I'm Park Shin-ae.
I look forward to working with you.
Hello. I'm Kim Bo-young.
Please help me out, Ms. Kim.
Kim Mi-poong.
Earlier, I pretended not to know you
because you might be uncomfortable.
From now on, I'll only act like
I know you when it's just the two of us.
Is that okay?
Sure.
And...
I hope you can call me Ms. Park
when we're in the company.
Sure, Ms. Park.
I'm busy, so I'll leave first.
(Director Park Shin-ae)
Grandfather! Mr. Heo!
Did you say hello to the marketing team?
Yes, grandfather.
- Mr. Heo.
- Yes, sir?
Shin-ae won't know a lot of things,
so I hope you can help her out.
Don't worry, sir.
Please help me out.
Work hard.
I will.
Then I'll draw some sketches before I leave.
Thank you for giving me permission
to do an interview with you.
It's not a problem. You donated
comic books to us and helped us a lot.
I didn't do anything.
Then I'll be going.
Mister, are you okay?
Does it hurt a lot?
Ouch! Yes, it hurts a lot!
A lump the size of my fist has grown!
Don't lie! There's no lump
that can be the size of a fist!
What's your name?
Kang Yoo-jin.
Kang Yoo-jin? That's a pretty name.
Yes! People say I have
a pretty name but a prettier face!
What?
But you speak in a dialect.
I'm an ethnic Korean from China.
I'm Miss Yanbian.
Miss Yanbian from China?
It's nice to meet you, Miss Yanbian.
Do you like the jacket?
I do.
It's very warm...
aunt.
When it's just the two of us,
you can call me mom.
Really?
Can I really call you mom?
Yes, but only when it's just the two of us.
You know what I mean, don't you?
Okay, Yoo-jin.
I'm starting to work now,
so I can only come on the weekends.
So don't wait for me, okay?
You didn't tell anyone about me, did you?
I didn't tell anyone.
Good.
You can't tell anyone about me.
You can't tell the orphanage director
or your friends either. Got it?
If they ask you who I am,
tell them I'm your aunt.
That way,
you'll be able to live with me later.
Do you know what I mean?
Okay, Yoo-jin.
Is it too dark?
No, no. This is good enough.
It's been a while since I wore a mini skirt.
What on earth am I
supposed to do with my legs?
Hello.
Hi, Won-bin.
The wind is blowing outside,
but you're almost naked. Aren't you cold?
What do you mean I'm almost naked?
And the room is heated nicely,
so I'm not cold at all.
Why? Is my outfit weird?
No, it's not weird at all.
It's totally my style!
Won-bin, go to the bakery downstairs
and eat some bread.
Yes, father.
What are you trying to do here?
What's wrong?
From now on,
don't come to work looking like this.
What? Can't I choose what I want to wear?
It doesn't suit my store.
I hate uncomfortable clothes like those.
Everyone else said I was pretty.
Your eyes are strange.
Who the heck said you were pretty?
I can't even look at you!
What did you say?
Geum-sil has a good taste of fashion.
You should ask her for advice
and dress like her.
What? Dress like her?
Yes! Sophisticated and ladylike like her!
Just like her!
Fine! I got it!
Take my sophisticated and ladylike
sister-in-law and work with her!
I'm going home now!
Nam-yi! Lee Nam-yi!
The primary banks are back to normal.
It's all thanks to you, sir.
Mr. Kim, you look tired.
The meeting with the presidents of
the banks went on for too long, didn't it?
No. I just need to go up to
my office and rest a bit.
- Mr. Kim!
Call 119!
Mr. Kim! Mr. Kim!
- Call 119!
- Mr. Kim! He's not breathing!
- Hurry! Hurry! Hurry!
- Mr. Kim!
Someone must have fainted!
- Call 119!
- Mr. Kim!
Mr. Kim isn't breathing!
Hurry up and call 119!
- Mr. Kim, wake up!
- Mr. Kim!
Hold on!
Are they on their way?
Stop it! You'll make it worse!
Get out of the way!
It hasn't been long since
I came here, and yet,
I miss home so much. How did
you manage to live all this time?
- Kim Mi-poong?
- My name is Kim Mi-poong.
My name is Kim Deok-cheon.
One day, you'll meet them.
When I met you at Imjingak for the first time,
you didn't feel like a stranger at all.
What a coincidence!
- Mr. Kim!
Hurry!
Hurry! Carry him!
Mr. Kim! Mr. Kim! Mr. Kim!
Hurry up!
Mr. Kim...
Mr. Kim, can you see me?
Are you okay?
What happened?
You fainted in the company lobby.
I remember that.
According to Dr. Yang,
you could have been in real trouble
if CPR hadn't been performed
on you when you had fainted.
I almost died today.
But who was the one who performed CPR on me?
She's a female employee of our company.
A female employee?
I'm very grateful to her.
Find out who that female employee
who saved my life is.
Grandfather! Grandfather!
Grandfather, what happened?
I was so scared something
bad happened to you...
I can't live without you!
I'm fine. I'm fine.
Oh, that fox. She's one great actress.
She would succeed as an actress.
I'm fine.
He's completely fine.
Human lives are so long and persistent.
Mr. Kim is fine.
- Thank goodness.
- Really? He's really okay?
Yes, I personally talked on the phone
with Mr. Heo who went to the hospital.
Mr. Kim asked who had saved his life.
Thanks to you, I was complimented.
He said our third marketing team was the best.
Really?
Mi-poong, are you crying?
You must have been very worried about him.
Just... in spite of myself...
Anyways, you're amazing.
I know. I should learn CPR, too!
I know.
How about we learn as a group?
That's a good idea. Let's do that.
Since we got our paychecks today,
how about we go get a drink?
- Deal!
- I'm in!
I have to hurry up and go home...
Fine, but only this time.
Okay.
Where did everyone go without me?
This is like living deep in
the mountains by myself.
Woe is me.
Hey, Sung-chik!
Gwi-ok, there's a big game today.
Want to play?
One of our members suddenly left.
Oh, really?
Where is it?
Yes.
I'll be there!
Bye!
Rather than leech off this house,
I'd rather win big
and leave this damn house with Chung-ja!
Hold on.
I have no money.
Chung-ja, I'm sorry.
I'll win big and pay you back
ten times as much!
- Goodness!
- Maid!
- Oh, no!
- Where did the maid go?
Maid!
Bring two warm cups of
Chinese quince tea to my room.
Close the door.
That old man got right back up.
I think he'll live to be
over a hundred years old.
I'm so anxious that I can't sleep lately.
No one else knows in this
world but us two, so don't worry.
What are they talking about?
The real one is hanging around him,
so how can I not be anxious?
What if Mr. Kim finds out you're an imposter?
I keep dreaming of being
kicked out in this cold weather.
What can I do?
Mom!
What do you mean she's an imposter?
Shin-ae is an imposter?
Mom...
Let go of me!
How can this happen?
Mom, please!
You damned woman! How dare you mess
with moral laws of family relationships!
You're going to get punished!
Mom, Shin-ae and I are
prepared to be punished, but
we'll be punished next time, so please mom...!
No matter how much you want
his inheritance, how can you do this?
Mom! This isn't just beneficial for us!
Look how happy Mr. Kim is
after finding his granddaughter!
That's good, isn't it?
You said his real granddaughter
hangs around him!
No! There's no real granddaughter!
I heard you say that with my own two ears!
How dare you blatantly lie to me!
I'm serious, mom!
There is no real granddaughter!
- Are you telling the truth?
- Yes.
You just have to pretend this
didn't happen. You'll do that, won't you?
Or else all of us will be kicked out of here!
Do you want to see me go broke?
There's no mother in this world
who wishes for her child to go broke.
Then you need to take this
secret with you to your grave.
Got it?
Fine.
It already happened.
There's nothing we can do about it.
I can't help you,
but I won't let you go under.
Thank you.
To your grave.
What's this? Then I don't have
to worry about my later years!
They're not home yet.
Let's go inside.
Mom! Yoo-sung!
- Mi-poong!
- Aunt!
What are you doing here?
You're right next door. I bought some
tangerines on my way home from work.
You guys love tangerines.
And this is your pocket money.
I got paid today.
Mi-poong, you're married now.
You don't have to take care of me like this.
Why do I go to work?
It's for you and Yoo-sung.
Right, Yoo-sung?
Of course!
- Mom, have a tangerine.
- I will.
It looks tasty.
- But mom...
- Yes?
The thing is...
do you know who Shin-ae's grandfather is?
He's the chairman of our company.
Oh my goodness. Are you serious?
Yes. Shin-ae became the director
of the marketing team.
That kind of influential person
is Shin-ae's grandfather?
She told me to call her Ms. Park.
Gosh, I don't want to. It makes me
so bad that I'm her subordinate.
Come on. Don't be like that.
That's her blessing.
Shin-ae was rebuked by
her mother-in-law all this time,
but now, she has an amazing grandfather.
Shin-ae lived a hard life. Wish her the best.
That way, you can be blessed, too.
You go ahead and wish her
the best. I can't do that.
Goodness. Fine.
I'll have to wish her the best twice
as much so that you can be blessed.
But mom, Shin-ae's grandfather,
who is our chairman,
had a heart attack in the lobby today,
but I saved him using CPR.
Really?
Yes.
My goodness!
You did something amazing! There's nothing
more amazing than saving someone's life!
You're amazing!
My daughter!
Hold on.
Mom, I'm late. Bye, mom. Bye, Yoo-sung.
Take some of these.
She must lead a hard married life.
Look at her get up and go so quickly.
Goodness! I forgot to give her
the green onion kimchi!
Mother.
Did you go to your family's house
as soon as you finished work?
Didn't you hear what I said?
Why did you get married
if you were going to do this?
Just live in your family's house.
I just dropped by...
What? Dropped by?
What time does your work end?
What do you mean "dropped by?"
And when I talk to you, all you
have to say is, "Yes, I understand."
How dare you talk back to me!
I'm sorry, mother.
What are you standing there for?
Go in and make dinner!
Okay.
I'm so full.
I already had a slice of pizza,
so I don't need to eat dinner.
Wash these, too, while you're at it.
Hee-ra.
What is it? Did you just call for me?
We need to talk.
Why did you call me out
all the way to the playground?
Hurry up and talk. I'm cold.
Hee-ra...
we're both daughters-in-law.
So?
While we're living together,
I believe we need to be courteous
of one another and get
all the chores done together.
Are you doing this just because
I asked you to wash the two cups
and one plate while
you were washing the dishes?
My goodness.
Since I'm working,
I was hoping you could make dinner.
I'll make breakfast, so please make dinner.
I never did such a thing before,
so I can't do it.
If you want to make breakfast, you can,
but why are you asking me to make dinner?
So you're just going to pile up the
dishes and do nothing about them?
Whether I do nothing or something,
it's none of your business!
Go ahead and make breakfast if you want to!
Stop right there!
This is ridiculous.
Who are you to tell me to stop right there?
Before you came into this family,
I lived a peaceful, perfect life.
After you came into our family, grandma
has been scolding me. It pisses me off!
Mi-poong!
Jang-go!
What are you doing here?
Well...
Were you waiting for me?
What is that you're hiding?
Huh? Oh, this?
Fish-shaped red bean buns!
- Fish-shaped red bean buns?
- Yup.
My mother loves these.
So I bought them as bribery
so she could treat you nicely.
Want one? They're still warm.
Let's eat them together at home.
Should we?
Let's go! It's cold.
Hi, Mr. Heo.
Hi, Mr. Kim.
The one who performed CPR on you today is Kim
Mi-poong who works in the marketing team.
What?
Kim Mi-poong?
Hold on.
She was the one who saved me?
My goodness!
Who did you prepare such a feast for?
The company board members?
I don't think so.
It must be an important person.
Mr. Kim insisted we prepare
a great meal with sincerity.
Really? Then is it that broker from China?
Broker?
No way!
Mr. Kim found his granddaughter, so why
would he need to meet the broker again?
That's why they say, "wrongdoing just
makes your own life miserable."
Don't mind her. She's just saying that.
Okay.
- What about father?
- He's on a business trip in Busan
running an errand for Mr. Kim.
Grandfather, who is coming today?
She's the person who saved me
with CPR when I fainted last time.
You know her, too.
I do?
Shin-ae knows her?
Who is she?
Hello.
Hello. Welcome, Mi-poong!
(Blow Breeze)
Is your grandmother in North Korea?
My grandmother...
Let's go to my room.
Shin-ae, I have something to tell her,
so can you wait outside?
We need to make her go
somewhere we can't see her.
I should shave my head
and go live in the mountain.
You should chase her out!
Wow! That's a lot of cabbage!
There are only a hundred of them.
Make kimchi on your own.
I know you.
- Don't make me tired.
- That brat!
Don't forget what I told you.
Can I call you when I miss you?
Subtitles by OnDemandKorea