Subtitles by OnDemandKorea
(Episode 29)
- What about father?
- He's on a business trip in Busan
running an errand for Mr. Kim.
Grandfather, who is coming today?
She's the person who saved me
with CPR when I fainted last time.
You know her, too.
I do?
Shin-ae knows her?
Who is she?
Hello.
Hello. Welcome, Mi-poong.
This skinny girl saved you?
Yes. She's my savior.
If Mi-poong hadn't saved me,
I would be in heaven by now.
Oh my god. How can this happen?
Did they somehow connect with each other?
She saved her grandfather's life!
So you were the one who
saved my grandfather, Mi-poong?
Thank you. Welcome to our home.
I'm so embarrassed. I just did
something anyone would've done.
Yet, you invited me
to your house. Thank you.
Hello. You're Hee-ra's sister-in-law, right?
I met you at the wedding last time.
Oh, yes! Hello!
Oh, is that right?
You're Hee-ra's sister-in-law?
She is.
Wow. You and I must have a deep connection.
You knew Shin-ae in North Korea, too.
We're not strangers at all.
Do you like the food?
A famous hotel chef came and prepared it.
Oh, no wonder! The food was so delicious that
there were fireworks exploding in my mouth!
They were like, "What's going on?"
Goodness. You're such a witty
and adorable young lady.
Now that I'm married, I'm an old lady.
- Old lady?
Oh my goodness.
But when did you learn CPR?
I learned it in Pyeongyang
when I was in college.
You went to college in Pyeongyang?
Which college?
I majored in dancing at
Pyeongyang Arts University.
Majored in dancing?
But why aren't you doing work in that field?
Because it's hard to make a living with
North Korean dancing in South Korea.
And I forgot about it all now.
Yes, that's right.
You must have suffered through a lot.
But during winter,
what do people in North Korea eat?
It's similar to here.
We eat bean-curd dregs stew
and bean-curd dregs rice.
Bean-curd dregs rice?
I used to eat a lot of bean-curd
dregs rice when I was in North Korea.
My grandmother loved bean-curd
dregs rice, so I used to eat it a lot, too.
Really?
Is your grandmother in North Korea?
My grandmother-
- Oh, my!
- Hey!
Mom, are you okay?
- What will you do?
- I lost my wrist strength.
I'm sorry. My wrist isn't well these days.
Maid.
You should've been careful.
Once I'm done eating,
bring the tea to my room.
I have to talk with Mi-poong privately.
Yes, sir.
Hold on!
I'll go wipe my clothes.
Grandfather, eat some more.
That way, Mi-poong will eat more.
No, I'm done eating.
- You should eat more.
- No. Don't push yourself.
You shouldn't get sick from overeating.
Right. Thank you.
Mi-poong, let's go to my room.
Sure. Thank you for the meal.
Come this way.
- I'm going to go up.
- Okay.
What kind of secrets are they sharing
that they have to go into his room?
What are you two doing?
Why are you guys secretly
making eye-contact? What are you up to now?
Mom, what are you talking about?
When did we secretly make eye-contact?
It's not like we're secret lovers.
- Shin-ae, take the tea inside.
- Yes, mother!
Please give it to me.
Grandfather, drink the green tea.
You, too, Mi-poong.
Shin-ae,
I have to talk to Mi-poong privately,
so can you go outside?
Sure, grandfather.
- Go ahead and talk.
- Okay.
- Did you eat well?
- Yes, the food was very delicious.
What does he need to tell her that
he told you to go outside? What do we do?
Mother!
Stop your rebel meeting. Come here
and eat some fruit. The pear is very sweet.
Take this.
What's this?
You saved my life.
I didn't think I should just
sit by and do nothing.
Don't worry. It's not a big amount.
Just think of it as pocket money
I'm giving you.
No, Mr. Kim!
It's my heart.
No, I'm just grateful you
invited me to your house. I mean it.
Accept it.
That way I'll feel comfortable.
How about you buy me a lot of delicious
meals later on instead? You can just do that.
What?
Then how many meals do I have to buy?
You can buy me many, many meals and coffee.
All right then.
Let's do that.
Where did it go?
What happened?
Where did it go? Chung-ja! Shin-ae!
What's wrong?
My ring! Where did my ring go?
Huh? Your ring?
Yes, my ring! My ring in the frame!
Where else would it be? It's in your room.
It's not there! That's why I'm doing this!
Did you remove the ring in
the frame in Mr. Kim's room?
No! Isn't that on top of the table?
I didn't touch it!
I'll look for it!
What's going on?
What kind of ring is it?
Well, it's-
Go and do your job.
Fine.
Mi-poong, I think you should leave.
- The situation is pretty bad right now.
- Okay.
I won't escort you out. Go home safe.
But I think I should say good-bye
to Mr. Kim and the other adults.
I'll talk to them. Don't worry about it.
Bye!
Oh, dear! Where did it go?
Did anyone come into my room?
Nope!
Only the maid and I came to clean in here.
This is very strange indeed!
For sure I saw that it was here!
You still haven't found it yet?
When was the last time you saw it?
I saw it this morning for sure!
Oh! Here it is!
- It's right here!
- Where?
- It was right here all along.
- Where? Where?
It wasn't there when I was looking for it.
Goodness. The maid must have left it under the
blanket on accident while
she was cleaning the room.
From now on, don't let the maid clean my room!
Yes, sir.
Grandfather, I'll clean your room
from now on, so don't worry about it.
Okay, I think that would be best.
Hold on. What about Mi-poong?
She left a while ago.
Oh, dear. She must have left
because of the commotion.
I feel so bad when I invited her over.
Don't worry.
It seemed like she had other plans.
Really?
But what ring was it?
Hey, I'm here.
Welcome.
What about Young-soon and Chung-ja?
Young-soon is almost here, and Chung-ja can't
make it. She has something going on at home.
Oh, really?
But did something good happen to Young-soon?
Why is she suddenly offering to buy a meal?
Young-soon's son is getting married.
She's so happy because her daughter-in-law
is the daughter of a hospital director.
Oh, really?
- I'm here.
- Hi.
We were wondering when you would be here. But
Young-soon, that mink coat is so beautiful!
My daughter-in-law gave it to me as
a wedding present along with this bag.
Your fate completely changed,
thanks to your wealthy daughter-in-law.
This won't do. The smell of
meat will get on my mink coat.
I'm going to put it in the car.
Go ahead and order.
But her son is a health trainer.
How did he end up marrying the
daughter of a hospital director?
He met her while helping her
work out at the gym.
As a wedding gift, her daughter-in-law gave
a foreign car and an apartment to her son.
Geum-sil, to be honest, I thought
your son would end up with the best life.
Why are you saying that? They just
have to live happily from now on.
Let's just order meat.
Geum-sil. Geum-sil.
What?
Isn't that your in-law over there?
Does your in-law work here?
No! She doesn't!
Oh, dear. I forgot I had urgent plans.
Sorry. I'll be leaving first. Enjoy the food.
Geum-sil!
Young-soon, you should have
just pretended you didn't notice!
Gosh!
Oh my gosh! I'm so humiliated!
I'd rather shave my head and
enter the mountains than endure this!
What do you want?
Mom, what should I make for dinner?
Should I make kimchi stew with pork?
Get out.
Pardon?
I want to live without seeing you.
I even hate seeing your heels!
Mother...
I hate your mother! I hate you, too!
I think I'm going to get sick
just looking at you.
Can't you just leave Jang-go alone
and take your family out of my house?
Mother, I'm sorry.
I'll do better from now on.
I'll make more of an effort.
I never told you to do better!
I tried holding it in for the sake of
Jang-go, but I really can't do this.
Mother...
Get out! Get out of this room!
I don't want to see your face!
Hurry up and get out!
Gosh. What's all this?
My goodness.
I can't live!
What about Hee-dong?
He's working in the other room.
What's wrong?
I'm so nervous I could die.
Mi-poong, the girl who came earlier,
is working at
Mr. Kim's company,
and she's the sister-in-law of Hee-ra.
It's only a matter of time before
it's revealed that you're an imposter!
That's not true.
As long as you and I keep our mouths shut,
we'll be fine, so why do
you keep saying such things?
The only thing we can do
is send Mi-poong and her
family far away to a place
where we can't see them.
First, chase her out of the company
using whatever method you can.
That way, Mi-poong and Mr. Kim won't meet up.
I know. That's why I entered the company.
All right. Do whatever
you can to chase her out.
I’ll do whatever I can to make her
leave Geum-sil's house.
That's the only way we'll be able to live!
Geum-sil, I'm here!
I knew you would be like this.
Why are you here again?
If you're here to put salt
on my wounds, just leave.
I just came to visit you. That's all.
Here. Have some sweet red bean porridge.
I'll eat it later.
I don't have an appetite right now.
Young-soon called me.
You guys met at a rib restaurant
yesterday, but you left without eating.
Why is your in-law
working there of all places?
My head hurts, so don't even bring that up.
It would have been wonderful if your son had
gotten married to the
daughter of that law firm.
Oh my goodness. Are you crying?
I don't know.
I just start tearing up for no reason at all.
I keep thinking about Ha-yeon.
Ha-yeon?
The daughter of that law firm?
I got attached to her. I miss her.
Poor you.
But is your new daughter-in-law that terrible?
I don't want to even look at her.
Either they move out or I shave my head
and move into the mountains.
I can't live with her.
Goodness. Why would you leave?
You should kick her out.
Kick her out?
How?
Even if I tell her to leave,
she says she'll do better
and sticks to this house like a leech.
Oh my goodness! You'll get ill with anger!
Oh, no.
Geum-sil, should I teach you the method
to chase your daughter-in-law out of here?
Method? What method?
Jang-go loves her so much,
so how will I be able to do that?
If you really want to chase her out,
you should make her quit her job first.
Make her quit her job?
Yes! That way, you'll be able to
keep her home and give her a hard time!
I'll teach you all you need to know in
order to chase your daughter-in-law out.
Thank you.
What will I do with her?
She's here. She's there. She's everywhere!
(Director Park Shin-ae)
I need to give Hee-ra a store?
Yes, right now!
If we want to make Mi-poong quit this
company and chase her out of her house,
Hee-ra shouldn't be home.
If Hee-ra is home, Mi-poong can't
be the only one to do the housework!
Did her mother-in-law say she would do that?
Yes. My friend Geum-sil will do
anything to get rid of Mi-poong.
She's so angry right now!
Really?
Yes!
She's going to make Mi-poong
quit her job and then give her
a hard time at home until
she leaves the house on her own.
Fine.
If her mother-in-law lectures
for her to quit her job
and you come up with
an issue to blame her with,
she won't be able to endure anymore
and she'll leave the company.
So hurry up and give a store to Hee-ra!
You're a director now. You have
enough power to do that. Come on. Here.
I got it.
Hee-ra, this is really your store?
Yes. After my training, I'll become
the owner of this store next week!
That's great!
This is all thanks to my mom and Shin-ae.
Thanks, Chung-ja.
No problem.
Thank you for everything. Thank you for loving
my daughter as your own. Thank you so much.
It's nothing.
- Hee-ra!
- Jang-soo!
- What's going on?
- Oh, come on!
Jang-soo! Thank your mother-in-law first!
Hello, mother!
Hi.
Run this store well and succeed.
Next spring, you can have an official wedding.
Mom, are you serious?
Yes, but if this business goes under,
you'll get nothing!
That'll never happen! Never!
Thank you, mother!
We'll do our best!
Jang-soo!
Hee-ra!
The store was so big, clean, and nice!
The location is so great
that business will go well!
When business goes well
and I make a lot of money,
I'll give it all to you, mother and grandma!
Don't even lie like that.
I'm serious!
Manage the business well
so that it doesn't go under.
That way, you'll be able to
have a wedding next spring.
Yes, grandma.
People without their in-law's
connections will be so sad.
Hey. Are you talking about me?
Don't blame me. Blame your fate.
Since we have good in-laws,
they gave us a store.
They're supporting us so that we don't
have to worry about their daughter's living.
That's why everyone is
bragging about their in-laws.
I was worried because Jang-soo didn't
have a proper job. Now I can relax a bit.
Geez, mom. Why worry about me?
We lived well so far.
And I'm going to succeed, so don't you worry!
Gosh. All you do is boast.
I'm going to make a lot of money from now on
and take care of Jang-soo, so don't you worry!
- Thanks.
- All right then.
This is all thanks to your family, so be good
to your parents. Jang-soo,
be good to your in-laws.
Yes, I got it.
But Jang-go,
you quit working for Jang & Ko Law Firm.
For how much longer
will you waste your life away?
What do you mean waste my life away?
I'm going to work at my friend's office.
Really? That's great!
Come on, mother. How is that great?
He doesn't even have his own office. He has to
walk on eggshells in someone else's office.
Obviously, he won't be able to make any money.
But that all becomes experience.
When will he be able to settle down?
That's why I told him that
he needs good in-laws.
Mom.
Goodness. You're embarrassing Mi-poong.
How can you say that right in front of her?
I don't even meet my friends lately.
Do you know why?
Everyone says that Jang-go
is a waste. That they thought Jang-go
would turn out the best. That he
met in-laws who leech off of him.
How would you feel if you hears such things?
I want to talk nicely, but I can't.
Kim Mi-poong.
What's on your mind?
Nothing.
Is it because of what my mom said earlier?
Don't worry about it.
What's with that expression?
Don't you trust me?
I can go work at my friend's
office and settle down quickly.
My mom won't be so upset
after she sees me settle down.
Don't worry.
All right. I trust you.
Excuse me.
I need to speak to you.
I'll get straight to the point.
You heard that I became the
owner of a fashion store, right?
Yes.
From now on, I'll be very busy
from early morning to late at night.
So don't make me tired with household chores
like making meals and doing the cleaning.
That's what I had to tell you.
Listen, Hee-ra.
I go to work early in the morning
and come home late at night,
too. Yet, I'm trying my best
to help with the housework.
Tell that to mother.
She told me to not worry about the
housework and just focus on the store.
So from now on, discuss the
housework with mother and not me.
Bye.
That brat!
What am I supposed to do?
Where are you? Come see me.
Quit your job.
Pardon?
What do you mean?
Hee-ra is going to be in
charge of the store now.
That's why you should quit your job,
stay home, and take care of our family.
Mother, I can't quit my job.
What?
Are you telling me to take care of
both my working daughters-in-law?
Mother, I'm working,
but I'm doing the best that I can.
Please tell Hee-ra that she and
I have to equally share the housework.
If you help me out a little...
How can you be so selfish?
Are you and Hee-ra alike?
Do you think your paycheck can even compare
with the money she makes at her store?
All of us have to help her out.
Goodness. You should be offering to quit
your work first. How can you be like this?
Mother, I would like to work.
Please allow me to.
It's the first official job I got ever
since I came here to South Korea.
I don't want to quit now.
Then what are you going
to do about the housework?
Nam-yi goes out to work. I need
to go to Hee-ra's shop and help out.
Do you want me to tell
my mother-in-law to do the housework?
Well...
I'll do my best.
So please allow me to work.
Really?
Then work and do all of
the housework by yourself.
I was telling you to quit your job because
you might have a hard time doing both.
But if you can do it,
then there's nothing I can do about it.
I'm done talking. You can leave.
Good night.
What are you doing in the middle of the night?
I was making some side dishes
for tomorrow's breakfast.
How can you only think of yourself?
Everyone else is asleep.
If you make so much noise
on that cutting board, they'll all wake up.
Or are you doing this
so that the whole neighborhood
will know I'm making you
work late into the night?
That's not it. The mornings
are really busy. That's why...
Then wake up early in
the morning and make them.
If you make the side dishes now,
will they be good in the morning?
All right.
How frustrating.
Hi.
What? Jung-geun's father?
All right.
I'll go to your house,
so let's carpool together.
Okay. Bye.
Hee-ra, eat this, too.
- Thank you.
- Me, too.
Here.
It's so delicious!
Did someone pass away?
Yes. My friend's father passed away.
I have to go to Yeosu.
All the way to Yeosu?
Then you won't be able to come home tonight.
Probably not.
Mi-poong, I'll be back.
- Bye.
- Be careful of cars!
- Okay.
- Bye!
Jang-go, be safe.
Hello!
Oh, my, Ms. Joo! You're here!
Have all of you been well?
You must be working here again.
Yes, I am.
I'm glad you came! The regular customers from
your home country have been looking for you!
- Really?
- Of course!
Ms. Joo, you're here.
Hello, Mr. Jo.
Hey, move.
Go away.
I was riding on the swings first.
Hurry up and move!
She must be a goat. She always does this.
Hey, you guys!
Why are you guys teasing
and bothering Yoo-jin?
Yoo-jin talks weirdly.
Don't cry.
Don't cry, Yoo-jin.
You're not a goat.
Last time I came, I told you about the bear
and chicken that traveled together, right?
Yes.
What did I tell you
when I was done reading the story?
You told us to play nicely with our friends.
All of you do remember.
Even a bear and a chicken became friends.
Should we tease and bother our friends
for speaking a little differently?
We shouldn't.
You guys are smart.
I brought storybooks today, too.
Make sure you share them
with each other and
play nicely with Yoo-jin.
Okay.
Yoo-jin, I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Good-bye, big brother!
Bye!
Thank you for earlier.
Did you just call me "big brother?"
You're handsome and cool,
so you're not an old man to me.
Wow.
I feel so happy that a pretty girl
like you called me her big brother.
But you really don't seem like an old man.
You seem like a big brother.
Um, Hee-dong...
Yes, Miss Yanbian?
Can I call you when something
happens or when I miss you?
Of course you can.
Then give me your phone number.
You have a cell-phone?
Yes. My aunt bought it for me.
You have an aunt?
Yes.
But that's a secret.
Only you should know it.
Promise.
Okay. I won't tell anyone.
What?
She can't quit her job?
Yes. She said she can never quit her job.
Geum-sil, were you being too soft to her?
No.
My daughter-in-law
was like that at first, too.
She said she would never leave
as long as she was alive.
She would leave when she was dead.
She really said that?
Yes.
I was so appalled back then.
Eventually, she left. She was a stubborn one.
Your daughter-in-law will leave, too.
But my daughter-in-law is stubborn, too.
She was making side dishes
at two in the morning.
That's why I told her to
make them early morning.
I don't know how she did it, but she managed
to prepare everything in the morning.
My goodness. She's not a normal one either.
If you told her to quit, she should quit.
She must think you were easy.
Make her quit her job and
force her to do the housework.
That's the only way she'll leave.
Chung-ja, my family is different from yours.
If she can't do the dishes because she's busy,
then my mother-in-law does it for her.
Sometimes, Nam-yi helps her, too.
Then...
send all the women in the house to the
hot springs for two nights and three days...
and force your daughter-in-law to make kimchi
with a hundred cabbages to exhaust her.
Should I?
Jang-go is away at a funeral and
won't be able to come home either.
Yes.
Hi, Geum-sil.
Hot springs?
Yes. Hee-ra's mother made reservations
at a nice hot springs for us.
Really?
I wasn't feeling well anyways, and I wanted
to dip my body into hot water, too.
But it will be for two nights
and three days. Will that be all right?
Yes. Don't worry.
Bye.
Yes. That's good.
I'm going to relax at the hot springs
and organize my mind there.
I should use this chance to quit, too.
Were there many customers today?
Yes.
I wrote it in the book.
Mr. Kim, I want to quit.
Pardon?
What are you suddenly talking about?
I told you to work with Geum-sil
who dresses so sophisticated.
Hold on.
You were serious?
Yes. Then I'm going home now.
Why on earth are you doing this?
If you  have a problem, you can just tell me.
I just think it would be the best
for the both of us if I quit right now.
You don't like me either.
Thank you for everything.
Good-bye.
Look here, Lee Nam-yi.
Lee Nam-yi!
Good-bye.
I'm so excited!
How long has it been since
we went to the hot springs?
I know. Let's relax in
the hot water, eat delicious foods,
and just forget about everything there!
You can forget about everything. If I forget
at this age, I'm going to get dementia.
- Oh, grandma!
- Why isn't Geum-sil coming out?
- I know.
- Mom!
- Mother!
- What?
- What do I do?
My friend's father passed away,
so I have to go the funeral.
We feel bad about going by ourselves.
I'm okay. I can go with my friends next time.
Nam-yi, take care of mother
and have a good time.
Okay. We'll be going then.
- Let's go.
- Be careful driving.
- I will.
- Bye, mother!
- Bye.
- Bye, mom.
Bye, mother!
- Bye!
- Have a good time!
Bye!
- It's so nice to go on a trip!
- I know!
Grandma, it's nice to go in a car, right?
Jang-soo, did you bring the flower cards?
Flower cards? No, I didn't.
- What?
- I brought them. You always
want to play flower cards on a trip.
Playing flower cards on
a trip is the most fun!
I can't stop you.
Don't stop me.
Yoo-sung, it's heavy, right?
No. I'm strong, so it's not heavy at all.
What about you?
I'm okay, too.
I'm not tired at all
because you're helping me.
- You mean it?
- Of course I do!
Wow! There are so many cabbages!
Are these all yours?
Wow! It's a mountain of cabbages!
Amazing!
Yoo-sung, put that over there and go home.
I'll make you yummy food soon. Okay?
Okay, aunt.
I'm back.
Hi. Did you buy the white radishes?
Yes, mother.
But there are a lot of cabbages...
That's not a lot.
There are only a hundred of them.
A hundred of them?
Unfortunately, my mother-in-law, Nam-yi,
Jang-soo, and Hee-ra went to the hot springs.
I'm not feeling very well, so go
ahead and make the kimchi by yourself.
Do I make all one hundred
cabbages into kimchi?
Is that too much?
I used to make a 100 cabbages
into kimchi all by myself.
Sometimes, I would make
150 cabbages into kimchi, too.
We need that much for all of
our family members to eat.
Why? You can't do it?
First, split the cabbage leaves
and preserve them in salt.
Good. Are you sick, Yoo-jin?
No.
Aren't you having a hard time there?
No, not at all.
Besides, you'll come pick
me up soon, so I can handle it.
You're a good girl, Yoo-jin.
Aunt, if I really wait six months...
if I really wait 150 days...
will we really be able to live together?
Of course.
So don't forget what I told you.
Okay. I won't tell anyone about you.
Good.
Shin-ae.
Who were you talking with?
Did you hang up because of me?
No, I had something to discuss with Mr. Yang.
- I'm done talking.
- You are?
Shin-ae, guess what I bought?
What is it?
Guess.
Close your eyes.
Open your eyes.
Oh, my! What are these?
Baby shoes.
They're so adorable!
But they're pink.
I was hoping we could have a daughter.
Do you like daughters?
I like both daughters and sons,
but I changed my mind today.
I really want a daughter
like that little girl.
Little girl?
Actually, I go to orphanages
sometimes to collect information.
One little girl called me her big brother.
It was so cute that I almost went crazy.
Really?
Shin-ae, can we have a pretty daughter?
That's not up to me.
Yes, it is.
All in.
All in. Accepted.
I'm dead.
Heukssal. Same thing.
Oh, dear. You're in a hurry.
I got jangttang.
- Wow.
- What the hell!
Thank you very much!
It was a fun game today.
Where do you think you're going?
Wait until I come back.
You're going to get more money?
I'm busy today.
I'll be back soon.
You better not go.
Come back again.
Mi-poong said she can't quit her job?
Yes. That's why she sent
her family to the hot springs
and forced her to make
kimchi out of a 100 cabbages!
Anyways, she won't be
able to come to work tomorrow.
Can't you fire people for
skipping work to make kimchi?
You can't fire people so easily these days.
Why can't you just fire people as you please?
Anyways, now that Geum-sil
has made up her mind,
she'll force Mi-poong to quit her job somehow.
But you never know what will happen.
Did you find out a way to get her fired?
Oh my gosh.
Mom, you scared me! Knock, will you?
Shin-ae, you were here, too. Good.
Where are you coming from?
What's with your face?
Did something happen outside?
Shin-ae. Chung-ja.
Give me $20,000.
$20,000?
Yes. Right this instant.
Mom, I haven't seen you all day.
Were you doing this again?
Are you going to give it to me or not?
If you won't, I'll go to Mr. Kim.
Mom!
When you get his inheritance later, you'll be
able to spend as much
as you want before you die.
Then what about me?
So give me some money right now.
That way it'll be fair.
Mom, what's wrong with you?
Fine then.
If you guys won't give me money,
I'll just go to Mr. Kim.
Mr. Kim! Mr. Kim!
- Mom!
- Grandmother!
Mr. Kim!
- Mom!
- Mr. Kim!
Mr. Kim!
What's wrong?
The thing is, I...
Is something wrong? Go ahead and tell me.
It's nothing, Mr. Kim.
- The thing is...
- Mom.
What's going on? Why won't you let her speak?
Please tell me.
I have something to ask you.
There's someone I know who sold balloon
flowers by lying that they were wild ginseng!
Mr. Kim, what should I do in this case?
It's someone I know really well.
What else should you do?
You must scold him.
You should report it to the police.
You can't let this slide just
because he's someone you know.
Right?
Of course.
That way, he'll never be able to do something
so terrible again. Then good night.
Grandfather, good night.
Good night.
He wants me to report someone for
selling balloon flowers as wild ginseng.
I wonder what he'll do when
he realizes you changed blood ties.
Mom, are you really going
to come out this way?
Grandmother, I'll give that money to you.
Thank you, Shin-ae! My granddaughter-in-law
is much better than my own daughter!
Thank you!
What's wrong with her?
Is she your biological mother?
She is.
The thing is...
she likes to play flower cards...
No. She loves to play them.
Flower cards?
So she's doing this for gambling money?
Shin-ae, overlook this just once.
Then I'll make sure this never happens again.
I'll make sure she never gambles
or blackmails us again.
So just help her out this once, okay?
I can't live because of her.
I'm about to die here.
- I'll finish up here.
- Bye.
- Thanks!
- See you tomorrow.
- See you tomorrow!
- Bye.
Why is the light on in the office?
Come in.
Oh, Mr. Jo. You were still here.
I'm going to go home now.
Sure. Go on.
Oh, dear. It'll be hard for you to sew
that while you're still wearing your shirt.
I have an appointment,
but I can't go out like this.
Then you should have told us.
Give me the needle.
I'll do it for you.
Sewing isn't easy.
Of course not.
It's like that if you haven't tried it before.
Oh, dear. It was sewed on
wrong from the beginning.
Oh, my! Did I poke you? I'm sorry!
It's fine. I yelled because
I was shocked, not hurt.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, Mr. Jo. I'll hurry up.
It's all done now.
I'll be going now.
Bye.
Ms. Joo, hold on!
Excuse me?
You forgot your cell-phone.
Oh, my.
I'll be going now.
Wait.
Yes?
Since it's on the way, I'll take you home.
No. This bus will take me right home.
I'll see you tomorrow.
What are you doing right now?
Mom...
I just asked you a question.
What are you doing right now?
Can't you tell?
I'm making kimchi.
But why are you doing all of this by yourself?
What about the other family members?
Well...
mother is sick, so she's inside,
and grandmother
and the others went to the hot springs.
What?
All of them went to the
hot springs without you?
What about Jang-go?
Jang-go went to a funeral to Yeosu.
He'll come tomorrow.
I can't believe this.
Your mother-in-law is doing this
just to give you a hard time, huh?
- No!
- What do you mean no?
No matter how much she hates you,
she shouldn't do this to you.
She should come out and help you!
How can she tell you
do all of this by yourself?
Look here.
- Come out here, Ms. Hwang! Look here!
- Mom! Don't do this!
Mother is sick. That's why I said
I would do it. Please ignore this, mom.
Mom, please.
Goodness.
Wait a little bit.
I'll change and come out.
No, it's okay. I can do this by myself.
Don't be ridiculous! How will you
make all of this kimchi by yourself?
Mom!
Her mother is helping her!
I can't believe this!
I need to chase her mother out first!
Oh, dear. It was sewed on
wrong from the beginning.
Oh, my! Did I poke you? I'm sorry!
Mom!
- You should sleep more.
- When did you come here?
You should sleep more. Why did you come out?
Mom, why are you doing this? I can do it.
Goodness, no. You don't need to do this.
Go and sleep more.
That way, you can go to work.
You work, too. Go and sleep.
I'll do the rest.
You won't be able to finish this by yourself.
I said go inside.
Fine. Let's do it together then.
I'm sorry, mom.
Why would you be sorry? Don't say that.
It makes me feel sorrier.
Thank you.
There are so many of them.
Hey! Where do you think you're going?
To work.
You're going to work while leaving behind that
pile of cabbages? Are you out of your mind?
Mother, I'm in charge of something important
at work today, so I have to hurry up and go.
Instead, I'll leave early
and finish the kimchi.
I'm sorry!
Oh my goodness! How can you
just leave like that?
Oh, no.
I almost passed it.
I can't be late. What do I do?
What's up with her?
I thought she couldn't come to work
because she's making kimchi.
Did she come to work
while she was making kimchi?
It got suddenly cold, you know, so we should
come up with a new
market plan for fur clothing.
I think that's a good idea.
I think pretty padding is in nowadays.
What about padding?
Women do love padding.
What do you think, Mi-poong?
Yes, it's a good idea.
You smell like garlic and salted shrimp.
You must not have taken
a shower before you came.
I'm sorry. Do I smell that much?
I was so busy that I couldn't even shower.
All I did was wash my face.
Did you make kimchi by yourself?
Why do you look so tired?
You didn't get enough sleep?
No, I'm okay.
You're supposed to send the new apparel
to the stores today. Will you be okay?
I don't think you can. The new apparel
we are sending today are
extremely valuable, so we need
to be extra careful with them.
Young-ju, can you support Mi-poong today?
I can't. I have to visit five stores today.
I'm okay. I'm totally fine.
All right then.
But I have something important
to do at home today, so
can I leave as soon as
I'm done with the warehouse?
Sure, go ahead.
Thank you.
Come in.
This is the list of new apparel to be sent.
These new apparel are quite pricey.
Winter apparel have fur in them,
so the prices increase.
There are many orders, so the reserved
apparel will be sent out first today.
Okay, I understand.
(Person in charge:
3rd marketing team Kim Mi-poong)
These are the stores
you will be delivering to today.
Please go carefully so that
you won't damage the clothes.
- Sure.
- Please be careful!
All right.
Oh my goodness.
Those are the new apparel that
will be sent to the stores, right?
Yes, ma'am.
The person in charge today is Kim Mi-poong
from the 3rd marketing team.
Yes, that's what we were told.
(Blow Breeze)
- It's fine.
- He looks at her differently than he looks at us.
- Let's watch a movie together.
- You came early, Mr. Jo.
What's this? I want to lose
to you, too, grandma.
You horrible brats!
My legs won't move!
What's all this?
You awful wench! Get out!
I can't leave.
Get up right now and make red bean noodles.
What do you mean?
Make sure he can't work
at Winner's Group again.
Give me those clothes right now.
Something went wrong!
Subtitles by OnDemandKorea