Subtitles by OnDemandKorea
These are the stores you will
be delivering to today.
- Please be careful so that
you won't damage the clothes.
- Okay.
- Please be careful!
- All right.
Are those the new apparel
that will be sent to the stores?
Yes, ma'am.
Oh my goodness.
The person in charge today is Kim Mi-poong
from the 3rd marketing team.
Does Mr. Kang work for our company, too?
He's an employee at our distribution center.
Oh, I see.
We're done.
Thank you!
(Mother)
Hi, mother.
Are you going to ruin this year's kimchi?
Are you trying to spoil the salted cabbages?
I'm on my way home right now!
Okay! I'll be there soon!
- (Episode 30)
- Thanks to you, I'll be able to
go to a massage shop today.
Women our age needs to be maintained,
or else we'll grow old really quickly.
I heard it's an expensive place.
Aren't you overdoing yourself
by bringing me along?
It's fine. My daughter-in-law gave
me enough massage coupons.
Lucky you.
Thanks to your daughter-in-law,
you have a nice life.
If you had gotten a daughter-in-law
from a law firm,
you would be getting massages, going
on cruise trips, and going golfing with me.
You would have had such a nice life.
Don't even mention Ha-yeon.
It's not too late.
Divorce isn't an issue these days.
Get them divorced before they have a baby
and then call back Ha-yeon from England.
I'm back!
Don't you know how to say hello?
Say hello first.
She's my friend and Hee-ra's mom.
Hello.
You must have ran here to make kimchi.
Yes.
I'm going out, so make sure you finish
making all the kimchi before I come back.
Yes, mother.
There are a lot of cabbages.
Poor you.
There are a hundred cabbages?
- It's not much. Back in the days,
I used to do 200 to 300.
- Good-bye.
Oh, yes!
Go.
We didn't even get to dip our feet into
the hot springs. What are we doing here?
Did you come here to play flower cards?
If you want to dip your feet in the
hot springs, go by yourself, you brat!
- Here she goes!
Oh, dear!
- Oh, no.
- Poor you, grandma.
Just lose to her. That way, she can win once.
What? Lose to me?
I should just rip your mouth off!
Come on. Stop it.
Fine. Here.
- Oh, my. Oh, my!
- My goodness!
What's this? I do want
to lose to you, grandma,
but what can I do when luck is on my side?
What's this? Pi and four kwang.
- Stop.
- It's starting to get crazy.
- Stop?
- Yes, stop.
I don't have pibak or kwangbak, but how did
you get pibak and kwangbak again, grandma?
Poor you.
Gimme.
Mom, give it to him.
I'm going home.
- Grandma.
You horrible brats!
- Grandma, what's wrong?
- Mom, what's wrong?
My legs aren't moving!
- Your legs won't move?
- Grandma, what's wrong with your legs?
Oh, my legs!
- Oh, no! What do we do?
- I'm dying!
- Carry her!
- Grandma, get on my back!
How can I get on your back
when my legs won't move?
- How will you carry her?
- What do I do then?
- Lift her up!
- Lift her!
Oh, I'm dying!
One, two, three!
Slowly! Slowly! Slowly!
I'm sorry. There's something going on at home.
I'm come earlier and
make up for the lost hours.
It's fine.
Fortunately, there aren't
many customers today.
I'll see you tomorrow. See you tomorrow.
- Bye.
It hasn't been that long since she started
working here again.
We all have issues at home.
She's relying on him too much.
What kind of relationship are they in?
What did you say?
You like Mr. Jo, too.
You need to stop giving him
smiles with your eyes.
Was I wrong?
He looks at her differently
than the way he looks at us.
I'm so embarrassed.
How can we come to the
emergency room just because you
couldn't use your legs
from playing flower cards?
Aunt, stop it.
They said there's a lot of people who
get stiff legs from playing flower cards.
Don't people who play cards use the bathroom?
How can they play cards
until they paralyze their legs?
Come on, aunt. That's enough already.
What's this?
Is this a hot springs trip?
Will you stop already?
I should just rip your mouth off!
Hello?
Yes, it's me.
What did you say?
There's a mountain of cabbages at my house?
You guys must be tired.
I can do this by myself.
Goodness. How will you be
able to do all of this by yourself?
Your grandmother-in-law and I help each
other out during kimchi-making season.
What are neighbors for?
We should help each other when we can.
So don't feel burdened.
Thank you.
Ma'am, have a taste.
Sure.
How does it taste?
It's very delicious!
But did you make the seasoning?
No, my mom did.
My mom did almost everything.
Your mom is very good!
It's delicious! It's so delicious!
Really?
Yes! Thumbs up! Amazing!
Thumbs up!
Mi-poong.
Oh, mom. Oh, dear.
Who is she?
Oh, she's my mom. Mom, these
are my grandmother-in-law's friends.
Hello.
But she's your mom?
Goodness! Other people
might think she's your sister!
Her sister? Thank you, ma'am.
- Mom, why did you come? You didn't have to.
- Why else would I come?
- Ma'am, we'll take it from here.
- Oh, no.
I'm doing this because
I want to, so don't feel burdened.
But where did everyone else go
while leaving you to do all the work?
Pardon?
That silly old cow! I'll give her
an earful when she comes back!
- I'm so tired.
- Cheer up.
- Oh my goodness!
- What's this?
What are all these?
Can't you tell, you brazen old cow?
It feels so nice! You feel great, don't you?
Of course I do.
Your skin is glowing!
You look ten years younger.
- Really?
- Yes.
Anyways, your daughter-in-law should
be working hard to make kimchi right now.
Call her and tell her to make broiled pork.
Broiled pork goes with just made kimchi.
But I think a hundred cabbages
were too many for her to do.
I should have just made her do fifty of them.
Fifty cabbages are nothing!
If you want to chase her out,
you shouldn't get weak-hearted.
I know, but...
what if all that kimchi tastes unpleasant?
We can't just throw them away!
I don't know if I can be here
while leaving everything up to her.
Who cares what the kimchi tastes like?
What's important is that
she gets sick and tired and leaves.
I know, but...
what can I do with all of that kimchi?
What's the problem?
Call Young-soon, Kyung-sook,
and Soon-jung up and tell them to take some.
Only if the kimchi is delicious.
All fermented kimchi tastes good.
Hurry up and call her!
- To broil pork?
- Yes.
Hurry up and call her!
You don't need to give us two boxes of kimchi.
Just take them and eat them.
I'll enjoy eating them.
The kimchi is so delicious
that I simply can't refuse them.
Yes, ma'am. Thank you
so much for everything today.
I'm not just saying this.
The kimchi is very delicious.
The southern and northern tastes
mixed up and... oh, that's right!
It's unification kimchi!
What? Unification kimchi?
That's a good one!
Thank you.
- Take them. Jang-soo, help them out.
- Okay!
- Give it to me.
- Here. Just kidding! I'll carry it!
- Bye!
- Bye! Thank you!
Ms. Joo, you worked very hard.
I'm too ashamed to face you.
No, it's fine. It's not hard
making kimchi together.
To be honest, I felt a bit
heartbroken that her in-laws
were purposely giving her a hard time.
Mom.
No! My mom and I really didn't know
she was making kimchi!
Of course. I know that as well.
Hello?
Yes, Ms. Kim.
Mi-poong, hurry up and come to the store!
We're in big trouble!
The new apparel you sent off are gone!
Ms. Kim, what are you talking about?
Yes. I'll be right there.
Why? Did something major happen at work?
No, but I have to go to the company right now.
Sure, go ahead.
I'll be leaving now, too.
I have to pick up Yoo-sung.
Thank you so much!
- It was nothing. Bye.
- Bye.
Geum-sil is too mean.
Where did she go after making Mi-poong
make 100 cabbages into kimchi?
She's Cinderella's step-mom.
I ought to...
I dare her to come home.
Hello. I'm Kim Mi-poong from headquarters.
What do you mean the apparel didn't come?
Why don't you check for yourself?
Look what's inside.
What are all these?
These are the boxes I sent?
How can you ask me that?
Look. These are the boxes
sent from headquarters.
That can't be! I really
put the apparel in there!
I really checked!
Kim Mi-poong!
Ms. Kim.
Mi-poong,
what on earth happened?
I don't know either.
I don't know what happened.
Hello, Ms. Park.
All right.
Mi-poong, Ms. Park
wants you to come to her office.
Ms. Park?
The new apparel that were supposed to
be sent today costs over $50,000 in total.
Opportunity makes the thief.
Anyone having a hard time can become greedy.
Mi-poong, hand over the apparel right now.
We need to keep the promises to
the store managers and the customers.
What are you talking about?
Are you saying I stole those items?
I don't want to think of you
as the culprit either.
But who else would have done it?
Do those apparel have feet or wings?
Where would all those items go?
It's not me. Why would I do
something that obviously points
to me as the culprit
when I'm the one in charge of it?
Is that so?
Then explain.
Who else would have done this besides you?
Where's the evidence that you didn't do this?
What did you say?
It's not me. I really didn't do it.
Bye.
- Thank you!
- You're welcome.
Hold on.
I'll go meet the driver who delivered
the apparel to check what happened.
So what you're saying is...
the truck driver would have taken them, right?
Mr. Yang, come inside.
Mr. Yang, did you check with the truck driver?
Yes.
Are you Mr. Kang Sung-jing
who delivered the apparel today?
Yes, I am.
Was there a problem while
you were delivering the apparel today?
No, there was no problem.
All I did was deliver the
apparel to the stores, just as
Ms. Kim Mi-poong from the
3rd marketing team told me to.
Why? Is there a problem?
Kim Mi-poong,
I'll pay for those lost items.
However, we broke
our promise to our customers,
and our company image has been damaged.
That can't be paid back with money.
You'll have to take responsibility for it.
Kim Mi-poong, you're fired.
What? Fired?
Ms. Park, I really didn't do it.
Why don't you believe me?
Something went wrong here!
Mr. Yang, take her out of here.
- Please leave.
- Shin-ae. I mean, Ms. Park. I really didn't do it.
Please give me some time.
I'll reveal the truth. Ms. Park!
What are you doing? Drag her out of here.
- Yes, ma'am. Come out.
- Shin-ae!
Please leave.
It's over now.
But...
Kim Mi-poong, get a hold of yourself.
Even if you go into
a tiger's den, you'll be able
to live as long as you pull yourself together.
Yes. That driver will
definitely know something.
Mr. Kang! Please think carefully!
Did you ever stop the truck
in the middle of delivery?
Why would I stop the truck?
I delivered to the stores like you told me to!
But why did the boxes change then?
I checked them with my own eyes!
Where did the items go?
Why are you asking me that?
Are you suspecting me right now?
Are you disrespecting me because I'm a driver?
You're really rude.
You were the one who did wrong,
so how dare you blame me!
Mr. Kang, that's not it...
Then what is it?
You shouldn't live your life like that.
Mr. Kang! Mr. Kang!
Mr. Kang!
Hi, Jang-go.
Hi, Mi-poong.
Where are you? I'm almost at Seoul.
Where are you?
Hurry up and come here!
What's wrong? Did something happen?
I was falsely charged with theft
and got fired from my job!
What? Falsely charged with theft?
Excuse me.
I'm sorry, but can I see this video
taken from a different angle?
Why? Is something strange?
No. I wanted to see if there were
any suspicious people in the area.
Do you have it?
There are a few cameras in the warehouse,
but this is the only one
that shows the entrance.
Is that so?
May I take a copy of this video?
Sure.
Okay.
There was nothing wrong captured
on the camera. What will we do now?
Don't be too disappointed.
This is just the beginning.
Let's go to the store. There might have
been something caught on camera there.
All right.
Good job.
Just trust me. I won't let
anything happen to you.
And I deposited money
into your account, so check it.
Can't you do help us out?
I want to, but all the
administrators went home already.
In order to see the CCTV files, you need
permission from the building owner.
Come back tomorrow.
Mi-poong, don't worry.
I'll find the evidence
that you're not the culprit.
What if we can't find the evidence?
I'm a lawyer.
If I can't find the evidence,
then I'll quit being a lawyer.
No, you can't do that!
So don't worry.
Okay?
It feels so nice after getting a body massage.
Right? I'm tired and hungry from
getting a massage and shopping.
- Should we have some broiled pork?
- Yes, let's eat broiled pork!
Let's have delicious broiled pork.
- Hey, come here!
- I'm so hungry!
Are you talking to me?
Hello, ma'am.
Mother, when did you come home?
Weren't you coming back
from the hot springs tomorrow?
It seems like she got a massage
with Ms. Hwang. Her face is glowing.
You sent us away to the
hot springs and then secretly
forced Mi-poong to make
a hundred cabbages into kimchi.
What do you think you're doing?
I didn't do it on purpose.
They were selling the
leftover cabbages for cheap.
You awful wench!
Do you think I'm stupid?
Excuse me. I got free tickets to a massage shop,
so I asked Geum-sil to go with me.
You shouldn't be like that either!
There is something called natural affection.
If Mi-poong had to make
a hundred cabbages into kimchi,
shouldn't you at least offer to help her out?
It's late, so I'll be going home now.
You awful wench.
Hey.
Did I give you such
a hard time with housework?
You wicked witch!
Get out of this house right now! Get out!
I can't go out.
What? You can't?
Half of this house is under my name.
So why do you keep telling me
to get out of this house?
My son worked hard to buy this house.
Yes! My husband worked hard to buy this house!
Then let's sell this house
and split the money in half!
Then I'll leave!
What did you just say?
Geum-sil, aren't you being too harsh?
What? Sell the house
and split the money in half?
And did my mom say something wrong?
Even I think you're being too much!
I don't like Mi-poong either,
but you shouldn't do this!
What am I supposed to do when I hate her?
What?
I don't know why I'm like this either.
I even hate seeing the back of her head!
I want to chase her out and get
Jang-go married to Ha-yeon!
What are you saying?
Don't criticize me for feeling
differently from you two.
They're my feelings!
Oh my goodness!
Was Geum-sil always so spiteful?
I should never have bought
a house together with her!
Goodness. That old cow has a temper.
My gosh. But what happened?
Mi-poong won't be the one who will have
a hard time doing house work. It's Geum-sil.
Poor thing.
Goodness.
(Daughter-in-law)
Hi, it's me.
What?
Kim Mi-poong was fired?
Then she won't come out to
work starting from tomorrow?
Yes.
Oh my gosh! That's great!
Now Mi-poong and Mr. Kim won't
bump into each other anymore, right?
Yes, they won't be able to meet anymore
unless they make plans with each other.
Why would they make plans with each other?
On top of that, she got fired
for such a shameful thing.
You're right.
I feel like a huge weight has
been lifted off my shoulders.
Are you coming home now? Come home safely.
I'll make the dried yellow corvina
you like so much.
That's great.
My daughter-in-law solved it in a single blow.
Yes.
Geum-sil would rather die than
look at her stealing daughter-in-law.
It's dinnertime.
You shouldn't just be lying here.
Get up right now and make red bean noodles.
How can I make red bean noodles
right now? It's going to take a lot of work.
I must eat red bean noodles no matter what.
Even though it takes
a lot of work, it'll be easier
to make than kimchi out of a hundred cabbages.
All right. I'll make it for you.
Hi, Chung-ja.
What? What are you talking about?
Mi-poong stole something?
What are you talking about?
We're back.
- You two are coming home together.
- Yes.
You.
Is it true you got fired
at work for being a thief?
Mom, what do you mean she's a thief?
You don't even know what's going on.
How can you say that?
Jang-go, you knew about this, too?
There was a misunderstanding.
What do you mean misunderstanding?
Lee Jang-go, now isn't the time
for you to be defending her.
There are rumors that a lawyer's wife
committed theft. Who would give you work?
My goodness. How dare you act so shamefully.
How will we be able to face anyone now?
Mom, I told you it's not true.
I'll reveal that she's not the culprit.
Reveal what?
Would they fire her for no reason?
Did you steal them
so you could help your family?
Or did you need money without us knowing?
My goodness. How can you steal now?
How much more are you going
to damage Jang-go's future?
Mother, I didn't do it. I really didn't!
How dare you raise your voice at me!
Mom, Mi-poong is your daughter-in-law, too.
She's part of your family now.
Can't you defend her and trust her?
I'll make sure to reveal that she's not
the culprit, so don't say anything until then.
Lee Jang-go, she's not the one for you!
You should get a hold of yourself now!
Now you see why I'm like this, don't you?
Now you understand how I feel, don't you?
My goodness.
Mom!
Hurry up and go inside.
Jang-soo, what's going on?
Stealing? Fired?
Let's just pretend we didn't hear anything.
That's the only way to survive in this house.
I waited such a long time
Where were you, what were you doing?
Do you remember me? I missed you so much
After much time, I finally met you
But when you looked at me,
There was only an unknown smile
My love for you is greater than anything
Even if I give up my life,
My love won't go to waste
My love will never change
There's no problem here either.
Where on earth did they go?
Now that you saw everything,
you should leave now.
Wait a minute.
Can you zoom in here
and enlarge the license plate?
Where? Here?
Yes.
Hold on.
We need to talk.
Why are you bothering me? If you're
going to say nonsense again, just leave.
Mr. Kang.
If you spill the truth now,
I won't report you to the police.
So just confess everything.
You people. What do you
keep telling me to confess?
You stole the clothes,
so who are you trying to blame it on?
Don't come looking for me again.
Look here!
Are you going to act innocent
when the evidence is right here?
Thank you!
Mi-poong.
Stop right there!
It's not me!
You better follow me quietly,
or I'll just take you to the police!
I said it's not me!
I'll relay your message to him.
Wasn't Kim Mi-poong dismissed?
What do you mean she was dismissed?
The thing is...
Mr. Kim, the truth is...
What?
What do you mean?
Come in.
Grandfather, what are you doing here?
Grandfather, why are you with these people?
I came because Kim Mi-poong
had something to say.
Please sit down.
- Mr. Choi, sit down.
- Yes, sir.
- Mr. Lee, you sit down, too.
What did you need to say?
I found the evidence that
can prove my innocence.
Evidence?
This is a photo of the
license plate of the truck
that Mr. Kang was driving
when he left the warehouse.
This is a photo of the
license plate of the truck
that Mr. Kang was driving
when he came to the store.
So Mr. Kang swapped the trucks?
I'm sorry.
How can you do such a thing?
I'm sorry. I misunderstood that it was you.
He can't do such a thing alone.
There's someone else involved in this.
Who is it?
The truth is...
I stole the items because my child is sick.
I did it because I wanted to sell the items
and use them to pay for the hospital bill.
I did it alone. No one else
was involved. I'm sorry.
No matter how much of
a dire situation you were in,
how could you blame
someone else for your misdeed?
That can never be forgiven.
Fire him and make sure he can
never work at Winner's Group again.
Mr. Kim, I'm sorry!
Please forgive me just this once!
And Ms. Park.
Yes, grandfather... I mean, Mr. Kim.
You didn't even attempt to find out the truth.
How can you fire your employee so rashly?
You shouldn't make such a decision so easily.
Their life depends on this. Next time,
you should be more attentive and careful.
And take care of
Kim Mi-poong's dismissal right away.
Yes, grandfather.
Thank you, Mr. Kim.
Don't thank me.
I'm sorry for upsetting you like this.
Jang-go, thank you.
Oh, my. It's been a while since I worked so hard.
Mi-poong, give me a massage here.
Good.
That feels great.
Should you or should you not
erve your awesome husband?
- I should serve him for the rest of my life.
- That's right.
Oh, that's right. Hold on.
Hi, grandma. Mi-poong was proven innocent.
Make sure you tell the family that the real culprit
was caught and that she's going back to work.
What?
Mi-poong and my mother-in-law did that?
Okay, I got it.
Mi-poong, is it true that you and your mother
made 100 cabbages into kimchi while I was gone?
Did grandma tell you?
Yes. She told me to treat you well.
The whole neighborhood is talking about how delicious it is. They call it unification kimchi.
What? Unification kimchi?
I should do kimchi business later on.
No wonder you smell like kimchi.
Really? Do I really smell like kimchi?
I was just joking.
It's so easy to tease you.
It hasn't even been a minute since you said you'd
serve your awesome husband for your whole life!
If you tease me again,
I'll make you bleed from both nostrils!
What? Bleed from both nostrils?
Fine. I'll be careful.
- Mi-poong.
- You came?
Mi-poong, I'm sorry for not being able to help
you when you were going through a hard time.
It's okay.
But we believed in you.
Thank you.
I'm sorry for worrying you.
Why should you be sorry? This is my fault.
I should have ordered for you
to go directly to the stores.
From now on, let's go directly
to the stores from the warehouse.
- Got it?
- Yes, ma'am.
- Good job.
I think it would be good to use something
that people can easily approach...
Tell me again
That you love me, those words, those words
So I can hear it in my ears
(Company newsletter:
Winner's Today. Activation plan.)
In the company? That sounds great!
How can you fire your employee so rashly?
Their life depends on this. Next time,
you should be more attentive and careful.
And take care of Kim Mi-poong's
dismissal right away.
Is grandpa disappointed in me because
of what happened with Mi-poong?
He's not doubting me, is he?
Come in.
Hee-dong, what are you doing here?
I came here for the first time
because of the newsletter.
Wow. This is your office?
It's nice.
Did you officially
start working for the company?
Yes. I'm starting with
this month's newsletter first.
Then I'll be able to see you
often at work, too.
Yes. Let's eat lunch together when we can.
Sounds good.
Hee-dong, if you don't have
any other plans today, how about
we go eat with grandfather
and go on a date with him?
Good idea. I don't have any other plans today.
You had a meeting for the newsletter today?
Yes.
Was it okay?
I did a newsletter for my part-time job
before, so it was fine.
Oh, really?
What kind of article are you planning to make?
We're planning on creating a series
out of photos of orphans in the country.
We're also planning to get donations so
that we can make a small library for them.
I think that's a great plan.
I'll give you a donation as well,
so tell me whenever you need it.
Thank you!
Hold on. I need to take this call.
Hi.
Shin-ae.
Yes, grandfather.
Business isn't only done with money.
People are the most important.
Even if you have a lot of money, you can't
succeed if you don't have any skillful people.
So treat your employees
like they're your family, okay?
Yes, grandfather.
I was rash this time.
I'll be careful from now on.
Please teach me more in the future.
Of course I will.
Eat up.
No. Next time let's go to a karaoke room.
- Oh, a karaoke room!
- Sounds great, huh?
Grandfather, hold up a V.
Oh, I'm so jealous!
You two look so good together!
- Grandfather, there's a carp here!
- Try and catch it.
There are so many carps here!
Grandfather thinks of me
as his real granddaughter.
Yes.
I'm his granddaughter. His real granddaughter.
(Pyeongyang Noodles: Deokcheonok)
J, in a passing wind,
J, if you appear,
Today, I quietly miss you again
Wow. That's wonderful to see.
Oh, Mr. Jo! I just felt restless since there's
only a month left in this year,
so I decided to sing a song.
It's nice to see you all of you having fun.
By the way, I was gifted a lot of movie tickets,
so I brought them to share with you.
All of you should go watch a movie together.
Oh, Mr. Jo, we really wanted to watch a movie!
- You're the best!
- Mr. Jo, what kind of movie is it?
I already watched this movie. It's really fun!
Really? I'm looking forward to it!
- Mr. Jo, can I have two tickets for my children?
- Of course.
- Thank you!
- Mr. Jo, come with us! We'll all go together!
Oh, should I?
Yes! Ms. Joo, come with us, too.
Yes, join us.
All right. I will.
I'm so excited!
Then popcorn and drinks are on me.
Wow, Mr. Jang is the best!
It's so cold.
Mother, I heard you suffered
a lot to make kimchi with Mi-poong.
I'm sorry.
No, I didn't suffer at all.
Mi-poong couldn't even take
a break. On top of that, she had to
go back and forth from work.
She's the one who really suffered.
I didn't know mothers-in-law in South Korea
gave their daughters-in-law such a rough time.
I'm sorry.
No, it's fine. I wasn't complaining to you.
You have to walk on eggshells around
your mother and look after Mi-poong.
You must be having
a hard time in the middle.
I'm just hoping time will solve everything.
Mother, take this.
What's this?
It's a coat.
You were dressed lightly last time.
Oh, dear! No, I'm fine!
Oh my goodness. This looks expensive.
I can do this much for you as your son-in-law.
Mother, try it on.
Oh, all right.
Oh, my. Look at the color!
It's so pretty!
Wow!
Wow! Amazing!
You look beautiful, grandma!
- Right, Yoo-sung?
- Yes!
- It looks good on her, right?
It's warm.
Jang-go.
What are you doing?
I was hungry, so I was looking
for something to eat.
My hubby.
Thank you.
Your mother told you, huh?
I dropped by her house and
saw the coat you bought her.
My mom said it's so warm
and pretty. She loves it!
I did well, huh?
But what about your mother's coat?
You didn't buy the same coat
for her as my mom, did you?
My mom's coat?
I didn't buy hers.
So you only bought a coat for my mom?
Yes.
Last time, your mother
was dressed too lightly.
Why?
What do you mean why? How did you
become a lawyer with that kind of mind?
You should have bought two coats!
What if your mother finds out that
you bought a coat only for my mom?
How betrayed would she feel?
If you were my son,
I would have hit you ten times!
You and your nagging.
My mom has a lot of coats.
I bought one for her last year. It's fine.
That was last year, and this is this year!
Hurry up and go.
What do we do?
How could he only buy
a coat for his mother-in-law?
Oh my gosh.
Mom, what are you doing?
Can't you tell? I'm wiping the floor.
Mom, let's go out.
Go where?
Mi-poong said we should buy you a coat.
You don't have to buy it for me, so get out.
Really? You don't need a coat?
I told you that you don't
have to buy it for me! Get out!
Why are you getting mad? Okay then.
Oh my god! He's really leaving? That jerk!
This is why they say it's no use having a son!
Oh my god! That jerk!
- Thank you.
- Please spread the news about us.
- Come back again!
We will.
Father, why isn't Nam-yi coming out?
I don't know either.
The store is very busy. Hurry up and call her.
We need to know why she's not coming.
What's wrong, father?
I'll call with my phone,
but can you talk to her?
- Why?
- Don't ask me why.
All right. I will.
If she answers, tell her she must come
to work and that the store is very busy.
Got it?
Yes, sir.
Here.
Hello?
This isn't Mr. Kim's voice.
Is this Won-bin?
Yes, this is Kim Won-bin.
My father would like for you
to come out to work.
I told him I was going to quit. Ask him
why he's making an irrelevant remark.
She said she told you
that she was going to quit,
so she wants to know why you're
making an irrelevant remark.
Tell her that she's irresponsible
and that I'm very disappointed in her!
Tell her that she has to work until I find
another employee! Tell her it's an order!
Nam-yi, my father is begging you to come
work until he finds another employee.
Kim Won-bin, you-!
Father!
Won-bin, I heard everything.
Am I his wife or his underling?
Who the hell does he think he is?
Tell him that I'll never come to work!
What did she say?
She said she can't come to work.
She said she's not your wife
or underling so that you can't
order her around anymore.
Father, you need to learn about women.
Jang-go, what about this?
Oh, it's awesome!
Then what about this one?
Yes, that's good, too.
You can't say that about everything.
But they're all great. What else can I say?
Forget it!
Don't talk to me for the next two hours.
I don't want to talk to
a pumpkin head like you.
I don't know how I'm going
to live depending on you.
You! You! You! You!
How many days has it passed since
you promised to serve your awesome husband?
I don't know! I'll have to make 100 cabbages into
kimchi again next year because of you!
Then choose one out of these three.
You can do that, can't you?
This one?
Yes, that one is good.
Then what about this one?
This one seems a little bit better...
Then this one...?
Let's buy that one.
Mom, pick one out of the three.
Which one do you like the best?
Mother didn't respond yet?
Yeah.
My mom seems to be very angry.
What do I do?
Mi-poong, let's just go home.
We'll bring her later
when she isn't angry anymore.
If we buy it and she doesn't like it,
it'll be a waste.
Something came.
- Is it mother?
- Yes.
Three.
I knew it would be number three!
- She's not angry anymore.
- I'm so glad!
Let's buy number three.
What? Mi-poong wasn't fired?
Yes.
Then what do we do?
If she's at the company,
she'll keep bumping into Mr. Kim!
We'll have to come up with a different way.
I'll kick her out of the
company somehow, so don't worry.
Do it as soon as possible
with whatever method you can!
Or I'll get a heart disease.
Grandfather doesn't doubt me
as his real granddaughter.
Make sure grandmother doesn't say
anything weird like last time, okay?
Okay.
I'm going up.
What happened to mom?
She left with $20,000 and
I haven't heard from her since.
Is she...?
The person you are trying
to each is unavailable.
Mom, please let me live! Please!
My goodness!
Dongah Cafe
Two hundred.
- Deal.
- Why are you guys coming on so strong? Sheesh.
Is it jangttaeng?
Three eight kwangttaeng!
I'm so lucky!
This is so delicious! The kimchi
is so refreshing and delicious!
Your in-law is a really good cook.
Last time I saw her at the wedding,
she had a nice figure
like a young lady,
and she was very beautiful, too.
She looks pitiful, not beautiful.
And glamorous bodies like mine
are the ones that men really love.
Oh, gosh. Good for you.
That's why Dal-ho can't go against me!
Ma Chung-ja, don't say that anywhere else.
They'll think you're nuts.
What?
At our age, it's the best to hold hands and
take a walk while looking
at the autumn leaves.
Says the widow.
- What did you say?
- Stop it. You'll fight again.
Anyways, you'll be the only one in this
country who made your daughter-in-law
and her mother make kimchi for you and
shared it with the whole neighborhood.
Yeah! Women these days
don't stand for such things.
If you had asked other women
to make a hundred cabbages
into kimchi, they would have
demanded a divorce right away.
That's right!
Stop hating your daughter-in-law
and be good to her now.
I'll bring coffee.
Forcing her to make kimchi won't work.
What can I do to chase Mi-poong
and her family out of here?
Geum-sil, I ordered a bunch of pumpkins,
and I'll give all of them to you.
Pumpkins? Why?
It's going to be even
more difficult to take off
the peels and cut them up than to make kimchi.
She'll hurt her wrists while doing it!
So tell your daughter-in-law
to take off the peels so
that she can make porridge and
rice cakes and dry the rest of them.
- Chung-ja.
- Yeah?
I can hate her because
she's my daughter-in-law.
But why are you so eager
to chase her out of here?
That's because you want to chase her out,
so I'm trying to help you.
Forget it. You don't have to help me anymore.
What? I don't have to help you anymore?
Yes.
It's not easy giving my daughter-in-law
a hard time with the housework.
And at this rate, Jang-go
and I will become enemies.
You said you wanted to chase Mi-poong
out and make Ha-yeon your daughter-in-law.
I was just saying that.
Do you think that's even possible?
Anyways, I'm an outcast in my family because
of you and those one hundred cabbages.
I was just trying to help you.
Sheesh. Forget it then!
You came first.
You came early as well.
It's going to take a while for the others
to come. Should we wait for them inside?
It's fine. They'll be here soon.
Oh, my.
I'm sorry, Mr. Jo.
Oh, it's fine. I'm okay.
Let's go to the karaoke room.
I can't go. I have to make dinner
for Dal-ho and Mr. Kim.
The food was great,
and I had a lot of fun today.
Are you guys really
going to betray me like this?
You widows can have a
grand time at the karaoke room.
I'll be going, too.
Look how that brat talks.
Geum-sil, how about us
widows go watch a movie?
Sure, let's do that. I feel a
bit blue anyways. Let's go.
Why aren't they coming?
We'll be late at this rate.
Should I call them?
Mr. Jo! Ms. Joo! I'm so sorry!
What about Ms. Hong?
She called me and told me that
someone in her family suddenly got sick,
so that the three of us
should just go by ourselves.
Really? Let's go inside then.
I was running so quickly.
I'm going to drop by the restroom first.
Go ahead then.
- Let's go inside and choose.
- Okay.
Isn't that Chung-ja's husband?
Come here.
He is, right?
He is Chung-ja's husband.
But who is that woman next to him?
Woman?
- Oh my gosh! He must be having an affair!
- No way.
Geum-sil, take pictures! No, I'll do it.
- Don't!
- Hold still!
My goodness.
Should we wait inside?
Oh my gosh. Isn't that your in-law?
(Blow Breeze)
Don't get shocked. Dal-ho is having an affair!
I'm going to kill them!
You wench! How dare you flirt with my husband?
Yes. Where? The police station?
Hello, Geum-sil. I really wanted to see you.
Me?
You home-wrecker!
Are you done talking?
You seem to be disrespecting Hee-ra.
When did I disrespect her?
Now your true colors are coming out!
- You brat!
- Mi-poong.
I'll rearrange the order of your ribs today!
Subtitles by OnDemandKorea