Subtitles by OnDemandKorea
(Episode 32)
Kids are kids.
How can she fall asleep so fast?
I know.
Then I guess Shin-ae knows Yoo-jin.
Of course. She got a lot of help from
Yoo-jin's mother when she was in China.
I should call Shin-ae.
(My granddaughter)
Speaking of the devil...
Hi, it's me.
Grandfather, where are you?
Did you eat lunch yet?
Of course I did.
Shin-ae, if you're not busy
right now, come home.
Home?
Why? Did something happen?
There's someone you would be happy to see.
Someone I would be happy to see?
I wonder who it is.
Okay. I'm outside right now.
I'll be home soon.
Bye.
Yoo-jin didn't talk about me, did she?
Yoo-jin, please...
Lay her down over there.
Hold on. Here.
- Put this blanket over her.
- Okay.
You woke up.
Where am I?
This is our house.
You fell asleep on the
way to the restaurant,
so we came here instead.
Are you okay with that?
Don't you remember this place?
You came here with your mom last time.
Do you want some juice?
No.
I'm going to go back to the orphanage.
What's wrong, Yoo-jin?
It's okay. This is my house.
She must have been shocked after waking up.
Yoo-jin.
Shin-ae.
Oh, Yoo-jin!
Yoo-jin, what happened to you?
I thought you went to China.
It's okay. You're okay now.
Grandfather. Hee-dong. What happened?
Hee-dong and I went to the orphanage to take
photos for the newsletter,
and Yoo-jin was there.
The orphanage?
Yoo-jin was at the orphanage?
She's the daughter of
the woman who helped you.
How can I just ignore her?
That's why I brought her here.
Thank you, grandfather. Thank you, Hee-dong.
Yoo-jin, I'm glad you came.
Yoo-jin, did you tell Hee-dong
or Mr. Kim that you met me?
No.
You didn't tell them that I took you
to the orphanage, did you?
No, I didn't. As promised,
I didn't tell them anything about you.
Good job, Yoo-jin.
You can never talk about me, okay?
I'm just an aunt you know, okay?
Okay.
And this is the first time we met after
the time you came to this house. Okay?
Okay.
Yoo-jin, let's eat some snacks.
Looks delicious, Yoo-jin.
Yoo-jin, is it good?
Yes, it's good! It's amazing!
But Yoo-jin, don't you have to call
your aunt to let her know you're here?
She could go to the orphanage
without knowing you're here.
I was asking Yoo-jin about her aunt.
She doesn't come to the orphanage anymore.
She can't get in touch with her either.
Oh, really?
Hee-dong, don't ask Yoo-jin
about her aunt anymore. She'll get hurt.
That aunt must have left Yoo-jin
behind and gone to China by herself.
She was the only one Yoo-jin
could rely on in this world.
How could she do such a thing?
I know.
I begged him, but he didn't even come home.
It's because of that wench!
He's bewitched by her!
I shouldn't be doing this right now.
Chung-ja, come out!
Hee-dong brought a little girl home,
and she's adorable!
Stop being ridiculous!
I'm being serious!
Whatever! I don't care if she's an adult
or a child! That's not important right now!
What's up with her now?
That's my mom.
Who is she?
Yoo-jin, say hi to her.
Hello.
Oh my gosh!
She's the daughter of that Yanbian woman.
Why is she here, Hee-dong?
I went to the orphanage
with grandfather to take pictures
for the company newsletter when he saw Yoo-jin
and remembered her as the daughter
of the woman who helped
Shin-ae when she was in China.
So we brought her home.
How can you bring her here?
Who will watch her?
Whatever!
Yoo-jin, it's okay. She's a nice person.
She's the daughter of the woman
who helped Shin-ae in China?
Yes, grandma.
Oh, really? You look so cute and smart!
What's this? Did you guys
plan this behind my back?
What are you talking about? What did we plan?
Mr. Yoon chose adult men's apparel.
Young-ju chose women's casual apparel.
Min-cheol chose innerwear.
Mi-poong chose sportswear.
I'm happy none of you concepts overlap.
I was going to do innerwear
but changed at the end. I'm glad I did.
I was going to do men's apparel, too.
I'm glad I didn't, or we would've overlapped.
I'm glad.
But why did you choose sportswear,
Mi-poong? It's a bit complicated.
Well, although the weather grew colder,
people are interested in health,
so many of them are
interested in playing sports.
That's why it won't just be for strictly
sportswear but for everyday use, too.
That's a good concept.
Focusing on both functionality
and daily wear. Not bad at all.
Really? I was worried.
All of you should do your best. I really wish
our marketing team can go to the final round.
- Ask me if you need any help.
- Yes, ma'am!
Oh, you chose that many?
You should just look at the data.
That's what everyone else does.
I thought I would be able to get good
ideas if I actually wear and touch them.
- Okay. Good work.
- Thank you.
(Deokcheonok)
I lived for thirty years with Jo Dal-ho.
My instincts are right.
That quack doesn't know anything.
I don't have delusional suspicion
of my husband's faithfulness.
I'm going to catch them red-handed for sure.
Just watch.
- Good job.
- Bye.
- See you tomorrow.
I got it!
- It's my son's birthday today.
- Oh, really?
- Oh, no.
- What is it?
I don't think I locked the gas. What do I do?
I'll check, so go on.
- Thank you, Ms. Joo! See you tomorrow!
- Bye.
What's going on?
I knew this would happen!
She sent all those people away
and went back inside!
That fox-like wench!
She snuck back inside like
a rat to seduce my husband!
I won't let her get away with this tonight!
You!
Why did you come back in here
after sending everyone else home?
Why do you need to come back in here?
Is this how you seduced
my husband all this time?
Ms. Ma, what are you talking about?
I came to lock the gas.
Don't you dare lie to me!
You came in here knowing my husband
sleeps in his office by himself!
You think I don't know that?
Hey! Tell me if I'm wrong!
Why? Are you thrilled that my husband
left home and is now living here?
I don't even want to respond
to such a ridiculous claim.
- Good-bye.
- Where do you think you're going?
Oh my god!
Oh my god! Blood!
Oh, no!
Ms. Joo!
Ms. Joo, wake up!
Ms. Joo. Ms. Joo!
Nothing will go wrong, right?
She seemed to be bleeding a lot.
What if she dies? No, that won't happen!
If something happens to her,
Dal-ho will never want to see me again.
What do I do?
She's gone. Thank goodness.
She must have gone home.
Yes. All I did was slightly push her.
That fox-like wench.
Did she fall down on purpose?
It's cold!
I'm so cold!
Yoo-sung, spare me!
Wow! This is the worst part-time job ever!
It's not even warm water!
Mi-poong, aren't you being too mean?
There's no such thing as warm rain.
This is the only way
I can figure out which type
of clothing is a better barrier against rain.
- This is what martyrs do.
- I know.
Is the water soaking through the clothes?
- Hold on.
- I don't think the water soaked through it yet.
- Mine, too!
- Oh, really?
- Amazing.
- Then Yoo-sung, do it one more time.
- Okay, aunt.
It's so cold!
What are you guys doing right now?
It's the middle of winter, and
you guys are soaked! Are you crazy?
Jang-soo, what are you doing?
- Well...
- What are you doing with my sons right now?
Mom, the thing is, Mi-poong is doing an
experiment with these work out clothes so that
she can submit a proposal to the company.
If she does well, she can get a promotion.
That's why Jang-soo
and I volunteered to help her.
Mi-poong didn't make us do anything.
That's right, mom! We volunteered!
This is ridiculous!
I'm so cold!
Oh, no. I think I'll have
to go in first. Let go.
- I'm freezing!
- How frustrating.
Make sure you wipe this place dry!
Are you going to take responsibility if
my mother-in-law slips and falls down here?
Okay.
Mom, I'll make sure to
wipe everything so that it's dry.
There's nothing I like about you.
No matter how hard I try
to like you, I just can't.
Don't worry. She'll be happy
if you get a promotion.
Don't you think she would be happy if
her daughter-in-law is acknowledged
and gets a promotion?
Are you awake?
What are you doing here?
You were unconscious in the
restaurant with an injured wrist.
What happened? Do you remember?
The injury was bandaged, but since it was made
by glass, there is a possibility of infection.
Come back tomorrow to get it disinfected
and make sure you take the
anti-inflammatory medication.
Once the IV is empty, you may leave.
Thank you.
Mr. Jo, once the IV is empty,
I'll go home on my own, so you can go home.
Come on, Ms. Joo.
Would you go if you were in my shoes?
The IV is almost empty, so I'll take you home.
Please go.
I'm begging you.
Ms. Joo. Ms. Joo, we need to talk.
Talk about what?
Is it my wife who did this to you?
Ask her yourself.
Did my wife really do this to you?
Yes, she really did this to me.
What did I do so wrong?
All I did was try to live my best.
What's wrong with that?
It's not even just a couple of times.
Why on earth is she doing this to me?
Mr. Jo, please tell me.
What happened to mom?
She would've called me a long time ago.
Did something happen to her?
Mom, where are you right now?
I called you, but you weren't answering.
Did something happen?
Of course not. Were you worried about me?
Of course I was.
Nothing happened, and I'm home right now.
I'll come to the front yard,
so bring Yoo-sung out.
Mom, Yoo-sung is in dreamland right now.
I'll bring him to you tomorrow.
Will that be okay? What if
your mother-in-law scolds him?
She won't scold him.
We had dinner together, and
she fried ham for him because he likes it.
Really? I'm grateful.
Mom, don't worry about Yoo-sung and
sleep well with the doors locked tightly.
Rock-paper-scissors!
I won!
Ouch! It hurts!
Let's do it again. That was unfair.
Hee-dong, do you know what time it is?
Why are you acting like a little kid?
Look at my forehead! Do you know
how many times Yoo-jin hit me?
I need to get my revenge.
Are you going to stay up the whole night?
Fine. Since it's late,
we'll play again tomorrow.
I won't let you win tomorrow. Just watch.
I'm not scared of you at all.
What?
But where will I sleep tonight?
I know.
I'll let you sleep with Yoo-jin tonight.
Yoo-jin, sleep here with Aunt Shin-ae tonight.
Okay.
Then good night, ladies.
- Good night.
Thank you, God. Thank you so much.
Yoo-jin, what are you wishing for?
Aunt, God really exists.
I always asked God to fulfill my wish.
I was thanking God for fulfilling my wish.
What wish did you ask for?
To be able to sleep with you at least once.
What?
I love your smell. I love this place, too.
Mom, thank you.
You're thanking me?
You gave birth to me, and
you're letting me sleep with you.
Jang-go.
- What is it?
- I have to ask you something. Please answer it.
What is it?
Do you really love me?
Did you wake me up to ask me that?
Just answer my question.
Do you really love me?
Yes, I do.
If you really love me, then get up right now.
Why? What is it?
If you really love me, prove it to me.
Not with your words but with your body.
With my body?
But Yoo-sung is here.
Oh my god!
Kim Mi-poong,
I'm going to remember this forever!
What kind of woman uses her husband this way?
I'm so tired I could die!
Are you tired already?
You said you loved me, but you're
complaining after just thirty minutes?
So you only love me this much!
What? "Just thirty minutes?"
Do you want to see someone die
in "just thirty minutes?"
I'm so tired!
Is your t-shirt wet with sweat?
Can't you see me sweating right now?
Hold on.
My t-shirt isn't wet yet.
Oh, really?
Then run around the playground ten times.
What? Ten times?
Oh, I'm so dizzy!
Ten times?
Are you out of your mind?
I need exact function data
about how well this clothes
soaks up your sweat and
how well the ventilation is.
Hurry up and run!
Why are you getting mad at me?
I'll run.
Ten times?
Mi-poong, get out of the way.
Go! Go! Go! Hurry! Hurry! Hurry!
- I'm so tired!
- Hurry up!
- Go! Go! Go! Hurry! Hurry!
- I'm so tired! I can't do this anymore!
Hurry up! You said you loved me!
I'm going to die.
- Screw this!
- Jang-go!
Grandfather, eat a lot of mushrooms.
I will. You eat a lot, too.
By the way, if you want
to live a long, healthy life...
you need to eat this, too.
Really? Thank you.
You must be happy to finally
meet your granddaughter.
It was like she dropped from the sky.
Yes. I'm thankful for each and every day.
Yes. Mr. Kim, have some balloon flowers, too.
By the way, what happened
to the person who tricked others
by saying balloons
flowers were wild ginseng?
I'm not sure.
It's the fault of the person
who was tricked into believing
balloon flowers were
wild ginseng in the first place.
She just seemed quite desperate
to do that, so I just ignored it.
Mom, are you really going to do this?
Can't you shut your mouth?
Is Yoo-jin still asleep?
Yes, grandfather. She must have been
tired from playing with me until late last night.
Be good to her before she leaves today.
Grandfather. Mom. Grandma.
I want Yoo-jin to stay here for a
few more days. Would that be all right?
Shin-ae said she was okay with it.
Sure, go ahead.
Thank you, grandfather.
But why don't I see Dal-ho at home nowadays?
Why? Did something happen?
What is it? Chung-ja, you tell me.
Yes, well...
The thing is...
Dal-ho isn't coming home lately.
What?
What do you mean he isn't coming home lately?
What will you do?
What do you mean you're living in the office?
Why would you live there when you have a home?
I'm sorry, Mr. Kim.
But I...
I don't think I'll be able
to come home for a while.
What do you mean by that?
Why can't you come home?
It's going to be difficult
to live with my wife.
What? You can't live with Chung-ja? Why not?
There should be a reason.
Dal-ho, this is my fault! I'm sorry!
So please don't say that you
can't live with Chung-ja!
What's going on? Why is this your fault?
I don't understand what's going on.
What on earth happened
for Dal-ho to act like this?
The truth is, Chung-ja...
- She has delusional suspicion of his faithfulness.
- What?
Delusional suspicion?
It's not anything severe.
It's just in the early stages.
My goodness.
What on earth?
That's why Chung-ja misunderstood
Dal-ho as being unfaithful to her.
She bothered him quite a bit.
So please understand. She has an illness.
She's taking medication and getting
treatment for it, so please understand her.
My goodness.
How can this happen?
Dal-ho, I didn't know that, and
I had the wrong idea about you.
It was wrong of me to go to the
noodle restaurant and do that.
I'm sorry. I was wrong.
What did you do at the noodle restaurant?
Please understand even if I don't
come home for the time being.
And I will do my job, so you don't
have to worry about that.
Mr. Kim, I'm sorry.
Dal-ho! Mr. Kim! Dal-ho!
- Dal-ho.
- Honey.
Let's go to the bedroom and talk.
I don't want to talk to you, and
I don't want to hear anything from you.
Honey, I'm sorry! I'm really sorry!
If you say sorry, do you think you can
be forgiven for all that you've done?
I love you so much. That's why I did that.
So please understand me.
I'm going to the hospital, taking
my medication, and getting treatment.
That will never happen again. So, honey...
Is that why you did that last night?
Because you took your medication
and went to the hospital?
Last night?
You hurt someone and ran away
because you have an illness?
Can you do such a thing
I don't want to see you, so don't
call me and don't come to the store.
Got it?
- Dal-ho!
- Honey!
- Chung-ja!
What did you do this time?
Last night, I went to the noodle restaurant
and saw that the wench was there alone.
I just gave her a little push, and
she fell over. What was I supposed to do?
Oh my god, Chung-ja! What's wrong with you?
- Get a hold of yourself!
- Mom, look at what he just did.
How did he know that she fell and got hurt?
He knows because they contacted each other!
Chung-ja, do you want to get
admitted into a mental institution?
Dal-ho left because
you're continuing to be like this!
Mom, do I really have delusional
suspicion of my husband's faithfulness?
I'm imaging things that didn't even happen.
Oh, dear. How on earth did my daughter
end up with such a tragic illness?
Oh, no.
Mom, what do I do?
Mom, what if I get divorced?
How did you injure your hand?
I got into an accident while working at home.
I'm so sorry.
If you don't work, you'll run out of
money quickly. What are you going to do?
We'll do your share of the work until you
- get better, so just come out.
- Yes, Ms. Joo.
Thank you for your kind words.
I won't be able to forget any of you.
All right.
It seems like there's
something you can't tell us.
Come visit us sometimes.
Yes, I will.
- Good-bye.
- Mr. Jo.
Hello.
Thank you for everything.
Good-bye.
- Is she quitting?
- Yes. She injured her hand and
has something going on at home.
Ms. Joo.
We need to talk.
Mr. Jo, please let go of me.
What if someone sees us and
we get misunderstood again?
I have nothing to talk about with you.
I do.
Get in the car first.
Mr. Jo!
(New Sports Line Launching Proposal)
This is the proposal for
the launching project.
Judging from your expression,
it seems like you're confident.
More than that, I did my best,
so I have no regrets.
Oh, that's great then!
Your efforts will pay off. Good job!
Aren't the rest of you going
to turn in your proposals?
Are you going to give
this good opportunity up?
Can I turn it in tomorrow?
That's not up to me.
The deadline is this afternoon.
Here, Ms. Kim.
What about you, Min-cheol?
If you're so tormented,
why are you turning it in?
Just in case.
I don't know if that'll work.
Yoo-jin, I have to go to work right now.
So you have to be with Hee-dong
until I'm done with work.
Don't say anything strange.
Do you think I'm stupid?
I remember everything
you told me, so don't worry.
Okay, my smart girl.
What were you two whispering about?
It's a secret between us girls.
Are you going to work now?
Yes, I have a meeting today.
Then how about just
the two of us go on a date?
Yes!
What are you two going to do without me?
Oh, it's a secret.
Yoo-jin, I'm going to work,
so have fun with Hee-dong.
I'll be going now, Hee-dong.
Be safe.
Bye.
Yoo-jin, where do you want to go?
Do you want to go to the
bookstore to buy story books?
- Pigs go...
- Oink! Oink!
-Ducks go...
- Quack! Quack!
- Chucks go...
- Peek! Peek!
- Sparrows go...
- Chirp! Chirp!
- Pigs go...
- I want to go to school, too, just like the others.
If you want to go to school, you can go.
Yoo-jin, let's go.
- Really?
- Yes!
Do you really take students for short periods?
Since you came today, do you want to introduce
yourself to everyone and play with the kids?
Yes!
Yoo-jin, have fun. I'll pick you up later.
Hi.
Oh, Yoo-jin!
Yoo-sung!
(New Sports Line Launching Proposal)
You can pick one of the two to become the
finalist. The other finalist will be this one.
Yes, ma'am.
But isn't this Ms. Kim Mi-poong's proposal?
I thought you wanted to chase her out of here.
We can't fire someone just
because their proposal is poor.
I understand what you mean.
I'll make a good reason for you to fire her.
She won't be able to get out of this one.
Then I'll leave it up to you.
Thank you.
Ms. Kim Mi-poong.
Yes, Ms. Park.
I liked the proposal you submitted this time,
especially about how you didn't
rely on the data for the
positive points about last season's
sportswear but researched it yourself.
Congratulations on becoming a finalist.
Thank you, Ms. Park.
The board members are looking
forward to it, too, so do your best.
I hope you can get a promotion, Kim Mi-poong.
Yes, I'll do my best.
By the way,
make sure to keep this a secret.
Be careful not to leak any
information about your efforts.
Got it?
Yes, I got it.
Thank you.
Nam-yi!
Since you're here,
the store is shiny and bright.
This place was somber
without you. I really missed you.
Thank you. I missed you, too.
Nam-yi, thank you for coming out.
No need to thank me. I just
came out because, like you said,
it was rude of me to quit without
you hiring another employee first.
I'm only going to come out until you get
another employee, so hurry up and find one.
Nam-yi, no!
Won-bin, go to the bakery.
You can eat whatever you want.
I'm going to pay for them.
Yes, father.
Nam-yi, let's have a sincere talk.
Why do you want to quit?
Why else? Because I don't like you.
You dislike me? Me?
Yes.
I'm bewildered because I've never met
someone recently who didn't like me before.
You're pretty full of yourself.
To be honest, you're a bit weird.
You should know that.
I thought I treated you
with manners all this time.
I even gave you a bonus last time.
How can you attack me like this?
I'm very hurt.
So you're saying I'm weird, right?
Is that why you dislike me?
I'm not saying you're very weird.
You just don't know a woman's feelings.
Fine. If you dislike me
so much, you should quit.
I'll hire another employee right away.
Until then, I hope you can bear with me.
This wasn't supposed to happen. What do I do?
Should I confess right now?
But why didn't you give Ms. Hwang
the gift I told you to give her?
Did you pocket it?
That's not it...
- I didn't know you were such a dull person.
- A dull person?
How can you ask me to give that to her?
I was trying to hold this in, but I can't
anymore! Do you like my sister-in-law?
Excuse me?
I'm sorry for dragging you here.
But I really wanted to talk to you,
and I felt like I had to...
I know you feel apologetic towards me.
And I know you'll feel guilty
that I'm quitting work like this.
And that's why you brought me here.
But I'm fine.
I'm fine. I'm quitting without any
resentment, so don't feel guilty anymore.
You're right.
I do feel very guilty towards you.
So on the way here,
I was thinking about telling you
how sorry I am and that
I'm hoping you won't quit.
I thought I had brought you
here to say those things to you.
But...
While I was bringing you here...
I realized that's not all
I wanted to say to you.
Mr. Jo, what are you talking about?
When you were leaving the store earlier...
I couldn't send you away like that.
I felt like I shouldn't just
let you leave like this.
I was going to bury these
feelings within me until I die.
Mr. Jo, what are you trying to say?
I'm going to take the bus home.
I think that would be best.
Ms. Joo.
I know it's shameless of me to ask you this,
but can't you come back out to the restaurant?
Aside from everything else,
I'd like to repay my debt to you.
You're not indebted to me.
Thank you for the kindness
you showed my family and me.
I mean it.
Then go home safely.
I am erasing you, I need to forget you now
You spread through my fingers, it hurts
What do I do?
Are you someone I can't forget?
Are you someone I can't erase?
While I live, will there be a day without you?
Is it too late for you to come back?
I love you, I can't erase these words
Oh, all right! All right!
I'm on my way right now!
I'm sorry, mom.
I promised Mi-poong I would pick up
Yoo-sung today, but I'm not done with work yet.
Mom, you can't scold Mi-poong for this, okay?
Hang up!
How frustrating!
Where did mother go today?
What on earth is that woman doing? How can she
let her grandson be cared for by someone else?
My goodness!
- Let's go home.
- I don't want to say good-bye to Yoo-sung.
- Can't I play with him a little longer?
- I want to play with her, too.
But the school is closed,
so we have to go home.
How about you guys play tomorrow?
I don't want to.
Can't we play at your house?
I want to play with
Yoo-jin at your house, too.
What's your name again? Yoo-sung?
Yes. I'm Kim Yoo-sung.
If you want to play at my house,
you have to get permission from your mom.
I don't have a mom.
I only have a grandma and an aunt.
Oh, really?
Yoo-sung!
Let's go! Your grandma and aunt
are busy today, so I came instead.
- Hello.
- Oh, you're Chung-ja's son.
Yes, Ms. Hwang. Hello.
Hi. But what brings you here?
This little girl is staying at our house.
But she wants to play with Yoo-sung.
Can he play at my house?
I'll take him home later.
Of course he can. All right. You can
take him. Just bring him home safely later.
I will. Thank you.
Go ahead and play, Yoo-sung.
Let's go.
That's good. I won't have
to bother with him anymore.
But why is Chung-ja so late? She said she was
hungry and told us to order a bunch of food.
They say women with delusional
suspicion can suddenly go mad.
What if she forgot her plans with us
and is stalking her husband right now?
Does she really want to do that at her age?
I want to throw my husband away.
I know!
Hi! I'm here!
I'm late, aren't I? There was so much traffic!
Why? Is there something on my face?
No!
You said you were hungry.
Eat up. Have some meat, too.
Thank you.
They say that your body has to be
healthy for your mind to be healthy.
At our age, health is more
important than money!
Come on! That's an old joke!
The barbecued beef here is good.
Chung-ja, have some potato pancakes.
Someone said that these
are good for your illness.
What illness?
If you eat well and relax, you can fix it.
Why are you so obsessed
with your husband at that age?
You should just meet up with us and have fun!
You guys heard something
from Geum-sil, didn't you?
Who cares where we heard it from?
The important thing is that
you need to cure your illness.
And you shouldn't hide your illness.
What are friends for?
It's times like these that you should get
some fresh air and meet up with us.
Or else, your delusional suspicion of
your husband's faithfulness will worsen.
You don't have to be embarrassed at all.
You have a good illness.
Geum-sil and I are widows,
so we can't even get such an illness.
Are you guys happy that I have delusional
suspicion of my husband's faithfulness?
- You brats.
- Chung-ja.
Hey, Hwang Geum-sil! Come out here!
- Come out!
- That sounds like Chung-ja.
What is it?
How can you do this to me?
Are you really my friend?
I trusted you!
How can you tell everyone I have delusional
suspicion of my husband's faithfulness?
Chung-ja, Young-soon was
there at the movie theater, too.
She was so worried about you.
That's why I told her. Is that so wrong?
And who cares if they know?
They're our friends.
Is that why they're laughing at me?
Come on, Chung-ja. Who did that?
No one would do such a thing!
I became like this
because of you and Young-soon!
If you two hadn't told me
about the movie theater incident,
then I wouldn't have such a terrible illness!
Chung-ja, sit down.
To be honest, compared to other women, you've
always been obsessive about your husband.
You have a maid at home,
and yet, you missed out on
several of our meetings
because you had to cook for him.
How can I come out when
my husband is home all alone?
You probably don't know
because you don't have a husband,
but you're not supposed to leave
your husband alone in the house with a maid!
See? Ever since then, you were in the
early stages of your delusional suspicion.
Oh my gosh, Chung-ja.
Anyways, you'll be able
to cure that illness if you just
take your medication,
so relax and think positively.
Geum-sil, do I really have delusional
suspicion of my husband's faithfulness?
Yes, you do. Oh my goodness, Chung-ja.
Everyone has been saying I have delusional
suspicion, so I feel like I really do have it.
What can I do?
What will I do if I can't cure this illness?
Chung-ja, don't cry.
My heart is starting to break.
Geum-sil, last night, I thought my husband
and that wench was together,
so I went to the noodle restaurant
and made an accident.
An accident? What accident?
I was spying on the noodle restaurant outside
when your in-law came out
with all the employees but
sent them away and went back
into the restaurant by herself.
What?
That's why I barged in there.
She said she came to lock up the
gas valve, but would I believe her?
So I accused her of coming
to seduce my husband
and just slightly pushed her on accident.
She was too weak and fell right over.
She injured her wrist on a glass rod.
That's why I'm about to get divorced.
What will I do?
Oh, no. I told you not to doubt him.
I told you to believe him.
Chung-ja, you didn't take the
medication the hospital gave you, huh?
I forgot to take it yesterday and today.
See! You should have taken your medication!
Mother! Nam-yi! When did you come home?
- Hello.
- Hi.
I overheard you have delusional
suspicion of your husband's faithfulness.
How did you get such a terrible illness?
- I'll be going now. Bye.
- Bye, Chung-ja.
Go home safely.
Geum-sil, was she talking
about Mi-poong's mom?
Yes.
Hold on.
I saw Mi-poong's mom this morning,
and she had a bandage around her wrist.
Then she hurt Ms. Joo's hand due to of
her suspicion of her husband's faithfulness?
No way!
Oh my goodness.
It must be sad to live
all by herself. On top of that,
she got misunderstood
and had her hand injured.
How heartbroken she must be.
Yoo-jin. Yoo-sung. I'm going to be upstairs,
so if you need anything, come see me. Okay?
- Okay.
- Please make snacks for them.
- Sure.
Kids, I'll give you your snacks soon,
so wait here and play for a little bit.
- Okay.
It's so nice to have kids around the house.
Yoo-sung, do you want to play hide-and-seek?
Sure. You can hide first.
Okay.
Come out come out wherever you are.
Ready or not, here I come.
Did you see Yoo-jin?
I'm not sure. I don't know where she is.
Got you!
It's my turn to hide now.
Okay.
Come out come out wherever you are.
I found you, Yoo-sung!
What are you staring at?
This ring looks exactly
like my grandma's ring.
Wow, it's pretty. It's a wedding ring.
Honey, is the baby sleeping?
Yes, he's sleeping, honey.
Honey, are you hungry?
Yes, I'm hungry. Hurry up
and give me food, honey.
Okay, honey. Come here and eat some snacks.
Be careful, honey.
Welcome.
Thanks to you,
Yoo-jin had a fun time. Thank you.
I had a relaxed time, thanks to you.
- Bye, Yoo-sung.
- Bye.
- Go home safely.
- I will.
Yoo-sung, let's go to your house and
leave your backpack and jacket there.
It's okay. I can do it by myself.
Really? Then change your clothes and
come back so that we can have dinner.
Okay.
- Yoo-jin.
- Aunt!
Goodness. Did you have a good day?
Where did you get this ring from?
From Mr. Kim's room.
Why would you play with this?
You're not supposed to play with it! Got it?
Okay.
Yoo-jin, where's the other ring?
I gave it to Yoo-sung.
What?
You gave it to who?
Yoo-sung? Which Yoo-sung?
I only know one Yoo-sung.
Then are you saying you gave
the ring to Yoo-sung, the little boy
who lived in that house that you
visited with Soon-boon last time?
Do you want to see me die?
I'm sorry.
(Blow Breeze)
Tell me the truth! Where is the ring?
- Will the police take me if I steal something?
- Of course.
- I asked if you like her.
- Yes, I do like her.
Mi-poong! You're going to break the machine.
Don't stop me!
Hello. I'm Kim Mi-poong
from the third marketing team.
Model, please come inside.
- What's wrong?
- You need to kiss me.
Isn't this demoralization?
Can a lawyer do this?
Aren't you Mr. Lee Jang-go?
Find out about lawyer Mr. Lee Jang-go for me.
Subtitles by OnDemandKorea