- (Episode 34)- Explain!
What are these?
If you have a mouth, explain yourself.Will you still deny it?
Stop the nonsense andcome back home this instant!
Mr. Kim,
I can't come home.
I can't live with her anymore.
What? You can't live with me?
Then are you going to live with her?
- Mr. Kim, just hear the wayhe talks! It's so unfair!
- Chung-ja, stay still!
How dare you be irresponsible and saythat you can't live with her so easily?
I have no desire to livewith a rude person like her.
I'm sorry, Mr. Kim.
What? A rude person?
He's the one who's being rude!
I thought this woman was gentle.
She's a terrible one!
Where do you think you're going?You made the house into a mess!
Do you think running away will solve anything?
I'll call you soon. We'll meet at court.
What? Court?
Why do we have to meet at court?
I did nothing wrong! All I did washave our kids and raise them!
You did nothing wrong?
Do you even think of me asyour husband? Is that why you hired
someone to tail me and take photosof me? Why would you do that?
So what did you find out?What did I do? You tell me!
Well...
Look here!
Was Chung-ja the one who had an affair?You get angry at others for your mistakes!
You should be begging forforgiveness on your knees! How dare you
raise your voice at her!Are you still going to deny this?
- You little...- Jo Dal-ho!
- What do I do?- My goodness! I'm so upset!
But who sent you these pictures?
Chung-ja, did you reallyhire someone to take these?
I didn't do this. I wonder who did it.
Did you take these photos?
Yes.
I was so upset that peoplemisunderstood you as having
delusional suspicion ofyour husband's faithfulness.
But I think I made a mistake. Father wasso angry when he left. What will we do now?
No, no. You did the right thing.
If it wasn't for you, I would'vecontinued to be a mental patient.
You did the right thing byproving I'm a sane person.
Thank you, Shin-ae. You did the right thing.
Mother, are you going to just let this slide?
What?
You should barge intoMi-poong's house with your friends.
Show them these photosand turn that house upside down.
Make sure they can't live in thatneighborhood without any shame.
You're right. I have these photos as proof.
I'm going to make sure tochase them out of Geum-sil's house
so that they can't come near us ever again.
- What are these?- Can't you tell?
So your husband really cheated on you?
It's so unfair.
Soon-jung, I'm about to losemy husband to a fox, just like you did.
- What am I supposed to do?- What else?
Let's go. Chung-ja, lead the way.
- Go where?- Evil home-wreckers like her must be crushed!
What are you guys doing?She's about to lose her husband!
- Yeah, let's go.- Okay, let's go.
Hey.
Get up and eat thisso that you can feel better.
I feel nauseous!
Why did you drink in the first place?
Why would you do somethingyou've never done before at this age?
Here.
My goodness. Serves you right.
Aren't you going to go to work?
I'm really going to quit.
Oh, be quiet!
Where else will you get sucha comfortable job at your age?
Just go!
Mr. Kim said he likes Geum-sil!
Do you still want me to go?
Your boss likes Geum-sil?
Father, why isn't Nam-yi here again?
Did you nag her again?
No. Nam-yi is sick.
She's sick? How is she sick?
Hello, ma'am.
- Hi.- Hello.
- Hi.- Is Nam-yi very sick?
Yes, she is.
Did she go to the hospital?
Won-bin, I came to talk to your father.
Can you go outside for a moment?
- Sure. Please tell Nam-yi to get well soon.- I will.
Please have a seat.
How is Nam-yi sick?
She was fine yesterday,but she suddenly said she was sick.
That's not it.
I came because I wanted to ask you something.
Mr. Kim, do you like my daughter-in-law?
Yes, I like her.
Oh, dear. I didn't think you were that kind
of person. Do you think this makes any sense?
Is it wrong for me to like Geum-sil?
She resembles my biological sister.That's why I like her.
So you like her as a sisterand not as a woman?
After my parents passed away early,my sister took care of me like I was her own son.
She passed away before she couldsee me succeed, and that broke my heart.
I really wanted to seemy sister, but Ms. Hwang
resembles her a lot,so I was happy to just see her.
So you really like her as a sister?
Yes. However, I can end upliking her as a woman.
Oh, you can't do that!
Don't even say that!Just like her as a sister!
Do you know the age gapbetween you and Geum-sil?
Men and women must meetpeople near their own age.
When there's a huge age gap,life gets very difficult.
You shouldn't meet older women.Find someone your own age.
If you look around you, you'll beable to find a woman around your age.
Why would you look for an older woman?
Who are you talking about?
Someone near you.Someone you'll be able to meet every day.
When you think about those things,someone will pop into your mind automatically.
What's this?
Fermented soybean paste.
My mother-in-law made it. If you just put
kimchi and tofu in there, it'll be delicious.
Oh, thank you! I'll enjoy it.
But did you come here just for this?
I had some time before I hadto go to work in the afternoon,
and I had something to tell you, too.
Something to tell me?
What is it?
It's about Mr. Jo's wife.
She's not allowed to come to Deokcheonok.
She can't come anywhere near there anymore.
We told Mr. Kim everythingshe had done to you.
Mr. Kim was so furious!I bet Ms. Ma was scolded very badly!
I see.
So come back to Deokcheonok.I came to tell you that.
Thank you. I'm very grateful...
but I don't think it would be rightfor me to return to Deokcheonok.
- Where is this horrid wench?- Hwang Geum-sil, you come out here, too!
What's going on?
- Is it here?- Break everything!
Break everything!
- You horrible wench!- Why are you doing this?
Let go of me!
Oh, no!
Why are you getting in the way?
Stop, everyone! That's enough!
How dare you barge into someone else'shome and do something so shameful!
Get out, all of you!
Chung-ja, are you crazy? Young-soon andSoon-jung, why are you guys doing this, too?
Chung-ja is abnormal!
How can you not stop her fromdoing this? Are you guys insane?
Hwang Geum-sil, are you takingher side because she's your in-law?
Look at these before you speak!
- What's this?- Here. Look.
What are these? My goodness.
Oh my god.
Oh my god!
What are these?
It's as you see them!
This woman seduced Chung-ja'shusband and had an affair with him!
No way.
How can you live with your daughter-in-lawwhose mother is a home-wrecker?
It's not true!
No! This isn't true! It's not!
All of you, get out of here! Get out!
- Get out!- It's not true!
Oh my goodness. What on earth is going on?
Why would she cry when I'm the onewho should be crying? Hwang Geum-sil!
If you still live withthat woman and her daughter,
I'm going to take Hee-ra out of here.
And I won't see you ever again either!
Chung-ja, now that Geum-sil knows,she'll do something about it. Let's go.
You better not tell Hee-ra about this.
Or else I'll die!
Hey Hwang Geum-sil,you better get your head together!
What on earth is going on?
But why did the hospital diagnose heras having delusional suspicion?
You know blood pressure cantemporarily rise if you get excited.
She was doubtful of her husband then,which is why she got that diagnosis.
But Ms. Joo really looked likeshe was in an unfair position.
I know.
What if something went wrong?
What if they were at a push-and-pullstage and got misunderstood?
What's that?
They're not going out, but theymight have feelings for each other.
Then you should just phrase it that way!Why do you have to speak in such weird terms?
I'm back.
Out of all people, it just hasto be with my friend's husband.
Out of all people, it just has to bewith your sister-in-law's father.
I hate the fact thatyou're my daughter-in-law!
Mother...
I'm back.
You fool.
What's wrong? Did something happen?
You idiot.
You left Ha-yeon behind to get marriedto the daughter of an adulteress?
Even if you choose a womanwith your eyes closed,
you'll choose a better woman than this one!
Grandma. Aunt.
What's wrong with mom?
Well...
Mom, what happened?
Why did you come here? I don'twant you to see this. Go back home.
I need to go pick up Yoo-sung.
Jang-go went to pick him up.
Mom, are you stupid?
Why didn't you do anything while they destroyedyour house? What did you do so wrong?
Mom...
let me ask you something. Be honest with me.
Mom, do you have feelings for Mr. Jo?
Mi-poong, what are you talking about?
Mr. Jo is a married man.
It's not like that at all.
Mom, I don't care what others say.
I'm only going to believe what you tell me.
Even if you tell me that you dohave feelings for him, I won't bash you.
I'm going to try to understand youbecause you're my mom.
No, Mi-poong, I didn’t.
Then what are those photos?
Did you see them, too?
Mi-poong,
I injured my hand becauseMr. Jo's wife pushed me.
After I came out from surgery, I was so
bewildered and frustratedthat I started to cry.
Mom...
I wanted to rely on anyone then.
I would've held onto anyoneat that moment and cried.
That's how I felt back then.
Mr. Jo apologized and said it washis fault that my hand became this way.
He wanted to apologize on behalf of his wife.
That's why I was holding onto him and crying.
Mi-poong,
if not for you and Yoo-sung...
I want to die.
- Mom...- How can I live in such a cruel world?
You did nothing wrong. Why wouldyou die? Why would you say that?
Why do people believe her and not me?
Is it because I'm a poorNorth Korean defector?
Is it because I'm a widow?
Why is no one believing me?
I feel like that's so unfair.
I believe you.
I'll believe you.
Mother, my mom is not in anyrelationship with Mr. Jo. I just asked her.
Then what about those photosof them hugging and holding hands?
Is that another person?
I don't know what happened in there either.
However, it's not true.
You don't know? But it's not true?
How stubborn. Like mother, like daughter.
My mom doesn't lie to me.
Please believe my mom's innocence.
If she did something wrong,she should acknowledge it and beg
for forgiveness. At least I wouldthink she was a human being then.
Oh my god. I'm too scared tolive with you and your mom.
Geum-sil, aren't you being too harsh?
I'm being harsh?
To be frank, we're both widows.
Widows know widows.
Widows can date other men.
But how can she date a married man?
That's just wrong.
- You shouldn't make others miserable!- My mom is not that kind of person!
I hate it that you're arguing aboutthis even if the evidence is right there!
Anyways, I can't live with either of you.
So either you divorce Jang-go,
or if you can't do that, takeyour family out of here. I'm begging you.
You're being too much.
Can't you believe her just this once?
Why do you keep telling me to believe her?
This is so humiliating!
Because of you two, I can't even eat!
My mom is not that kind of person.
Please believe her! Grandma! Mother! Aunt!
Mi-poong, I examined the photos,
and it seems like someonewas tailing them to take
photos of them only whenthey were closely together.
The camera was angled so thatthey would look close to each other.
If someone was trying to trap them,then they couldn't help but fall for it.
Whoever took those photosis a horrible person!
Mi-poong, stop crying.
Your mother must be having a hard time.We should help her out, don't you think?
You're right. I'm not going to cry.
- You believe me, don't you?- Of course I believe you!
Even if you say adzuki beans aresoybeans, I'll believe you. Even if you say
you could make fermented soybeansout of adzuki beans, I'll believe you.
- What?- When did I say adzuki beans are soybeans?
I said adzuki beans are adzuki beans!
Even in this situation...
Fine.
- I'm going to get revenge.- Revenge? On who?
Everyone! I'm going to get revenge oneveryone who made my mom miserable!
Okay, go ahead.
I'm on your side no matter what!
Stop crying.
Come in.
Mr. Jo!
You didn't answer your phone!Where were you all this time?
What's going on?
Did you fight someone today?
Yes, I did.
I dropped by Ms. Joo's housebefore I came here.
Your wife barged into her homewith all her friends!
They wrecked her houseand pulled her hair out!
My wife went to her house?
It was so chaotic!
She showed the photos of youand Ms. Joo together
and tormented her like they were after a rat!
Photos?
I'm telling you this becauseI think you should know about it.
She worked so hard to survive aftercoming down here from North Korea.
This is just wrong.
(Deokcheonok Boss)
Grandma, are you very sick?
I'm not sick. I'm okay now.
Yoo-sung, would you like toeat some rice cakes for a snack?
Yes!
All right.
Wait a little bit.
It's been a while.
Why did you come here, Mr. Jo?
- Well...- Did you come here to see my mom?
Yes. She wasn't answering her phone.I was worried that she might be sick.
Is she okay?
Why would you worry if she's sick or not?
- I heard she suffered because of me today...- Mr. Jo.
Yes, you're right.
Because of you, my momwas humiliated as a woman.
Because your actions.
Since you're acting like this, peoplekeep misunderstanding my mom,
and she keeps being humiliated like this.
How much more are you trying tomake her suffer by coming here?
I'm sorry. I'm very sorry.
If you're really sorry,please don't come here.
Don't call my mom,and don't be curious about her.
That's the way you can help her.
If you consider my mom at all,
please be careful so that thereare no more misunderstandings.
I'm begging you.
Good-bye.
Hi, honey. It's me.
Right now?
Okay, I'll come out right now.
Chung-ja, have some jujube tea.
- What's going on? Where are you going?- Mom, Dal-ho wants to see me outside.
Mom, how do I look? What if my make-upisn't right? What can I do about my face?
Did Dal-ho call you out becausehe wants you to sign the divorce papers?
What? No way.
Even if you want me to signthe divorce papers, it won't work.
I'd rather die than divorce you.
I heard you went to Ms. Joo's house today.
What? Did you meet her again?
Did she tell you that I destroyed her house?
Did you call me out to scold me for that?
How can you go to her houseand do such a thing?
What? "Such a thing?"
You barged into an innocentperson's house and wrecked havoc.
Do you think you did the right thing?
She's innocent?
I'm still alive!
Should I do nothing whenshe seduces my husband?
She hugged you,held your hand, and smiled at you.
But she's innocent?
I hugged her!
I held her hand! I looked at her!
Don't you have eyes?Can't you tell from the photos?
That woman didn't do anything! I did it!
What?
I felt bad for her.
I felt bad that she had toplay your punching bag.
What did she do so wrong for youto make her suffer this way?
I met her so that I couldapologize on your behalf.
I met her to take her to thehospital on your behalf.
Don't lie.
Then why did you leave home?
Didn't you leave because of her?Because you're going to live with her?
I left home because of you.Not because of Ms. Joo.
So don't bother her anymore.
If you bother her again...
I won't forgive you.
Did you call me out at this hourjust so you can tell me this?
Fine.
If you come home,I'll believe everything you just told me.
But if you don't come home,I'll keep going to her house.
What?
If you don't come home tonight, I'll go toher house again tomorrow and destroy it!
If you don't come home every day,I'm going to torture her every day!
Why? You think I can't do it?
Then just wait and see!
Then if I come back home,
will you never go to see her again?
Can you promise me?
Good. You did the right thing by coming home.
I'm sorry for creating a commotion.
Married couples can't always be happy.
You can be swayed.
That's all part of life.
Still, you shouldn't go down the wrong path.
Be careful from now on.
You shouldn't meet people so carelessly.
The kids are watching.He won't do that anymore.
- Chung-ja.- Yes?
As long as a man's pride as the head of thehouse isn't damaged, he won't leave home.
Be careful from now on. Got it?
Yes.
What's that good smell?
Chung-ja, are you making loach soup?
Dal-ho wouldn't have eaten well while he was
staying at the office. That's why I made this.
My goodness. What a faithful woman you are!
If it was me, I wouldn't even wantto give him a bowl of cold rice!
Why would you serve loach soup toyour unfaithful husband? My goodness!
- Don't eat it then!- We're back!
Hello! Did you guys eat dinner?
Yes. I heard father came back home.
Yes.
He did come back,but he's in Hee-dong's studio.
Tell him to get out of that room.
Okay.
Yoo-jin, let's go.
- Go on up.- Okay.
Mother, I'm so happy for you.
I know. It's all thanks to you.
It's nothing. Wait a little bit longer.
Everything will settle down soon.
Thank you.
Taste this loach soup.
Looks delicious, right?
Father, are you drinking?
Yes. Can I use your room for a few days?
Of course.
I'll pour you a drink.
Thanks.
I'm sorry.
It's nothing.
- Mi-poong.- Are you leaving right now?
Yes, but I have a meeting, so I won'tbe able to go to work with you today.
I'm okay, so hurry up and go.
Tie my necktie for me. I havean important meeting today.
Sure.
I'm sorry I can't help you today.
I told you that you canhelp me by not helping me.
If my mom says something, let it go inone ear and out the other. Okay?
Cheer up.
- Done?- Yes.
Kiss.
What are you two doingin the middle of breakfast?
- Mom.- And in the kitchen, too.
I asked Mi-poong to tie my necktie for me,since I have an important meeting today.
When Mi-poong ties my necktie,it's good luck for me.
- I'm off.- Aren't you going to eat
breakfast before you go?
Yes, I have a meeting this morning.Bye, Mi-poong!
- Drive safely.- I will.
- We're off.- You guys are going early, too?
It's not time for the store to open yet.
I have to arrange theinventory and new products
are coming in today, so I have to leave early.
Mother, I shouldn'thave opened up a shop!
I can't get enough sleep, andmy legs swell up so much!
That's why I massage your legs every day!
I know! That's why I hold it in andcontinue to go to work! All because of you!
- Oh, my sweetie.- What a load of crap.
- How lovey-dovey!- Hee-ra, we're going to be late. Bye!
You can't go on an empty stomach.Hold on. Drink some milk before you go.
- We're fine.- We're fine.
Of course you're not fine.
What are you doing? Go pour some milk.
Oh, okay.
We're fine...
Hold on. At least eat some of this tofu. Here.
Drink some milk, too.
- It's good.- Hurry up! They're running late!
- Coming!- Drink some milk before you go.
- Thank you.- You'll be able to work that way.
- Thank you.- Thanks you, mother. Bye.
- Kiss, kiss! Bye!- Thanks, mom!
Mi-poong, hurry up and eatso that you can go to work.
Okay.
Why are you so surprised?
Did you do something wrong,just like your mother?
Pardon?
Come outside.
I bought these at the fish market,and they just delivered them.
Clean the scales and leave them to dry here.
When they become firm,we'll move them to the freezer.
Mother, I have to go to work.
Don't you think I know that?
You can just say somethingcame up and go a little later.
I don't think that's possible.I have a team meeting in the morning.
And it's not an emergency either.I can't be late
just because I haveto clean up these fish.
I'll clean them after I come back from work.
How dare you talk back to me. If I tellyou to do it, you should just do it.
- Do my words mean nothing to you?- Of course not.
I'll do them after I come back from work.
Then what about these fish?Do you want them to rot?
If you like the company so much,divorce Jang-go
and go work at the company all you want.
That works out. You should do that.
Ms. Hwang,
I'll take care of these, so pleaselet Mi-poong go to work.
How dare you touch this! Take your hands off!
- What's all this commotion about?- What's wrong, Geum-sil?
Oh my gosh!
- What's going on?- What happened to the fish?
I told Mi-poong to clean up the fish, andshe and her mother are acting so dramatic.
What on earth did you teach her thatmakes her talk back to her mother-in-law?
What could you have taught her whileyou were dating another woman's husband?
You're being very offensive.
How can you say suchrude things in front of someone?
I said rude things? I'm being offensive?
You're the one being offensive around here.
I'm so ashamed to haveyour daughter as my daughter-in-law!
When I see her face, I think ofwhat you did, and I start to shudder!
Yet, I have to put up with her underthe same roof! Do you know how I feel?
Mi-poong, I'm so sickand tired of hating you now.
Please leave Jang-go now!
- Divorce him!- Geum-sil!
That's enough!
To be frank, it's not like Mi-poongwas the one who had an affair!
What are you doing early inthe morning? How embarrassing.
You're a parent, too,so how can you tell our kids
to get divorced when they're happy together?
I'll leave this house instead.Would that make you happy?
How would that make me happy?
If you leave this house,isn't she still your daughter?
My goodness. It's like you'rehiding your head in the sand.
Then what should I do?
Would you be happy ifI severed ties with my daughter?
- Mom.- You stay quiet.
If that's what you want, I'll do it.
So please be good to my poor,innocent Mi-poong.
Please don't torment her.
Mom, I'm okay.
I'll take care of the fish,so Mi-poong, hurry up and go to work.
Yes, Mi-poong. Go to work.
I'll move out as soon as possible.
I'll get out of your way as you wish.
You could've moved outdozens of times already.
Please actually leave this timeinstead of just saying it with your words.
Ms. Kim, Mi-poong is runninga little late today, too,
so how about we start the meeting first?
She'll come soon.
That's right! She's taking thebus today, so there must be a lot of traffic.
Do other people come earlybecause there's no traffic?
Good morning! I'm sorry!I'm a little late today.
Since I was late, should I get coffee?
Mi-poong, we need to talk.
Why did you come so late? Ms. Kim is angry.
Mi-poong, I am proud of thefact that you use your lunchtime
and stay after work to finish your tasks.
However, if you're alwayslate to work like this,
the work atmospherewill get a lot more difficult.
I can't just let you get away with this.
I'm sorry.
If your proposal gets picked,then the products
will be made in the factory right away.
Then you'll be the soleperson-in-charge for all the steps,
starting from the marketingplanning to the launching event.
What can you do if you can't evencome to the team meeting on time?
I know you're a passionate worker.
I'm saying this because I feel bad for you.
It makes me upset.
So don't be offended.
I won't. I'm sorry.
Try to find a way.
Isn't your mother-in-law being too much?
Move out of the house or...
Forget it.
Hi, mom.
Were you late?
No, I wasn't late.
Thank goodness.
I was worried you would be late.
You shouldn't be.
Mi-poong...
I'm so sorry.
What are you talking about?Why would you be sorry?
Because of me, your mother-in-law dislikes
you, and you're leading a hard married life.
Other married women don't have to even lifta finger at home because they go to work.
Work life must be hard for you,but on top of that,
you're suffering through a hard married life.
I'm so upset and sorry.
Mom, I'm okay.Work life isn't hard for me at all.
I should've moved out fromthe beginning. I was thoughtless.
I'm going to look for a room for rent today.
So just know that.
Mom!
I told you she's very angry!
- I'll bring coffee.- No, she said just come right now,
since we're busy.
- Hurry up.- Okay.
Sit down.
I have a special order from the chairman.
Each and every department of Winner'sGroup must go through an internal audit.
Get ready.
Yes, sir.
- I'm sorry. May I get this?- Go ahead.
Hello? This is lawyer Lee Jang-go.
It'll be taken care of today? Thank you.
Mi-poong.
What's wrong with your expression?Did something happen?
Nothing happened.
What is it?
I'm busy, so I have to go back to work.
I got a call that your lease compensationwill be given to you today.
Really? Are you serious?
What? Didn't something happen to you?
You look so happy now thatyou're getting money.
Who wouldn't be happy to receivemoney in their bank account?
It's really being deposited!
But the amount is pretty small.
How much is it?
I thought you would be able to get atleast $30,000, but it'll only be $20,000.
$30,000 would've been great,but so is $20,000.
Jang-go, thank you so much.My mom will be so happy.
A deposit of $10,000?
You won't be able to geta room here with that kind of money.
There is a studio.
The deposit is $10,000 and themonthly rent is a thousand dollars.
The monthly rent is a thousand dollars?
Hi, it's me.
The lease compensation came out?
Will you and Yoo-sung reallybe okay by yourselves?
Of course. Don't worry about us anymore.
If we get a place nearby,we'll be able to see you often.
Mi-poong,
I don't want to live in that house any longer.
If I can just get a room that willprotect us from the wind and rain,
that will make me comfortable.
Do that then.
Move away.
Thank you, Mi-poong.
The heavens helped us.
The lease compensation came out on time.
I know.
I was so hopeful whileI was coming to see you.
It's my lunchtime,so let's go find a room together.
Okay.
Right this way.
Sit down.
The house is very sunny, andhot water comes out very well. I like it.
To pay a deposit of $30,000and pay a monthly rent
of only $300 in this neighborhoodis very cheap.
Can I move in next week?
Of course! They're moving out tomorrow,so come in whenever you'd like.
All right. Then I'll sign the contract.
You're moving out next week? Really?
Yes, I just signed the contract.
Oh, dear. I don't know what to say.
I was the one who saidwe should live together.
It would have been nice ifwe could live together happily.
- I'm sorry.- Don't be, ma'am.
The thing is...
Go on.
I know it might be strange for me tosay this, but I haven't done
a single shameful thing in my life thatwould embarrass Mi-poong and Yoo-sung.
Please be good to Mi-poong.
And please tell Ms. Hwangto be nicer to her, too.
I'm pleading you, ma'am.
Don't worry about that.
You should be happy and healthy.
Yes. Please take care of yourself, too.
- I'll be going home now.- All right.
- Bye.- Bye.
Are you happy now that you kicked her out?
Oh, dear. The only personshe can rely on is Mi-poong.
I was hoping we could gowith Kim Mi-poong's proposal.
What do you think?
Premium sportswear isn't bad at all,but she's a newbie without any experience.
It's a bit odd if we leave theentire launching process up to a newbie.
Mr. Heo, do you think that way also?
I think differently.
It's true that Mi-poongdoesn't have much experience,
but her ideas are original,and she's very passionate.
We can have the workerswho have experience support her.
Oh, it's up!
- Oh my god!- Mi-poong is amazing!
- Does Mi-poong know, too? Young-ju, call her.- Okay.
Oh, Mi-poong is coming.
Mi-poong, hurry up and come here.Did you get the notice that your proposal passed?
Pardon?
Really? I was really chosen?
(Successful candidate: Kim Mi-poong)
Ms. Kim, did I really get chosen?
- Of course! Congratulations!- Congratulations, Mi-poong!
Really?
Mi-poong really got chosen?
Mi-poong! Mi-poong!
Congratulations! Kiss!
Jang-go, what's wrong with you?
Mr. Lee, you can't do this here. You canget taken away for disorderly conduct.
That's right.Don't anger the lonely singles here.
I'm sorry. I was so happy.Mi-poong, congratulations!
Mi-poong's mother was kicked out of Geum-sil'shouse! She's going to be moving away!
Really?
Yes!
It would've been better if Mi-poong divorcedJang-go and moved out with her mom.
Don't worry, mother.
I'm planning somethingright now, and if that works out,
her married life won't be so smooth anymore.
There better not be any mistakes this time.
Don't worry.
- Don't make it like last time where I...- Aunt!
Oh my god. Hey. Knock, will you?
- Okay...- Knock, knock!
- Mother, I'll come down after I change.- All right.
When is she leaving?
Grandma said she'll send me to the orphanagenext week. Do I have to go back there?
No, Yoo-jin.
I'll never send you away,so don't worry, okay?
- Merry Christmas!- Please help out your poor neighbors.
Thank you.
Hello! Thank you!
Please help your poor neighbors.
- Thank you.- You're welcome.
- Bye.- Bye.
Mi-poong, are you sure we don't have to have
a party for you being the final candidate?
You can't change your mind later.
Don't worry. I'm a woman of my word.
Instead, I'm on a date with you.
That's enough for me.
I love it that I don't needto spend any money on you.
You're just satisfied going ona walk with me. Yes! I saved money!
There you go again! You're hittingyour amazing husband again!
I have something to tell you.
What is it?
Tell me.
The truth is, earlier today,my mom and I went to sign
a contract for the new houseshe'll be living in.
What?
Don't say anything. Don't lecture me.I know what you're going to say.
With the $20,000 leasecompensation you got today?
You can't get a house inSeoul with that kind of money.
We combined it with the $10,000we had and made a $30,000 deposit.
No.
If your mom really wantsto move away, then I'll get more money,
so let's get a better house for her.
I didn't tell you becauseI knew you would be like this.
My mom doesn't want that.
- But Mi-poong...- Jang-go.
This time, I want to do whatever my mom wants.
I want to make her comfortable.Please do this for her.
All right.
I'm going to make a lot of moneyand buy a pretty house just for her.
A sunny house where she can plant a garden.
That's my goal and dream from now on.
Good idea. Le's make sure to do that for her.
- Cheer up!- Cheer up!
Are you sure you really don't need a party?You better not say anything else later on.
Good!
Yes. I can't fail this plan,for the sake of Yoo-jin.
Good job.
It's tonight.
Take care of it with no mistakes.
That's it. Thank you.
- Mi-poong!- Jang-go!
- This looks good. Thank you.- Thank you.
- Eat a lot.- The spicy rice cakes are delicious.
- They're really good.- Very good.
But aunt, is it only me andgrandma that's moving away?
Can't you and Uncle Jang-go come with us?
Yoo-sung, do you notwant to live with just me?
I want to live with just you.
That's not what I meant. I'm just saidI won't be able to see aunt every day.
I'll visit you often. Are you satisfied now?
Yes, aunt. You have to visit me often.
Okay, I will.
Mom, I have to go to work now.
I'll go to your new house with Jang-goafter work, so let's organize everything then.
I'm sorry for making you move on your own.
Don't say that.
If you're busy with work,you don't have to come. All right?
- See you later.- All right.
Hello?
What? What did you say?What do you mean by that?
Ms. Kim, what do you meanthere's a problem with my sportswear?
Young-ju, show her.
Isn't this my sportswear that I launched? It's
It's supposed to come out tomorrow!Where did you get this?
It's not yours. It's the sportswearthat Good Time released today.
What? How could theymake the same things as us?
This doesn't make any sense!
Hello. This is Mr. Han of Winner'sGroup legal investigation team.
Leaked information?
All right. I'll investigate Kim Mi-poongfrom the third marketing team.
We're the legal investigation team.We'll be investigating the leakage of information.
Where is Kim Mi-poong's desk?
I didn't do it!I never leaked any information!
- Look here, Kim Mi-poong...- I'll do it.
Jang-go, it's not me! I didn't do anything!
Where is her desk?
Start.
Why isn't this opening? Where's the key?
Why is that locked? I neverlocked it before. I don't know anything!
Open it.
(Blow Breeze)
She would never do such a thing.
Make sure she can never hangaround the company again.
I don't want to see that woman ever again.
He's Kim Mi-poong's husband.Will he be part of this investigation?
From now on, you won't be partof Kim Mi-poong's investigation.
Who...?
She's here for an interview.
An interview?
- Please believe me!- She's a thief! A con-artist!
Mom!
I think they're really moving away.They're moving their belongings.
It's that ring!
BioskopKeren.ORG