(Episode 35)
Ms. Kim Mi-poong, what is this money?
I don't know.
I don't know what that money is!
Isn't this your drawer?
It is, but I don't know anything
about that money.
I didn't do it!
We're going to confiscate this as evidence.
Please follow us to the audit
room for further investigation.
I'll take her.
Fine. Please bring her to the audit room.
Let's go.
What did you say?
Cash was found in Kim Mi-poong's drawer?
Yes.
$300,000 was found.
We are currently investigating her past and
the process of the leakage of information.
However, she keeps denying it,
so it'll take some time.
Leaking company information is unacceptable.
Make sure you thoroughly investigate this
to find out how the design was disclosed.
Yes, I will.
Mr. Lee Jang-go?
What brings you here?
Oh, he works as a lawyer in
Winner Group's legal investigation team.
Oh, really?
Since when?
Just recently.
- Hello.
- Hi.
But he's Kim Mi-poong's husband.
Will he be part of this investigation?
Of course not. As the rules state, families
cannot be involved in the investigations.
Mr. Han. Ms. Park.
I am Kim Mi-poong's husband, but I am
also part of the investigation team.
I have the confidence to be
as objective as possible.
Please let me be a part of it.
Mr. Lee, please abide by the rules.
You can't help but be subjective
to your family members.
Mr. Han, make sure Mr. Lee
can't be part of this investigation.
Yes, ma'am.
Sir.
Please allow me to at least
speak to Kim Mi-poong.
Mr. Lee.
I'm begging you.
How can Mi-poong's husband be
working in our investigation team?
However, no matter what he does,
she won't be able to get out of this one.
I don't know what happened.
I don't know how the apparels I designed were
released as the products
of our rival company.
I don't know why such a large amount
of money was in my drawer either.
What happens to me now?
Mi-poong. Kim Mi-poong.
Look into my eyes. Focus here.
You can't become weak-hearted.
Get your head together, got it?
Did anyone approach you lately?
Did anyone ask you to hand over the design?
No.
I never saw or met anyone.
Really?
Then when was the last time
you opened that drawer?
Yesterday.
There wasn't any money in it yesterday.
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
That means this happened last night.
I don't know why this happened to me.
I feel like my heart is going to burst.
Mi-poong, I'm going to find out
who did this to you.
You didn't do this,
so the truth will be revealed.
So don't worry.
But that's not what's important right now.
I don't care what happens to me,
but the apparels
I made were supposed
to be released next week.
But the apparels that were made
in the factory are useless now.
What do I do?
Grandma, this, too.
Oh, dear.
We almost forgot the fly swatter.
Yes, we almost left this
important thing behind.
Good job, Yoo-sung.
- It seems like you're almost done packing.
- Yes, I'm almost done.
Oh, dear. I couldn't even help
you out. You worked hard.
No, it's fine. I don't have a lot of things.
Until a few days ago,
we had a party together.
I was happy that we were
finally getting along.
You're moving away out of the blue.
I feel so upset and guilty.
No ma'am. I should be the sorry one.
Thank you for everything.
Don't worry about Mi-poong.
I'll treat her like she's
my own granddaughter.
Thank you.
Oh, my handsome Yoo-sung.
I'm going to miss you
so much. What will I do?
Your aunt lives here,
so come visit her often.
Yes, grandma.
Take this and buy something yummy.
Yes, grandma. Thank you.
You're so precious.
- Should we take these out?
- Yes, please.
Mom, what's wrong? Did someone die?
Don't say such nonsense!
Ms. Joo is really moving away.
- They're moving out their things right now.
- Really? Right now?
Geum-sil,
I don't think this is right.
What's not right?
About Ms. Joo. I feel terrible about this.
Aside from everything else,
you shouldn't send her away like
you're kicking her out of here.
Don't you think that's wrong?
Geum-sil, how about we stop
them from moving right now?
Mother, why are you saying this now?
I don't know how you feel, but
I feel like a load is off my mind.
Now that they're finally moving out,
I feel like my toothache is gone.
Oh my goodness.
How could you be so cruel?
The three of them came down
from North Korea together.
Do you think it's right that
you tear them apart?
Especially in this frigid weather?
Mother, we didn't tear their family apart.
Mi-poong left her family behind
to get married to Jang-go.
And they lived for free
in that house until now.
We did as much as we could,
so we don't have to feel terrible at all.
And even if we beg that woman to stay, do you
think she'll be able to out of embarrassment?
If she has a conscience,
she wouldn't be able to live here.
My goodness.
No matter how much she needed a man.
No matter how much there was no man around.
Because I'm so ashamed
of what she did, I can't even
go out and I'm stuck here
preparing the bean sprouts.
Goodness, Geum-sil.
Ms. Joo said that isn't true.
It's not that big of a deal to like someone.
If she did like him, she would've said so.
She said it isn't true because it isn't true.
And I don't think she's the type
to steal another woman's man.
So let's believe her.
You go ahead and believe her.
I don't want to see that woman ever again.
How dare you call
your in-law "that woman!"
Where did you learn your
manners from? How ignorant!
Stop it. You lost.
I'm back.
Aunt. Grandma. It seems like
Yoo-sung's family is moving away.
There's a moving truck outside.
- Is this the last one?
- Yes.
Oh, it's that ring.
But why is this here?
The ring was here.
How did this happen?
I thought I had lost this ring.
I guess it was under
the wardrobe all this time.
Is that your ring?
Yes, this is my ring.
I was so upset when I had lost it.
Because we're moving,
I was able to find this ring.
But I think I saw a ring like this before.
Of course you did because I was wearing it.
You did something great today.
You found this precious ring for me.
We're done. Should we go?
- Yes.
- Okay.
Let's go, Yoo-sung.
Thank you for everything. Good-bye.
- Hurry and get in the car. The driver is waiting.
- Okay.
- Go safely.
- Bye, Yoo-sung.
- Bye.
You're right. I don't feel right
since they're leaving like this.
I know. Mi-poong will feel really sad when
she comes home and sees the empty house.
People feel sad even when
a dog runs away from home.
But she doesn't even
come out to say good-bye?
Just ignore it.
You're going to make it noisy.
I'm going to work.
- Me, too, grandma.
- Let's go.
What will she do with
little Yoo-sung on her own?
Grandma, are you happy
that you found the ring?
Of course I am.
This is the ring that
your grandfather gave
your grandmother when
they separated from each other.
I see. It really is a precious ring.
I should call your aunt and let her know.
She'll be so surprised.
The person you are trying
to reach is unavailable.
Maybe she's busy.
She's not answering her phone.
It's the same one.
What did you say?
It's nothing.
Yoo-sung.
From now on, only you
and I will be living together.
Now that we found your grandfather's ring,
let's be strong and live well.
Okay.
Ms. Kim Mi-poong.
(Accident Report)
Please write down everything in order that
has happened from the design planning
of the leaked sportswear to the
situation that has happened today.
Make sure you write down all
the people you have met, the time
you met them, the locations,
and the topic of the conversations.
All right.
Welcome!
Is the boss here?
My boss?
Why are you looking for him?
Hello.
You have a guest.
Shin Jung-mi?
Yes. Hello.
Hello.
Who...?
She's here for an interview.
An interview?
Continue what you were doing.
Have a seat.
Here's my resume.
You were born in 1990. Your age...?
- Twenty-seven.
- Twenty-seven?
You're very young.
Young customers do come to our store,
but there will mostly be elderly ones.
Will you be able to talk to them?
It's not a problem.
As you can tell from my resume,
I have a lot of experience selling things.
Clothing stores in malls, health supplements,
cosmetics, and etcetera.
I have a lot of experience
selling things, so I can do a great job.
How long is the distance
from here to your house?
It's about two bus stops away.
It's pretty close.
You're perfect for my store.
Yes!
Please excuse me while I answer this call.
Hello?
Excuse me. Is it nice working here?
If it was, why would I quit? Wouldn't
there be a reason why I want to quit?
What's the reason?
It's my first time meeting you today,
but I'm telling you this
because you seem like a nice woman.
Don't work here.
The boss is really weird!
He's weird?
How?
How can I explain this?
He's very picky.
For example, he asked me how
many customers came here, so I
told him there were about ten.
He got extremely ticked off!
He asked me,
"Is it nine people? Ten? Eleven?"
What the heck?
He's really weird.
Right? His motto is, "Let's not live dully."
"Let's not live dully?"
So weird!
That's not all.
He gives you a hard time for your outfits!
Really?
I can put up with everything but people
who nag you about your clothes!
So what if he's the boss?
Why else would I want to quit?
On top of that, he has mysophobia.
Miss, make sure you think well
before you make a decision.
But if I were you, I wouldn't work here.
Shin Jung-mi, you can start working tomorrow.
Sir, I can't work here!
Good-bye!
Shin Jung-mi!
Did you say something strange to her?
Why would I do that?
This won't do.
Since you're having a hard time
hiring someone,
I should continue working here.
What?
Don't you understand Korean?
I'm going to work here for your sake.
Please move, sir.
So this company bought the
sportswear design legally?
Yes. We used  legal means to buy
this design. Is there a problem?
Who was the one who sold this design?
Mr. James Kang from
a company called K Design.
Mr. James Kang from K Design?
Where is he right now?
I'm not sure.
He might be somewhere in the Philippines.
I'm sorry, but can I have
his contact information?
His phone number is in my office.
I'll text it to you.
Thank you.
Yes, sir.
Right now?
What did you need to tell me urgently?
There's another crucial evidence that shows
Kim Mi-poong did leak the information.
Pardon? Crucial evidence?
Through her e-mails, we were able to find out
she did hand over the plan to James Kang.
That can't be.
Something has gone wrong.
She's not that kind of person.
Someone is blaming her for this.
You want to believe that's the case.
It's not that I don't
understand how you feel.
This is why I said you shouldn't
be a part of this case.
You should stay out of this now.
Mr. Han...
It's my order as your team leader.
From this point on, you will not
be able take part in this case.
Do you understand?
Why is there no video file
for this day and time only?
The CCTV was broken that day.
We tried to restore it the next day,
but we weren't able to restore that time.
It was deleted?
Rather than being deleted,
it could have been broken or
someone could have damaged it.
It would be impossible to check.
How could that happen?
How can be so careless?
I have no excuse to offer.
However, if someone purposely deleted it, the
one who would be responsible is Kim Mi-poong.
What?
It's true. The one who leaked the information
would be the one to delete the video file.
I'll call you if we can restore it.
Please leave now.
We need to get back to work.
I'm going to see the videos
from the past week to now.
- Mr. Kim.
- Yes.
- Show the videos to Mr. Lee.
- Yes, sir.
What?
Money was found in Kim Mi-poong's desk drawer,
and the e-mails were confirmed, too?
Yes, grandfather. That's what
the investigation team found out.
Is that true?
Did Mi-poong really do that?
This happened at the last stage
of the sportswear production,
so we suffered a great loss.
Maybe there's a misunderstanding,
just like that box incident last time.
I wanted to trust her
because of what happened
last time, but the
evidence is clear this time.
I don't know what I should do either.
How could this happen? I saw her
positively because she saved me.
Her mother is the same way.
Did I misjudge their characters?
I don't know why these things keep happening.
Grandfather, I didn't want to tell you this.
What is it? Tell me.
To be honest, Ms. Joo
and Mi-poong had a bad habit
of stealing when they had been in China.
They would date any men they pleased.
What?
Are you serious?
Yes.
There was the incident with father, too.
I don't think we should let them
off the hook anymore.
Fire Kim Mi-poong immediately.
Yes, grandfather.
Mi-poong, what will you do?
The truth will be revealed one day.
We believe you. You know that, don't you?
That's right. We believe you.
You have to come back, Mi-poong.
We'll be waiting for you.
Keep in touch. Okay?
Okay.
Following the silent road,
I wonder where I am
I can't see anything
So I'm getting afraid
Sometimes, I feel alone
I feel like I'll continue to be alone
I'm going without change
Tell me I'm close, to go a little more
I hear it
Thank you. If you're able to
recover the file, let me know.
I will.
Mr. Han, Kim Mi-poong isn't inside the
audit room. Is the investigation over?
Didn't you hear?
Kim Mi-poong was fired,
so she was sent home for now.
Pardon? She was fired?
What? Is he going to the
chairman's office right now?
What is it?
It was unfair for Kim Mi-poong
to be dismissed.
Please revoke your decision.
Kim Mi-poong's dismissal was decided
according to the company regulations.
There's something suspicious about this.
The CCTV was broken during that time.
And even if she did leak the design,
does it make sense
for her to keep the money in her desk drawer?
What you're saying right now
are all assumptions!
Don't bring me assumptions. Bring me
clear evidence that I can believe in.
Don't just bring me words!
Then I'll take care of her dismissal.
- Mr. Kim!
- Mr. Lee!
What are you doing using
your emotions like this?
Then hand this case over to the
police for a public investigation.
What? A public investigation?
That can't happen.
If this is revealed to the public,
our brand name will be stained.
We have enough losses already.
If people find out the products we are
hurriedly preparing right now are substitutes,
Winner's Group will suffer a great blow.
So you'll just let a hard-working
employee be fired with false charges?
False charges?
Then are you saying all the evidence found so
far has been used by someone to set her up?
Who would do such a thing?
Well...
If she really has been falsely charged, bring
the evidence, just like the chairman said.
Get out.
There was enough investigation.
The money was found and
the e-mails were confirmed.
What more do you need?
I was trying to solve this
in a sensible manner.
Sensible manner?
Have you considered how much
we suffered because of this incident?
How will you compensate for
the loss in a sensible manner?
Tell me as Kim Mi-poong's husband.
I had to beg the chairman in
order not to demand
a compensation for the
great loss from Kim Mi-poong.
So you should end this now.
One more thing.
You have been hired to
work for Winner's Group.
Before you defend your family,
you should consider the company first.
If you don't like that, you should leave.
Mi-poong!
Jang-go!
Why didn't you answer your phone?
I'm sorry. I didn't know
I had run out of battery.
You're frozen. You should have
gone in somewhere. It's cold.
I didn't want to take that box and
go inside a place with a lot of people.
I'm sorry.
Jang-go, I thought I had lived a good
life without being mean to anybody.
I have no idea why this is happening to me.
If I had really done something wrong,
I would gladly be punished,
but this is really unfair!
I'm so shocked that
my heart is beating fast.
I'll return you to your place. I'll make
sure to reveal that it's not your fault.
I promise.
But what do I tell the family?
Mother will say something if she finds out.
And what do I tell my mom?
My mom will be so upset
if she finds out I was fired.
For now, let's not tell anyone.
I'll do something about this in the meantime.
Then what do I do tomorrow?
Tomorrow...
Just leave the house with me
as if you're going to work.
You can go to the movies,
bookstore, and museum.
You can have some alone time.
Thinking about it,
it sounds like a good idea.
Thank you.
No problem.
We're a married couple.
And what are married couples?
One body and soul.
You're so smart.
Let's go now.
Go where?
Look at you. Wake up.
- Aren't you going to your mother's new home?
- That's right! She moved today!
I wasn't in my right mind.
Are you in your right mind now?
Mi-poong, you need to come
to your senses. Okay?
Okay.
It's cold.
Jang-go, can you tell that I cried?
No. You look pretty.
Are you sure?
My mom can always tell whenever I cried.
I can't get caught.
Do you think it'll be okay
if I smile like this?
Yes.
Let's go.
Mom!
Mom! Yoo-sung!
Mother! Yoo-sung, I bought pork feet!
- Aunt! Uncle!
- Welcome! It's cold outside, isn't it?
- Sit here.
- Okay.
It's cold.
Mother, I'll move you to a bigger,
better house in the future.
Thank you. This house is
enough for Yoo-sung and me.
The house is warm.
Yeah, it's totally warm.
Is that so?
Mom, here.
Is this toilet paper? You bought
exactly what we needed.
In South Korea, you buy
toilet paper for people who
just moved in so that things
will go smoothly for them.
Really? I think things are
going smoothly for me already.
Look.
Where did you get this ring?
I found it under the wardrobe
while I was moving out.
Didn't you lose this when you were mugged?
It's so strange.
I never took this ring off before.
Oh, I was so happy after I found this ring!
Mom, I think things will go
smoothly for you from now on.
If I had known this would have happened,
I would've moved out a long time ago.
After moving here, I feel so relaxed.
This feels like a palace to me.
If you're relaxed and happy, I'm happy, too.
From now on, don't worry
about Yoo-sung and me, and
just live a happy life with
Jang-go and your in-laws.
I have no more wishes other than that.
All right.
But when are we going to eat pork feet?
How about now?
Mother, did you eat yet?
I'm hungry.
Are you serious? Mi-poong was fired?
Yes, mother, so don't worry anymore.
But what if she's able to come back again?
That won't happen this time.
Grandfather fired her himself.
Oh my goodness! How could this happen?
Oh my god! She deserves to be fired!
How could she-
How dare she hang up on me!
Oh, dear! I shouldn't be like this!
Geum-sil! Hwang Geum-sil!
What is she doing here at this hour?
Geum-sil!
What is it? Did your husband
cause trouble again?
My in-law doesn't live here anymore.
She moved out.
So I hope you won't
come here for her anymore.
That's not it.
Then what is it?
Your daughter-in-law isn't
back from work yet, right?
Why do you care about my daughter-in-law?
Should I tell you this or not?
What is it?
Rummage through her bedroom.
You might find money in there!
What are you suddenly talking about?
What do you mean money?
You don't know anything.
Your daughter-in-law got caught for leaking
company information and getting money for it!
$300,000 came out from her desk!
What?
Mi-poong was fired.
What will you do, Geum-sil?
Is everything you said true?
Would I have come
all the way here if it wasn't?
Mi-poong made the company suffer
thousands of dollars in losses!
So she's supposed to go to prison right now,
but my daughter-in-law begged the
chairman not to go that far.
Prison?
If it wasn't for Shin-ae, Mi-poong
would be in big trouble by now!
Mi-poong was supposed to have paid
out of her pocket to pay for the damage.
If she couldn't do that, then your son
would've had to clean up the mess for her!
Even if you had sold this house, you wouldn't
have been able to pay for everything.
My son...?
Oh my god! Geum-sil!
Oh! What's going on? Geum-sil, what happened?
- What's wrong with her?
- I didn't do anything.
- We're back.
Lee Jang-go, did you know about this, too?
What do you mean?
I heard Mi-poong received money
by leaking company information.
Money was found in your desk drawer.
Is that not true?
Jang-go, don't try to lie
and tell me the truth.
Is that true or not?
Mom, the thing is...
it's true that money was found, but...
It's true. It's true!
- Mom!
- Mother!
Move!
I had my doubts...
I didn't think this was true.
But you're saying that
everything I heard is true!
Mom, calm down and listen to me.
Calm down? Listen to you?
Mother, what do we do?
Nam-yi, what do we do about Jang-go now?
Tell me! Why did you do that?
Who are you trying to ruin?
Were you going to give that
money to Jang-go or me?
Why on earth would you do such a thing?
What the heck did you do
when you were in North Korea?
You put on an innocent front.
How can you steal?
Mother, it's not me. I really didn't do this!
I don't know why this happened
to me, but please believe me!
Money was found in your drawer!
But you still don't know about this?
You and your mom are the same!
Like mother, like daughter.
Both of you commit all
the wrongdoings and yet
you declare you're innocent.
Mom!
Oh, now I see! You were going to
give that money to your mom,
weren't you? Were you
going to buy her a house?
No. I really didn't do it.
No need to talk this out. Pack your things
and get out of my house.
I don't want to talk with you, so get out!
- Mom!
- Get a hold of yourself, Geum-sil!
Mother, I can put up with everything
else but a daughter-in-law like her.
She's a thief! A con-artist!
Mother, no matter how poor
I was, I never stole anything!
Even if I got extra change,
I couldn't sleep from the guilt
and had to go give it back in
order to fall asleep well!
Yet, you want me to live with
a daughter-in-law like her?
Mother, I can't do that even if I die!
Oh my goodness. What will we do?
- Why are you just standing there? Get out!
- Mom!
Get out!
- Mi-poong!
- Where are you going?
What are you going to do with that thief?
Mom! Mi-poong said it wasn't true!
How can you only trust someone else?
You're too much.
Fine! You leave, too!
Leave and never come back again!
All of you leave! All of you!
- I must have lived for too long.
- Mom, what's wrong with you?
- What do I do?
- Mom, get a hold of yourself!
Grandma...
Massage her.
- What will we do?
- Mom.
I can see all the stars tonight.
It would be nice if Mi-poong
could see those stars, too.
She could make a wish, too.
Mi-poong...
will be all right now, won't she?
Mi-poong.
When I see you, my heart wavers
I'm just staring at you
It was like that
After loving someone like me,
I became afraid of farewells
I'll think of love simply
I won't regret while living
I'll live like that, I'll simply love
Mom, what do you think
you're doing right now?
You don't listen to me, do you?
You want me to eat the food you made?
I'd rather starve to death than
eat food made by a thief like you.
No matter how angry you are,
how could you go this far?
Mi-poong, let's go.
Jang-go, why are you
being like this to mother?
Mother, I was thoughtless.
I should have prepared
everything before you came out.
I'm sorry.
Just get out.
Get out. Why aren't you leaving?
How sickening!
Oh my goodness.
You shouldn't be like this!
No matter how much you hate her,
you shouldn't turn the table upside down!
Are you the only one living here?
- I'm still here, you fool! I'm still alive, you fool!
- Mom, go inside.
How can she do such a thing?
There you go.
Is my school really near here?
Of course it is. Let's go.
Hello, Ms. Hwang.
Take your daughter right now.
How can both of you do this?
How can she steal?
Pardon?
What do you mean steal?
What are you talking about?
Pardon?
Mi-poong was fired?
Ma'am, where are you going?
I'm here to see Director Park Shin-ae.
Do you have an appointment?
No, I don't, but I know her very well.
What floor is her office on?
Come on, ma'am.
You know her very well, but you
don't even know where her office is?
If you want to see her,
make an appointment first.
I really do know her very well.
She's not answering her phone.
So you should get in touch with her first
before you come here. You can't be here.
You need to leave. Come back
after you get in touch with her.
Young-ju, I'm almost there.
I'll be waiting in the front.
Bye.
- Mi-poong.
- Young-ju.
Here you go. I took it by accident.
It's fine. I was in the
middle of a meeting. Bye.
Bye.
Mom!
Mi-poong.
What are you doing here?
You were falsely charged, weren't you?
Why didn't you tell me?
How can I do nothing about it
when you were unjustly fired?
I'm going to talk with Shin-ae.
I heard she was a director here.
Jang-go is searching for
evidence right now, so-
Isn't he the owner of the noodle restaurant?
Is he Shin-ae's grandfather and
the chairman of this company?
Yes.
Oh my goodness.
Good. I'm glad he's here.
You wait right here.
Mom!
Hello, Mr.Kim.
What brings you here?
I have to talk to you about something, so I
know it's rude, but I came all the way here.
I know you're busy, but can you
give me some of your time?
I'm busy, so hurry up and tell me here.
Yes, sir. Thank you.
I heard that my daughter was falsely
charged and unjustly fired here.
I just can't believe that.
She  isn't that kind of person.
I have nothing else to say about that matter.
The evidence is clear.
What is there more to talk about?
- You should return home.
- Mr. Kim!
Please give Mi-poong a chance.
She's not that kind of person.
Please help her with the false accusations.
I can't let her live on with
such unfairness. Please, sir!
Please help her just this once.
Ms. Joo, those who do
wrong must get punished.
Do you know how much damage we're
suffering because of your daughter?
We already helped you enough. You should
be grateful. How can you be so shameful?
Pardon?
No matter how hard life is, there
are things you can and can't do.
You were after another
woman's man's money, and
your daughter was after the company's money.
How can you live so ruthlessly?
You should try to live with your efforts.
Where did you learn such rudeness from?
Mr. Kim, what are you talking about?
For the sake of the hard-working people
who came from up North, live honorably.
One bad apple spoils the whole barrel.
Don't taint other people.
Make sure this woman can never
hang around the company again.
Mom!
James Kang.
His number is fake.
This is a perfectly set up conspiracy.
But who on earth would want
to do that to Mi-poong and why?
It's dangerous!
Faster! Go! Go! Go!
Are you having fun?
Look! Say hi!
Don't. You'll fall.
Hold on tight.
Shin-ae, how will we send
Yoo-jin back tomorrow?
Just thinking about it hurts my heart.
I feel the same way.
How will we be able to
send her back tomorrow?
We must have become very attached to Yoo-jin.
Yes, I think so, too.
We're having a hard time, so imagine
how sad Yoo-jin will be tomorrow.
I think I'll cry just thinking about it.
That's why I was wondering...
Is there any way we can keep her?
The orphanage must have rules,
so how can we keep her?
Unless we officially adopt her...
Adopt her?
- We're back.
- Welcome back!
Yoo-jin, come over here.
- Okay.
- You're back.
- Come here and eat some fruit.
- Have some fruit.
Did you have fun today?
- Yes.
- Really?
All of you went to have fun for the last time
before you went back to the orphanage.
She's going tomorrow, right?
Yes, she's going tomorrow.
Yoo-jin, when people meet,
they have to separate, too.
But you can always go
and come back here. Okay?
Okay.
So you don't have to feel sad at all.
You can come visit whenever you want to.
- Okay.
- Good.
Yoo-jin.
- Yoo-jin, what's wrong?
- Maybe she ate the wrong food outside.
Give her some plum tea.
My stomach hurts!
Yoo-jin, what's wrong
with you all of a sudden?
- We're taking her to the hospital.
- Okay.
Go on.
- What's wrong with her?
She had fun, so what's wrong
with her all of a sudden?
My goodness! Taking care of kids is a hassle!
Of course! It even takes a lot
of work to take care of a dog.
There isn't any internal problem with her.
Really?
Then what's wrong with her?
She had a fever and
broke into a cold sweat.
She was in so much pain.
Was she ever stressed recently?
Stressed?
Sometimes, kids pretend to be sick
so that they don't have to go to school.
Often times, when that happens,
they get a fever and feel pain.
In my opinion, she's like this
because of psychological factors.
Yoo-jin must not have wanted to
return to the orphanage tomorrow.
Yes, I think so.
She must not have really wanted to
go back if she became sick like this.
This makes me more upset than if
she would have gotten cut or scraped.
Hee-dong...
thank you.
Hello, Ms. Hwang.
What are you doing?
I told you to take your daughter,
so why aren't you coming?
Must I pack her belongings with my own hands?
Do you want me to send them through mail?
Geum-sil, what are you doing?
You stay out of this.
Take these and leave.
Ms. Hwang, you're being too harsh.
How can you go this far?
Think about this in my shoes.
If you were in my shoes,
you would've done the same thing.
I can put up with everything but a thief.
She isn't a thief, Ms. Hwang.
She was falsely accused!
I don't want to hear such words!
Because of your daughter,
the entire family was about
to live on the streets
in the middle of winter!
Because of the compensation
for the damage she caused!
How would my son feel at work?
Have you ever thought about that?
My heart is bleeding right now!
I don't want to talk with you
anymore, so take these and leave.
I can't live with a thief
as my daughter-in-law.
Ms. Hwang.
Don't even call my name!
I'm done with you.
Ms. Hwang.
Please think about our kids.
They've living nicely together.
This is wrong.
They'll get hurt.
Ms. Hwang,
if I'm the problem, I'll cut off my ties with
Mi-poong, just as I promised to last time.
I won't look at her. I won't meet her.
I'll cut off all ties with her.
So please let her live with Jang-go.
Please love her as your daughter-in-law.
That's all I want, Ms. Hwang.
I'm begging you, Ms. Hwang. So please...
Take these and go! Just go!
Why are both of you being so stubborn?
- I told you to leave!
- Ms. Hwang.
I'm glad you're here.
Take your belongings
and leave with your mother.
Please just go!
Mom.
- Mom, let's go.
- Mi-poong...
I can't do this any longer.
- No, Mi-poong. You can't do this!
- No!
I've done enough.
We didn't suffer through all
those troubles to live like this.
Father wouldn't want me to live like this.
So let's go.
Good-bye, mother.
Good-bye, Aunt Nam-yi.
Please tell grandmother that I'm sorry.
- Let's go!
- Mi-poong!
Let's go.
Geum-sil! My goodness!
- Let's talk.
- Let's go.
Mi-poong left home. It's late, but
you should learn to move on now.
Mom, you really-!
If you want to go after her, go ahead.
However, I can't accept her as
my daughter-in-law anymore.
Fine.
I'll leave, too.
Hi, Mi-poong. Where are you right now?
Jang-go.
I have a favor to ask of you.
You must do it for me.
What is it?
Let's... get a divorce.
What?
The wind, the sunlight, the memories
I can't forget the beautiful days
(Blow Breeze)
I hate you. I hate everyone.
I hate even looking at you now!
Mom, don't send me back there.
Don't tell me to go.
You don't have to go.
The three of us can live together.
What are you doing?
You just have to say one
warm word of apology to her.
Make red bean noodles.
- Red bean noodles?
- Yes.
I can't digest it. Make pumpkin porridge.
- Yes!
- I'll go!
Use your words!
- You're going to own this one day.
- Me?
It's been a long time.
Have you found my father?
Your father?