Subtitles by OnDemandKorea
Yes, I'm the one who put up the ad in the newspaper.
You know Kim Soon-ok?
Did he call because of the newspaper?
Yes.
Yes, I understand. I'll go there right away. Bye.
Did he really call because of the ad in the newspaper?
- Does he know your grandmother Kim Soon-ok? - Yes, mom!
He wants to meet us right away.
Right now?
Try calling him.
Hello?
Yes, we're here already.
You arrived at the cafe right now?
Is that him?
Yes, I think so.
Did you say your hometown was Pyeongyang?
Yes. What about you?
My hometown is Wonsan.
Wonsan?
Soon-ok and I had two daughters. Do you know...?
My mother-in-law doesn't have any daughters.
She only has one son named Kim Dae-hoon, who is my husband.
Is that so?
Then she must not be the Kim Soon-ok I'm looking for.
Our hometowns and family relations are different.
I see.
Then do you know this ring?
My mother-in-law used to wear this.
No. This isn't it.
My wife's ring was bigger.
I was hoping you would be the one I was looking for.
I'm sorry for asking to meet up with you.
It's all right, sir.
I hope you'll find your family.
Yes. If they're alive, I'll meet them one day.
I hope you two will find your grandfather.
Thank you.
Geum-sil! Hwang Geum-sil!
I'm here! Hurry up and come out!
Okay! Hold on!
Why didn't she get ready sooner?
They really moved away.
I feel so much better now.
They left this house, and she was kicked out of the company, too.
I won't have to deal with this family anymore, right?
Look how messy it is.
What are you muttering about while looking at an empty house?
It's nothing.
Aren't you going to rent this house out to anyone?
My mother-in-law told me not to.
Why not? It's not good to have an empty house
for a long time. Hurry up and rent it out.
Don't you think I know that? I need to make money, too.
Your mother-in-law isn't going to bring that woman back in here, is she?
Goodness. How would I know?
That can never happen! Never!
Of course not! That wouldn't make any sense!
Why would we bring back the mother of my ex-daughter-in-law?
I'd rather break this house apart.
You wicked thing!
Just look at the way you speak.
Who are you to break my house apart?
Mother, it was just a joke!
- Chung-ja, let's go. - Good-bye.
You're living the good life after your son got a divorce, huh?
You evil wench!
Hurry back home and make grilled wheat cake!
Okay. Let's go.
Good-bye.
She broke her son's heart, but she's all happy and dressed up nicely.
Goodness! That awful wench!
I won't let you get away with this.
Hello. Hello.
Hello. I hope you're having a good day.
You came again.
I was curious if the video file was restored yet.
How many times do I have to tell you that it's going to be difficult to restore that?
Then may I have the copies of the videos from a
week before the incident to the day it happened?
Oh, you're thirsty, aren't you? Please drink this.
May I please have them?
Sure. Hold on.
Thank you.
Come in.
- About the video file of Kim Mi-poong's incident that was deleted... - Yes?
Since that couldn't be restored, Mr. Lee took the videos
from the previous week up to the day it happened.
There won't be any problems, right?
Yes, there won't be any problems.
No matter how much he looks, he won't be able to find anything.
Mr. Lee is very tiring.
But Mr. Kim scouted him himself.
You don't have to worry about anything.
He'll never be able to find out the truth about this incident.
Still, you never know, so make sure you keep an eye on him.
Yes, ma'am.
Once grandfather steps away from the chairman
position, Mr. Lee is the first one I'm going to fire.
(I'm looking for a person)
I'm looking for my grandfather who gave this ring with
the symbol "Cheon" on it to my grandmother Kim Soon-ok.
His son's name is Kim Dae-hoon.
What's this?
Mi-poong was looking for her grandfather?
They had this ring with them?
Is it true that your son got a divorce?
Oh, my. Really?
They were bound to find out anyways.
I didn't tell them on purpose.
Yes, it's true. It's nothing good, so just pretend like you don't know anything.
No matter how much you despised her, divorce isn't the answer.
Did they get a divorce because Chung-ja's husband had an affair with your in-law?
My husband came home.
They're not in that kind of relationship!
I heard they were in a good relationship. You should have just let them stay together.
There was a different reason why they got divorced.
Chung-ja, you better stop.
What happened? Did she have an affair, just like her mother did?
It's not like that!
Mi-poong isn't that kind of girl!
Your son must be in shock. When I saw him at the
wedding, he seemed to love her more than she loved him.
If they're not meant to be, they should separate as soon as they can.
No. When my cousin was young, my aunt stopped him
from getting married to the girl he was in love with.
He's over fifty-years-old, and yet, he's still thinking
about her, and he's about to die as a single, lonely man!
My aunt is still doing his laundry and cooking his meals.
She regrets stopping him from getting married now.
Young-soon is right.
While your daughter-in-law worked, she made 100 cabbages
into kimchi and made breakfast and dinner, too.
Stop talking nonsense!
There's a valid reason why she kicked her out!
Is she your daughter-in-law? Why are you so worked up about her?
When did I do that?
I'm just saying this because you guys are being
rude by saying strange things and making Geum-sil upset.
Someone's cell-phone is ringing.
Isn't that your phone, Chung-ja?
Oh, it is.
It's my daughter-in-law.
Hi, it's me.
Why weren't you picking up your phone?
I picked up now.
Mother, does the Sky Newspaper come home?
- Why? - Just answer me! Does the Sky Newspaper come home?
Yes, it does.
But what's wrong?
What do we do?
What do we do? We're in big trouble, mother!
Big trouble? What kind of big trouble?
Mi-poong put up an ad in the newspaper looking for
her grandfather along with a picture of the ring!
What do you mean she put up an ad? Along with a picture of the ring?
Are you serious?
Mother, where are you right now?
I think grandfather is home! Please make sure he can't see the newspaper! Hurry!
Oh, no! I'm outside though!
What?
Then hurry up and go home! Hurry up!
All right! Bye!
I have to go home.
What's up with her?
What does she mean by the ad and ring?
But is she being controlled by her daughter-in-law? She's
shivering with fright because her daughter-in-law yelled at her.
I know.
- Mr. Kim? - Pardon?
- Where's Mr. Kim? - He's reading the newspaper in his bedroom.
Newspaper? What do I do?
Give me that.
Mr. Kim.
(I'm looking for a person)
Chung-ja, what are you doing?
I brought you some tea.
Oh, no!
What are you doing?
I'm sorry, Mr. Kim.
What's wrong?
I spilled tea on the newspaper.
Oh my goodness.
You should've been careful.
I'll tell the housekeeper to clean this up.
I wasn't done with the newspaper.
How are you always so clumsy?
But Shin-ae, what are you doing home at this time?
I left a document at home.
What about you?
I'm going to go to work a little bit later.
I see.
It's over there.
My goodness.
Oh my goodness. Where did she get this ring from?
That little kid had really taken it.
What will we do?
What if Yoo-sung tells them that there's a similar ring at our house?
There are many similar rings like this in this world.
That's not the problem right now.
Why the heck did they suddenly put up this ad?
How did they know they have a grandfather?
Oh my gosh. What will we do?
We somehow solved this today, but what about next time?
They can put ads anywhere else besides the newspaper, too.
We need to somehow make sure they can't put up another ad.
How?
How can we stop them when they're using their money to put up this ad?
- (Homemade Kimbap) -Buy kimbap! Buy some kimbap!
This is homemade kimbap!
-Buy kimbap! - Four rows, please.
Sure!
- Here you go. - Enjoy.
Thank you!
Here.
Hello?
Oh, yes, I'm the one who put up the ad!
You know Kim Soon-ok?
The ring, too?
Oh, yes! I'll go over there right now!
Yes! Bye!
- He knows the ring? - I think this is really grandfather, mom!
- Okay, let's hurry up and go! - Let's go!
Are you the one who called us because of the ad?
Yes. Please have a seat.
This is the ring my mother-in-law used to wear.
Is this the right ring?
Yes, this is the ring I gave her.
I gave it to her when we got married.
I can't believe that you still have this ring with you.
Then where is your hometown?
Pyeong...
It's been so long that I don't remember, but Kim Soon-ok is the right person.
Then do you know my father, Kim Dae-hoon?
Is he really your son?
But I don't know if I have a son or not.
Then what's your name?
Kim Han-cheon.
I think I'm the one you have been looking for.
That is the ring I gave her.
Yes. Yes, you are my father-in-law.
I knew your name would have Cheon in it.
That's why Cheon is engraved into this ring.
- Father. - Grandfather.
I'm sorry.
I'm grateful that you searched for me, but I hope you won't contact me anymore.
What do you mean?
I'm sorry for saying this as soon as we meet for the first time,
but I already have a family here.
I have a wife, son, and daughter.
If they find out about this, they'll be shocked and uncomfortable.
I'm begging you.
Don't put up an ad again.
That's why I asked for us to meet here today.
Father, but still-
But still, aren't you curious about your son?
My father is your son, too.
All this time, I didn't know I had a son in North Korea.
I thought Kim Soon-ok was dead, too.
What's the point of my children finding out about this right now?
So don't contact me anymore.
But-
Okay, I understand.
I'm sorry.
Let me beg you one more time.
Don't put up an ad again.
I hope you'll live well in South Korea.
My father...
passed away while escaping North Korea.
I see.
Mi-poong...
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have suggested we look for your grandfather.
If I hadn't done that,
we would've still had hope that we would find him one day.
I'm sorry.
I might mean nothing to him...
but you're still his granddaughter.
He has Yoo-sung, too.
Mom, we lived well without grandfather all this time.
You, Yoo-sung, and me.
The three of us will live happily together.
Yes.
Yes, let's do that.
Mi-poong, what are you doing?
Mom, grandfather should meet Yoo-sung at least once.
I wanted to tell him to meet Yoo-sung once and give him a hug.
He's not answering his phone though.
It's true that he doesn't want to meet us.
Mi-poong, let's just pretend your grandfather passed away.
Still, if he's really my grandfather...
He's too much.
Good job.
I put enough money in there, so make sure to change your phone number.
Of course I will.
Did you make any mistakes?
Did you make sure to tell them not to put up another ad?
Don't worry about a thing!
Didn't they doubt you?
I did as you taught me, and they didn't seem to doubt me at all.
Tell me if you need me again.
Bye.
She got kicked out of the company and the house, so I thought it was all over.
But now she even put up an ad searching for her grandfather.
I feel so uneasy that I can't live.
Anyways, what will we do now that the ring is back on that woman's hand again?
It's not like you can steal it back now. How will
you be able to do that when it's on her finger?
Just stealing that won't solve this problem.
Then what can we do in order to never see them again?
Mother, I have a good idea.
Good idea? What good idea?
Ms. Joo, it's me, Shin-ae.
Can we meet up right now?
- Hi, Ms. Joo. - Welcome.
It was hard finding the house, right?
No. I followed your directions and got here in no time at all.
It's shabby, but come on in.
Sure.
You said you had something to tell me. What is it?
I'm sorry I couldn't help Mi-poong this time.
I tried to prevent her from getting fired, but my grandfather
was so adamant that I couldn't do anything about it.
Thank you for your kind words.
I heard Mi-poong got divorced.
Was it because of what happened at the company this time?
I don't know what happened either. I felt hopeless and resented the heavens.
But Mi-poong is doing fine, so you don't have to worry.
But did you come here just to say that?
To be honest...
I was wondering if you, Mi-poong, and Yoo-sung would be willing to go to America.
What? America?
Yes. I'll make sure Mi-poong can work at the headquarters in America.
Many people go to America to study these days.
Yoo-sung can study there, too.
I'll support you guys.
What? Are you serious?
Yes.
But why would you give us such a good opportunity?
I'm very indebted to you.
I would like to pay you back now.
Discuss it with Mi-poong.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
Make a decision as soon as possible, so that I can get started on the procedure.
Okay, I'll discuss this with Mi-poong when she comes home and let you know.
Shin-ae, thank you so much.
Hello!
Delivery!
- Hi, Mi-poong. This is the last stop for you, right? - Yes, I'm done for today.
We're going to order late-night snacks. Join us.
No, I have plans already.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
Thank you. Enjoy your snacks.
Oh my god!
What's this?
You left your cosmetics at home. I brought them all here for you.
I'm cool, aren't I?
Is that why you've been calling me the entire day?
It's nothing important anyways.
You're started to tick me off!
I'm so busy, but I brought these for you because I thought you would
be uncomfortable without them! Should I just throw them away?
Why would you do such a thing? There's still a lot left.
You're grateful, aren't you?
Thank you. Good-bye.
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
You're so mean!
I brought your cosmetics for you, but you're just going to leave like that?
We signed the divorce papers, Jang-go.
It takes one month for the final decision to go through.
We can only get divorced if we report to the borough office a month later.
We're still a married couple.
So...
at least send me off.
You're such a lawyer. You're all bark and no bite.
Quiet! Follow me.
Hurry up!
Good-bye.
What's wrong with you? You're acting like a stranger.
I told you that we're still a married couple.
Get in. I'll take you home.
-Jang-go! -I know. I know.
"Why would I ride in your car? You go your way, and I'll go mine."
That's what you were going to say, right?
You know, so why did you even say such a thing?
Just leave already!
She'll turn back at least once, won't she?
One, two, three.
Drive safely.
Whatever! I'm going to drive as I please!
What? She's going to America? Is that true?
My daughter-in-law took pity on Mi-poong's family, so out
of old times' sake, she's going to send them to America.
Great, isn't it?
It would be nice if they really did leave.
But are they really leaving?
Of course they are. What kind of fool would lose such a good opportunity?
On top of that, she's divorced!
I guess. All right. Anyways, thank you.
Thank you for letting me borrow this.
But Mi-poong's family is going to America?
I guess so.
Chung-ja's daughter-in-law is going to send them.
They're really going to leave? What about Jang-go?
What do you mean? They're divorced.
They have nothing to do with Jang-go now.
Shin-ae is going to send me to the American
headquarters? Why would she do such a thing?
She said she's indebted to us and wanted to pay us back for it.
Also, she felt bad she couldn't help you when you got fired from the company.
She really said that?
Mi-poong, if it's all right with you, I want us to go to America.
It would be good for Yoo-sung's future. On top of that, you can
forget about all the bad things here and start fresh there.
Mom, I don't have a good feeling about Shin-ae making such an offer to us.
And I don't really want to go either.
Is this because of Jang-go?
It takes one month for the final decision to go through. We can
only get divorced if we report to the borough office a month later.
We're still a married couple.
Mi-poong.
I should keep wearing this ring, shouldn't I?
Of course. It's father's ring.
It's the ring that grandmother always wore.
You're right.
I'll do that.
Mi-poong, are you okay?
I'm fine, mom.
I don't have anymore hope of finding your grandfather anymore.
Mi-poong, I want us to go to America.
It won't be easy living there, but it'll be easier than living here.
Think about it.
Okay, I'll think about it.
"Please drop us a thick rope! Please!"
And that's how the kind brother and sister climbed up the thick rope to safety.
Then what about the terrible tiger?
The greedy tiger that tried to eat the brother and sister
climbed up a tattered rope that snapped, and he fell to his death.
Then did the brother and sister who went up to the sky live happily ever after?
Of course they did!
They became the sun and the moon and lived happily ever after for a long time.
So should you be good or bad?
You must be good!
Oh, you're so smart!
How could that tiny thing make me do this for her?
- Oh! - Oh!
Weren't you asleep yet?
Yes. Yoo-jin wanted to eat ice cream.
Yoo-jin isn't sleeping yet either?
Yes, she has no sleep at all.
- Good night. - Good night.
Mr. Kim!
- Dal-ho! Chung-ja! Hurry up! - Mom!
- Mr. Kim! - Mr. Kim!
Grandfather!
- Grandfather! - What's going on?
Dae-hoon.
- Here. - Thank you.
Geum-sil, is Mi-poong really going to America?
Looks like it.
It seems like she's really going to divorce Jang-go.
What do you mean? They already divorced.
There are many couples who go to court to get divorced but
end up changing their minds during the consideration period.
But if she's going to America, it means she's determined to divorce him.
I didn't think Mi-poong and Jang-go were actually going to get divorced.
If she goes to America, they'll really become complete strangers.
Aunt, is it true that Mi-poong is going to America?
Yeah, the director of your company said she was going
to send Mi-poong to the American headquarters.
Right, Geum-sil?
Jang-go.
Nam-yi, why would you tell him such a thing?
Jang-go, what are you doing here?
Is it true you're going to America?
- How did you know that? - That's not important!
Are you really going to America?
Jang-go, what's wrong with you?
Whether I go to Russia or America, it's my choice now.
Kim Mi-poong.
I divorced you because you said my house was like hell.
Because I wanted you to be free from my hell-
like house. Because I wanted you to recover.
That's why I divorced you.
But what? You're going to America?
You can never go. You got that?
Jang-go.
Fine. You can go to America or Russia.
But tell me when you make a final decision.
Why? Why do I have to do that?
If you go, I'm going, too.
What did you say?
I'll never send you by yourself.
If you go, I'll go, too. Just keep that in mind.
We got a divorce, so why is he being like this?
Is Mi-poong really going to America?
Does this mean she wants to stop her feelings for Jang-go and live away from him?
Hello.
What are you doing here during lunch time?
Lee Nam-yi, let's have a company meal today.
Excuse me? Why are we suddenly having a company meal?
Because I think the reason you were trying to quit
is because we never had a company meal before.
There can be no other reason besides that.
That's why we're going to have a company meal.
Really?
Then how about pork belly and soju-
Excuse me!
- Please put it here. - Yes, sir.
Eighty dollars.
- Enjoy. - Thank you.
What are all these?
We're having a company meal.
How is this a company meal? And who has a company meal in the daytime?
This is why I wanted to quit!
Anyways, I'm going to eat outside, so pig yourself out!
Do you really not like company meals in the daytime?
No...
Father, should I leave?
I brought my friends because I heard we were going to have a company meal today.
Should we go to the bakery?
No, come on in.
And from now on, Won-bin, read the atmosphere before you come in.
I'll be careful from now on.
Come and eat, all of you.
Won-bin, just like you said, Nam-yi is so pretty!
- She's super sexy! - Right?
Kids these days are so honest! What are you doing? Eat up!
- Thank you. - You guys are so smart!
What are you doing? Eat a lot!
How much is the kimbap?
Two dollars per roll.
Please give me two.
Dae-hoon, are you hungry?
- Yes. - We're almost there.
It looks like they're selling food near the subway station.
They sell a lot of things, like kimbap, rice cakes, and coffee.
Mr. Yang, I'd like to try Seoul kimbap.
Sure, let's do that.
Please stop next to the subway station.
Sure.
All this time, I didn't know I had a son in North Korea.
I thought Kim Soon-ok was dead, too.
What's the point of my children finding out about this right now?
Let me beg you one more time. Don't put up an ad again.
He met his bloodline, so how can he be so cold?
Is he really Mi-poong's grandfather?
How much is the kimbap?
Two dollars per roll.
Please give me four rolls.
Enjoy.
Thank you.
Dae-hoon, let's go.
Dae-hoon.
Dae-hoon! Dae-hoon!
Hi, mom.
Mi-poong. Mi-poong!
Mom, what's wrong? Did something happen?
Mi-poong, come home at once! I saw your father!
What? You saw who?
Mom, drink some water.
Mi-poong, I saw your father! He bought the kimbap that I made! I'm serious, Mi-poong!
Mom.
You think I'm crazy, don't you?
I feel like I've been bewitched, but I'm serious, Mi-poong!
Your father looks a little different than before, but I'm telling you the truth!
The person with him called him Dae-hoon! I heard him with my own two ears!
He rode away in a taxi, so I couldn't catch him, but I'm sure he was your father!
Mom, calm down.
I thought your father died from a gunshot at Amnok River, but he's alive!
He's alive, and he's here in South Korea!
Mi-poong, what if your brother is alive, too?
Mom, what's wrong with you?
I wish father was alive, too. I wish the man you saw was father, too.
But if he really was father, why didn't he search for us all this time?
If he really is father,
shouldn't he have recognized you right away?
How could he not recognize you? That just doesn't make any sense!
Yes.
He would have, right?
If he was your father, there's no way he wouldn't have recognized me, right?
But then who did I see? Was I seeing a hallucination?
You probably did see a hallucination because you were so
hopeless and devastated after what grandfather did to us.
To be honest, I didn't tell you this,
but I was so bitter and upset because of your grandfather.
Your grandmother wore this ring all her life and couldn't rest in peace
because she couldn't meet your grandfather before she passed away.
How could he do this to us? Is he really your grandfather? I feel so upset and bitter!
Yes. That's why I saw a hallucination, Mi-poong.
That must be it.
Mom.
It's okay.
But I really saw him.
I really did.
Okay, okay.
Grandfather, you promised to be by my side for a long time.
But you keep getting sick...
I'm so distressed, grandfather.
Dr. Yang said this keeps on happening because I'm old.
But don't worry.
I will never leave you behind and die so soon.
How tenacious can he be? He looks like he's about to die, but he never does.
No. Mr. Kim can't pass away right now.
Shin-ae, go to work. I'll stay here.
No, father, I'll stay here, too.
No, Shin-ae.
I'm okay, so go to work.
Yes, do that.
I'll be here, too. Come, come.
Mother, is something wrong?
Shin-ae, this won't do. We need to hurry up and put you in the family registry.
Why so suddenly?
Why else?
Mr. Kim keeps fainting like this. What will happen if he passes away?
You're Park Shin-ae, not Kim Shin-ae.
Then you won't be able to become the legal heiress.
No way.
I already filed to change my last name. Isn't that effective?
On top of that, everyone in the company knows I'm his granddaughter.
How frustrating can you be?
To be frank, you can't even get a DNA test with
Mr. Kim, so what's the use of all of that?
In front of law, documents are the answer.
No way.
We need to be sure of it.
Hi, Lawyer Cha. It's me.
I was just curious if my daughter-in-law Shin-ae
was on Mr. Kim's family registry yet.
What did you say?
You think it's going to take over a month?
Look here, Mr. Cha! Mr. Kim wanted you to hurry up, so what's taking you so long?
Mother.
Mr. Cha, speed things up.
Mr. Kim is waiting for you.
Please do your best.
What's so hard about changing someone's last name? Why is he taking so long?
He's getting paid a lot, too.
Mom! What are you doing out here? I told you to rest tonight.
I'm fine.
Mom, by any chance, did you come out here because you thought you could meet father?
Mom, you said you were hallucinating. Why are you doing this? It upsets me.
It's not like that. I said I'm fine.
What kind of phone call does he need to take outside away from me?
Mr. Yang, what do you mean you think you found Mr. Kim's son?
I'll tell you the details after I meet Mr. Kim.
However, I can't get in touch with him.
He's in the hospital right now because he isn't feeling well.
No.
I think it would be better if I go over there and check it out myself first. Bye.
Honey, where are you going?
Mr. Kim is lying in the hospital, but where is he going in such a rush?
Is he going to meet that woman again?
No way.
He's devoted to Mr. Kim.
Mr. Kim is lying sick in bed. Yes. He won't do such a thing.
He's Mr. Kim's son?
According to the information I gathered, I'm sure he is.
I brought him so that he could do a DNA test with Mr. Kim.
We thought he was dead, so how could this miracle happen?
But Mr. Yang, his behavior is a bit peculiar...
He's like a child, isn't he?
Yes.
Because of the trauma of the gun wound he received while running
away from North Korea, he thinks he's ten years old right now.
Ten?
Yes. His memory stopped at the age of ten.
Where have you been?
Where's my wife?
I sent her home.
I was going to discharge when you came back.
You're going to discharge?
Of course. I know all about illness, so why would I stay here?
I'll be careful, so let's go home.
Mr. Kim, are you sure you're okay?
Yes, I am.
That's why Dr. Yang took out the IV.
Hold on.
Mr. Kim.
What?
Do you have something to tell me?
You can't be shocked.
Brace yourself.
What's going on?
Mr. Kim, the broker Mr. Yang is here.
Why would he be here when he should be in China?
Mr. Yang brought someone who he suspects to be your son, Kim Dae-hoon.
What did you say?
What are you talking about?
My son isn't dead? He's alive?
My son Dae-hoon?
Mr. Kim...
Where is he?
I need to meet him myself. Where is he?
- Mr. Kim, are you sure you'll be okay? - I'm fine!
Where is he?
- Where is he? - Mr. Kim.
Where?
Come in.
Mr. Yang.
What happened?
The man you came in with...
Dae-hoon.
Say hello.
Are you Dae-hoon?
Kim Dae-hoon?
But who are you, mister?
Kim Deok-cheon.
Have you heard my name before?
Then...
what's your mother's name?
What is it?
My mother's name is Kim Soon-ok.
Do you know my mother?
Of course I do.
But...
your father.
Have you heard about your father?
Of course.
My father is an amazing person.
He's a national hero who died during the Victorious War.
What? National hero?
Because of his gun shot wound, his mind is stuck at ten years old right now.
Sometimes his memories do return, but he lost most of them.
Mr. Kim, are you all right?
Mr. Yang,
are you saying he comes back to normal sometimes?
Yes. A few days ago, his memories came back, and
when I asked him, he seemed to know your name.
What?
He really knows me?
That's why Mr. Yang brought him to Seoul. So that you two could do a DNA test.
Yes, let's do that DNA test right now. Let's go do it right this minute.
Mi-poong, I'm sorry.
You're going through trouble because of me.
Why should you feel sorry? I should be the sorrier one.
Why should you feel sorry?
It's all my fault that you're like this.
Would you have done this if I was happily married with Jang-go?
This has nothing to do with that.
Mom, the day after tomorrow is father's birthday, right?
Let's go to Imjingak with Yoo-sung.
We can go there and call for father and Yeong-cheol as much as we want.
Sure, let's do that.
Mom, from now on, I'm going to live thrice as harder as I did before.
So make sure you prepare yourself.
I am going to grow stronger.
From now on, nothing like today will happen again.
Good.
- The test results are out. - Thank you.
Dal-ho,
you should check it.
(DNA Test Results)
Mr. Kim.
He's your son!
He is?
Are you serious?
(99.99% probability of paternity between Kim Deok-cheon and Kim Dae-hoon)
Dae-hoon, you are my son!
Dae-hoon! My son Dae-hoon!
Let go of me!
I'm your father.
During the Third Battle of Seoul, I got separated from your mother.
No.
No!
My father is a national hero who died during the Victorious War!
How could you be my father, mister?
Don't lie to me!
Dae-hoon!
Look at this.
It says right here that you and I are son and father.
I'm your father, Dae-hoon!
You are my son, Dae-hoon!
Dae-hoon,
during science class at school, you learned about DNA testing, didn't you?
These are the results of the DNA test.
Do you see that it says you two are alike?
This man is your father.
Dae-hoon!
He's really my father?
Your mother's name is Kim Soon-ok.
Your uncle's name is Kim Seung-ok.
Your grandmother's name is Kang Mi-soon.
If I wasn't your father, how would I know the names
of your family members on your mother's side?
I'm not lying.
Father!
- Dae-hoon! - Father!
Yes, Dae-hoon.
Father!
- My son, Dae-hoon! - Father!
- My son! - Father!
Come in.
Isn't that the Chinese broker from last time?
Mr. Kim found his granddaughter, so why is he coming again?
I don't know. I have a bad feeling about this.
But who is that ditzy-looking man right there?
Mr. Kim, are you okay now?
Yes.
Hello.
Say hello to him.
Who...?
He's my son, Dae-hoon.
Who?
Dae-hoon, Shin-ae's father and my son.
Oh my goodness! He's Mr. Kim's son!
Mr. Kim's son was alive!
- Oh my god... - Chung-ja!
The person you are trying to reach is unavailable.
You still can't get in touch with Shin-ae?
No, it's still off.
How surprised would Shin-ae be if she found out her father was alive?
- I know. - Dae-hoon.
You have a daughter.
You got married. You have a son and daughter.
Do you remember your daughter's name?
The name your daughter used in North Korea
is Kim Seung-hee.
Don't you remember?
No.
She said you told her not to use that name here in South Korea.
You don't remember that either?
That's why she's not using the name Seung-hee in South Korea.
Her name is Park Shin-ae now.
How nice would it be if your memories of your daughter came back?
He's getting better than before, so his memories will come back soon.
My daughter's name is...
Kim Seung-hee?
It's all over now.
Chung-ja, why don't you go to Mr. Kim right now and beg for forgiveness?
But mom, that man lost all of his memories.
Will he realize that Park Shin-hye isn't his daughter?
Of course he will!
Even if I was dead and turned into dust, I'd recognize you!
If he's a dad, how could he not recognize his own daughter?
Even if he lost his memories, he'll recognize his own child.
What do I do, mom?
Call Shin-ae right now and tell her not to come home!
Tell her to just disappear! We'd survive, at least! Tell her to never come home!
The person you are trying to reach is unavailable.
Why is her phone turned off?
Then wait outside for Shin-ae to come and warn her that there is a bomb at home!
Okay.
- Good-bye. - Thank you, Mr. Yang.
I'm forever indebted to you.
I'll never be able to forget your kindness.
- I'm grateful to you, too. - Yes.
- We're home! - We're home!
What do we do?
Shin-ae, why weren't you answering your phone?
Do you know how many times we called you?
Why? Is something...?
Hey.
Shin-ae, do you recognize him?
(Blow Breeze)
Let's keep it simple today. Make some dumplings.
- Yoo-sung, I'm hoping you can help me out. - Sure!
Mr. Kim, do you like me as a woman or not?
She's fake!
Are you talking about the elder in your house?
Forget what I said!
You're lying. You're lying, aren't you?
Dad!
Why am I your dad? Where's Seung-hee? Where is she?
Subtitles by OnDemandKorea