Subtitles by OnDemandKorea
- (Episode 38) - Shin-ae, why weren't you answering your phone?
Do you know how many times we called you?
Why? Is something...?
Shin-ae.
Do you recognize him? Look who's here!
Dae-hoon, do you recognize your daughter?
She's Seung-hee! She's Kim Seung-hee!
That woman...
is my daughter?
Shin-ae, don't be shocked.
Your father lost his memory and became a baby.
Father?
He has no memory.
Dad!
Are you really my dad?
Dae-hoon, she's your daughter!
You should at least recognize your daughter!
How can you not even recognize your own daughter?
Dad, I'm Seung-hee!
I didn't know you were alive!
Why did you just come now when you were alive all this time?
I thought you were dead!
But what's wrong with my dad?
Dad, what's wrong with you?
Dad, look at me. Look at me, dad!
While running away, he got shot, and because
of that trauma, he can't remember anything.
Oh, no, dad...
I'm sorry I don't recognize you.
But I really don't remember.
No.
It's okay, dad.
I'm just grateful that you're alive.
It's okay if you don't remember me.
What kind of tragedy is this?
Seung-hee, don't worry.
I'll do whatever I can...
to bring your father back to normal.
Are you serious, dad?
Grandfather found his son?
He wasn't dead?
We thought he was, but he was actually alive.
We're going to have a celebratory dinner tonight, so bring Jang-soo
over to introduce him to the family and celebrate with us.
Can I bring Jang-soo with me?
Of course. You must come together.
Are you going to come without your husband?
No! We'll come together! We'll come right now!
Yes!
Did something good happen?
My grandfather found his long-lost son whom
he thought was dead in sixty-something years!
What? Are you serious?
Hurry up and change, so we can go to my house.
- Where? - My house!
What? Really?
Yes! Hurry!
Oh my goodness! What kind of joyful occasion is this?
He met his son in sixty-something years! This is a miracle!
Last time he found his granddaughter, and now he found his son.
Mr. Kim's wish came true.
He had really wanted to find his family.
Oh my goodness. What is more tragic than being separated
from your family and not being able to meet them?
I know.
So they invited you over for a party?
Yes. My dad said that I must come with Jang-soo.
Oh, then you must go!
Tell them we said congratulations.
- Okay. We'll be back. - Bye.
Bye.
Gosh. This is the first time Jang-soo is going
to his in-laws' home after he got married.
I think they're accepting Jang-soo as their son-in-law now.
I feel so happy now, mother.
How nice is it to see them walking out while holding hands together?
I know!
Poor Jang-go had to get a divorce because of his selfish mom.
Would he even want to come home?
Why aren't you making dinner? Are you trying to starve your mother-in-law?
Let's keep it simple today. Make some dumplings.
Eat it when it's warm.
It looks delicious!
Someone came.
Who can it be?
It's freezing cold! Oh, you were home! Hello, mother!
Hi.
Yoo-sung!
Hi, uncle.
I love dumpling soup.
Did you eat yet?
No. Can you give me one bowl, please?
- Jang-go. - Huh?
What are you doing?
That's right. This is yours.
What is this?
You left your scarf at home, so I brought it to you.
You're grateful, aren't you?
I'll accept this one, but if you see anymore
of my belongings around, just throw them away.
Goodness. Why would you throw away good things?
Wouldn't that be wrong, Yoo-sung?
You shouldn't throw away good things, aunt.
See? Even Yoo-sung says it's wrong.
While you're here, hurry up and eat this while it's warm.
I will! Thank you!
Wow! The soup is amazing, mother!
It's so hot and delicious!
The soup is hot and delicious! I feel better already!
Yoo-sung, after we eat, do you want to come
to the supermarket with me to buy desserts?
Yes, uncle!
Okay! Let's eat!
Thank you for the food!
You're welcome.
Aren't you going to eat?
- (Grocery Store) - Here, Yoo-sung. Eat this.
I want to ask you for a favor.
A favor? What is it?
Yoo-sung, what I'm about to tell you right now...
is between you and me. Man-to-man.
So it's a secret, okay?
Okay! I'm good at keeping secrets because I'm a man!
Oh, you're so cute!
Okay then.
So, Yoo-sung, you know that your aunt and I are living separately right now, right?
But I want to live with your aunt again because I love her so much.
What do you think, Yoo-sung? Do you agree with me?
Yes, of course I agree with you.
You're so darn cute!
Okay, Yoo-sung, that's why I would like your help.
Can you help me?
Sure!
Mi-poong, come and sit here for a moment.
Jang-go is using all kinds of excuses to come and see you here.
He can't seem to forget you.
How about you change your mind, Mi-poong?
Mom.
If changing my mind was all it took to be happy with
him, why would I have divorced him in the first place?
I guess that's true, but I feel bad for the both of you.
You two love each other, so why can't you live together?
I'm so upset.
Mi-poong, please reconsider one more time.
If you two move out of his mother's house and live happily with your kids,
wouldn't your mother-in-law be happy then?
Mom, I don't want to be part of a family with people who don't accept us.
And if I decide to get back together with Jang-go,
his mother will really severe ties with him.
I don't want Jang-go and his mother to turn out that way because of me.
If someone told me to severe ties with you, I'll never be able to do that.
So how could I tell Jang-go to do such a thing?
Jang-go keeps on coming here. What will we do?
Mi-poong, let's go to America then.
If we went far away, wouldn't you and Jang-go
be able to forget each other more easily?
Okay, I'll think about it.
It's cold. We're back.
Uncle bought a bunch of ice cream and snacks for me.
He did?
- Jang-go. - Huh?
We need to talk.
Okay.
Mother, I'll be going now.
Yoo-sung, man-to-man. You know, right?
Okay!
Bye!
What is it?
Jang-go, don't ever come back here again, and if
you see my belongings, don't bring them to me.
We're divorced, so don't come to my house ever again.
Mi-poong,
I didn't come here to see you.
I came to see Yoo-sung and your mother.
I was curious if Yoo-sung was growing well and if your mother was doing well.
I came to check on them.
Why would you be concerned about my mom and Yoo-sung?
You don't have to do that.
Wow, look at you. The way you talk disappoints me.
If not me, who else would take care of them?
- If you're going to be ridiculous, just go back inside. It's cold. - Jang-go!
If you keep this up, I'm really going to go far away!
I'm going to disappear without you knowing!
I definitely told you that you can't do that.
If you were going to do this, why did we divorce?
Do I need to remind you again?
Because you wanted to.
Because you said you were going to die. Because you can't die.
That's why I let us get divorced.
We're living separately right now, but nothing else has changed.
Got it?
You'll catch a cold. Go inside.
I'll be going now.
Seriously, what's wrong with him?
What do I do?
"I'm pleased to meet you!"
Congratulations, grandfather!
I'm so pleased to meet you!
Thank you.
Grandfather, say something.
Today is a very touching and happy day.
Sixty-something years ago, I separated from my family and came here to South Korea.
I lived all this time with the hope of meeting my family in North Korea.
I miraculously met my granddaughter Shin-ae and my son Dae-hoon.
On this day when my wish was granted, all of you gathered here to celebrate with me.
Now I can die without regrets.
And Dal-ho...
thank you.
It's all thanks to you that I can be blessed at such a late age.
How would I have lived all this time without you?
Mr. Kim...
I'm the one who suffered the most here! I cooked and did the laundry for him!
How can he not even glance my way?
My wife, Soon-ok, who is in heaven right now...
Thank you.
How you must have suffered raising Dae-hoon all by yourself.
Why did you have to leave first?
Father, when are we going to eat?
If you make a long speech in front of the dinner table, you'll be cursed at.
Yes, you're right.
Let's all be healthy and happy. Cheers!
- Cheers! - Cheers!
- Congratulations! - Congratulations!
I can't tell if Mr. Kim's son is an adult or a child.
I'm confused whether I should speak to him formally or not.
What kind of bolt out of the blue is this?
It seems like he really doesn't remember, right?
Yes, it seems like that for now, but when you watch dramas
or movies, the character suddenly gets his memories back!
Then what do we do?
No way!
Those are just dramas.
Anyways, I hid the ring in the drawer.
But whether he's a child or a man, he's a human being
with legs, and he'll be walking around everywhere now.
Then what if he bumps into Mi-poong or her mom? What will we do then?
Then it'll be over for us!
Mi-poong's family said they were going to America,
so we just need to be careful until then.
Oh my god!
You scared us. You should've knocked!
This is my room.
Your conspiracy meetings won't work anymore.
What do you mean conspiracy meetings? How could you say that?
Don't be like that and just turn yourselves in.
Would he kill you if you begged for forgiveness?
Mom, what are you talking about?
What did we do wrong? Why do we have to turn ourselves in?
It's only a matter of time before he finds out she's an imposter!
What are you talking about?
Mother, do something about her!
Okay...
Look at that rude, little thing! You rude witch!
What's wrong with you? My head hurts enough already!
Chung-ja, I ignored all this for your sake until now,
but after seeing Mr. Kim being reunited with his son after sixty-something years,
I can't just overlook this anymore.
And if you can't just overlook this?
Are you going to expose everything then?
Aren't you scared of the heavens?
What are you going to do if you get punished for this?
Mom, I'm prepared to get punished!
But I can't reveal the truth right now! Aside from
everything else, what will happen if Dal-ho finds out?
He'll want a divorce then!
Then it's all over! I'm not the only one whose life
will be for! It'll be over for Hee-dong as well!
Do you want to see that happen?
No, I don't want that. No! No!
So please keep your mouth shut!
So you live here on the second floor?
Yes, dad.
Wow. My father's house is very spacious and nice.
My father must be very rich!
He lives in such a nice house.
Dad.
Did you just call me?
It's strange that I'm your dad.
But am I really your dad?
Yes, dad.
Dad, you really can't remember anything?
Yes.
I'm sorry, Shin-ae.
I don't remember.
Nothing at all?
Yes, nothing at all.
Then you don't remember how we tried to escape by crossing the Amnok River?
Amnok River?
I've never been there before.
You really don't remember going there?
Yes.
Then what do you remember about being in North Korea?
My mother's face.
Holding my mother's hand and walking along the Taedong River.
The mung bean pancakes my mother used to make.
And her bean-curd dregs rice.
And...
playing a game of slap-match with my comrades Min-soo, Jin-gook, and Dong-shik.
Oh, do you know what Dong-shik's nickname is?
It's "Dung Tub!"
"Dung Tub!"
But...
are you really my daughter?
I feel like you're not my daughter.
No, dad!
I am your daughter!
You're lying, aren't you?
You're lying right now, aren't you?
No, dad!
Just kidding!
Why would you joke around like that?
Do you know how much I missed you? Did you not miss me at all?
I have to remember you in order to miss you...
I'm sorry I can't remember you.
Still, since we met like this, I'll be good to you from now on.
Shin-ae, I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
What do you mean you can't go home unless I come here?
No matter how much I think of it, I don't
think what we had earlier was a company meal.
Did you...
just threaten me that you couldn't go home for that reason?
Do you know how quickly I sped over here from Cheonan
because I thought something terrible had happened?
All I told you was that I couldn't go home. When did
I threaten you that something terrible had happened?
Fine.
What do you mean when you say that our lunch wasn't a company meal?
How was that a company meal?
It was a food gathering for Won-bin's friends.
I had to listen to Won-bin talk behind his teacher's back, his friends' school
lives, and their worries. That was a counseling session, not a company meal.
- Your point is? - A company meal has alcohol and grilled meat.
We need to talk about how the store will develop in the
future and exchange ideas about how to increase sales.
It's a time when you can ask questions and get to know each other better.
Fine!
We'll do the darn company meal!
- When should we do it? - Now.
- Let's go, Mr. Kim. - What?
Come on.
We already drank a lot. How about we stop drinking and go home now?
No.
How can we go when we haven't solved the difficult situation?
I can't go home.
Difficult situation?
What's that?
I never met a man who was as tactless and dim-witted as you are.
I'm dim-witted?
That's the first time I heard that one before.
I'm a very exact person. You know that.
Look at you now.
You don't even understand what I'm saying right now.
What don't I understand?
I sent you all these signals, but you don't see them.
Just like now.
This is our first company meal, but how can you only
talk about medical appliances for the past two hours?
How can you not know a woman's feelings?
This was why I was going to quit.
Because you're so dim-witted!
To be honest, I said we should have a company dinner
tonight in order to settle things once and for all.
Settle things once and for all?
Yes.
No matter how many signals I send you, you don't realize anything, so...
I'll ask you straightforwardly.
Mr. Kim...
do you or do you not like me as a woman?
Since you're not answering, I guess you don't.
I got my answer now.
Thank you for everything.
Then I'll be going now.
Why are you doing this?
A man responds with actions rather than words.
Grandma.
This is rice punch. It's cold, so it'll be refreshing to drink.
Thank you.
It's great. Did you make it?
No. Your mother made it.
I'm giving her a hard time with the housework these days.
Are you looking through those again?
Did you find anything?
No, not yet.
Mi-poong's innocence should be revealed as soon as
possible so that your mother can soften up a bit.
Has Mi-poong changed her mind about the divorce?
- No.- I understand. Your mother was so horrible to her.
Mi-poong must have felt like dying after being fired
for being blamed for something she didn't do.
Gosh. She was treated as a thief.
Her mother got on her knees in front of your mother while she was watching, too.
If I was Mi-poong, I would never want to come back to this house either.
But Jang-go, you still need to check on Mi-poong.
I know. I went to her house today, too.
Good. You did well.
Yes.
Out of sight, out of mind.
Even though Mi-poong pushes you away, you just
put on a thick face and go right for her.
Then she'll come to you.
Leave your mother to me.
- Got that? - Yes. I'll trust you.
Yes, do that. Everything will work out.
Dae-hoon, if you're not sleeping, get up. I want to show you something.
Dae-hoon...
have you seen this ring before?
This is my mother's ring!
My mother's ring has the word "Cheon" engraved on it.
- But this one... - Yes. This has the word "Ok" on it.
So you do remember this ring.
This is the ring I wore on my finger.
I heard you gave the ring with the word "Cheon" on it to Shin-ae.
Don't you remember?
I gave it to Shin-ae?
I don't remember that.
Then where is mother's ring right now?
Some fool lost it while she was cleaning my room.
If I had that ring,
it could have helped bring your memories back.
Still, look at this ring frequently, think of
your mother, and try to
regain your memories.
Yes, father.
Father.
Yes.
I just wanted to call you.
I really like the word "father."
To be honest, I was envious of my other comrades who had fathers.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
Yes.
Now that we met, call me as much as you want.
Yes, father.
Dad, what's wrong?
Why am I your dad?
Who are you to call me father?
Where am I?
Where's Seung-hee?
My Seung-hee!
My Yeong-cheol! Where are they?
Where did everyone go? Seung-hee! Yeong-cheol! Honey!
- Dad! - Why am I your dad?
Who are you?
Where is Seung-hee? Where is she?
Father!
- Are you okay? - Hee-dong.
What's going on?
- Oh my god! - Dae-hoon! Dae-hoon!
- Shin-ae! - Grandfather.
Dad is acting strange!
Dae-hoon, what's wrong?
Father.
Yes, it's okay.
- Father. - Yes. You're okay.
What on earth is going on?
Dae-hoon. Dae-hoon, what's wrong? Did you have a frightening dream?
Why are all of you out here?
Is it because of me?
Dae-hoon.
Are you okay now?
Dad, do you recognize me?
Yes.
You said you were my daughter.
Don't worry too much. He must have been shocked
because his environment suddenly changed.
It could be a good sign that his memory is coming back.
I think it would be best for him to go to the hospital tomorrow.
Yes.
That would be best.
- I'll make an appointment at the hospital tomorrow. - Okay.
Here.
Sleep after you take this medicine. You'll be okay then.
- Go on. - Thank you.
Hee-dong, what if my dad continues to be like this?
He didn't recognize me and said strange things.
I was so scared.
Like grandfather said, your father is a bit sick right now,
so even if he says strange things, just forget about them.
It worked out for the better.
No matter what he says now, everyone will think he's just saying nonsense.
You wench!
You didn't answer your phone all night long. Where did you spend the night?
My battery went out, so I couldn't call you.
Why did you wake up so early anyways?
You seriously don't have any morning sleep.
- Let go of me! - Be quiet, will you? Or else the rest of the family will come out!
Did you make him sleep with you?
What are you talking about? All we did was just hold hands and sleep.
What? All you did was just hold hands and sleep?
Hey. Do you think I was born yesterday?
They say the one who wants to eat the fruit will climb the tree first.
Good job!
- All we did was hold hands and sleep! - I got it!
You did well! That was one good accident!
There was no accident!
Okay, I got it.
After just holding hands with him while sleeping, do you think he's the one for you?
I don't know!
Yoo-sung, why are you throwing a tantrum?
Yoo-sung. Yoo-sung!
Go to school today, and we'll go to the amusement park on Sunday. How about it?
No! I'm going to go today! Today!
You never threw a tantrum before. Yoo-sung, do
you want to go to the amusement park that much?
Yes. I'm the only one in my school that never went to an amusement park before.
Oh, dear. Is that true?
Okay, okay. I'm sorry.
Okay, Yoo-sung. Don't cry.
You must have wanted to go to the amusement park so
much. You never threw a tantrum like this before.
This won't do.
Mi-poong, take Yoo-sung to the amusement park today.
Come with us, mom.
I want to, but what about all the kimbap and dumplings I made to sell today?
The two of you should just go by yourselves today.
Yoo-sung, brush your teeth and change your clothes.
Let's go to the amusement park.
Wow! I'm so excited!
My goodness. He is a kid, after all.
Oh, it's uncle's car!
Oh, Kim Yoo-sung! Kim Mi-poong! You two must be going somewhere.
This isn't the way to school.
Mind your own business, and you go your way.
We're going to the amusement park right now.
Oh, really? The amusement park?
Wow! I got the goosebumps! I was on my way to the amusement park right now!
What? You're going to the amusement park?
Oh, I must not have told you. I go to the amusement park sometimes.
What a coincidence! Get in the car. I'll give you a ride.
- Forget it. - Yes, uncle.
Yoo-sung!
Aunt, we're going to be late. Hurry up and get in.
Hurry up and get in. Oh, it's cold! Cold! Cold!
I examined the medical records of Kim Dae-hoon he brought from China.
It seems like he had a severe gunshot injury.
And he had three major surgeries as well.
Really?
I heard he barely made it alive.
That's why it is written down that his memory loss is due
to dissociative amnesia and stress from his gunshot injury.
We, too, think his memory loss is from those reasons.
He was trying to get rid of shock, pain, and
fear at the time and lost his memory also.
How painful must it have been for you to throw your memory away, too?
Dr. Hong, will he be able to get better?
If he can get recuperated,
I'll do anything.
As you know, the brain is rather mysterious and vast, so I can't guarantee anything.
However, I know the causes, so I'll do my best, Mr. Kim.
Thank you. I'll put my faith in you then.
Dae-hoon, you heard that if you come to the hospital on a regular basis
and do as the doctor says, you'll be able to get your memory back, right?
So let's get treatment, okay?
Do you understand me?
Yes, I understand, father.
But even if my memory doesn't come back, I'm okay.
I'm happy just living like this with you.
You're very optimistic, aren't you?
Okay, let's think that way.
Even if your memory doesn't return, Shin-ae, you, and I will live happily together.
- Sounds good, right? - Yes.
Good.
But where are we going right now?
Is there someplace you would like to go?
Tell me whatever you want to do. I'll do everything for you.
I heard amusement parks in South Korea are very nice.
I want to go there, father.
- Amusement park? - Yes.
Okay then. That's not hard at all. Let's go right now.
- Right now? - Yes.
- Really? - Yes.
Let's go.
That'll be three dollars.
- Enjoy. - Thank you.
Lady!
Didn't I tell you not to do business here?
What a tick you are!
There's an empty spot here, ma'am. We can do
business here together. That will work out.
You saw that, didn't you, honey? I told you she's like this.
Hey, lady. How will this work out when you're doing business in someone else's spot?
You're being very stubborn. Move this.
Why are you doing this to food?
- How dare you. - No! You can't do this!
God damn it!
- Why are you doing this? - Move!
We're in the same situation!
I didn't even move into your spot! All I did was set up a table in an empty spot!
You little-
Who are you?
I won't say much, so just leave.
Mr. Jo...
Let go.
I got it.
- Let's go, honey. - Okay.
I can do this by myself, so please go.
I don't want to show this side of me to you.
So please don't do this and just leave.
- Yoo-sung, put your hands up! - Hands up!
What?
I smell something fishy going on here.
Smell? Smell what?
I only smell something good from you.
Be honest.
You coaxed Yoo-sung into going to an amusement park first, didn't you?
Hey! Why would I coax Yoo-sung and...?
How'd you know?
Wouldn't I be stupid not to know? Yoo-sung never throws tantrums, but he
suddenly threw one to go the amusement park, so I knew something was off.
How can you be so thoughtless?
Would I have done this for no good reason?
And I never pulled Yoo-sung into this mess. He was on my side all along.
- How can you say that? - I'm sorry.
- Jang-go. - Kim Mi-poong.
I thought about it, and I realized we haven't done so many things together.
I thought we would have a lot of time together.
That's why I thought we could do things later.
But I regret that now.
I did this so that we can do the things we didn't
do before during this consideration period.
I'll apologize for using Yoo-sung. That was my fault.
Jang-go, how many times must I tell you?
We can't get back together. We have no choice.
Why don't we have a choice? We can get back together. I believe so.
Is divorce a joke to you? Do you think you can do as you please?
Kim Mi-poong, I did what you wanted me to do.
Then it's your turn to do something I want you to do.
I need some time. Time to reflect and heal.
Aunt! Uncle!
Yes.
I'm done eating this. I want to go on a ride.
Should we?
Mi-poong, while we're here today, let's just
forget about everything and have fun. Okay?
Yoo-sung, let's go!
Should we go on a ride?
Hi!
Uncle!
Father...
Father!
That's my father! Father!
- Father! - Mi-poong!
Jang-go! Excuse me! Please let me down!
- That's my father! - Mi-poong, what's wrong?
My father is over there! Jang-go!
Father. Father!
Please let me down!
- Dae-hoon! Dae-hoon! Dae-hoon! - Father!
Where did you go?
I was so scared! I thought I had lost you!
I was looking around.
Didn't you say you wanted to ride something?
- The merry-go-round. - Yes, the merry-go-round.
It's that way. Let's go.
- It's fun! - It's fun?
Father! Father!
- Father! - Mi-poong!
- Aunt! - Yoo-sung.
Aunt!
Kim Mi-poong!
Father!
Father! Father!
Mi-poong, are you sure you saw your father?
Yes, it was him! I saw him for sure!
I made eye-contact with him, too! He's here for sure!
- Hold on! - I don't have time for this! I have to find my father!
Mi-poong, how will you be able to find him here?
I have an idea, so follow me.
- Excuse me, but we would like to make an announcement for a lost person. - Sure.
Will you write down his name and anything special about him?
We're looking for a person. Kim Mi-poong is
searching for Kim Dae-hoon from Pyeongyang.
If you hear this, Mr. Kim Dae-hoon, please come to
the information desk in front of the front gate.
- One more time... - Aunt, who are we waiting for?
My father.
Your grandfather.
My grandfather?
Yes.
Wow! I have a grandfather?
Chung-ja, no matter how many times I think about it, this is wrong.
This is all Shin-ae's fault!
You weren't always such a terrible person!
You became like this after you met her. Do you know that?
Mom, Shin-ae is Hee-dong's wife! What's going to happen to Hee-dong?
You need to tell him the truth now!
If you can't, I will.
You're crazy!
If you're going to be like this, get out of this house!
What? You horrible wench!
Whatever! You can call me whatever you want, but I won't go back to the old days!
I'd rather die than live poorly again!
If you're going to say those things, just leave!
Fine, I'll leave.
I don't have any attachments to this house any longer!
Oh my goodness. What is wrong with her?
- Bye. - Bye.
Come again.
Oh, grandma!
- Hee-ra. - What are you doing here?
What's this?
You reek of alcohol!
Did you drink?
Grandma, what's wrong?
Why are you crying?
I left home. I'm not going back.
Why not?
Did you fight with mom?
Did you play flower cards again? Is that why you two fought?
It's not that.
Then what is it?
Did something upsetting happen at home?
The truth is, Hee-ra...
Never mind. What's the point of telling you this?
I'm so frustrated.
Oh, you were here.
Hello.
Yes. Hello.
Is something wrong?
Of course now.
How about we go get some rice wine together?
Sure. That's not hard to do at all.
(Deokcheonok Boss)
Hello?
It's me, Ms. Joo.
Can I see you right now?
Right now?
What's this?
This will be enough to buy a small store.
You should get a store.
A store?
Why are you giving me this?
I don't have any other intentions.
It's not like I don't know you.
On top of that, I already saw you being humiliated
after doing business outside during this cold weather.
I couldn't just do nothing about it.
No.
I have no reason to take this money from you.
If you're so burdened, you can work hard and pay me back.
Mr. Jo, I'm very grateful to you,
but this isn't right.
I'll be going now.
Ms. Joo.
Ms. Joo. Ms. Joo, hold on.
If I make you so uncomfortable,
I won't act like I know you, even if we coincidentally run into each other.
But...
I hope you won't suffer like you did today.
I hope you won't suffer through such trouble like the ones
you experienced at my restaurant and on the streets today.
Why can't you know my feelings?
Why wouldn't I know your feelings?
Why wouldn't I want to lean against such a grateful person like you?
Ms. Joo...
I'm a woman, too.
If I hadn't been Mi-poong's mom...
If I hadn't been Yoo-sung's grandma...
And if you hadn't been a man with a family already...
I would have leaned against you and relied on you.
But you and I shouldn't do that.
How can people just do whatever they want?
That's not what we should do as human beings.
So that's why I think this is the end of you and me.
Thank you for everything you did for me so far.
I'll never forget it.
Good-bye.
Oh, dear. You should stop drinking now. You've already drank so much.
I'm not drunk at all.
I'm a pretty heavy drinker.
Still, wouldn't your family be worried? It's pretty late.
There's no one waiting or worrying about me at home,
so it's fine.
I'm sure that's not the case.
Why wouldn't they worry about you?
Truth be told, I was kicked out of the house, so I don't have anywhere else to go.
What? You were kicked out?
What do you mean by that?
- Dal-rae. - Yes?
This isn't about my family. It's about a family I know.
Will you listen and tell me if I'm wrong or not?
Sure, go ahead.
The grandfather of this family I know very well  is extremely wealthy.
However, he doesn't have one bloodline in this world.
Is this about your in-law Mr. Kim?
Heavens, no! This is about another family!
He just managed to find his granddaughter,
but she's an imposter.
So do I have to tell him the truth or just ignore it?
So the granddaughter your in-law Mr.Kim, the owner of the house, found last time...
is an imposter?
Pardon?
Oh my god. What are you talking about?
No! I don't know what I just said, but I'm so drunk that I'm just talking nonsense!
Forget about it!
You're pretty drunk right now. You should go after you sober up.
No!
You can never tell anyone what I just told you right now.
It was all nonsense!
- Good-bye! - Gwi-ok! Hold on!
Gwi-ok, I'll take you home. Let's go together.
Don't come out.
- But... - You can never tell anyone what I just told you right now.
- Bye. - Hold on...
Oh my gosh. If what she said was true, this is awful!
Mother, wasn't that Ms. Chun?
She seemed to be Chung-ja's mother, but why was she leaving in such a hurry?
It's because she was shocked after telling me
something she shouldn't have while she was drunk.
- Do you know the granddaughter that her in-law Mr. Kim found last time? - Yes.
She's an imposter!
What are you talking about?
What?
She's an imposter?
You two look so cute and pretty.
Shin-ae. Yoo-jin. Do you like them?
Yes, I do.
I like it, but I don't have to wear this outside, do I?
I think everyone will stare at me if I go outside like this.
Still, he tried so hard to pick a present for you, so make sure you wear it often.
Thanks, dad.
You're welcome.
But since you two are wearing the same headbands, you two look just like each other.
You're like mother and daughter.
Is that so? I think Yoo-jin looks more like me.
No, she looks more like Shin-ae.
Dae-hoon is right. Sorry, Hee-dong. Yoo-jin looks more like Shin-ae than you.
Oh, well.
But it's so strange.
My father and I look very alike.
So why don't Shin-ae and I look alike?
Really?
We don't look alike?
Shin-ae must look like her mom then.
Wow. If you look like your mother, then she must've been a real beauty.
What did you do at the amusement park today?
We went on the merry-go-ground, bumper cars, and viking.
- That one's scary. - Father, let's go again.
Again?
What am I doing going on all these rides after I met you?
Let's all go together next time.
Yes. As long as Mi-poong's family goes to America, there will be no problems.
He's just a ten-year-old child living in the body of an adult.
This is another announcement.
Kim Mi-poong is searching for Kim Dae-hoon from Pyeongyang.
If you hear his, Mr. Kim Dae-hoon, please come
to the information desk in front of the gate.
- One more time... - Jang-go.
We made an announcement, so why isn't he coming?
It was really him. He really was my father.
What if he was just someone who resembled your father?
That might be true.
Yes.
You said he made eye-contact with you.
If he really was your father, he wouldn't have just left.
You're right. There's no way my father wouldn't recognize me.
I think you're right.
It's late.
Yoo-sung seems to be very tired.
What is it? Do you have something to tell me? Did something happen today?
Mom...
to be honest, at the amusement park today...
I think I saw father.
What? Are you serious?
I thought I saw wrong...
but no matter how many times I think about this...
I think he really was father.
Tell me the details. How did you see him?
We were on a ride, and father was right in front of me.
What? Right in front of you?
I couldn't get off the ride, so I called for him, and we made eye-contact...
but he just left...
What? He saw you but just left?
Did I just see someone who resembled him?
No, he is your father!
Last time I saw him, I thought I saw wrong, too, but
that's not the case. How can I mistaken your father?
I really saw father, too.
But why did he just leave after seeing me?
That's because...
Wouldn't he have a reason for doing that?
Mi-poong, let's look for your father.
Your father could be alive. He could be alive and here in South Korea.
Mi-poong, your father's face was so vivid in my dreams.
It felt like your father wanted us to find him.
Okay, mom. Let's look for him.
Let's search for father.
Yes.
(We are looking for a person)
We are looking for a person.
We are looking for Kim Dae-hoon who came from Pyeongyang.
If you have seen Kim Dae-hoon who gave this ring to his wife, please give me a call.
Excuse me.
We're looking for someone. Please read this.
We're looking for someone. Wait, mister-
- Here you go. - We're looking for someone.
Please help us.
Ms. Joo. Mi-poong.
Shin-ae.
What are you doing here?
This is the apartment in America where the three of you will live in.
It's close to Winner Group's American headquarters.
There is a foreign school nearby, too.
Everything is prepared, so you just have to choose
the date you'll leave and get your plane tickets.
Shin-ae, we're not going to America.
What? You're not going to America?
Are you stupid? How can you lose a good opportunity like this?
Ms. Joo, Mi-poong said the wrong thing, didn't
she? You're going to go to America, right?
Shin-ae, we can't go to America.
There's a reason we can't go.
Why? Why can't you go? What's the reason?
We think...
our father is in South Korea.
What?
What did you say?
My mom and I saw him.
That's why we're going to find him.
(Blow Breeze)
What do I do? What will I do about them now?
Is it true that she's pretending to be the real granddaughter?
If you're going to be like this, get out!
Shin-ae is an imposter?
Where the hell did he come from?
You glared at me.
My eyes usually look like this.
I know everything.
What are you talking about?
- Jang-go. - Mother.
Jang-go.
How long were you going to stand out here?
My dad isn't coming...
Subtitles by OnDemandKorea