Subtitles by OnDemandKorea
- (Episode 39)
- This is the apartment in America
where the three of you will live in.
It's close to Winner Group's
American headquarters.
There is a foreign school nearby, too.
Everything is prepared,
so you just have to choose
the date you'll leave
and get your plane tickets.
Shin-ae, we're not going to America.
What? You're not going to America?
Are you stupid?
How can you lose a good opportunity like this?
Ms. Joo, Mi-poong said
the wrong thing, didn't she?
You're going to go to America, aren't you?
Shin-ae, we can't go to America.
There's a reason we can't go.
Why? Why can't you go? What's the reason?
We think our father is in South Korea.
What?
What did you say?
My mom and I saw him.
That's why we're going to find him.
What do you mean you're going
to find your father?
Ms. Joo. Mi-poong.
Mr. Kim passed away at the Amnok River.
But where did you see him?
What kind of nonsense are you saying?
No, I definitely saw him,
and Mi-poong even made
eye-contact with him at the amusement park.
We didn't believe it in the beginning,
so you won't be able to believe it either.
But he was really my husband.
That's impossible.
It's just someone who looks like him.
Shin-ae, thank you for
being concerned about us.
However, my father might be alive,
so we can't go to such a far place.
- Yes.
- So you can give this chance to someone else.
How can you do this?
You said you were going
to go to America, Ms. Joo!
You shouldn't have said
you were going to go then!
Do you know how hard I worked to prepare this?
I made a spot at the American headquarters
and signed the apartment contract!
Ms. Joo, just go to America!
You should think about Yoo-sung!
What is there for you to do here?
Shin-ae...
calm down.
Shin-ae, there's no reason
for you to be so angry.
We never begged you to
send us to America.
Neither did we make
the final decision to go there.
You planned and prepared this all by yourself.
That's true...
but Ms. Joo, you said
you were going to go to America.
I said I would think about going.
I never said I would go.
And even if we said we were going to go,
shouldn't you tell us
that we should find my father?
Finding my father is more
important than going to America.
Or is there a different reason
why we must go to America?
So you're really not going to America?
Yes! We're not going to America!
Shin-ae, I'm sorry things turned out this way.
Fine.
Opportunities like this one don't come
by easily. Just don't regret it later on.
And how on earth will you
be able to find your dead father?
Mom, isn't she a bit strange?
Is this something she has
to get so angry about?
(We are looking for a person)
What do I do now?
What will I do about them?
Is her daughter-in-law really an imposter?
Her mother knows about it,
so wouldn't she know about it as well?
Is Chung-ja playing along with it
even though she knows Shin-ae is an imposter?
No way.
You said you had something to tell me.
What is it? Why are you hesitating?
Well, it's a bit difficult to believe...
You're frustrating. What's wrong with you?
Oh, fine.
The truth is, your mother came to
my house yesterday and said something strange.
What? My mother was here?
What did she say that was so strange?
Chung-ja, I heard your daughter-in-law...
is pretending to be
Mr. Kim's real granddaughter.
Is that true?
Oh my goodness! Oh, no!
What do we do?
- You must've gotten burned! Are you all right?
- It's hot!
- It's hot! Oh, no!
- I'm fine.
What did my mom say?
You must be really shocked.
You didn't know about it?
What are you talking about?
Oh, my. You really didn't know about this.
But if your daughter-in-law really is an
imposter, shouldn't you do something about it?
No matter how much
she coveted the huge inheritance,
how can she try to fool bloodlines?
Oh my goodness.
That's a terrible thing to do to Mr. Kim.
No, it's not like that.
Shin-ae really is his granddaughter.
She is?
Then why would your mom say such a thing?
There's something weird going on!
Did they do a DNA test?
Of course they did!
He was looking for his bloodline.
Don't you think he did that already?
You know how Mr. Kim is.
Do you think he'll be lax about such a thing?
Are you sure they're a 99.99% match?
Of course!
That was hot.
I guess you're right.
He wouldn't have accepted her
as his granddaughter
without doing a DNA test first.
But why did your mom say such a thing?
Wouldn't she be in trouble if
she went around saying things like that?
Well, the truth is,
my mom is showing signs of dementia lately.
What? She has dementia?
Oh, my. So that's what happened.
I didn't know that, and I got the wrong idea.
Geum-sil, I'll be going now.
I have to take my mom to the hospital today.
Okay, go on.
- Bye.
Mom!
- Oh, I lost again! Woe is me!
- Mom!
Mom, what the heck are you doing outside?
What did you say to Hee-ra's
grandmother-in-law yesterday?
I was so drunk yesterday,
so I don't remember what I said.
I heard you revealed to her
that Shin-ae is an imposter!
Are you insane?
Do you really want to see me die?
Chung-ja, I told her that I made
a slip of the tongue because I was so drunk!
I told her it was nothing like that!
How could you do such a thing
when you never did anything great for me?
Chung-ja...
I get so sick and tired
when I think of the past!
I never got to eat proper meat, and every
single day we had to eat the dough soup!
At a young age,
I couldn't wear new clothes, and
I always wore stockings with holes in them!
Despite everything, I met Dal-ho,
and I was able to start living a proper life.
What? I'm going to get punished?
I told you I'm okay with getting punished.
I'm doing this because I don't want
to live a pathetic life anymore!
I'm sorry.
I couldn't even do anything nice
for you as a parent, yet I just
stick to you like glue and
give you nothing but a hard time.
But Chung-ja, I'm doing this because
I'm worried you'll get in big trouble later.
Eventually, lies will always be exposed.
That's how this world works.
I don't have any inheritance
to leave you, but I just want to
give you some words of wisdom
about what the world is like.
Mr. Kim's son has appeared now.
One day, everyone will find out
Shin-ae is an imposter!
Why do you keep saying frightful
things that make my heart burst?
If you're going to be like this,
get out of this house!
Shin-ae is an imposter?
Shin-ae isn't my father's granddaughter?
She's an imposter?
Then Shin-ae isn't my daughter either?
No, you misheard!
Of course she's your daughter.
Whose daughter is she then?
Whose granddaughter is she then?
Ms. Chun just said that
Shin-ae is an imposter!
I definitely heard her say that.
Why are you lying?
Look here! When did I say that?
I never said that before!
I heard very clearly with my own two ears!
I'm very offended!
I'm going to call Shin-ae.
When I press number one,
I'll be able to talk to my father.
I'm going to call him and tell him
that you called Shin-ae an imposter!
- Oh, no! What do we do, mom? No!
- Chung-ja!
You evil woman! This is my cell-phone!
I'm going to call Shin-ae!
I'm going to call my father!
You're going to die if you call them!
You evil woman! This is mine!
Oh my god. What's going on?
Dad, what's wrong?
Shin-ae!
That evil woman tried to take
my cell-phone so that I couldn't call you.
Also, she said I was going
to die if I called you or father.
Mother!
The thing is...
And Ms. Chun said you were an imposter.
Then those two had a fight about it.
If you're not my father's granddaughter,
it means you're not my daughter either.
I felt offended, so I was going to
call father, but that evil woman stopped me.
Mother...
what is he talking about?
Dae-hoon, you misheard.
No! I heard you very clearly
with my own two ears!
Shin-ae, I don't want
to live with such mean women.
I hate them!
They're so offensive!
How can they call you an imposter?
So hurry up and scold them, huh?
The thing is, my mother has dementia,
so she was saying nonsense.
Dementia?
What's that?
Dad, I'll explain everything,
so let's go upstairs.
Okay.
My father said that
I'm the owner of this house!
What do we do?
Is that true?
Yes, dad.
Dementia is a disease when you grow old
and your brain doesn't function well.
When you get dementia,
you start to say ridiculous nonsense.
Just like how you're upset
that you don't remember anything,
that grandmother says
strange nonsense sometimes,
so they fought because they're upset.
Oh, I see.
So you should understand her and
not feel offended. It's because she's sick.
Okay.
Since she's doing this because
her head hurts, I'll understand her.
Thanks, dad.
And you can never tell this to grandfather.
Why not?
Didn't you get angry because
she said I was an imposter?
Grandfather will get angry, too, and he
might kick grandmother out of the house.
It's the middle of winter, so if she
gets kicked out now, she'll freeze to death.
Do you want her to freeze to death?
No. No.
So you can never tell grandfather, okay?
Okay.
That's good.
Promise.
I'm so glad you're not an imposter.
Mother, I have no idea what I should do!
I'm sorry. I have no excuse.
Look at this flyer!
Oh my goodness. This is...
Mi-poong is trying to
find her dad, so what am I
supposed to do when grandmother
is making such a mess?
I asked you to make sure
nothing like this happens!
Do you think I'll be the only one
who will die if this gets exposed?
I know we're all going to die.
I'll make sure nothing
like this ever happens again.
How? How are you going to do that?
I'm sorry.
Mom, we need to-
What are you doing?
I'm going down to the country
where your Aunt Dae-bok lives.
Is this because I told you to get out?
Mom, why are you upsetting me like this?
I'm doing this because
I don't want to see you!
Let me just say one last word to you.
You should beg for
forgiveness now when you can.
You won't be able to stop this
if it gets any bigger.
Mom, why do you keep being ridiculous?
Fine. Fine.
Mom! Mom! Mom! Mom!
Mom! Mom!
Mom!
Mom, I'll send you enough money,
so just wait a little bit, okay?
Mom!
(Mr. Kang, distribution center)
Mr. Kang...
Mi-poong.
Mr. Kang?
The case of the missing boxes
at the distribution center.
The case of the leaked information.
Yes.
Those two are definitely related.
When we put an ad in the
newspaper, we got a lot
of calls, so how come no one is calling now?
Mi-poong, it might cost
a lot of money to put an ad in
the newspaper,
but I think it would be much better.
Come on, mom. This is just
the beginning. Would they call already?
If there is no response
after we spread out all the
fliers we ordered, let's put
an ad in the newspaper then.
Sure, let's do that.
Hello?
Pardon? You're calling because of the flyer?
What? You know where Kim Dae-hoon is?
Where is Kim Dae-hoon? Where is my husband?
I'll tell you after I get my money.
I'll give it to you.
As long as I can find him,
I'll give it to you. How much do you want?
How do we know if the person
you have is really my father?
You're very suspicious.
Kim Dae-hoon was born in 1951,
and he's from Pyeongyang.
His son's name is Kim Yeong-cheol.
His daughter's name is Kim Seung-hee.
His wife's name is Joo Young-ae.
His mother's name is Kim Soon-ok.
He got shot while trying
to escape, and he gave
a ring with the character
"Cheon" on it to you.
Need I say more?
No, no. He's really my husband.
Where is he right now?
Please bring my father to us.
I'm begging you.
Then prepare $20,000.
$20,000?
Yes. It took $20,000 to
bring him here from China.
I need that money in order to
bring Kim Dae-hoon to you.
But we don't have that
much money right now...
You don't have money?
- It's too bad then.
- No, wait!
No, no.
We'll give you the money.
We'll come up with the money somehow.
So please take care
of my husband until then.
When you have the money,
give me a call.
How will we be able to come up
with $20,000 immediately?
Mom, let's ask the owner
of the house if we can
take some money out of
the security deposit.
You want me to give you $20,000
from the security deposit?
Yes, something urgent came up,
so we really need the money. Please.
If I take out $20,000
from the security deposit
of $30,000, then there's only $10,000 left.
I can't let you live on a security deposit
of $10,000 with a monthly payment of $300.
If it's really an emergency,
let's raise the monthly rate to $500 then.
Then I'll give you $20,000.
Yes, okay.
Let's raise it then.
But if you can't pay the monthly rent,
it'll become troublesome for me.
So give me a year's worth
of monthly rent in advance.
Pardon? A year's worth?
If you don't like that,
I can't give you the money then.
It's common for people who
take the security deposit in advance to
run away in the middle of the night
because they can't pay the rent.
Yes, all right. We'll do that.
Then I'll deposit the money
into your account right away.
- Thank you. Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
What brings you here?
Hello. Your co-workers said
I'll be able to meet you here.
There's no reason for us to meet anymore.
I would like to ask you something.
You know Kim Mi-poong is my wife, don't you?
But this time, my wife was involved in a
case of leaked information and was fired.
I keep thinking that the
case of the missing boxes you
committed is connected to
this case of the leaked information.
No matter how many times I think about this,
I don't think you would plan such a thing.
It seems like someone
ordered you to do this, but who?
Am I wrong?
It's all over already. If you're going to
mention this again, don't come back here.
Please leave.
Sure. I'll go for today.
I'll see you next time.
Hello? I deposited the money
into your account. Where should I go?
The first exit at Cheonggu Station
in front of the park?
Okay. Bye.
Let's go. We're going
to meet him an hour later.
An hour later?
Okay, let's hurry up and go!
Your father used
to love my dumplings.
He said they tasted
just like the dumplings his
mother used to make
and never got sick of them.
That's why I had thought of
your father a lot when I made dumplings.
Today, we'll be able to eat
dumpling soup with your father.
You're right. When I think
about how I'll be able to eat
dinner with father later tonight,
I feel like I'm dreaming.
Mom, this isn't a dream, right?
It's not a dream.
But why isn't he coming?
Ten minutes have already passed.
Oh, mom!
I think he's coming. That looks like father.
Where? Where?
That's not him.
All the men who pass by
look like your father now.
But why isn't he coming?
- Go ahead and call him.
- Okay.
- Your call cannot be completed at this time.
- Why? He's not answering?
No, I think he's on his way.
Okay, let's wait.
He'll be here.
They fell into the trap?
Good job. I'll send you your payment later.
They fell for it?
Yes.
How did they fall so easily?
That's amazing!
Because they used their
security deposit, they'll
never be able to refuse
my offer to go to America.
That's great!
But, despite their loss, what if
they still refuse to go to America?
They wont' be able to last long.
We just have to
make sure they don't
meet him in the meantime.
So mother, even though I'm not around,
make sure you check if grandfather's son's
memory is coming back or not. Also check
if he says or does anything strange.
All right. Don't worry.
Here.
What's this?
Use this to get an
apartment for grandmother.
It's going to be hard for
her to live in the country.
Shin-ae, thank you.
You're the best.
Mom, I'll stay here, so go home.
No, I'm okay.
But what happened? Why isn't he here yet?
He's not answering his phone either.
What if something happened on the way here?
What if they got into a car accident?
I'll call him one more time.
- The number you have dialed does not exist...
- What's wrong with the phone?
Why? What's wrong?
The number you have
dialed does not exist...
What does it mean it doesn't exist?
Did it say this earlier, too?
Why can't I reach him?
No, it wasn't like that earlier.
Give it to me.
- The number you have dialed does
not exist, so please check again.
- Mom...
what do we do?
Did we just get conned?
What do we do?
(Yoo-sung's Teacher)
- Yoo-sung!
- Yes, our Yoo-sung!
Hello? I'm so sorry! I'll come
pick him up right away.
Bye.
- Mom...
- I'll stay here, so hurry up and go.
This can't be true. No.
Mom, why did grandma
suddenly go to the country?
I didn't even get to say bye to her.
Well, your grand-aunt
was sick and summoned her.
Then shouldn't we go, too?
But it turned out that
she was faking her illness.
She lied because
she wanted to see your grandma.
Oh, I see.
She said she's going to stay there for
a while to keep your grand-aunt company.
She said she was sorry
she couldn't leave without
telling you good-bye
since she had to leave urgently.
Really?
It's not like she's gone forever.
She'll come back.
Yes.
Did you give her enough bus fare?
Yes, I did. Don't worry.
Here.
If it wasn't for him, my mom wouldn't
have gotten kicked out of here!
Gosh! That moron! That idiot!
Where the hell did he come from?
Do you hate me?
Me?
No. Why would you suddenly ask me that?
You just glared at me.
Like this.
I did? Oh, no, I didn't!
I'm not stupid. You did glare at me.
I think you saw something wrong.
I didn't glare at you.
My eyes normally look like this!
Even when I don't do anything,
people think I'm glaring at them!
I really didn't glare at you!
I really didn't!
Right, honey?
Mom!
Mom...
Mi-poong.
Mi-poong...
Mom, I'll stay here, so take
Yoo-sung and go home first.
No.
I'll stay, so go home with Yoo-sung.
He'll catch a cold at this rate.
Mom.
Okay.
Okay, I got it.
Yoo-sung, go to grandma.
Oh, Yoo-sung.
Mom, go.
If you meet your father by
any chance, call me right away.
I will. Hurry up and go.
Oh, it's cold!
Yoo-sung!
Yoo-sung! Mother!
What's this?
Why isn't anyone home at this hour?
Mother! Are you just coming home? I'm just
going to give you this pizza and go home.
Mother...
Jang-go.
- Yoo-jin is good at this!
- Dae-hoon, do you love games so much?
Father, don't talk to me.
I won!
- I lost.
- I won!
You're so amazing!
How can you be so good at this game?
You're the best!
You're better at this
than my friend Seung-yeon.
- Really?
- Yoo-jin, do you want me
to get revenge for you?
- Yes!
- Father, let's play.
Sure.
Start.
- What's so great about games?
They're crazy over them.
- Go, Mr. Jo!
Go, Mr. Jo!
Kim Mi-poong!
Jang-go.
You're completely frozen.
You're such a fool. How long were
you planning to stay out here?
Seriously.
My dad isn't coming.
The season silently leaves
I'm silently crying
I miss you, I miss you so much
The one person who crashes into the empty air
My goodness. How could that happen?
Isn't there a way to
catch that horrible jerk?
I'm trying my best,
but I think it's going to be difficult.
It's impossible to locate him
because his phone is fake.
My goodness.
He was resolved on conning them.
It's like trying to
squeeze water from a stone.
How could any human being
do such an awful thing?
They suffered to come
all the way here from
North Korea and managed
to barely get a room.
Goodness. Now they wasted their money
trying to find her father.
Oh, no. What will they do now?
That vulgar bastard!
Such terrible jerks will
be struck by lightning one day.
Of course!
But I'm worried about
Mi-poong and her mother.
They lost their money in a fraud,
but since it was while trying
to find her father,
they're even more heartbroken about it.
Of course they would be.
They lost their security deposit.
I would feel much better if they
moved back into the back house.
Mother, what are you saying?
They already left, so why would
you want them to come back?
Those people have nothing
to do with Jang-go now.
What were you doing?
Were you eavesdropping on us?
Of course I wasn't. I just happened
to hear the two of you talk.
Those people are so hopeless.
They lost their security deposit
trying to find her dead father?
- Mom.
- What?
Jang-go, get a hold of yourself.
You already divorced her,
so why would you see her?
So what if she's looking
for someone or got
conned? She has nothing
to do with you now!
Oh my god.
Mi-poong's father must be alive.
I know. My grandfather
found his son, too.
I hope she can find her father.
It would be even better
if she found him, and
he was rich like your grandfather! Right?
That won't be easy.
Mom, I bought medicine.
Did Yoo-sung go to school?
Yes. Take your medicine.
How are we going to live now?
If I think about losing
our precious security deposit...
I become so hopeless.
Why are you saying
something so weak?
We lived well under the
bridge with Yoo-sung before.
At least we have a house now that
will shield us from the rain and snow.
Compared to the past, aren't we rich?
We need to leave here next year.
What will we do then?
We'll think about it when
we come to that bridge.
At least we have hope that father
is alive here somewhere in North Korea.
So mom, you need to be healthy
so that we can find
father and work hard
to make money for the rent.
Don't you think so?
Yes. I do
Mom, don't worry.
I'm going to get my head on straight
and live harder than before.
Mi-poong.
When you met him, was there anything
strange or suspicious about him?
No.
He just said that he called us
after he saw the flyer we put up.
He said that he would bring my father to us
as long as we pay him for the broker fees.
That's all.
He even knew my mother-in-law's name, too.
He also knew about what happened at
the Amnok River when we escaped here.
If he hadn't heard it from my husband,
where would he have heard that from?
I think they're doing this
to get more money from us.
That's possible, but since
they used a fake phone, it seems
as if they approached you
with the intent to con you.
First of all, I think
it would be best if we find
out if father is here
in South Korea or not.
How do we find that out?
Is there a way?
We need to go to
a non-governmental organization
or center run by North Korean defectors.
If father is really alive, then
he would have left his traces somewhere.
So there was that method.
Why didn't I think of this before?
Yes. Mi-poong, let's hurry up and go.
- Okay.
- Let's go right now.
Unfortunately, for the past
two years, the Kim Dae-hoon you
are searching for has never
visited our office before.
I heard this was the most active center.
Then was there anyone searching for
Kim Mi-poong, Kim Seung-hee, or Joo Young-ae?
I searched through the forms,
but there isn't such a person here.
Really?
Then isn't there
a program that helps the
defectors search for
their family in South Korea?
You can put up information,
such as name, age, and hometown,
of the person you are searching for as
well as your phone number on our homepage.
If you film a video searching for
your family, we can upload that also.
A video searching for their family?
Honey...
Dae-hoon...
Mom, I'll talk.
Father, it's me, Seung-hee.
It's been a long time, hasn't it?
Here in South Korea,
I'm living well as Kim Mi-poong,
the name you gave me.
Kim Mi-poong.
Do you remember the name you gave me?
All this time,
we thought you were dead...
so we didn't even think
about searching for you.
But...
mom and I...
saw you here in South Korea.
The person we saw is you, right?
You're alive, aren't you?
Father, we miss you so much.
Dad...
let's meet for sure.
Hi.
You're late today.
Yes.
But why are you suddenly wearing glasses?
Is there something wrong with your eye?
No, it's not that. I just
can't make eye-contact with you.
Why can't you make eye-contact with me?
Is it because of what happened that night?
Nam-yi, have a seat.
Let's straighten what happened that night.
Straighten?
Straighten what?
So that night was...
We were very drunk and...
So...
So are you trying to
say that you made a mistake
that night because
you were very drunk?
I understand how you feel now.
I'll be going home now. Bye.
When did I say it was a mistake?
I didn't even get to say anything yet!
Mr. Kim...
Nam-yi...
Father, what are you doing?
Are you scolding Nam-yi?
It's not like that!
Then what is it? Father,
don't hurt Nam-yi's feelings anymore.
Won-bin, don't call her Nam-yi anymore.
Why not?
Nam-yi is my girlfriend.
So you're forbidden to
call her Nam-yi from now on.
Call her something else.
What? Girlfriend?
Oh my god! What's wrong with the house?
Kang Yoo-jin!
Is this your house? If you keep doing this,
I'll send you back to the orphanage!
I'm sorry.
Take these to the second floor
and play there! Hurry up! Go!
How annoying!
Look here, Ms. Ma.
What is it? Did you call me?
My father said
I'm the owner of this house.
I'm the owner of this house,
so why are you the one who's yelling?
What?
The house is messy because Yoo-jin was
playing with me, so don't yell at her anymore.
Got it?
Fine.
And apologize to Yoo-jin
for getting mad at her.
I'm sorry, Yoo-jin.
Mr. Kim, let's go play upstairs.
Okay, let's go.
He thinks he's the owner of
this house. What can I do about him?
But Yoo-jin, why do you live here?
Did your mom die, too?
Do you not have a mom?
No, my mom didn't die.
I have a mom.
You do?
Where is she?
Well...
she's here in this house.
Huh?
Really?
Your mom is in this house?
Who is she?
The truth is...
I'll tell you if you
promise to keep this a secret.
I'll keep it. I promise.
The truth is, Aunt Shin-ae is my mom.
What?
My Shin-ae?
Really?
Yes.
But why do you call
her aunt instead of mom?
There's an important reason, so she said
I have to call her aunt for three months.
That way, I'll be able
to live here with her.
So you can never tell this to anyone.
I told you this because
you're my one and only true friend.
Okay.
You must keep this a secret. Promise.
Promise.
Now that they lost their
security deposit, they'll be
as desperate as a drowning man
who would catch a straw.
Where will they be able to
find such a big straw as this one?
Excuse me!
This is driving me crazy!
This is why I said I wouldn't
hire a newbie like you!
But what did you say?
You said there was no problem!
You were bragging how well you
could do the job! How is this doing well?
I'm sorry. I'll quickly clean all this up.
That's not the problem right now!
What are you going to do about all this fish?
They dropped onto the floor!
Who would buy these?
Sir, I'll pay for all the damage.
Just take it out of today's pay.
God damn it!
I'll never hire a woman again!
Ms. Joo, did something happen?
You don't look very well.
No, nothing happened.
Nothing happened?
She lost the security deposit in a fraud.
Is she trying not to ask me for anything?
You're supposed to be begging me for help.
Is this the time for you to be so prideful?
But what brings you were again?
No matter how many times I think of it,
this is an opportunity
that is too good to lose,
so I came to persuade you again.
These are the photos of
America and the documents
you'll need to go there that
I showed you last time.
Look at them again
and discuss it with Mi-poong.
Shin-ae, thank you.
However, Mi-poong will say no.
I don't want to go right now either.
Why not?
Do you really think Mr. Kim is alive?
Are you really not going to America
because you're searching for him?
I'm certain that he's alive.
I met someone, and he knew
so much about my family.
If my husband wasn't alive,
how would he have known all of that?
What's going on? Did I fail because
I told the fake broker too much information?
And right now, we're looking up
different ways to find him.
We even uploaded a video on the website
of a center that will help us find him.
A video?
Ms. Joo, you should go
to America for Yoo-sung's sake.
You can still search for
Mr. Kim when you're in America.
You don't have to be in Korea. Nowadays,
you can find people through the internet.
Really?
Of course!
If you go to America, Mi-poong will have
a high-paying job, and you'll have a house.
I don't know why you're suffering here.
The benefits are so great that it would
be a waste to give to anyone else.
We'll still decline.
Thank you for your kindness though.
If we go to America
to live a comfortable life,
do you really think
we'll feel comfortable?
Thank you, but give
this opportunity to someone else.
They lost their security deposit
and don't have any money now!
I was going to give them a job,
house, and resettlement funds!
Why the heck can't they go to America?
Fine.
Let's see if you can resist
my temptation until the end.
Mom! Mom!
Mr. Kim said we're going to watch
a cartoon film! Join us, mom!
Kang Yoo-jin, who told you that you can
call me mom so loudly in the house?
No one is on the second floor.
This won't do.
From now on,
you must always call me aunt.
Don't call me mom. Got it?
No.
You said I can call you mom
when it's just the two of us.
If someone finds out about us,
we can't live together!
Is it okay if you don't live with me? Huh?
I'm still going to call you mom!
I don't want to call you aunt!
Why are you being so disobedient?
Are you going to upset me, too?
I hate you!
Yoo-jin!
Dad, what are you doing here?
Shin-ae, why won't you
let Yoo-jin call you mom?
What?
What are you talking about, dad?
Why would Yoo-jin call me mom?
I know you're Yoo-jin's mom.
She told me everything.
What?
Don't worry. I promised Yoo-jin
I wouldn't tell anyone that you're her mom.
So I won't tell father or anyone else.
But if you made a promise,
why are you telling me?
You're her mom, but she can't call
you that, so imagine how sad she would feel.
It's not wrong to call your mom "mom."
So don't scold her. This is my command.
Then, as promised, I'll keep this
a secret for the next three months.
Okay, dad.
Like you said, I won't scold her,
so go down and watch the movie with her.
I'll be down soon.
All right.
What are you two talking about?
It's a secret.
I'm even more curious
since he said it's a secret.
It's nothing.
He just wanted to watch
a cartoon movie together.
I'll quickly change and join you guys.
Come out, "Frozen!"
- Which cartoon movie are you going to watch?
- "Frozen."
Again? You already watched
that so many times!
It's still fun, and Mr. Kim
hasn't watched it yet.
Okay, then "Frozen" it is.
When you watch a movie, you need popcorn.
Popcorn?
What's that?
Pop! Pop! It's puffed rice
made out of corn! It's delicious!
Really?
Ma'am, do we have popcorn at home?
Yes, there's microwaveable popcorn.
Do you want me to make that for you?
- Yes, please give us juice, too.
- Okay.
But can you really
make puffed rice at home?
Yes. It quickly turns
into something like snow.
Then I need to watch it happen!
We can even say, "Pop!" Let's go!
It's so fascinating!
The corn is really popping
and turning into snow!
What's wrong? Ms. Chun!
- Father!
- Dad!
What's going on?
- Dad! Dad!
- Father!
Are you okay?
Aren't you Kang Mi-jung?
But why am I your father?
Oh my god.
Father. Father!
Father, are you okay? Father!
Father.
Dae-hoon! Dae-hoon!
Dae-hoon.
What happened?
Do you recognize me?
I was watching the popcorn popping.
Did I faint again?
Popcorn?
I think he was shocked
by the popping sound.
Don't ever pop popcorn again! Got that?
- Yes.
- Yes, sir.
Dae-hoon, you really don't
remember fainting today?
Yes, father.
I don't remember.
Shin-ae, you were pretty shocked
because of your father, huh?
Yes.
But who is Kang Mi-jung?
What?
Do you know her?
No, I don't know who she is.
But why did he call you Kang Mi-jung?
I don't know.
Maybe she's someone from his past.
Anyways, how frustrated will he be?
I hope his memory will return soon.
Yes. Me, too...
I think his memory
is returning bit by bit.
Kang Mi-jung is your old name.
How did he remember that name?
Just like my mom said,
are we going to get caught now?
If we get caught,
that'll be the end of us.
Shin-ae, should we turn ourselves in now?
Mother!
We came too far to turn ourselves in now.
And if we turn ourselves in,
we'll be doomed!
Mr. Kim, Dal-ho, and Hee-dong
will never see us again.
Shin-ae, what do we do now?
We just need to get rid of Mi-poong's father.
Get rid of him?
How?
Yoo-jin is going to school, and you'll
be home all by yourself. Will you be okay?
Of course!
I'll study and play games.
I'll be busy, too.
Good!
Then I'll come pick you up
when I'm done with work.
I'll show you around my company today.
I'll be back.
- Bye.
Grandfather, I'll see you
at the company later.
Okay.
Bye, Mr. Kim.
I'm meeting my friends today,
so I should get ready and leave.
Father, I need to talk to you.
Sure.
Today is my father's birthday?
Yes, dad. So how about you and
I give him a surprise party?
A surprise party?
No one will know, not even grandfather.
We'll prepare a birthday party
and surprise him.
Wow! That sounds fun!
- The housekeeper can't know
that we're planning a surprise party.
- Okay.
I'll go out and wait for your first.
Dad, do you remember the building
where you ate ice cream last time?
Come to that building.
We can go to the mall and
buy things we'll need for the party.
Okay.
You need to come out secretly
so that the housekeeper can't see you.
No problem.
(Blow Breeze)
- Are you really going to tell my mom?
- Yes.
- I'll make you bleed from both nostrils!
- Isn't this Chinese Quince Tea?
You divorced him, and yet,
you take his money behind my back?
- Kim Dae-hoon.
- Yes, that's me. Who are you?
He didn't come there yet?
There's one person
who witnessed Kim Dae-hoon.
- Did they catch him?
- Just stay still!
Find him. Find him at once!
Subtitles by OnDemandKorea