Subtitles by OnDemandKorea
Aunt!
Speaking of the devil. He's here.
You have a client.
Hello. But what brings her here?
She lost her entire security deposit!
-(Lawyer Lee Jang-go) -Lawyer Lee Jang-go?
Jang-go?
Tell Mr. Lee the exact details of your story.
Please have a seat first.
Never mind. I'll be going now.
Excuse me.
What's wrong with her?
Oh. It must be because of the legal fees.
I'll go after her.
Excuse me.
Hold on.
Yes?
If you're worried about the legal fees, you don't have to be.
No, it's not that.
It seemed like you were in a troubling situation.
Come inside and tell me the exact details.
Forget it. I don't need your help.
(Episode 4)
Why are you coming back alone?
Did that girl just leave?
Yeah. She said she didn't need my help and just left.
That's odd. She told me her family is out on the streets because
she lost her security deposit. So why would she just leave?
She sounded like she was from China.
She's not from China. She came from North Korea.
She lost all her resettlement funds from the
country and the money she saved up all this time.
How dare they con such a poor girl.
There are so many terrible people.
But aunt, don't you feel like you saw her from somewhere?
She seems very familiar to me.
Come on. How would you know someone from North Korea?
It's my first time meeting her.
I guess.
(Lawyer Lee Jang-go)
I made a mistake.
Jang-go wouldn't be here.
Yes.
It's someone else.
Someone with the same name.
Mr. Lee, please take a look at this document.
Sure.
-Oh, you're applying for this. -Yes.
I didn't do anything. Your sister, that little tadpole, did this to me.
I almost died.
Isn't he ugly?
I'm dumbfounded.
This is the first time someone told me that I'm ugly.
Let's go.
We need to make sure Seung-hee goes home first.
She'll go home on her own.
She said her mom is going to pick her up.
Still, how can we leave Seung-hee here alone?
Jang-go.
You really are that fish boy.
Jang-go, we'll definitely meet again!
You heard that music in the music room yesterday, didn't you?
So you can never forget me!
Got it?
Seung-hee.
-I think that's all you need to do. -Thank you.
Come inside and tell me the exact details.
Forget it. I don't need your help.
Hi, aunt. It's me.
Do you have the phone number or the house address of that girl from earlier?
Oh, you don't?
Okay.
She was just on my mind.
It's too bad then. Bye.
Mom.
Hi. I'm glad you came.
I have something to tell you.
Something to tell me?
Jang-go, my friend you helped out last time
wants to buy you lunch tomorrow to thank you.
It's fine. She doesn't have to do that.
It's not fine! You helped her, so the least she can do is buy you lunch.
Leave your lunchtime empty tomorrow. You can't make other plans.
-All right. -Wash up. Dinner is almost ready.
Okay.
-Jang-go, you came home earlier than I did. -Yeah.
Geum-sil, did you already find a matchmaker?
No, I didn't. The truth is I'm going to let him meet my friend's daughter tomorrow.
Your friend's daughter?
What kind of family are they?
Later on, my friend is going to inherit a hundred million dollars.
A hundred million dollars?
What kind of business do they own?
They do real estate and own several lands, buildings, and shopping areas in Gangnam.
They have a lot of properties.
Indeed, a building in Gangnam is worth several million dollars.
Oh my goodness! This is great!
But Nam-yi, the distant relative of my friend who will
pass on his inheritance to her came from North Korea.
However, he has no relatives in the North or South, except for my friend.
So the cousin of that Elder, who is my friend's father-in-law, passed away.
Can my friend, who is his distant relative, get the inheritance?
Of course she can.
Really?
They say you can make a big catch with three years
of practice. I'm the office manager of a law firm.
An inheritance by representation allows your friend to have the
money that your friend's father-in-law was supposed to inherit.
So it is true.
Oh my goodness.
Geum-sil, I really hope this works out.
But is your friend's daughter a good woman?
I met her once, and she's very pretty and bright.
She studied abroad, too!
Geum-sil, that's great!
Don't tell Jang-go.
If he finds out, he won't come.
Okay, I got it!
What were you two whispering about?
Dinner is almost ready, mother.
Mom, you don't have to know.
What did you say? You little-
At this rate, something really terrible will happen to Jang-soo.
He really didn't even drink a drop of water today.
He really didn't?
Yes!
Maybe we should let him date Ms. Song.
-Mom! -Mother!
Are you out of your mind, too?
Love is a mental illness.
What can be solved when all we do is corner
him and yell at him when he's already sick?
I'm so upset!
Gosh, that little punk!
Hey, Lee Jang-soo.
Lee Jang-soo, get up. We need to talk.
Are you a little kid?
If you're sure of your feelings, you should persuade the elders.
Fasting won't solve anything.
Lee Jang-soo!
Come out and eat dinner.
Lee Jang-soo, aren't you going to get up?
Jang-soo, hurry up and come eat.
Your mom made your favorite braised pollack.
Jang-soo, I heard you ate two chicken legs. So why are you pretending to starve?
He didn't!
I ate them!
Jang-soo didn't eat them!
Mom, how could you have ate them when he's the one who ate them?
That's how much you love Ms. Song.
You ate chicken legs already, so why can't you eat braised pollack?
You already ate, so just come out and eat!
Jang-soo! Oh my goodness! Jang-soo! Where are you going? Jang-soo!
Where are you going, Jang-soo?
He's totally gone mad.
You can't even soothe him, so why did you hurt his pride?
What? It's not like I said something wrong!
You should've used any means to try and separate him from Ms. Song!
What if he lives with Ms. Song out of anger? Will you take responsibility for that?
Oh, no! Jang-soo
!
This is too much. Mother!
-Mother! -Jang-soo!
Dinner is all set up, but what are we doing?
I'll get him!
Joo-ri!
(Inquiry for leasing)
The person you are trying to reach is unavailable.
Please call again or leave a message after the tone.
Song Joo-ri!
Where on earth did you go? Joo-ri!
Jang-soo, you fool! Get a hold of yourself!
Jang-soo, what's wrong with you?
I was wrong, so let's go home, okay?
Let go!
Oh, dear.
Joo-ri disappeared because of you three!
Is it a crime to be old?
Is it a crime to be divorced?
Is it a crime to have kids?
If something happens to Joo-ri, I'll die, too!
Just know that!
-Oh my goodness! -Hey! Hey! Hey!
Jang-soo! Mother!
-Mother! -Mom!
-I'll find Jang-soo, so go home first. -Okay.
Mother, get a hold of yourself.
-Mom! -Jang-soo!
Oh my gosh.
-Watch it! -Sorry!
I'm sorry!
Jang-go.
What?
Do you know how pitiful Joo-ri is?
Shut up and just walk.
She's a very pitiful woman.
I have to protect her!
Okay, fine. Protect her.
Jang-go.
What?
I miss Joo-ri.
Jang-soo.
Joo-ri!
Jang-soo!
What's wrong? You can't sleep?
No. I just...
What's wrong? Did something happen when you
went to the lawyer's office on the third floor?
Of course not.
Nothing happened.
Did the lawyer say there's no way to get our money back?
No. I went, but the lawyer wasn't there, so I came back.
Mom.
I trusted my friend's words, lost all our security
deposit, and made you and Yoo-sung suffer like this.
I'm sorry.
You didn't do it on purpose.
Think of it as learning a lesson here in South Korea.
As long as Yoo-sung, you, and I are healthy...
we'll be able to stand up again.
I'm going to harden my heart, too.
Eye gunk.
Blow.
There you go.
There. You're done.
Let me see. You're so cute, Yoo-sung!
I'd rather be cool than cute.
All right.
But who do you take after that you're so cool like this?
I'm cool like daddy because I'm a man!
Huh?
That's right.
Oh, my handsome and cool Yoo-sung.
-Hello! -Hello.
Yoo-sung, say hello.
Hello.
Hey.
It must be uncomfortable because there's no bathroom in the room.
No, we're not uncomfortable at all.
Thank you so much.
This is a leasing building and not a place suitable for living.
It's fine.
This place is as comfortable as a palace for us.
I'm grateful that you think so.
Oh, Mr. Jo.
-Hi. -Hello.
Oh, you're the woman who came to my office yesterday, right?
Yoo-sung, we'll be late for school.
Bye.
Mr. Jo, do you know her?
Not really.
She lost her security deposit and had nowhere else
to go, so I told her to use the empty storage room.
Why?
Nothing. I just think she came to my office because of that problem.
But she just left.
She looks so weak, and her child looks like he's only a kindergartner.
I felt so bad for her after hearing her story.
Goodness.
Yoo-sung, did you pack your pencil?
Okay, let's get on.
Hello.
What are you doing here?
I heard the simple version of your situation from Mr. Jo.
You came to my office yesterday, but you just left.
I thought I might be able to help you.
I told you that I don't need your help.
I'm fine.
I heard that you're not fine at all.
The house you planned to move in was put up for
auction, so you're staying here temporarily.
So are you saying you'll be able to get me back
the security deposit that was conned from me?
Yes, I'll get it back for you.
I can't get all of it back, but there should be a way to get part of it back.
There's a way to get my security deposit back?
Are you serious?
Yes.
(Lease Contract)
It looks possible.
According to the Housing Lease Protection Act, I
think you'll be able to get a part of it back.
There is such a law in South Korea?
You can't take it back later on.
Yes, there is such a law.
I won't take it back later on, so don't worry.
But...
if I can't get back all of it, how much can I get back?
It's a good thing you did a moving-in notification beforehand.
It's also good that you got an extension.
According to the law, if the security deposit is less than a hundred
thousand dollars, you will be able to quality for right of payment.
So...
you'll be able to get about $34,000.
$34,000?
Thank you so much!
But when will I be able to get that money?
I'll update you as it progresses.
Thank you, Mr. Lee. Thank you so much.
See?
It's able to be easily solved, so why did you run away?
Were you worried we would ask for a lot of legal fees?
It wasn't that.
But how much is the legal fee?
This is something you naturally get according to the law, so you don't have to pay us.
But you're helping me get a lot of money back.
No, it's really okay. You don't have to pay us.
Aunt, give me the copy of her ID.
Here you go.
Her ID.
Kim Mi-poong?
Here you go.
Thank you so much, Mr. Lee. I'm sorry for troubling you, Ms. Lee.
That North Korean girl is actually kind of cute.
She speaks her mind.
I'm glad that she's able to get some of her money back, but where
will she be able to find a place to live with only $34,000?
It's very pitiful.
Should I tell him that I'm Seung-hee?
No. He didn't even recognize me.
He's just a good lawyer that I met in this country. That's all.
Hello?
Yes, sir, of course I can work.
Then tell me the color and sizes you need through a text message.
Okay. I'll head over to the factory right now. Bye.
Hi.
I'm about to leave now. You didn't forget our lunch today, did you?
Come on. How can I forget when I'm the one buying?
Your daughter is coming, too, right?
Yes, she is.
She's out right now, but she'll come to the restaurant right away.
Then I'll see you later.
Why is she so interested in Hee-Ra?
(Mr. Yang)
What do I do?
This is so annoying!
Hold on.
What do you want?
You scratched that car just now, didn't you?
What?
You can't just leave after scratching someone
else's car. You need to leave a memo at least.
The car owner will be angry.
You're not even the car owner, so why are you meddling in someone else's business?
I'm not meddling, but you shouldn't do this.
Leave a memo.
You're weird.
Get out of my way.
I can't do that.
Leave a memo before you go.
Wow. Are you a gangster or what?
If you keep bothering me, I'll report you as a stalker!
It seems like you're kind of dim-witted.
There are security cameras around, so you'll
get caught right away once they check them.
So? Why does it matter to you if I get caught
by the security camera and get taken to jail?
I saw it.
I saw it, so how can I just go?
Leave a memo.
Thank you.
Hold on. Let me check first.
Wow, you're really annoying.
There. Happy?
Gosh, what a psycho.
So annoying!
Out of all places, why did mom ask me to come here?
(Jo Hee-Ra)
Hello?
What? They won't make the settlement?
Ma'am, don't cry.
I'll be there soon. Bye.
(Mr. Yang)
Lady, answer your phone.
If you ignore my call one more time,
you'll regret it.
What do I do?
Hello?
Do you think ignoring my calls will solve everything?
I'm sorry.
Just give me a few more days.
Of course. I'm not someone who wouldn't pay back money I borrowed.
Of course I must pay you back.
Yes. Yes. Yes. Good-bye.
Chung-ja.
Did you borrow money from somewhere?
What kind of call was that? Is something wrong?
It's nothing.
What would I need to borrow money for?
I guess. You don't need to borrow money when money is all that you have.
But what about your daughter?
Huh? Oh, yes. She's on her way here right now.
Mom!
What's wrong, Hee-Ra? What happened?
Just now, in the parking lot, some crazy psycho-
Oh, my. What do you mean a crazy psycho?
Did he do something to you?
It's not that.
I was parking my car when I just slightly scratched the car next to mine.
My goodness.
It wasn't even his car, but he told me I had to leave a memo
and blocked me to stop me from leaving!
Oh, my!
That's a strange man!
Come with me.
I'll get him.
Hey.
You're supposed to avoid strange, crazy people like him.
What if something happens to you?
Don't you watch the news?
You're right.
Nothing really happened?
Yeah.
From now on, if something like that happens, call my son.
My son is a lawyer.
He'll be here soon.
I see.
You should be careful.
Hi, Jang-go. Why aren't you here yet?
What is it?
You should've stopped by at least. We prepared this meeting for you.
Okay then. It's too bad.
What do we do?
My son came here, but he has an urgent matter to attend, so he has to go.
Really? That's too bad.
I wanted to introduce my son to you, but I'll have to do that next time.
Lawyers are usually like this, since they do very important things.
Oh, I see.
Excuse me. I need to use the restroom.
Sure.
Your daughter is so beautiful.
Does she have a boyfriend?
What's wrong with her?
She kept asking me to bring my daughter out. It was
all because she wanted to hook her up with her son?
How dare she.
No, she doesn't.
She's going on blind dates to get married.
Tomorrow, she's going on a blind date with a congressman's son who's a dermatologist.
She's going on a blind date?
With a congressman's son?
Yes.
What should we order?
Geum-sil, what happened?
Do they seem to like each other?
They didn't even meet.
Why not?
I thought you said they were going to meet today.
Something important came up for Jang-go, so he couldn't come out.
What's more important than this? This is ridiculous.
My friend's daughter won't do.
She's going on a blind date.
With a congressman's son who's a dermatologist.
What? She's going on a blind date with a congressman's son?
Yes.
Geum-sil,
just because there's a goalkeeper doesn't mean we can't make a goal.
It's just a blind date, so there's no goalkeeper anyways.
And all blind dates don't end up in marriage.
That's true.
Geum-sil, are you just going to give up like this
when she's the heir of a hundred million dollars?
We couldn't even dream of a family like that unless it was your friend's daughter.
There are plenty of lawyers around lately. We have nothing else to offer.
The only thing is Jang-go's title as a lawyer.
I guess.
Geum-sil, we've got nothing to lose.
Just be straightforward. "What do you think about my son?"
Jang-go is handsome.
Your friend's daughter might like Jang-go better than that congressman's son.
You're right.
I can't watch Jang-go rot in this tiny office any longer.
Geum-sil, let's come up with a good plan to get Jang-go married to that family.
After hearing your words, I don't think it's time to give up yet.
Of course not!
(Kimchi cup ramen)
Listen to me carefully.
This is my mother's ring.
When you go to South Korea, make sure you find my father.
His name is Kim-
Grandma. Grandma, what's wrong?
Grandma.
Grandma, what's wrong?
Yes. Yes, Yoo-sung.
Grandma, someone is here.
Who can it be?
Who is it?
Hello.
How do you like it here?
Oh, dear.
Come eat at our restaurant.
No, it's all right.
It's better for the child to eat something other than ramen.
It's fine, so come on.
It's fine.
I'm grateful for your offer.
Don't be like that, and come on.
Mr. Kim who has let you stay in this place
will be coming soon, so you can say hi to him.
Are you talking about the owner of this place?
(Deokcheonok)
Just leave it alone. My goodness.
Just leave them.
I wanted to pay back for the delicious noodles. I'm sorry. I'm very clumsy at this.
It's not a problem.
I'm glad you thought they were delicious.
Hello.
She's the person who Mr. Jung told us about.
Oh, I see.
I heard you suffered quite a bit.
Still, if you want to live in this country, you must stay alert from now on.
Yes. Thank you so much.
I don't know how I can repay you for this.
Where in North Korea did you come from?
I came from Pyeongyang.
I see.
Who did you come with?
My daughter and my grandson.
My daughter went to work.
You don't have any other family members?
Well...
Oh, I see.
It might be very uncomfortable,
but please rest comfortably here until you find a place to go.
Yes. Thank you very much.
Grandma!
You look very smart.
I should give you some money.
No, sir.
It's fine.
Eat a lot and grow up strong and healthy.
Yes, sir.
Good boy.
Say thank you.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Bye.
Geez. She looks very gentle and calm.
Goodness.
How did she end up that way?
The lawyer on the third floor helped them get a part of their security deposit back.
Really?
He's a very nice fellow.
According to Mr. Jung, while they were escaping, her son and husband died.
Goodness.
What is going on?
Geez.
How much longer must this continue for?
Goodness.
Hello! Here are your samples.
Hello, ma'am! Here are your samples! Bye!
Hello, ma'am. These are the samples. Can you reform them?
I'll do it nicely for you.
Thank you!
Kim Mi-poong, what's wrong with you?
Thanks to Jang-go, you're able to get part of your security deposit back.
And it's very fortunate that Jang-go doesn't recognize me when I'm in this state.
Kim Mi-poong.
Get a hold of yourself.
Cheer up.
You need to protect mom and Yoo-sung.
You can do it!
It's been a while since I came to Macau, but I
haven't been able to look around the city yet.
We met like this, so can't you give me a tour of Macau?
Mr. Lee,
it's Kim Mi-poong.
Thank you so much for helping me.
I don't know if you'll like this or not, but please enjoy.
Oh, my!
Mi-poong, what are you doing here?
Hello.
Well, I was just...
Did you bring those for me?
Yes, well. The thing is...
I was so grateful.
And you wouldn't accept any payment.
But I was very sorry and grateful.
I was slightly hungry anyways, so I bought some beer and snacks.
Hold on.
Let's see.
There are the fish cake skewers I like.
Then enjoy.
Mi-poong.
Let's eat together.
No, I'm fine!
I'm full and-
Oh, my.
What's wrong with my stomach?
It didn't make that sound because I'm hungry!
Sometimes my stomach does that on its own.
I'm really full.
Oh, that's right.
I forgot to tell you something important.
Something important?
Yes. Come inside.
Come in.
Didn't you say you have something important to tell me?
Eat first. I'll talk while we eat.
Now tell me.
What is it?
Is something wrong?
No. Nothing is wrong.
I wanted you to eat with me. How can I eat all of this by myself?
And it seemed like your stomach was trying to tell you it was hungry.
It didn't make a sound because it was hungry! I'm serious!
I got it.
I got it, so eat first.
Eat up.
Which part of North Korea did you come from?
I came from Pyeongyang.
Pyeongyang?
I know people from there.
By any chance, do you know Kim Yeong-cheol and Kim Seung-hee?
Who?
Kim Yeong-cheol and Kim Seung-hee.
Do you know them?
No, I don't.
How would I know them?
You're from Pyeongyang, so how can you not know them?
Just because I'm from Pyeongyang doesn't mean I know everyone there.
There are many people who live there.
But still, you're the same age as them.
Do you really not know them?
I said I don't know them. Why do you keep asking me?
Do you know everyone who lives in Seoul?
I'll be going now.
Good-bye.
Did I ask her something I shouldn't have?
He didn't forget about me.
He still remembers me.
I'm sorry for lying to you.
But...
I don't want to show you this side of me.
And now I'm not...
the Kim Seung-hee you used to know.
I said I don't know them. Why do you keep asking me?
Do you know everyone who lives in Seoul?
Geez.
Did she have to get so angry when all I asked her was if she knew those people?
No. What am I thinking right now?
Mi-poong can't be Seung-hee.
I should just sleep.
Yes.
I have nothing to lose.
Just because there's a goalkeeper doesn't mean I can't make a goal.
I need to find out how Hee-ra's blind date went.
Mom, take your medicine.
I'm sorry for being sick in this situation.
Mom, come on.
How can you be sorry for having a cold?
Then everyone in the world would have to be sorry.
Right, Yoo-sung?
Yes!
Still, I can take Yoo-sung to kindergarten, so you go on to work.
I said I'll do it.
You need to get better so that I can gain strength.
Today, take your medicine and get plenty of rest.
I bought porridge, too, so make sure you eat it.
Okay, mom?
Okay.
I'm going to be late for kindergarten.
You won't be late. The next bus will be here soon.
What if it doesn't?
Then should we have a bet to see if the bus comes soon or not?
Loser gets a clout on the forehead.
Mi-poong.
Hello.
Are you going somewhere?
Hop in. I'll give you a ride.
It's fine. The bus will take us there in no time.
Thank you!
Kim Yoo-sung!
If the bus doesn't come soon, I'll be late!
Hurry up and get in, aunt!
Hurry up and get in.
Put on your seat-belts. We'll be leaving now.
Wow! Mister, your car is so nice!
Aunt, I wish we had a car, too.
Wait a little bit. When I make a lot of money, let's buy a car.
Really?
Of course!
Then let's buy a red car.
You got it.
Instead, you need to eat all your food at school today.
You can't leave leftovers like yesterday.
Can't I leave just a little bit?
I don't want to eat.
If you don't eat, you'll turn into a dry fish!
What's that?
Huh?
That's...
A bony pollack.
A pollack that you rip up into pieces and make into a soup.
Please stop the car.
We're almost here.
Oh? We have to go a little further.
Please stop the car. Hurry!
Are you sure this is the right place?
Yes.
This is the right place.
We need to get off here.
Thank you for the ride.
Yoo-sung, let's go.
That little tadpole is driving me nuts!
If I'm a tadpole, you're a fish! A fish!
What? A fish?
Yes! A fish! A bony pollack!
If you bully my brother again,
I'll rip you up into pieces and make you into soup!
Got it?
If you don't eat, you'll turn into a dry fish!
By any chance, do you know Kim Yeong-cheol and Kim Seung-hee?
(Kindergarten)
-Bye, Yoo-sung! -Bye, aunt!
Kim Seung-hee.
What are you doing here?
You're Seung-hee, aren't you?
Kim Seung-hee.
What are you talking about?
You're a very strange person.
Is this how South Korean men flirt with women?
You followed me all the way here.
Are you a stalker?
If you keep doing this, I'll look for another lawyer.
I'm sorry.
I'm busy, so I'll leave first.
What do I do?
(Mr. Yang)
Who can I borrow money from?
Young-soon.
No. Her husband is really strict, so I won't
even be able to get five hundred from her.
Hee-kyung.
If I borrow money from her, rumors will start flying within a day.
Gosh. What do I do?
Ms. Ma, please come out.
-What is it? -Some men are kicking the gate and demanding for you to come out.
What?
Wow, Ms. Ma.
You live in such a nice house, but you won't pay me back?
I live in a semi-basement because of horrible
people like you who won't pay my money back.
-I'm trying to come up with the money- -Forget it.
I have no choice but to get the money from your husband.
Mr. Yang, I'll pay you back the money with interest this week. Okay?
Really! I'm serious!
-My husband can never know! -Let go of me!
Oh my goodness!
Oh my goodness! Chung-ja!
Chung-ja!
What are you doing to my friend?
Chung-ja, what's going on?
Who are those people?
-What happened? -Geum-sil...
Hold on.
My husband, father, and kids can never know about what happened today.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Are you okay now?
Thank you so much, Geum-sil.
$30,000 must be a lot of money to you.
Yet, you let me borrow it so suddenly.
But what's going on?
Why would you need to borrow money from such people?
Geum-sil,
appearance can be deceptive.
Appearance can be deceptive?
What do you mean?
So what if I inherit a hundred million dollars later on?
I have no cash right now.
No cash.
Elder must give you living expenses for maintaining the household.
Yes, he does.
But it's only $10,000. That's all.
She gets $10,000 for living expenses?
But that's not enough, so she's in debt?
If I combine that with my husband's salary,
I'll have about $15,000 in living expenses.
What? A month's living expenses is $15,000?
But I need to manage such a big house,
and you even saw my mother causing trouble.
I had to pay for Hee-ra's tuition to study abroad.
$15,000 a month is nothing. I'm living in a bottomless pit.
How can $15,000 a month not be enough?
To be honest, these days, a thousand dollars is nothing.
Is there anything to buy with a hundred dollars?
Of course not. You can use that money up so
fast that there will be a hole in your wallet.
That's right!
I'm paying this and that, which is how I ended up here.
Who would understand my feelings?
You're the one I can tell this to.
So that's what happened.
But Geum-sil...
nobody else knows I live like this.
-So... -All right. I got it.
I won't tell a soul.
Chung-ja, if you need to borrow money from now on, tell me.
It would be better than borrowing small amounts of money here and there.
I won't be able to let you borrow too much, but I can help you out this much.
Geum-sil, thank you for your kind words.
You're the best!
Should I ask how her daughter's blind date with the congressman went?
No, no, no.
Now is not the right time.
Hee-Ra!
Hello.
Hi. You're dressed so nicely. Did you go somewhere?
How did it go? Did you decide to meet him again?
Mom, I'm never going on a blind date again.
You didn't reject him, did you?
I did. I told him that I don't like him and that he should never contact me again.
So what if he's a congressman's son? So what if he's a dermatologist?
He's shorter than I am!
He has to be taller than be!
And what about his face?
The height and face are not important!
He's a congressman's son!
He's a dermatologist!
Height and face are important to me.
Don't you think so, Ms. Hwang?
That's right. If he doesn't have either, it would be difficult.
Right?
How can you kiss a guy who looks like that?
Would you want to kiss or sleep with a guy who looks like fermented soybean?
You can just close your eyes and kiss him! It's not such a big deal!
If you like him so much, then you should just get married to him!
What did you say?
What is she so happy about?
Grandma!
Grandma, what are you doing here?
Hee-dong.
You want me to stay here?
It'll be better than staying at a motel.
You can watch TV with other people. There's food here, and you can wash, too.
All right.
I'm not in the position to be picky right now.
When the time is right, I'll talk to mom for you.
If she's going to buy me a place to live, tell her
to get me an apartment in Gangnam. All right?
All right.
Hello?
Oh, that house was successfully auctioned off?
All right.
Bye.
Verbal abuse is another type of violence.
Seung-hee!
How dare a young boy like you you act indecently?
You piece of trash!
Yeong-cheol's mother?
Seung-hee's mother?
(Seoul Law Office)
I won't leave until I hear the music!
You're going to spend the night here because of that superstition?
-It's a ghost! -It's a ghost!
Hurry up!
Open the door!
Wasn't that really the melody of our fate?
(Lawyer Lee Jang-go)
You're Seung-hee, aren't you?
That Kim Seung-hee I know?
Subtitles by OnDemandKorea