Subtitles by OnDemandKorea
(Episode 40)
Yes! Yes!
- That way! - Is this fun?
Can't you tell? It's freaking fun!
- Yes! That's right! - "Freaking fun?"
Does that mean it's not fun?
Oh my god.
Are you a foreigner?
What?
Totally awesome! The best! It's freaking fun!
Really?
- That's it! That way! - To the right! Oh my gosh!
How did it go?
Kim Dae-hoon isn't here.
Is this the right place?
He isn't there yet?
Hold on. Hang up.
(Dad)
- That's right! Good! - He's good! Hurry! To the front!
Mister, isn't someone calling you?
Huh?
Someone is calling you.
Oh, right.
You play this.
Hello?
Dad, where are you? You promised to meet me! How can you not be here yet?
Okay! I'm on my way!
Okay. I'm sorry. Sorry!
Kim Dae-hoon?
Yes.
But who are you?
You're leaving now?
Okay. Call me when you're done.
Nothing can go wrong.
- I'm looking for someone. - Bye.
Buy some rice cakes. They're two dollars each.
Please give me two portions of dumplings.
Oh, no. The dumplings are all sold out.
Already?
I came all the way from Yeongdeungpo just to buy them.
I'm so sorry.
It's too bad then. I'll come next time.
I'll prepare more dumplings next time.
Please come back.
Hi, Mi-poong. It's me.
Mom, I have a lot of work today, so I won't be able to pick Yoo-sung up.
What do we do?
Of course I'll pick him up then. There's nothing to worry about.
You're not doing any rough labor behind my back just to make money, are you?
Of course not.
Did you sell a lot of kimbap and dumplings today?
I still have kimbap left over, but the dumplings were sold out a while ago.
I think our dumplings are good. Everyone wants to buy them.
Really? Then we should make more dumplings!
Yes, we should.
I'll see you at home.
Be safe.
- Buy rice cakes. They're two dollars. - It's cold!
Do you have any dumplings?
The dumplings are all sold out.
Then please give me two rows of kimbap.
All right.
- That will be four dollars. - Here you go.
Please look at this.
- (We're looking for someone) - What's this?
It's a flier for a missing person.
If you find someone like this, please contact the number here.
- Sure. - Thank you. Bye.
Who's that?
Oh, my. Isn't that Ms. Joo?
Oh, dear. I heard they had lost their security deposit in a fraud.
Oh my goodness. It's cold, but she's selling kimbap on the streets.
Oh, no.
- The first project. - What will happen?
Oh my goodness!
This is hilarious!
It's so funny!
Your mouth will rip apart from all the laughing.
Mother, watch this with me.
It's so funny!
Look at Jung Jun-ha and Park Myung-soo. They're hilarious!
What a good life you have.
Some people struggle to make a living on the cold streets.
You get to sit here in the warm house eating tangerines and laughing at other people.
You don't want to see me laugh. Fine then.
Delivery!
- Please put it here. - Okay.
- Good. - What's all this?
Bye.
Why did you buy so many quinces?
Make quince tea.
With all of these?
Yes.
Dice them into thin slices. Put your heart into making it.
Mother, we can just buy tea in the market these days. Why did you buy all of these?
Is buying it from the store and making it at home the same thing?
Mother, it takes a lot of hard work to cut a quince up.
It takes more work than cutting pumpkins.
If I told you to do it, you should just do it.
How dare you talk back to your mother-in-law.
Besides, would it be harder than making a hundred cabbages into kimchi?
Hurry up and do it!
For how much longer is she going to mention the hundred cabbages of kimchi?
But when will I be able to cut up all of these?
Here's your snack-
Where did he go?
We're in big trouble!
Mr. Kim's son is gone!
My father-in-law?
- Isn't he in his room?- No.
I went to his room to give him his snack, but he wasn't
there, so I checked upstairs, but he wasn't there either.
Did he say he was going somewhere?
No. He was definitely in his room earlier.
What do we do?
What's wrong? What happened?
My father-in-law is missing.
What? Are you serious?
- Oh, no! - Where did he go?
Fortunately, thanks to Ms. Park's quick decision, the new products were
able to come out right away, so the company didn't suffer much losses.
Good work.
Thank you, sir.
From now on, make sure that the company information isn't leaked.
- Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
What do you mean my dad is missing?
What? Dae-hoon is missing?
What happened? Tell us the exact details.
Well...
he was playing games and watching TV in the living room.
He wasn't there though.
I went to his bedroom to give him his snack, but he wasn't there.
You really didn't see my dad leaving the house?
Yes.
- There wasn't anything strange either? - Of
course not. There wasn't anything strange at all.
Father really did leave the house by himself.
- What? Let me see. - Sure.
- Rewind it again. - Okay.
Judging from his expression, he seemed pretty keyed up to go somewhere.
What if he went to a nearby arcade or playground?
That seems possible, sir.
But why hasn't he come home yet?
His phone is off, too.
- We'll go look for him. Hee-dong, let's go. - Okay.
Grandfather, you should stay home. It's cold outside.
Mother and I will go find him.
Being cold isn't the problem right now.
I need to go find my son.
Dae-hoon!
Father!
Did you see a man with glasses and white hair who speaks in a North Korean dialect?
No, I didn't.
- Okay. - Thank you.
He's not here!
- Dae-hoon! - Father!
What happened? Did you see Dae-hoon?
- No, we didn't. - Oh, no. Where on earth did he go?
- Grandfather! - Mr. Kim, are you okay?
Where did he go?
He probably went somewhere.
Just wait a little bit.
These situations happen very often.
He's over sixty years old. He'll be able to find his way home.
He came from China just recently, and he's suffering from memory loss, too.
He only has memories until he's ten years old. That's why we're doing this.
Dae-hoon doesn't know his way around.
He doesn't know anything about Seoul.
He doesn't have any money either.
His phone is off as well.
Please help us. My dad is like a ten-year-old child.
Okay. We'll look into it.
Don't worry. Please go home and wait.
Oh, hi, Won-bin!
- Did you eat? - No.
Then should I buy you bread or black bean noodles?
No, it's okay.
I didn't come here to eat.
I came here to sincerely talk to you.
Have a seat.
Sincerely talk to me?
Oh, it's because you don't know what to call me, right?
I was okay with you calling me Nam-yi.
But since your dad told me not to call me that...
How about Ms. Lee then?
I cannot allow you and my father to date.
What?
So you're against our relationship?
Yes.
Why?
You like me though.
Do you hate me?
No, I like you.
Then why are you against us?
I like you, but I don't want you to be my fathers girlfriend.
I really don't want you to be my mom.
Why not?
If I'm lacking in anything, or if there's something
about me you don't like, tell me. I'll fix it.
No, you don't have to do that.
I just don't want my father to have a girlfriend.
Then you...
want your dad...
to be alone for the rest of his life?
Why is he alone?
He has me, my grandmother, and my mom in heaven.
I just want you to remain as an employee of this store and my friend.
Do you mean that?
Yes.
Nam-yi. Nam-yi.
Won-bin, what's wrong with her? What happened?
Did you fight with her?
Of course not. All I did was tell her my honest feelings.
Your honest feelings?
What did you say?
That I didn't want her to become your special girlfriend.
Didn't you say a man only has one love?
What?
I hope you'll stick to your words.
I'll be going to the academy now.
Mother, are you taking those somewhere?
Yes, you don't need to know where.
How can you take those to someone else?
I hurt my wrist making those. Look.
Can't you see I put a patch here?
There are people struggling to sell kimbap in the streets in this cold weather.
And you're making a great fuss about making quince tea in a warm house?
Goodness.
If I had forced you to make a hundred cabbages into
kimchi, you would've gotten admitted to the hospital.
How long are you going to talk about the hundred cabbages of kimchi?
Until the day I die! Happy?
Who on earth is struggling to sell kimbap in the streets?
Is it...?
Oh my god! My coat!
Oh my goodness! What are you doing here?
Ms. Joo, what are you going through?
Oh, dear. I'm too ashamed to look at you.
Still, I stopped by because I couldn't just ignore you.
No. I wore a lot of clothes, so I'm fine.
I sell a lot of dumplings, so that's a lot of fun.
Then I'm glad.
Let's go inside and have some warm tea. You can't be out here. It's too cold for you.
No. Don't mind me at all.
I came here to give you something.
They're not much, but I came here to give these to you.
Oh, dear. What are they? Oh, they're quince tea!
My goodness. How did you manage to bring these in this cold weather?
I can't believe this.
Oh, it's cold.
Mother.
Who did you give the quince tea, which I hurt myself making, to?
Why do you want to know?
I gave it to someone who deserves it.
The one who deserves it is Mi-poong's mom?
How can you do that?
I wouldn't feel so wronged if you had given it to an orphanage or a nursing home.
What? Did you follow me?
Yes. I followed you because you were acting strange.
Because I thought you were taking it to them.
Are you crazy?
Do you feel so wronged about making quince tea?
What's the big deal about giving them the quince tea?
Mother, look at my wrist.
I couldn't even lift my spoon earlier because of the pain from making that.
But how can you give it to that woman?
We have nothing to do with her anymore!
Are you really asking me because you don't know the answer to that?
I was scared you would drop to the pits of hell after you died. That's why I
did this. Are you saying you don't understand my deep meaning behind this?
Do you really not know?
I don't. I really hate being linked to them in any way. How could you do this to me?
I really can't live like this with you anymore.
I really can't!
Okay, fine!
Let's end this once and for all!
I can't live with an inconsiderate fool like you for an hour longer, so get out.
Get out of this house at once, you awful wench!
Mom! Geum-sil! What's wrong with the two of you?
You shouldn't be so obnoxious to people who are working hard to make a living!
It is an old cow's notion that she never was a calf.
Do you know you're the old cow?
How is there not even one day of peace around here?
Things are just getting worse and worse.
Where on earth did he go in this cold weather?
Don't worry too much.
The police are looking for him, so he'll be found soon.
Dae-hoon doesn't know anything about the streets of Seoul.
He doesn't have any money either.
In this cold winter...
What if he freezes to death in this cold weather?
Grandfather, don't say such a thing.
Yes, grandfather. Don't say that. Father will be back soon.
I think he went to get some fresh air because
he felt stuffy to just be inside the house.
He's a bright boy- I mean, he's smart...
so he'll come back for sure.
But why isn't he answering his phone?
I'd feel much better if I could just get in touch with him.
We're locating his phone right now, so wait just a little bit longer.
All right...
This is the ship, right? Is everything prepared according to the plan?
Why is the van door open?
Where did he go?
What the hell are you doing?
Look for him over there! You go that way! You, follow me!
Go that way!
- Look for him back there! - Yes, sir!
Hey, you.
What are you doing to my truck?
I'm looking for someone.
Get out of here.
Search for him back there!
Is this Kim Dae-hoon's cell-phone?
Yes! This is my son's cell-phone!
Where did you find this?
In the alley near the stationary store before the big street.
Then this means my dad passed by the alley.
It seems like he had dropped his phone while he was passing by.
Please show us the CCTV in that alley right now.
The thing is...
There's a CCTV in front of the stationary store, but
there aren't any near the alley where he disappeared.
What?
There are no CCTVs in that area?
Yes.
Mr. Kim.
But there's someone who has witnessed Kim Dae-hoon today.
A witness?
Yes. A fourth-grade boy played games with him today.
He said that Kim Dae-hoon got a phone call and ran off.
Did that kid say that my son said anything else?
No, I don't think so.
That phone-call is suspicious.
Please find out who made that phone-call to him.
It's probably me. I had called him.
According to the kid, he said Dae-hoon had run off after getting the phone-call,
so I'm pretty sure it wasn't from you.
Anyways, we'll know when we see the history of phone-calls.
We'll call you after we investigate it further.
My son should be able to find his house. Something definitely went wrong.
I'll widen the search area and try to help you as much as I can.
Good-bye.
- Bye. - Bye.
Dae-hoon, where did you go? Dae-hoon!
- Grandfather. - Dae-hoon.
We're in trouble.
Oh my goodness. My heart is thumping madly. I can't breathe.
I won't be able to endure this even if I have ten hearts.
They wouldn't suspect you, would they?
Of course not.
Why does there have to be a witness?
What would we have done if he had told the little
boy he was on his way to meet his daughter?
Cold sweat started to drip down my back when he said there was a witness.
I almost fainted.
Shin-ae, do you think ship departed to China?
Did those people call you?
- Not yet. - Why not?
The ship should have departed already! They should have already called you by now!
What if something went wrong?
Mother, just stay quiet!
Hello?
Did the ship leave?
What?
You lost him?
How can you say that?
Find him right now!
What is it? What happened?
Oh my goodness...
Oh, I need to go!
My shoe!
Darn it!
Where am I?
Father!
Mother!
I'm here, mother.
Yoo-sung!
Uncle!
Come here! Have you been doing well?
Of course I've been doing well. What about you, uncle?
I've been doing well, too.
Ta-da!
- I bought chicken. - Yes! It's chicken!
Grandma, it's chicken!
What about Mi-poong?
Oh, she went to her part-time job.
Work? What kind of part-time job?
She works at a convenience store.
Oh.
Grandma. Uncle. When are we going to eat chicken?
Chicken? Should we eat it now?
- Sit down, Jang-go. - Okay.
Let's eat chicken.
Come here.
You didn't eat dinner yet?
- It's good to see you. - It's really great to see you.
- You're the same. - I know he is!
Let's congratulate our friend Lee Chang-ho for
becoming the Korean branch manager of KALMA. Cheers!
- Cheers! - Thank you.
Seeing you guys makes me feel like I'm really in Korea.
Chang-ho, are you back for good?
Not yet. If things work out, that could become possible.
Chang-ho, why didn't you get married yet?
It's not because of Hee-ra, is it?
Jo Mee-ryung!
Why would you say such a thing?
I'm not sure. Anyways, I heard you got married, Hee-ra. What does your husband do?
Oh, my husband?
He's a free-lancer artist.
I see.
Excuse me. Let me take this call.
Hi, it's me, Jang-soo.
Baby, baby, my baby!
I ended practice early, so I came to pick you up right away. I did well, didn't I?
You're at Summer Winter, right?
I'm right in the front.
You're right in the front?
Don't come here, Jang-soo.
Go home first.
What? Why?
I want to say hi to your friends.
And I'm too nervous to let you ride the cab alone at night.
I said I'm really fine!
So don't come in and just go home first. Okay?
Hello? Hee-ra? She hung up already?
I'll just go by myself then.
Today is a great day! Let's eat up!
Hee-ra!
Hello.
May I join you?
There's a seat just for me!
Hee-ra, I came pretty fast, didn't I?
So are you saying you did the right thing by
dressing like this to come see my friends?
What did I do?
And what's wrong with my outfit?
It's not like I'm naked.
How can you say that after seeing my friends?
My friend Chang-ho is the branch manager of the famous global company KALMA.
My friend Mi-ryung's husband is the director of a plastic surgery hospital.
Eun-mi's husband is a prosecutor.
Now I see what you're trying to say.
So you're saying you were embarrassed by me in front of your friends.
Are you embarrassed of a no-name actor like me?
When did I say that?
That's what you were saying!
Why did you come? I told you not to come, but you ignored me and came anyways!
If you had listened to me and not came, then we
wouldn't have this problem in the first place!
Oh my gosh. Are you guys fighting?
Yeah. It's about time you two had a fight.
What's wrong with my outfit?
The key of fashion is the face anyways.
Is that why she's mad?
Did I see something wrong?
What's wrong with me?
I should just go buy Hee-ra's favorite ice cream.
- Kim Mi-poong! - Oh my god!
- What were you doing all this time? - Jang-go!
What are you doing here at this hour?
You scared me!
What were you doing until this time?
You have no fear.
What if something happens to you at night?
I can protect my worry, so worry about yourself.
Do you have nothing else to do but stay here at this hour?
Mi-poong, you're going to get sick if you overwork yourself.
What kind of part-job ends at this time of night?
Why should I tell you that?
What's this smell?
Hey! Are you...
working on fishing boats?
What?
What kind of smell are you talking about?
And what is it to you if I ride a boat or a plane? Don't mind me, and just go home!
This won't do.
I understand you need to work, but you can't do this
kind of job where it ends late. Change your job.
Jang-go, you really don't have to worry about me, so don't do this.
At this rate, you're the one who will get sick.
Hurry up and go home.
What if she's really working on a fishing boat?
It can't be true.
- Mom. - Mi-poong, try this dumpling.
It's hot, so be careful.
I think we might have made too many dumplings.
I'm worried we might not be able to sell them all today.
Mom, you don't have to worry about such a thing.
These dumplings are much tastier than the ones you made yesterday.
- Really? - Yes.
The seasoning is just right, and the dumpling shell is chewy.
The dumplings are to die for.
Don't make me blush.
Eat some more.
I'm going to be late. I'm going to work now. Do your best today, too!
- Watch out for cars. - Okay.
Bye. Be safe.
Where is she going?
(We're looking for a person/ Name: Kim Dae-hoon/ Age: 67-years-old)
- Mi-poong. - Yes?
You know the fish shop in front of the market entrance, right?
Take these boxes to them quickly. They're very demanding.
Yes, all right.
- This is outrageous. So outrageous. - Oh my gosh!
Jang-go, what are you doing here?
Is this the convenience part-time job you were talking about?
Oh my gosh. You're like a goblin. You appear everywhere I go and get in the way.
Let's go home.
Don't be ridiculous. Get out of the way.
I'm on my way to a delivery. I'm busy!
All right. All right.
Move.
Where do I need to go?
- Jang-go! - Weren't you in a hurry?
Where do I have to go?
How did you know I was here?
Did you follow me?
Do you think my nose is for decoration purposes only?
Why are you working here while lying to your mother about it?
It's obvious. Why would you even ask me?
This place pays you more than other places.
That shouldn't even be a reason! Even men have a hard time with this job!
Look around and see if there are any other women around!
- There are women over there! - I'm sure there are.
Jang-go, I'm strong.
I'm doing this because I can.
You keep talking back to me.
I'm not in the position to be picky about jobs right now.
I need money to make ads to find my father. I need a lot of money.
Okay, fine.
I'll tell your mother you're working at the fish market.
If she approves, I'll let you work here. That works, doesn't it?
- Jang-go! Are you really going to tell my mom? - Yes.
If you tell my mom, I'll make you bleed from both noses!
Just don't work here then!
Didn't you hear what I said? I'm not in that kind of position right now!
Are you listening to me or not?
Don't work here!
Oh my gosh!
If you were my sister, I would have beaten you up.
Hello, sir! Yes, I'm on my way! Bye!
Jang-go, I'm begging you! Please!
You can never tell my mom! Never! You can never tell her!
Hey.
What are you doing here?
Mister, please find my father for me.
My father's name is Kim Deok-cheon.
My father lives in Seoul.
Then what's your name?
My name is Kim Dae-hoon.
Should I buy you that steamed bun?
Yes!
- Let's go inside. - Thank you.
(Store Contract)
What's this?
A store contract.
I looked for it urgently, but it's quite nice. The location is great, and
it's near here, too. Also, it's empty, so you can open up right away.
Why are you giving this to me?
I thought it would be nice if you and Mi-poong opened up your own business.
I was thinking about it, and you can open up a store that sells side dishes or...
Oh! You're good at making dumpling soup. You can
sell dumplings. What do you think?
Jang-go, did you discuss this with Mi-poong already?
No.
You know what she's like. Do you think she'll accept this?
Then I can't either.
How can I accept something she doesn't know about?
Thank you, but take it back.
I didn't know you would do this.
If I tell you this, Mi-poong will make me bleed from both noses.
Mother.
You didn't know Mi-poong works at the fish market, do you?
What?
Mi-poong works at the fish market?
Yes.
It's hard for even men to do.
No matter how many times I tell her to quit, she won't listen to me.
That's why I came to you.
Please take this.
If you feel uncomfortable taking it, just think of it as alimony.
It would be terrible if she got hurt while doing such hard labor.
Mother.
Jang-go, thank you.
I feel ashamed, but I'll accept it gratefully.
And I'll make sure to work hard and pay you back with interest.
So you're accepting it, right?
I should go before you change your mind.
Mother, please make sure Mi-poong won't come see me with this contract.
I'll be going now!
Bye!
Grandfather, you're going to get really sick at this rate.
What will I do if something happens to you, too?
You need strength in order to find dad.
Okay.
What if someone kidnapped Dae-hoon?
Kidnap?
Yes, kidnap!
Otherwise, why would we not be able to find him?
He wasn't kidnapped. If he was, we would've received a call for ransom right now.
He's right, grandfather.
Dad must have lost his way home. We reported it, so we'll be able to find him soon.
So please eat.
I don't even know what happened...
to my poor, mentally unstable son in this cold winter.
How will I be able to eat this?
Grandfather.
That old man isn't even drinking a drop of water. What if he passes away like that?
You're not even on the family registry yet!
I think you made the wrong decision this time.
Still, it's better that he's gone this way.
That's true.
That old man won't die so easily until he finds his son.
We need to make sure he survives until your name is on the family registry.
What if Mi-poong's father comes back here?
He only rode around in a car, so he won't even know our address.
He won't be able to find us.
How could someone with a ten-year-old mind find his way back home? He'll never find us.
Oh my goodness. If you watch TV, those kind of people get sold to shrimp boats.
It'd be perfect if that happened to him!
Oh, my back.
Stop pooping!
If you keep pooping, I'm going to set your butts on fire!
Mom.
How can you accept this?
I wasn't going to accept it at first.
But we don't have anything.
We need to work hard to find your father.
That's why I accepted it.
Still...
How could we accept this from Jang-go?
Mi-poong, I know it's shameless of us, but let's just accept this.
Jang-go told me to take this as alimony. If we don't
accept it, imagine how uncomfortable he'll feel.
He gave it to me because he knew you would reject it.
Mom.
Mi-poong, let's work hard and pay him back with interest. Let's just do that, huh?
(Father's Dumplings)
(Dumpling soup, meat dumplings, kimchi dumplings, noodle dumplings)
(North Korean Defector Hometown Alumni/ We wish you the best)
- Welcome! - Welcome to Father's Dumplings! Have a seat.
- Please give us two plates of kimchi dumplings. - Please hold on.
- Hello. Please give me three packages of dumplings. - Sure. Please hold on.
Please take a seat and wait a moment.
- I'm here! - Jang-go, welcome!
- Mother, please give me twelve packages of dumplings. - Twelve?
Yes, I'm supposed to buy lunch for my co-workers.
And here.
Okay. Please hold on.
Sure.
Kim Mi-poong, here you go.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
But aren't you supposed to be working right now?
How can you just be here then?
What's this? Are you nagging me like you're my wife?
Wife? No way. I was just saying this because you might get fired.
Why? Are you worried I might get fired?
Do you want me to help you?
Hello.
- Grandma! - Hello, ma'am.
Oh, Jang-go, you're here, too?
Of course!
I came to congratulate the opening. What about you?
I came to promote this dumplings store to the senior center.
Mi-poong, give me eight packs of dumplings.
Yes, grandma!
- Jang-go, these are meat dumplings. - Okay.
- Enjoy. - Please give me two packs to take home.
Sure!
Enjoy!
- Please sit over there. - Okay.
- Please give us two plates of dumplings. - Okay.
Here you go.
These are kimchi dumplings.
Hello. Hi, Soo-jung.
Why did you come again?
I saw a storybook at the book store and thought of Soo-jung.
Soo-jung, I brought you a present.
Thank you.
Did you eat yet?
My wife sells these. I brought them so that you could try them.
Why are you doing this?
I don't need these, so take them back!
I'll go, so eat them.
The caretaker has to eat better than the patient.
Bye, Soo-jung!
Bye!
The dumplings are delicious! They're aromatic and light.
You're right, aunt. Mi-poong's store will do well.
You guys should go out and help them sometimes.
- Of course! - Dumplings! Dumplings! Dumplings! Dumplings!
Are you eating dumplings?
- Mom, try it. - Okay.
It's delicious. Where did you get it?
Grandma bought these from sister-in-law's dumpling store.
Whose?
Sister-in-law's?
You mean Mi-poong?
Yes...
Mother, why did you go see that family again?
I went to see them with my own two feet, so why are you getting angry?
You won't even go help them, so why would you care if I go see them or not?
Mother, if you keep doing this, both Jang-go
and Mi-poong won't be able to start fresh.
So please stop.
Fine.
Go and chatter all you want.
We have different goals.
I'm going to do whatever I want to achieve my goal.
My goal is to make sure Mi-poong and Jang-go get back together again.
But where did they get the money for a store when they lost their money in a fraud?
By any chance...
What's this?
It's a loan bankbook.
$30,000?
He took out $20,000 from his deposit bankbook.
Both are from the same day.
$50,000 in all.
What did he use such a large amount of money on?
He definitely bought a store for Mi-poong.
Jang-go, where are you?
Why?
You bought a store for Mi-poong, didn't you?
You loaned $30,000, withdrew $20,000 from your
account, and bought a store for them, didn't you?
Mom.
Am I right or wrong?
Did you search through my room?
So I'm right.
Fine. Bye.
Mother.
Let me ask you something.
Did Jang-go buy this store for you?
Right?
I had my doubts...
You cunning, evil thing.
You told me you were going to divorce him,
but you steal my son's money behind my back?
Of course. You got caught selling the company's information. What can't you do?
Mother, I really didn't do that.
And I'll make sure to pay Jang-go back in the future.
So please don't talk that way.
You're really funny.
If you need money, you can borrow it from a bank or anywhere else.
Why must you take money from Jang-go?
Isn't it a lie that you're borrowing it from him?
If you got a divorce, you should neatly step away from him.
You're sticking to him like a parasite. What do you think you're doing?
Mother, you're being too harsh.
I'm being too harsh?
I think you're the one who's being harsh.
You made my son into a divorcee.
If it wasn't for you, Jang-go would've married Ha-yeon
and become the son-in-law of Jang & Ko Law Firm.
If I think about that, my heart still crumbles!
I'm so relieved that I chased you out of my house.
Fine.
It's better this way.
Just take that money and get the hell away from us.
Get the hell away from my son! Go far away from him!
Don't leech off my son any longer, you got it?
Your words are too cruel.
How can you speak so cruelly to your former daughter-in-law?
I was the one who accepted that money.
I'll pay him back somehow, so please stop treating Mi-poong this way.
What did my son do to deserve all of this? Even his mother-in-law
is leeching off of him. My heart feels like it's collapsing!
You were going to pay him back?
You'll be the only woman in the world to borrow money
from her former son-in-law to open up a business!
- Mom! - If you had any shame, you wouldn't be able to do this!
Mom.
What are you doing here?
- I came here because I was so furious! - Get out.
Mi-poong, you better not leech off my son again!
- Hurry up! - I won't leave you alone then!
Let go!
Let go of me! What are you doing? Let go!
Mom, why are you doing this?
I gave that money to Mi-poong as alimony.
What? As alimony?
Why would you give her alimony? Were you the one who broke this family apart?
This house didn't have one day of peace because of her!
So why would you give her alimony?
She should give you alimony for ruining your life!
Mom, stop being obstinate.
It's because I'm upset.
Who will know about my broken heart?
Mi-poong and I didn't get a divorce because we disliked each other.
She left home because she was hurt by you!
Am I wrong?
I tried to accept her and live with her somehow for your sake.
But do you want me to allow that thief who
embarrassed our family to be my daughter-in-law?
Fine.
What's the point of talking about all of this now?
You gave it to her as alimony anyways, so it's all over now.
So back off her now.
Don't go anywhere near her.
End it with the alimony. Got it?
I'm sorry, mother.
I'm sorry, Mi-poong.
Jang-go.
We need to talk.
(Father's Dumplings)
I'm sorry.
I'll apologize on her behalf.
My mother won't come back here ever again.
You're very angry, aren't you?
Jang-go, I'm not angry.
And I don't want to fight with you about things like this anymore.
I'll make sure to work hard and do whatever I can to pay you back.
Why are you talking that way?
Why can't you realize my feelings?
What will happen if I do?
You saw what your mother did earlier.
We won't work out.
You do know our court appointment is coming up soon, right?
We'll see each other then.
And don't come back here ever again.
Ma'am, did you see a man with white hair wearing glasses?
- Where are you going? - I'm going to Seoul. Give me a ride. Please?
Go away!
Oh, that awful stench!
Business isn't doing well either! My goodness!
Go away!
Father...
Mother...
(Father's Dumplings)
It's hot!
Father...?
Father! Father!
Father!
What did she say?
It's hot!
Father! Father!
- Father! - Dae-hoon!
(Blow Breeze)
- That was your father, wasn't it? - It was him! He was right in front of my eyes!
Hurry up and open this!
Yes, that's right!
Hey! You crazy woman!
They bought those dumplings from Mi-poong's dumpling store!
What?
What is he talking about?
- You told me to come out! - Why are you making things up?
Listen to me carefully.
I'm going to tell grandfather and lock you up in the hospital.
How can you do this to me?
I'm scared, father.
Please go your way!
Kim Mi-poong, I can't live without you.
I don't want to see you ever again.