Subtitles by OnDemandKorea
- (Episode 41)
- Father!
Dae-hoon!
Father! Father!
Father! Father! Father! Father!
Father...
Mother...
Why is this dumpling so delicious?
It's hot!
Father! Father!
I'm sorry.
Father!
That was your father, wasn't it?
Yes, that was him! He was right in front
of my eyes! He really was father, mom!
- Where did he go?
- It really is him!
- Father!
- Dae-hoon!
Grandfather.
Please get up.
Mr. Kim, please eat some porridge.
You'll get very sick at this rate!
Grandfather, what will I do if
something happens to you, too?
Shin-ae, don't cry.
I'll get up.
Mr. Kim, you need to gain strength
in order to find Dae-hoon.
Yes.
Where did dad go in this cold winter?
What if something happened to him?
No, that's impossible.
It took so much effort to find him.
Grandfather.
Oh, she's definitely a fox. How the
heck is she able to cry so easily?
I can't even release one teardrop.
Hurry up and answer it.
Hello?
Pardon?
Where?
What happened?
Did they find Dae-hoon?
Or did something happen to him?
Mi-poong, are you sure that was your father?
Did you mistaken him for someone else?
How can I not recognize him?
But why can't he recognize you?
How can he not recognize who you are?
I was right next to you.
How could he not recognize us?
But the strange thing is...
father...
looked a bit strange.
I was so close to him,
but he couldn't recognize me.
On top of that, he stole a dumpling.
Mom, what if father lost his memory?
Father would have definitely searched
for us if he was in South Korea, but
he didn't. What if he couldn't find us
because he had lost his memory?
No way.
Also, his clothes were so shabby,
and he looked like one
of those homeless people
who wander around the streets.
He really was father,
but he didn't seem like father.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
If father really lost his memory, then
we must find him as quickly as possible.
I hate to think of him wandering around
on the streets in this cold weather.
You're right.
Let's find your father.
Seeing that he came to eat our dumpling,
he's probably somewhere in this area.
Let's search this whole area.
If father really did lose his memory,
he wouldn't be able to
know anything about the ads
and fliers we posted about him.
Still, someone else will see it
and contact us.
Let's write down all the characteristics
about your father to make sure
someone can contact us about him.
Okay.
(Out at the moment)
Mom, let's go underground.
There are many homeless people there.
Sure. Let's go everywhere from
the underground tunnel to the park.
- I'll carry those.
- It's fine.
Mi-poong, stick close to me.
Hello.
- Try these dumplings. They're still warm.
- Thank you.
Mister, we have a question for you.
Did you see anyone here who
speaks in a North Korean dialect?
He's my father. His name is Kim Dae-hoon.
You can't find anyone here
with just their names.
Everyone is wandering around
with their own stories.
He has big and bright eyes,
and he wears glasses.
He's in his mid-sixties,
and he's of medium height.
I don't know. I've never seen him before.
Yes, we understand.
Thank you for listening to us.
Mi-poong, let's go.
- (Father's Dumplings)
- We're looking for someone.
Where is my son Dae-hoon?
We got your call. Where is he?
He's right here.
Oh my god.
Dae-hoon.
Dae-hoon! Dae-hoon!
Dae-hoon!
Father! Father!
- Dae-hoon!
- Father!
Dae-hoon! Where did you go?
Do you know how much I was looking for you?
But why do you look like this?
Where have you been?
I don't know, father.
I was searching for you
for a long time, father!
You were searching for me?
What?
You weren't lost?
Someone had forcefully dragged you away?
- Are you saying someone had kidnapped you?
- Yes.
Who kidnapped you?
Tell us, Dae-hoon.
Tell us who had kidnapped you.
Is it someone you know?
They were men I have never met before.
Two men forced me into a van.
When I woke up, it was night.
I peeked outside and realized I was
at a sea port that was filled with ships.
Sea port?
So they were planning
to force you onto a ship?
Where is that sea port?
I don't know. I don't know where that is.
Two men were talking to another man outside.
The driver was snoring while he was sleeping,
so I snuck out of the van and secretly
climbed into the back of a truck.
But that truck kept going deeper
and deeper into the woods!
The truck driver stopped the truck to go pee.
I quickly got out of
the car and ran away then.
I was so scared.
How frightened you must have been to be in the
forest all by yourself
in the middle of winter.
It's a miracle that you came back alive.
I was cold, scared, and hungry.
But this one man said he'd give me food if
I clean up cow dung, so I followed him.
Those darn cows pooed all day long!
I thought I was dying from
cleaning up all the cow dung!
Really? My goodness.
Oh, my poor Dae-hoon.
You suffered so much away from home.
So you should've just stayed home.
Why did you go out by yourself?
Shin-ae said it was your birthday,
so she wanted me to
secretly come out to plan
a surprise party for you.
That's why I had gone out.
Shin-ae, what is he talking about?
What's this about my birthday?
Dad, what are you saying?
Maybe you dreamt the whole thing.
I had an important
meeting that day, so I was at the company.
You told me to come out.
You said nobody should know
about our surprise party for
father so I should sneak out
without the housekeeper knowing.
When did I say that?
Dad, what's wrong with you?
Why are you making things up?
You told me to come out! You told me to meet
you in the alley next to the stationary store!
So why are you lying?
- Dad, what's wrong with you?
- Please calm down.
Shouldn't he go to his room and rest now?
Yes, I think father is very shocked.
Dae-hoon, go to your room.
I'm serious, father. That's why I really left.
I understand.
You'll be fine after you go to
your room and take a nap.
Let's go inside.
I'm telling the truth.
You told me that!
I'm serious.
What do we do about my dad? I'm so upset.
Are you sure you never
said that to him before?
Yes. It wasn't even
grandfather's birthday that day,
so why would I tell him such a thing?
What if he's going back and forth
between the present and past?
It seems like he had been
pretty shocked after being lost.
Hee-dong is right!
Shouldn't we admit him into the hospital?
Don't even say that.
- Well...
- Don't say that in front of Mr. Kim.
We can't live with him if he keeps
saying whimsical things like that.
Mother, didn't it seem like grandfather,
father-in-law, and
Hee-dong were suspecting me?
No. How could they suspect you?
It seemed like they thought he was saying
whimsical things while he was out of it.
Right?
Of course. They didn't
seem suspicious of you at all.
Anyways, how did he manage to come back alive?
He's indestructible!
How nice would it have
been if he could have just
cleaned up cow dung for the rest of his life?
Anyways, keep an eye on him.
His memory can't come back, so if you think
something is fishy, let me know right away.
All right. But what will we do
about that bomb from now on?
Dae-hoon.
Do you know how anxious
I was when you were gone?
I can't live without you.
I'll die.
Father, don't die. Okay?
Please live for a long, long time.
Okay.
Dae-hoon...
let's never be apart
for the rest of our lives.
Yes, father.
I'll never let go of your hand from now on.
All right.
I cried so much after losing you.
I was so cold, hungry, and scared.
But father, the truth is...
I was so hungry...
that I stole something just once.
What?
You stole something?
Yes.
I stole one dumpling and ate it.
One dumpling?
Oh my goodness. How hungry must
you have been to do something like that.
But Dae-hoon, the owner
would have understood you.
So don't blame yourself.
No, father. I really want to
pay that dumpling store back.
Sure, let's do that.
Let's go back there tomorrow and
pay them back for the dumpling.
Yes, father.
But that dumpling was so delicious.
It tasted just like the
ones mother used to make.
Really?
While I ate that dumpling...
I thought of mother...
and cried so much.
You did?
I want to eat those dumplings, too.
Dae-hoon, let's go to that
dumpling store tomorrow,
pay them back for the dumpling you stole,
and buy more dumplings to eat.
- Yes, father.
- Good.
Mom.
Are you thinking about father?
It must be because we saw those
people staying underground.
I keep thinking of so
many different possibilities.
Where is your father and what is he doing?
If he really is mentally unstable,
did he get beaten up while trying
to steal food from somewhere else?
Mom, why are you saying such nonsense?
You know father is a strong person.
If he's alive, he'll be safe.
I'm going to believe that.
Yes.
That's true, right?
Mom, how about we give out
dumplings to those homeless people
living in that underground
tunnel every single day?
We won't be able to give much,
but wouldn't father come there
one day when he hears out
we're giving out free dumplings?
Yes, that's a good idea.
We can help those in need by
giving them the dumplings we made.
It would be great if we could
find your father while doing that.
- Right?
- Yes, it's a good idea.
We will need to work harder
and make more money if
we want to give many
dumplings to the homeless.
Yes, we will.
You're a much better person than I am.
Shin-ae said it was your birthday,
so she wanted me to secretly come
out to plan a surprise party for you.
That's why I had gone out.
When did I say that?
Dad, what's wrong with you?
Why are you making things up?
You told me to come out! You told me to meet
you in the alley next to the stationary store!
So why are you lying?
Did Shin-ae really...?
No.
Why would she make up such a lie?
Of course she wouldn't.
My goodness.
Goodness.
You had witnessed your son and
wife being shot in front of your eyes.
Of course you wouldn't be sane.
Still, it's okay.
It's okay.
You just have to stay by my side.
Grandfather, are you going somewhere with dad?
I feel nervous about leaving
Dae-hoon at home by himself.
I'm going to take him
around with me for a while.
Last time I wasn't home, so that
incident occurred, but don't worry now.
I'll stick to him like a bodyguard
and take him around with me!
Chung-ja, how dare you! It doesn't matter
that he has the mind of a child right now!
What? Take him around with you?
I'm sorry.
I'll take care of him very well.
You can leave him at home, grandfather.
Mother will protect him well.
No, it's fine.
After my meeting today,
we're going to go to the
dumpling store to pay them
back for the dumpling he ate.
Dumpling?
Yes, dumpling.
It tasted exactly like the ones
my mother used to make.
- Yes.
- Father and I will go
and buy a lot of dumplings.
Okay, dad.
- Dae-hoon, let's go.
- Yes, father.
Bye.
I'll see you later.
But what if his memory comes back
while he's with Mr. Kim?
We need to separate those two somehow.
Grandfather became sensitive
because of what happened,
so let's take some time to think
about a way to solve this.
If we make the wrong move,
they might suspect us.
That's true. We did touch
the tiger's whiskers.
- Hey, bring that in here.
- Welcome- oh! Hello, ma'am!
- Hi.
- Hello.
Congratulations! I wish you success!
If you need any extra help, call me anytime.
Oh, thank you for your kind words.
- Put that up there.
- Yes, grandma.
Oh, what's this?
It's kimchi. It was fermented
very well, so I brought it.
You can use it in your kimchi dumplings.
Oh, you didn't have
to do that. Thank you.
Please have a seat. I'll prepare
a plate of dumplings for you.
Oh, dear. We're not your customers.
Just treat us comfortably.
Ms. Joo, please give me ten packs of dumplings
so I can give them to my theater colleagues.
- Sure. Please wait a moment.
- Okay.
Where's Mi-poong?
She took Yoo-sung to school.
I see.
Here you go.
- Here.
- No, you don't have to pay me.
You even brought kimchi for me.
- That's not even my kimchi. Please take it.
- Oh, no!
- Grandma, I'm going!
- Bye.
Bye!
- Ma'am...
- Just take it. It'll make
everyone feel comfortable.
All right. Thank you.
What's wrong? Do you know him?
The truth is...
I saw my husband yesterday.
What? Are you serious?
Your husband is really alive in Seoul?
I think so.
But he must be living on the streets.
Mi-poong said that
his appearance was terrible.
I feel like he'll come back again.
That's why every time a man passes by,
I can't help but check on him.
Oh my goodness!
How could something like that happen?
You don't look well.
Why? Is something wrong?
I don't know.
Nothing works out the way I want it to.
Are you holding a candle to the sun?
Who else has a better life than you?
You must be joking.
Fine. I'm sorry for complaining
when my life is perfect.
But what did you need to see me for?
I want you to find a prospective
marriage partner for Jang-go.
You said you would take responsibility and
find marriage partners for him
once he gets a divorce.
What's with you?
You said you would do this after
the consideration period is over.
Mi-poong signed the divorce papers but
continued to meet Jang-go behind my back.
And now, she even took his money.
What?
Oh my goodness.
She has no conscience whatsoever.
Mi-poong and her mother took his money
and opened up a dumpling store.
What? A dumpling store?
Yes!
I was so stunned and
frustrated thinking about how she
ruined my son's life and took
his money that I almost died!
Goodness. Of course you'd feel that way.
Didn't you do anything about it though?
You should've grabbed
her hair and ripped it off!
I really wanted to do that, but I held it in.
It's like he gave her an alimony,
so they're totally over now.
So even if I tell him to date other women,
he'll have no other choice but to.
Okay, don't worry. Just trust me.
Are you coming just now?
Hello, ma'am.
Are you standing up to go
just because I'm here?
Don't worry about me and stay here longer.
Have some dumplings as well.
- Try them.
- Mother.
Did you go to Mi-poong's dumpling store again?
That family has nothing to do with us anymore!
Whatever. I'm going with my own
two feet, so mind your own business.
Mother, that dumpling store
was bought with Jang-go's money!
Doesn't that anger you?
If you live such a hardscrabble life,
all of your blessings will disappear!
Jang-go bought that store
for them because they deserved it!
Thanks to Jang-go, Mi-poong's
family was able to meet
her father whom they
thought was dead all this time.
Jang-go will become very blessed!
What did you say? They were able to meet
her father whom they
thought was dead all this time?
Why are you so shocked?
It's my granddaughter-in-law
who found her father.
Mother, what are you talking about?
What do you mean she met her father?
She thought her father had died while
they were escapingNorth Korea,
but he came to the dumpling store,
although they did lose him.
Why would they lose him when they met?
It seems like he lost his memory.
He didn't recognize them and just ran off.
So Mi-poong and her mother are
going crazy trying to find him.
- They said they were going
to buy dumplings today.
- What's wrong?
- Chung-ja! What's wrong?
- What's wrong? Are you okay?
What's wrong with you all of a sudden?
I'm okay. I just have anemia lately.
I'll be leaving now. Bye, Geum-sil.
- Chung-ja, don't forget my favor!
- Okay...
She must be eating
all the best things in life.
Why would she have anemia? Why would
she faint all the time? My goodness.
That's odd.
Shin-ae!
Shin-ae, we're in big trouble!
What will we do?
What's all the fuss about?
I think the dumpling store Mr. Kim and his son
are going to today belongs to Mi-poong!
It's Mi-poong's dumpling store!
What? What are you talking about?
Mi-poong opened up a dumpling store.
Her dad came by the store
yesterday, but she lost him,
so she's going crazy looking for him!
Impossible.
Mr. Kim and his son wouldn't have
met Mi-poong already, would they?
No.
He was at the company.
His meeting ended just now.
Is Mr. Kim in his office?
What did you say?
All right.
What did he say?
He's not in his office, is he?
Oh my goodness. They must have
gone already. What do we do now?
Do you know where that dumpling
store is? Hurry up and find out.
Okay, I can find out. Hold on.
Geum-sil, where is that
dumpling store located?
Oh my goodness! It's true!
They even named it Father's Dumplings!
- (Father's Dumplings)
- Oh my god. Shin-ae,
what can we do about them?
I just want to set that store on fire!
We told them to America, but
they wouldn't! Why are they doing this?
He must have gone there by
coincidence while at night.
He won't be able to find this dumpling store.
Yes. He doesn't even know the Seoul streets-
No.
He's coming with Mr. Kim over there!
Come out.
I think it was somewhere here.
How did they come here? What do we do?
Mother, stay still. Stay still!
Do you think this is the wrong place, too?
This place seems right...
but it seems wrong, too...
Father, all Seoul streets look the same.
Yes.
How would you be able to memorize
a street that you only came once?
But Dae-hoon, do you remember
the name of the dumpling store?
I was so hungry back then. I only looked at
- the dumplings. I didn't see the sign.
- I see.
Let's take our time searching for it.
Since we're here, let's go
to that alley over there.
- Over there.
- Yes, father.
Hold on. I'm getting a call.
Oh, it's Shin-ae.
Hi, Shin-ae.
Grandfather, where are you? I'm sick!
Okay! Your father and
I will be home immediately!
Okay. Bye.
Father, what's wrong?
- Shin-ae seems to be very sick.
- Huh?
Let's hurry up and go.
Where is she sick? Hurry up and get in.
Good job. You did well.
Thank goodness.
Like you said, it seems like he doesn't
know where the dumpling store is.
We need to arrive at home
before grandfather does.
- Hurry up and go! Hurry!
- Okay.
You were completely fine
when I saw you at the company earlier.
What happened?
Shin-ae had acute indigestion.
She must have been very shocked
about not knowing her dad's whereabouts.
Of course she must have been.
But Shin-ae, you don't have to worry anymore.
Your father returned safely, and
something like this will never happen again.
Shin-ae, don't worry.
I'm sorry.
Okay, dad.
But you said you were going to buy dumplings.
- Did you find the dumpling store?
- No, we didn't.
Dae-hoon doesn't remember where it is at all.
Dad, mother and I will make you
delicious dumplings later on.
So don't waste your energy looking for it.
I must find it.
I really want to pay them back
for the dumpling I ate.
One dumpling doesn't cost much.
One day, you'll be able to pay them back.
Do you know how wide Seoul is?
You don't even know where it is. How will you
be able to find that small dumpling store?
But how did you know that
dumpling store is small?
Dumpling stores are usually small.
I've never seen big dumpling stores before.
Dad, later on, I'll go with you
to find the dumpling store.
- Really?
- Really.
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
- It's freezing! I'm here, mother!
- Welcome!
I came to eat lunch.
Okay. Have a seat.
Where is Mi-poong? Why are you alone?
Oh, she went to make a delivery.
- Oh.
- Sit down.
- Okay.
- This place is delicious.
- It is?
- Yeah.
- Welcome!
- Welcome! Please sit here.
What would you like?
- Dumpling soup.
- Three dumpling soup.
- Yes.
Three dumpling soup, mother!
All right.
- I'm back!
- Hi.
Jang-go.
What are you doing?
What else would I be doing?
I'm helping your mother.
Gosh, I'm busy!
What did you need to tell me?
If you're going to tell me not to
come here again, don't even start.
I'm not going to listen.
Jang-go, what's wrong with you?
Didn't you hear what I said? I told you
to never come back here again!
I told you to not even start with that.
Jang-go.
Our consideration period is
almost over. If we just go to court
and report our divorce,
we'll be completely strangers then.
So why on earth are you doing this?
If you do this, not only does it get harder
for me, but it'll get harder for you, too.
So please get over me as soon as you can.
Forget about me and go your way! Please!
Kim Mi-poong, must I tell you again?
I can't live without you.
Even now, I want to leave home
and get back together with you.
Jang-go!
Should we do that?
You saw what your mother did here yesterday.
So how can you say that?
Let's believe that time will
solve our issues with her.
When she sees us living happily with
our adorable kids, she'll come to accept us.
And when is that?
I don't want to be hurt any longer.
No.
I don't care about getting hurt, but I don't
want to see my mother getting hurt again.
So move on and have a clean, fresh start.
If we get a divorce and you meet an
amazing woman who your mother will like,
you'll be able to forget about me, a lowly
woman who works at a dumpling store.
Are you really going to talk that way?
See you at court.
I'm going to pay you back for this!
You don't even know my how I feel.
Hi, Mr. Kim.
You came early today, too.
Yes, well, when I thought about
how bored you would be without me,
I sped over here from Bundang.
Don't ever do that again! What will
I do if you get into an accident?
Mr. Kim, here is the record of today's sales.
Oh, yes.
Yes, right here.
Nam-yi, is this a six or a zero?
Where?
Here.
It's a zero.
Won-bin, aren't you hungry?
Go downstairs and eat some bread.
Call your friends over and eat as
much as you want. I'll pay for everything.
It's fine. I already bought bread.
Won-bin...
there are customers
going in and out of here,
so it's pretty noisy.
Wouldn't that bother your studies?
That's why I bought you
a pass to a study room.
A quiet and safe study room.
How about you go over there and study?
No. I study much better here.
You can return the pass to the study room.
Don't make eye-contact with each other.
I hope the two of you will quickly go back
to an employee-employer relationship.
Mr. Kim, this won't do.
Let's come up with a plan after work.
All right.
I'll see you later.
Father, don't make any dinner plans today.
Grandmother wants us to come home early
since she's making braised spicy seafood.
- Come out.
- Okay.
Yoo-sung, I'm hitting the card really hard,
but why isn't it flipping over?
I think it's because our card is really weak.
Really?
Yoo-sung, we lost all of
our cards to Jung-won today.
It's so unfair that I don't think
I'll be able to fall asleep tonight.
Don't worry, Yoo-jin. I'll go home
and make stronger cards tonight.
Do you have the paper to make strong cards?
Yes. I have plenty of strong paper at home.
Count on me.
Okay. Let's win against Jung-won tomorrow.
Okay. One day, if we try hard,
we'll be able to win many cards.
All right. Make plenty
of strong cards at home.
All right.
(We are looking for someone)
Dad, sit here.
Are you okay now? Are you feeling better?
No, I'm still sick.
Do you know why I'm sick?
Of course. You told me earlier.
You said you were sick because
you had gotten upset
when I had suddenly disappeared.
You're right.
And I'm also sick because
you keep saying whimsical things.
Whimsical things? Like what?
When did I tell you that we were
going to have a surprise party?
You did say that. That's what you said.
You told me to sneak out so we
can prepare father's surprise party.
See? You're lying right now, too.
No. You're just saying
nonsense because you're ill.
No! You really said that!
You just imagined eating
that dumpling. It's not real.
You imagined being kidnapped
and cleaning up cow dung.
Something is wrong with your head.
It's all just your imagination.
You're just making it up,
like a cartoon movie.
No!
No. It's real.
Listen to me carefully.
If you keep saying weird things
and making up stories,
I'm going to tell grandfather
to lock you up in the hospital!
Shin-ae, what's wrong?
You're my daughter.
How can you be like this to your father?
So disrespectful.
So stop giving me a hard time!
Stop saying strange things!
Got it?
Aren't you going to answer me?
I got it...
I dare you to tell grandfather
or anyone else I said this to you.
I'll get you then!
Got it?
Aren't you going to answer me?
I got it.
- What are you two talking about?
- Hee-dong!
Yes, father. What is it?
It's nothing.
I was scolding him to
not go outside by himself.
Go downstairs, dad.
Don't forget what I said. Got it?
Shin-ae,
did you get angry at your father?
I don't know.
I'm so upset because of him.
He keeps saying strange and whimsical things!
I don't know what I should do about him.
"Frailty, thy name is woman!"
"To be or not to be! That is the question!"
"Do you think all of you are so smart?
The soldiers will cut your heads off!"
"Oh, my love."
"Oh, my love! Juliet!"
Song Joo-ri! Joo-ri!
Joo-ri!
Song Joo-ri!
Joo-ri, why are you running away?
I wasn't running away. I have to go
home quickly. I was just going my way.
But what are you doing here?
My friend lives around here.
I saw you coincidentally while I was
on my way home after meeting her.
But what's the point of meeting up?
We have nothing to say to each other.
That's why I was going
to just ignore you. Really.
What about the kids? Are they doing well?
Yes, they're doing well.
What about your husband?
He's doing well, of course.
What about you? Are you doing well, too?
Of course I am. There's no reason
I wouldn't be doing well.
Okay.
As long as you're doing well, it's fine.
Yes.
I'll be going now.
Jang-soo, I hope you'll be happy, too.
Hi. It's me, Jang-soo.
You said you know Joo-ri's friend, right?
Find out how Joo-ri is doing lately.
Yes. Help me out.
Did you just come home?
Yes. I had plans with my friends.
It's been a while
since I met them,
so I went shopping with them.
I don't think it's been a while.
You've been coming home late these days
because you're hanging out with your friends.
I have?
Some days I'm late. Some days I'm not.
Now that Mi-poong isn't around, can you
come home earlier and help out my mom a bit?
Jang-soo, do you think
I've been playing around all this time?
I've been working all day long.
It's been a while
since I saw my friends, so I ate
dinner and had coffee with them.
Are you that unhappy with it?
I'm not saying I'm unhappy with it.
I just feel bad for my mom because
you're always late these days.
If you feel that bad for her,
you can help her out then!
I'm going to wash up,
so go ahead and sleep first!
What's wrong?
You can't sleep?
Father.
I'm really curious about something.
Curious?
About what?
About Shin-ae...
Is she really my daughter?
Yes, she's really your daughter.
Were you worried about that?
But father...
Shin-ae doesn't feel like my daughter.
Do you still feel that way?
I think that's because your memory
hasn't returned yet.
I don't that's it, father.
When I'm with you,
I feel comfortable and happy.
I'm scared of Shin-ae though.
You're scared of Shin-ae?
She keeps saying that I'm lying.
- She keeps getting mad at me, too.
- Shin-ae got mad at you?
She said she'll get me if I told you this.
She said she would send me
to the hospital, father.
That's why I'm really scared of her, father.
Shin-ae really said that?
Yes, she really did.
So I'm really scared of her father.
What's going on? Did Mr. Kim
just go up to see Dal-ho?
Why now?
Why is he going up at this hour?
What's going on?
What brings you up here?
Dal-ho.
Yes, Mr. Kim.
About Shin-ae...
Last time, I couldn't check on her because
doing a DNA test with her was impossible,
but wouldn't it be possible for Shin-ae
and Dae-hoon to get a DNA test now?
Yes, of course. Fathers
and daughters can be tested.
Then Dal-ho...
I think Shin-ae and Dae-hoon
should get a DNA test.
I see.
So I wanted to run the test
without Shin-ae knowing about it.
That's why I came up here.
You're the only one
who I can discuss this with.
Don't worry, Mr. Kim.
When Shin-ae goes to work tomorrow,
I'll get her toothbrush
and Dae-hoon's toothbrush
and take them for DNA testing.
Yes, Dal-ho. Please help me out.
Sure.
DNA test?
Oh, no! What kind of bolt out
of the blue is this?
Shin-ae, we're in big trouble! It's an
emergency! Come to my room at once!
Mr. Kim is with Dal-ho right now,
so be careful when you come down!
Are you sleeping?
This isn't the time to sleep!
Mother, what's going on?
Shin-ae, what do we do? We're in big trouble!
Mr. Kim is going to run a DNA test
on you and his son tomorrow.
What?
DNA test?
(Father's Dumplings)
Oh, dear. How could I forget?
What's wrong?
I made kimchi dumplings last night
and left them in the refrigerator.
Oh, mom. I'll go home and get them.
No, I'll go.
- I'll be back.
- Okay.
- Hi.
- Hello!
- Please give me two packs of dumplings.
- Sure. Wait just a moment.
The customers at my hair salon
kept saying how delicious
your dumplings are,
so I came to taste them myself.
Oh, really? Come often.
They're very delicious.
What's this?
Oh, it's a flier searching
for my missing father.
I thought he died while
we were escaping North Korea,
but I think he's alive,
so I'm trying to find him.
My goodness.
Then I'll take a few of these
and post them up in my hair salon.
Really? Thank you so much!
- You can just take these today.
I won't take your money.
- Are you sure?
Yes. You're putting up my fliers in your salon,
so how could I accept your money?
Then I'll come by tomorrow
for lunch and try your dumpling soup.
- Okay. Bye!
- Bye.
Enjoy!
Hurry up and open it, mister!
You're awfully impatient. Please be still.
I'm trying my best to open it right now.
Are you sure you can open doors?
Why are you so slow?
Ma'am, are you sure this is your house?
Of course I am! I'm just cold, so hurry up!
It's done.
Here. Hurry up and go.
All right.
Where's the bathroom?
Is it here?
Oh, that's strange. I know I had definitely
locked the door before I left. Why is it open?
What are you doing here?
What are you doing inside
my house with your shoes on?
Are you a thief?
What? A thief?
How dare you call me a thief!
You're the thief! A husband-stealing thief!
What did you say?
Is that why came into
my house with your shoes on?
Yes, that's why!
Where's my husband?
Hey! You crazy woman!
Fine! Go ahead and search for your husband!
You shouldn't be at my house!
You should be at the mental hospital!
Oh my goodness. How dare you hit me!
How dare you lay a hand on me!
Oh, my heart.
Get out of my house at once!
Get out of here at once!
Try doing something like this again!
It won't end with just a slap!
Just watch. I'll make sure
to pay you back one day.
Shin-ae, I got Mi-poong's toothbrush!
Good job, mother. We're safe now.
Honey, drink some coffee.
Father and mother, I'm going to work now.
Okay, bye.
Bye.
Here are the results.
(Explanation of test results)
(99.99% match)
I did the test for no reason at all.
It's good to be sure. You did the right thing.
Shin-ae can never find out about this test.
Yes, sir. Don't worry.
Grandfather, what brings you here?
I came to see my granddaughter.
You see me every day.
Shin-ae.
Yes, grandfather.
You're having a very hard time because
your father lost his memory, aren't you?
No, I should understand him.
No matter how much of
a hard time he gives me or
how much he hurts me,
I'm just happy that he's by my side.
Yes.
That's the spirit.
I'm so happy that you're
by my side healthy like this.
Thank you.
Oh my goodness.
What do you think? Is it pretty?
Oh my goodness! It's so sparkly!
What do you think?
Do you like it, mother?
Of course I do!
Is this my necklace?
Are you giving this to me?
Yes, mother.
Oh my goodness! It's so pretty!
Thank you, Shin-ae!
I'm the grateful one, mother.
Thanks to you, I'm here.
Thank you for helping me out this time, too.
Mother, I'll take care of you
for the rest of your life.
Thank you.
Let's live happily together.
Okay.
- Oh my goodness!
- It's so pretty.
Yoo-jin, you can have all of these.
They're my gift to you.
Wow! You're awesome! Thank you so much!
Mr. Kim!
Yoo-jin!
But who is that man?
He's like my grandfather,
but he's actually not.
- He's just my friend.
- Really?
We're friends.
- Yeah.
Wow!
Why are there so many cards?
Yoo-sung gave them to me as a gift.
- Did you make all of these, Yoo-sung?
- Yes.
Wow. You're amazing.
Are you Yoo-jin's friend?
Yes. He's my friend.
Yoo-sung, say hi.
Hello. I'm Kim Yoo-sung.
I'm Dae-hoon. Kim Dae-hoon.
It's nice to meet you.
(Blow Breeze)
You can't fold these into cards again, okay?
What is that?
My treasure box.
What? Treasure box?
Did you buy expensive rib eye
to celebrate Jang-go's divorce?
I do want to live with Jang-go,
but I shouldn't do that, mom.
Isn't that Mi-poong's mom?
- I'm fine!
-Dae-hoon! What are you doing to Shin-ae?
Who is it?
I'm Yoo-sung's grandmother.
(The most brutal dictatorship
in the history of Joseon)
Father!
People of low status like me
will never stop having hope.
You can never tell anyone.
(In the midst of chaos, he appeared)
Someone like you could not have
been born from someone so low.
- (A hundred million years
worth of history, Hong Gil-dong)
- This is the end, right?
No, this is only the beginning.
(Rebel: Thief Who Stole the People)
Subtitles by OnDemandKorea