Subtitles by OnDemandKorea
If you see this person,
please let me know. Enjoy.
Please contact me. Enjoy.
(We are looking for someone)
We are looking for Kim Dae-hoon who speaks
in a North Korean dialect. Please call us.
Here.
We're looking for
Kim Dae-hoon from Pyeongyang
who speaks in a North Korean dialect. Enjoy.
Yoo-jin, you can have all of these.
They're my gift to you.
Wow! You're awesome!
Thank you so much!
Mr. Kim!
Yoo-jin!
Why are there so many cards?
Yoo-sung gave them to me as a gift.
- Did you make all of these, Yoo-sung?
- Yes.
Are you Yoo-jin's friend?
Hello. I'm Kim Yoo-sung.
I'm Dae-hoon. Kim Dae-hoon.
It's nice to meet you.
Father, what's wrong?
Oh, it's nothing.
It just felt like I saw him before.
It's my first time seeing you.
Really?
You must have seen
someone similar to him before.
Probably.
Yoo-sung, let's play at my house today.
Yeah, Yoo-sung. Let's go to our house.
Let's go to our house and play slap-match.
- Yoo-jin's house?
- Yes.
(Father's Dumplings)
- I'll be back.
- Be safe.
Okay.
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
Welcome! Sit anywhere you want.
The person you are trying
to reach is unavailable.
Please leave a message after the tone.
Yoo-sung's grandmother and aunt
are not answering their phones.
Oh, I see.
Yoo-jin, Yoo-sung's grandmother and
aunt are not answering their phones,
so I don't think he'll be
able to come over today.
Yoo-sung, let's play together next time.
No!
We can't just say good-bye like this!
If his grandmother isn't answering her phone,
we can try calling her when we get home.
So Yoo-sung, let's go to our house, okay?
Let's go to our house, eat yummy food,
and play slap-match. Okay?
Okay! I'd like that!
I'm so excited!
- Let's play slap-match together!
- Okay!
We'll take Yoo-sung to our house for now.
He came to our house to play last time,
so his grandmother should be okay with it.
Okay. When I get in touch with
his grandmother, I'll let her know.
Flip over!
Oh, yeah!
- It's your turn!
- Okay!
Here I go.
We won them all!
Father, I surrender. I surrender!
Yoo-jin, I'm sorry. I'll fold
more cards for you next time.
No, it's okay. Yoo-jin,
you can have all of these.
I have a lot of paper at home,
so I can make more.
Thanks, Yoo-sung.
But I don't need cards because I'm a girl.
Mr. Kim, you can have all of these.
Are you serious? Are you
giving all of these to me?
Thanks, Yoo-jin.
I have a ton of cards now!
Father, I'm going to go upstairs. You can
eat snack with Yoo-jin and Yoo-sung.
Oh, okay.
Hello?
Ma'am, what are we eating for snack today?
I'll make spicy rice cakes.
Yay! Spicy rice cakes!
Spicy rice cakes!
- Bye.
- Bye. Come again.
Oh, my.
Why are there so many customers today?
I lost control of time.
It's cold outside.
The delivery was tiring, wasn't it?
No. Since there are many customers
and business is going well,
I'm not tired at all,
and I lost a sense of time.
I'm really happy!
It's the same for me.
Oh, dear. Yoo-sung!
Oh, no! My cell-phone was off.
Oh, his teacher had called me.
She must have called
because it's past the time
to pick him up. Go ahead and call her back.
Okay.
Hello, teacher. I'm Yoo-sung's grandmother.
I'm so sorry. I'll come pick him up right now.
Pardon?
Yoo-sung went to Yoo-jin's house?
The spicy rice cakes are yummy.
My grandma makes yummy spicy rice cakes, too.
Do you live with your grandma?
Yes. I live with my grandma and aunt.
What about your mom and dad?
My mom and dad are in heaven.
Is that so?
Yoo-sung, eat a lot, and come to
our house whenever you want.
My father said the owner of this house is me.
So come over whenever you want. Okay?
Okay, Mr. Kim.
But isn't that scary woman
the owner of this house?
No! My father said the
owner of this house is me!
So don't worry.
Okay, Mr. Kim.
Who can that be?
Who is it?
Hello. I'm Yoo-sung's grandmother.
I came to pick him up.
Yoo-sung? Okay. Please hold on.
Yoo-sung, your grandma is here.
- My grandma?
- Yes.
I'll bring him down soon.
Okay. Thank you.
Yoo-sung, quickly put your jacket on
and get your backpack.
Oh my god. Isn't that Mi-poong's mom?
Oh my god!
What is she doing here?
Oh my god. She knows I stole her toothbrush.
That's why she's here! What do we do?
Or did she come here to tell Dal-ho
that I snuck into her house?
What do we do?
Mother, calm down!
That's not the problem right now!
You're right.
She's not here because she knows
her husband is at our house, is she?
That's impossible.
What if she bumps into Mr. Kim and his son?
Oh my god. Just thinking about it
makes me want to faint. What do we do?
The first thing we need to do
is find out why she's here.
So ask her why she came here.
Okay, I will.
Ms. Joo, what are you doing here?
Why are you here? Did you
come here to meet my husband?
How brazen you must be to come here.
I feel bad that such a crazy
woman is your mother-in-law.
What? "Crazy woman?"
- Are you done talking?
- Mother.
Yoo-sung is playing here,
so I came to pick him up.
He is?
What? Who's here? How come
he always comes to our house?
He must think this is his playground!
You should know how to act
according to the circumstances.
How can you send that kid here?
Do you have any conscience?
I didn't send him here on purpose.
The kids came here after school on their own.
I see.
Ma'am.
Please wait a moment.
After Yoo-sung puts his jacket on,
I'll bring him out.
I'll be going in now.
Yoo-sung, I'll do it for you.
- Yoo-sung, come over again.
- Okay.
You're so cute.
My goodness.
Your hands are tiny, too.
Yoo-sung, are you leaving?
Yes. My grandma came to pick me up.
I see. Did you have fun?
- Yes!
- Father, I'll take him.
No!
I'm going to take him.
Let's go, Yoo-sung.
Oh, Shin-ae, are you just coming now?
Yes, dad.
Yoo-sung, it's okay. She's my daughter.
Hi.
Hello.
Dad, are you going somewhere?
Yes. Yoo-sung's grandma is waiting outside,
so I'm going to take him to the front gate.
I'll take him!
Oh, no, Ms. Ma.
I brought him, so I'm going to take him.
Dad, let my mother-in-law
take Yoo-sung.
You and I need to talk.
I need to tell you something.
All right.
You can tell me after I take
Yoo-sung to his grandma.
No, dad! What if you get lost like last time?
I'll go with them.
I'll take him!
- What's wrong with her? Yoo-sung!
- No, dad! Don't go outside!
Shin-ae, what's wrong?
I don't want my dad to meet strangers.
I'm scared something awful will happen to him.
Am I stupid enough to
get lost in front of the house?
Why do you keep treating me like I'm stupid?
On top of that, Yoo-sung is Yoo-jin's friend,
so how can his grandma be a stranger?
Mr. Kim!
Shin-ae...
I understand how you feel, but aren't
you acting too sensitive about him?
I was?
Yes. He can think on his own, but you keep
treating him like a child in front of Yoo-jin.
His pride must have been wounded.
I think you're right.
I should apologize to him.
Why isn't he coming out?
It's not like I can go inside.
- Yoo-sung!
- Grandma!
Yes.
Don't ever come to my house again!
Don't send him to our house again!
We shouldn't be meeting like this!
Don't yell at my grandma.
Yoo-jin and Mr. Kim were
the ones who invited me first.
And Mr. Kim is the owner of the house,
so why are you being like this?
What did you say?
That little brat! Oh my god!
Like grandma, like grandson!
Oh!
Ouch.
Grandma, that witch got punished!
Yoo-sung, you shouldn't do that.
If you laugh when she fell,
she'll be embarrassed.
I don't like that lady.
She seems like a mean one.
Still, you shouldn't say things like that.
Let's go.
Ms. Joo!
Hello.
What brings you here?
Well...
Hello.
Hi.
Wow. You grew a lot.
Yes.
It's cold. Get in. I'll take you home.
No. We can ride the bus.
The bus stop is far from here.
Get in.
Thank you, but it's fine. Good-bye.
- Yoo-sung.
- Hmmm?
From now on, don't go to Yoo-jin's house.
Can you promise me that you won't?
Why? Why shouldn't I go there?
Well, if you go to Yoo-jin's house,
it'll put your aunt and me
in an awkward position.
Why?
I'll explain everything to you
when you get older.
So don't go to Yoo-jin's
house from now on, okay?
Okay. I won't go if you tell me not to go.
That's a good boy.
You can play with Yoo-jin
as much as you want at school.
Okay, grandma.
Good boy.
Let's play after we organize your backpack.
Today-
Yoo-sung.
Yoo-sung, you shouldn't use
these papers to fold them into cards.
These are important papers your aunt
and I made in order to find your grandpa.
Grandpa?
Yes. You remember your grandpa, don't you?
I see.
We think your grandpa
is alive here in South Korea.
Since we need to find him using these papers,
don't fold them into cards again, okay?
Okay.
Good.
I'll make cards for you
out of the calendar. Okay?
Okay.
- (We are looking for someone)
- You unfold these, too.
How did you manage to fold all of these?
Dae-hoon, I'm home.
Welcome, father!
What are you doing?
You're not even looking at me.
What are those?
This is my treasure box.
Treasure box?
Inside are treasure cards from my friend.
So, father, don't touch this
treasure box without my permission!
Okay, I won't.
Who would touch your treasure box?
Mother, the spicy
yellow croaker stew is delicious!
Really? Eat a lot.
Try the cockle, too. It's in season nowadays.
It's delicious! It's so chewy!
There's a lot of iron in it, so it's good
for anemia and other things. Eat up.
It's tiring to work, isn't it?
No, mother.
Even if you had sweetly
told Mi-poong to try a cockle,
she wouldn't have left the house
determined to get divorced.
Mother, are you done eating?
I made your favorite water parsley
and salted oysters for you.
Do you know what tomorrow is?
Even if no one else does, you would know...
because it's the day you've been waiting for.
It's the day that Mi-poong and
Jang-go will be officially divorced.
I can't even manage to swallow my food.
How would Mi-poong and Jang-go feel right now?
Then tomorrow is the day they'll make
the final decision about the divorce?
I don't know.
Why? Eat some more.
It's not like this is new.
It's already been decided anyways.
Why is she doing that and
ruining everyone's appetites?
I was going to drop off Yoo-sung at the
study room, but he fell asleep already.
I can't wake him up when he's sleeping deeply.
What do I do?
Mom, you don't have to come out.
The dumplings are sold out.
What? All those dumplings were sold?
Yes. There's a rumor going around that
our store is famous for selling tasty food.
Really? Is that true?
My goodness. What if we really
become rich at this rate?
Let's make more money and buy this store.
Okay. Let's do that.
I'm glad that business is going well,
but aren't you supposed
to go to the court tomorrow?
Yes, I am.
I'll hurry home after I clean up the store.
Okay.
(Father's Dumplings)
Oh my god! Why are you so shocked?
Let's go. I have something to tell you.
Where...?
Where are we going right now?
What do you need to tell me?
You can just stop the car
over there and tell me.
My goodness. You talk too much.
How dare you act that way
to your precious husband.
Married couples are what?
I don't know. I forgot everything.
Married couples are one in body and soul!
You should answer right away.
We're one in body and soul,
so just quietly follow me.
- Jang-go.
- Yeah?
We're going our separate ways tomorrow.
We're going to be officially divorced,
so how are we a married couple?
That's tomorrow.
According to the law,
we're still a married couple
until today, so don't question
your precious husband.
Got that?
Precious husband? Yeah, right!
I want to eat something.
Honey, if you look down there,
there will be candy. Unwrap one for me.
Don't you have hands?
Can't you see that I'm driving?
Should I just let go of it then? Just let go
of it so that I can eat some candy?
It's good.
Dearie , you should eat some, too.
Stop calling me things like honey and dearie!
I will divorce you tomorrow!
Okay, honey. Do whatever you want.
Seriously!
Hurry up and get out.
Jang-go, isn't this a sledding resort?
Why did we come here? What are we going to do?
You come to a sledding resort
to sled. What else?
I'm going home, so go ahead and
sled until your butt lights on fire.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
Hey, hey, hey!
You and your temper.
Ever since you opened up the
dumpling diner, all you've been doing
is making dumplings and delivering them.
You've been busy and tired.
I wanted you to go sledding to relieve
some stress. That's why we came here.
We're going to divorce tomorrow, but
how can we come here today to sled together?
Are you in your right mind? Are you crazy?
I want to do the things that I've never
done with you before we divorce.
I did something crazy like
sign the divorce papers for you.
Compared to that, isn't this something cute?
- It's my last request.
Can't you even do this for me?
- Fine! We'll ride it!
You were going to ride it anyways.
You came to me like the wind
It's too fast!
I can't forget it
When the day comes that you'll return
I will love you, I will love you
Tell me that you like me
Mi-poong!
I can't forget
Tell me again
That you love me, those words, those words
So I can hear it in my ears
Oh, my back!
Jang-go, let's go again!
Ms. Kim Mi-poong, didn't you say
you were just going to go home earlier?
Your butt is going to light
on fire at that rate.
Just hurry up and come!
Mi-poong!
What are you doing?
You're supposed to play like this here.
Stop it! Stop!
That you love me, those words, those words
So I can hear it in my ears
Jang-go!
What are you doing?
What did I do? What's wrong
with married couples kissing?
I'm going to go home,
so you sled all you want!
Hey, Mi-poong!
Wait for me!
Just like my dry lips, my heart is dry, too
Like the rain...
Ever since you opened up the
dumpling diner, all you've been doing
is making dumplings and delivering them.
You've been busy and tired.
I wanted you to go sledding to relieve
some stress. That's why we came here.
Love silently leaves, I'm crying out loud
I miss you, I miss you so much
I'm shouting into the empty air for that person
The one person
(District Court)
That one person
Thirty minutes have already passed.
Why isn't he coming?
Kim Mi-poong.
Yes?
- This is from Lee Jang-go.
- What?
Excuse me! Wait a minute!
What's this?
Mi-poong, I'm sorry. It's cold,
so don't wait for me and go home.
I won't be coming today.
I can't come.
I can't divorce you.
So hurry up and go in. You'll catch a cold.
It's cold, so drink this hot coffee.
I love you, Mi-poong.
Gosh, Jang-go! Seriously!
I won't let this slide.
(Little Tadpole)
Stop being stubborn and hurry home.
What if you catch a cold?
Jang-go, seriously!
- Is it good?
- It's so delicious!
- The seasoning is just right.
- Really?
I'm here!
She's always late!
- What's that?
- I bought oxtail.
Geum-sil had a hard time lately.
Geum-sil, eat this and gain strength.
Why did you buy this? You didn't have to.
You've been having a hard time
because your mother-in-law is hard
on you. You should eat that and
restore the health of your body.
How would her mother-in-law
give her a hard time at this age?
You don't even know the half of it.
Her mother-in-law was ticked off
that Geum-sil kicked Mi-poong out.
She made Geum-sil make red bean
noodles and pumpkin porridge.
She made Geum-sil make
quince tea until her wrists
were sore then gave the tea to someone else!
She made Geum-sil make a hundred rows
of kimbap and took them to the senior center.
She forced Geum-sil to make
wrapped kimchi and boil pork.
- Oh, my.
- And when Geum-sil retaliates,
she always says,
"Is it as hard as making a
hundred cabbages into kimchi?"
Oh my goodness!
So what did you kick your daughter-in-law
out for? Even if you hated
her, you should have just lived
with her for your son's sake!
Hey!
Don't talk so easily about this just
because it's someone else's business!
Would Geum-sil have done
that if things hadn't been so bad?
So is the consideration period over?
Yes, it's over, so they went to court today.
Once the divorce is finalized and they turn in
the papers to the
borough office, it'll be over.
Anyways, you must feel much better now.
You guys should also search
for a prospective marriage partner
for Geum-sil's son. I'm looking, too.
Won't her son make a fine partner?
Yes, but he still has
feelings for his ex-wife.
Would any woman want to get married to him?
If he was wealthy, at least women
would get married to him for the money.
Oh, dear. Don't get offended.
Wasn't I telling the truth though?
- Just eat the porridge.
- Let me taste it.
Try it. It's good.
Mom, how would Mi-poong
and Jang-go feel right now?
Divorce is very heartbreaking.
I know that better than anyone else.
Goodness. You're his aunt. Don't you know him?
Jang-go didn't go to court.
He didn't get a divorce.
What? What are you talking about?
Take a look at this.
Do they look like they're
going to get a divorce?
Oh my goodness! They went sledding together
when they're in the middle of a divorce?
They're so weird!
What's weird about that? They love each other,
so they can go sledding together.
Geum-sil thinks they're
about to get a divorce.
The house is about to get noisy again.
I should move out!
Why?
Did your boss ask you to live with him?
Mom!
Hello, ma'am.
Did you eat?
If you didn't, would you like me
to order something for you?
No, I already ate.
- Sit down.
- Sure.
Mr. Kim,
I'm not against you dating my daughter.
After watching you
all this time, I realized...
you're faithful,
kind,
and good-looking.
Thank you, ma'am.
- But...
- Mom, what are you going to say?
Just hold still.
You can speak comfortably.
The two of you are old enough.
If you're going to just have a "fling," as the
young ones call it nowadays, don't even start.
I can never allow that.
Mom.
I heard your family motto is
"don't live a vague life."
So what I mean is, don't date vaguely.
I want the two of you to date
with certainty while promising to
be with each other in the future.
Don't worry, ma'am.
I'm not a vague person.
I, Kim Seung-jun,
am sincere about dating Nam-yi, mother.
Mother?
These two are very passionate
about each other.
Hurry up and come out, father! Hurry!
Dad, why are you waiting for grandfather?
Let's hurry up and go look
for the dumpling diner, father!
Dae-hoon, how about we go look
for that dumpling diner next time?
I have something important
to do today, so I need to go out.
Father!
Dad, go with me then.
Grandfather, I'll take him.
That sounds like a good idea, Dae-hoon.
Shin-ae knows Seoul streets better than I do.
No, father!
I'm going to go with you.
Dad, I'll find it with you. Go with me, okay?
No! I'm going to go with father!
Oh my goodness!
Shin-ae, are you okay?
Are you all right?
Yes.
Dae-hoon, what do you
think you're doing to her?
I hate Shin-ae!
I don't want to go with her, father!
Fine, fine.
Then put on your jacket and get ready.
Oh, my jacket!
Okay, father!
Shin-ae...
- Yes?
- Are you all right?
Yes, grandfather.
Shin-ae, your father is ill right now.
If you don't understand him, who else will?
I know, grandfather, but it still upsets me.
I know.
Why wouldn't I know that you're upset?
It's okay.
Have some tea. It's quince tea that I made.
The color is pretty.
Geum-sil, it smells nice. It tastes good, too.
Chung-ja, is that a diamond necklace?
Oh, this?
Yes, it's a diamond necklace.
It's pretty! You must have spent a
fortune on it. Where'd you get it from?
Where else?
My daughter-in-law.
I envy you! Since you have
a well-off daughter-in-law,
you get things like that. You're lucky!
That's my phone.
Oh, it's my daughter-in-law.
Hi, it's me.
Mother, where are you right now?
I told you to watch my dad!
What are you doing out so early?
What else? I'm meeting my friends?
Meeting your friends?
Mother, this isn't the time
for that right now.
Hurry up and come back. Hurry!
Okay, I'll be there soon.
I'm going to go home first.
Ma Chung-ja, how can you leave first?
I'm sorry. See you later!
Does her daughter-in-law
hold a sword over her head?
She did this the last time, too.
Why does she follow all her orders?
She's not just any daughter-in-law.
She's a daughter-in-law who buys
diamond necklaces and
has 100 billion dollars- no. More than that.
She's the heiress of Winner's Group.
That doesn't mean Geum-sil
has to be so intimidated by her!
Who cares if she's the heiress of
Winner's Group? My goodness.
Or did something happen at home?
Look here.
Dae-hoon, it's not this place either?
Yes, father.
It's not here either.
Really? Then let's go home for today.
You're going to catch a cold at this rate.
Okay, father.
Let's go then.
Thank goodness they came
to the wrong place today.
But we can't tail them forever
like this. This won't do.
I know.
What will we do if they come
across Mi-poong's dumpling diner?
So we need to block them before they do.
How?
Is there a way?
We can just buy the building where
Mi-poong's dumpling diner is.
Yes! Let's chase them out
of that dumpling diner!
Yes.
You can't sell it?
Yes. I won't sell it.
Ma'am, don't be like this. Just sell it.
We'll give you a good price for it.
No, thanks.
I have no intention of selling that building,
so don't come looking for me again.
(Park Shin-ae. Marketing Director.)
What do we do?
It's not just a small store. It's a building.
She wouldn't make a decision right away.
Then is she playing
hard-to-get to get more money?
I'll buy that building no matter what,
so don't worry about it.
Okay.
That way, we'll be able to chase
them out of Father's Dumplings.
Mi-poong, did something happen?
Did you and Jang-go separate on bad terms?
Mom.
Jang-go is driving me nuts.
Oh, dear. What's wrong?
Tell me about it. Okay?
I'm in disbelief.
Mom, Jang-go didn't come to court today.
What? He didn't come?
Did he get into an accident?
That's not it.
Look at this.
(Mi-poong, I'm sorry...)
How can you laugh right now?
Divorce isn't a joke. How can
he do something like this?
He won't even answer his phone.
I can't get in touch with him.
Mi-poong...
you might get mad if you hear this...
but I'm grateful Jang-go
didn't come out today.
Mom!
Do you know how heartbroken I was
after you left to the court like that?
I wondered if you two were going
to end up getting a divorce after all.
I don't want you to get a divorce.
Those are my true feelings.
Welcome.
What can I get for you?
- Three dumplings.
- All right.
Three dumplings.
- What are all these?
- Jang-soo, take pictures for me.
Oh, you're putting up styles
for gifts up on SNS?
Yes. There are many people who ask for gift
suggestions, so I'm going to put these up.
- Okay. Pose for me.
- Okay.
One, two, three.
- So pretty!
- One more.
One, two, three. Nice!
- Three! Good one! Next!
- Next!
Next! Make a pose!
Three! Good!
One! Two! Three! Shoot!
One, two, three!
Hee-ra, I'm going to answer this call.
Why would you answer it outside?
Answer it here!
What kind of call is that?
I'm going to upload these photos!
What?
Joo-ri didn't remarry
her ex-husband that time?
What?
Is that true?
- Bye.
Mi-poong, it hasn't been long since we started
this business, but it's going so well...
that I'm honestly getting scared.
Come on, mom.
It's good if business go well.
Why would you be scared?
And I heard the customers
talking about how the other stores
are talking about how
delicious our dumplings are.
Really?
This is great!
What if we become really rich at this rate?
Mom, since we're not busy anymore,
I'm going to go see Jang-go.
I'm so frustrated that he didn't
come to the court today.
Mother, I'm here.
- Hi, Jang-go.
- Hi.
What happened?
I'm sorry I didn't come out today.
Mother, I'm sorry for worrying you.
I'll explain everything.
Please sit down. Mi-poong, sit down.
How can you do that?
You should have come out.
You kept me waiting in the cold.
Is divorce a joke?
Just like you said, divorce isn't a joke.
That's why I didn't come out.
What?
I'm sorry for making you wait in the cold.
I'm sorry for not coming out either.
However...
I never had the intention of divorcing
Mi-poong from the beginning, mother.
What do you mean?
Jang-go, why are you doing this?
I still love Mi-poong.
Mi-poong loves me, too.
I told you.
I'm not divorcing you because I hate you.
I know that.
I know why you wanted a divorce, too.
But Mi-poong...
we love each other,
so there must be another way.
Jang-go-
Mother...
please trust me and help us start over again.
Mi-poong, let's think
about this a little longer.
We love each other.
I don't think this is the answer.
This isn't it.
I said everything I wanted to say.
I'll be going now.
Mi-poong...
let's just think about this a little longer.
Okay?
Mom, let's take the dumplings
and go out to find father.
Sure. Let's do that.
Are you grilling expensive rib eye because
you're happy Jang-go got a divorce?
I'm grilling meat to lift up
his mood when he comes home.
Why wouldn't I care about his feelings?
I see. Then grill a lot.
Jang-go didn't get a divorce,
so he'll have a big appetite.
Excuse me? What do you
mean he didn't get a divorce?
What are you talking about?
He went to the court this morning to get
a divorce, so why didn't he get a divorce?
Mother, don't even joke like that.
Why would I make such a joke? My goodness.
It's delicious! Eat up!
- Thank you for the food.
- Thank you.
I'm back.
Lee Jang-go.
What is it?
I heard you didn't get a divorce.
Is that true?
It's not. It's not true, right, Jang-go?
Your grandma was mistaken, wasn't she?
She's right. I didn't get a divorce.
Why not? Why didn't you get a divorce?
Did Mi-poong say she couldn't get the divorce?
Did she say she wouldn't let you go?
- Why I ought to...
- Mom!
I didn't go to the court.
Mi-poong went. I didn't.
Why not? Why didn't you go?
Because I don't want to get a divorce.
What?
I already went to Mi-poong and
told her I couldn't divorce her.
And I begged her to change her mind.
I'm not going to divorce
Mi-poong, so just know that.
- Oh my gosh!
- You idiot!
Why can't you divorce her?
What's so good about her?
So are you going to live
with that thief again?
How many times do I have to
tell you she was falsely accused?
Oh my goodness!
What do you think you're doing?
How dare you throw water
at the eldest son of our family!
- Do you want a taste of this?
- Mom, stop it!
Mom, I'm going to wait until
Mi-poong changes her mind.
I'm never going to get a divorce.
Keep that in mind.
You can never be with her!
Never! Just grow old alone!
Geum-sil, you should just give up.
They can't get a divorce.
How could they get divorced when they
went to have fun at a sledding resort?
Sledding resort?
- I can never forgive her!
- Mom!
- Let's go to your room.
- How could this happen?
How could he do this to me? That jerk!
What did you bring up the sledding resort for?
I was just trying to get her to give up
and it just came out of my mouth...
What are you doing not sleeping at this hour?
I just couldn't sleep.
Mom, go back in and sleep.
Mi-poong, you need to make up your mind.
Accept Jang-go's heart.
Mom, to be honest...
I was scared that Jang-go
would come to the court today.
That's why I had hoped and
prayed that he wouldn't come.
Oh, dear.
Sweetie.
I want to accept his heart, but
I really don't know what I should do.
Should I just live with Jang-go whether
he cuts off ties with his mother or not?
I really want to do that...
but I shouldn't, mom.
Mi-poong, just like Jang-go had said,
let's just wait a little bit longer.
Then some kind of solution will appear.
Okay.
While we sell dumplings and search for father,
we'll be able to find a solution, won't we?
Of course.
- Let's do it together.
- Go in and sleep.
No, I can't sleep either.
(Father's Dumplings)
Mother.
What's wrong with you, mother?
Are you asking me because you don't know?
If you said you were going
to divorce him, you should!
Why aren't you letting Jang-go go?
You seduced Jang-go into getting you this store!
What more do you want from him?
What is it that you want?
If there's something you want, tell me.
Don't go behind my back
and ask my son for it. Tell me!
Mother.
I was going to divorce him
like you wanted me to.
That's why I went to
the court yesterday after the
consideration period was
over to finalize the divorce!
But Jang-go didn't come out!
He said he didn't want to get a divorce!
So why are you doing this to me?
What more do you want from me?
If you really want us to get a divorce,
then you should change his mind.
Then I'll do it.
What? Where do you get your courage from?
Mother,
I married Jang-go because I liked him.
Do you think it would have been
easy for me to decide to divorce him?
It's hard for me to push Jang-go away now.
Oh, I see. Now your
true colors are coming out.
This must be how you're
trying to hold him back.
Do you think I'll just watch that happen?
Nothing will happen the way you want.
So it would be a good idea for you to give up.
- Welcome!
- I saw the styles recommended for gifts.
- Oh, those?
- Do you have this coat?
- Of course I do. Right this way.
- Okay.
It's right over there.
- It's this navy one, right?
- Yes.
- I took the picture and
uploaded it myself. Do you like it?
- Yes.
Where's the hair salon?
Yes, I know that place.
- I coordinated this outfit. Do you like it?
- Oh, you did?
Okay. Thanks.
- Enjoy. Bye.
- Bye.
Bye!
Hee-ra, I have plans, so I need to go.
What plans?
You're supposed to clean the store today.
Who will clean if you're not here?
I'll clean when I come back!
Why would he be busy when he's unemployed?
Jang-soo?
What brings you here?
Did you come here to see me?
Yeah.
What reason do we have to meet?
Joo-ri, why did you lie to me?
What lie?
You lied about getting back
together with your husband.
Why is that important now?
I heard you lied for me.
Why is it important if it's
the lie or the truth right now?
You're happy right now.
Didn't it work out then?
Then you should be happy, too.
What's wrong with you?
Why are you being so annoying?
Don't mind me, and just be happy.
So cute.
Dad, Mr. Lee made a frog.
Why did you come again?
I just stopped by while I was passing by.
We need to talk.
Soo-jung, I'll come again next time.
Have fun.
Mr. Lee, why are you exhausting me like this?
Please don't come here.
I'm not someone who could be of help to you.
Mr. Kang, I'm begging you
to confess the truth.
Then I'll never forget your kindness.
Why are you doing this?
Just tell me who was behind the box incident.
After that box incident, my wife
was falsely accused and unfairly fired.
After that, she was forced
into an unwanted divorce with me.
Imagine you were unjustly fired
and your family was destroyed.
I already told you I was the one who caused
the box incident because I needed the money!
Please don't bother me anymore.
One woman's life is on
the line here, Mr. Kang.
Please reconsider. I'm begging you.
I'll come see you again next time.
What does he want now?
Hello?
I called you because I have a favor.
A favor?
Mr. Lee Jang-go keeps
showing up at my daughter's
hospital and bothering me.
It's driving me nuts.
Mr. Lee Jang-go?
All right. I'll see you there then.
Pardon? Is that true?
Yes. Please take care of it for me.
All right.
That Lee Jang-go...
He's annoying.
Take this and transfer
to a different hospital.
It should be enough. And move
to the provinces while you're at it.
- All right.
- If Lee Jang-go comes to see you again, make
sure you make it clear to him
so that he can't come again.
Yes, I understand.
Why did Mr. Kang meet Mr. Heo?
Something is going on.
Mr. Kang!
What is that?
Why did you get money from Mr. Heo?
Whether I get money from someone
or not, it has nothing to do with you!
Mr. Kang!
Mr. Heo...
Mr. Heo.
Oh, Mr. Lee.
Let me ask you one thing.
I saw you meeting Mr. Kang earlier.
You gave him money.
Why did you give it to him?
I heard his daughter is going to get surgery,
so I thought I could be of some help to him.
Did that answer your question?
Mr. Heo, Mr. Kang was fired from
Winner's Group for stealing the products.
But you're using his sick child
as an excuse to give him money
when you're one of the
directors of Winner's Group?
Do you want me to believe that?
Look here, Mr. Lee.
I'm using my money to help a person in need.
Is that a problem?
Wait a minute.
Are you doing a background check on me?
Winner's Group hired you to do work here at
Winner's Group, not do
a background check on me.
I can never forgive you
if you do something like this again.
There's something going on.
What did you say?
Mr. Lee saw you give money to Mr. Kang?
I apologize.
However, I made sure to keep
Mr. Kang's mouth shut, so there
shouldn't be any problems. So don't worry.
You said Mr. Lee saw you!
I told Mr. Lee I gave it to
Mr. Kang for his sick child, so
as long as Mr. Kang keeps
his mouth shut, it'll be fine.
Isn't there a way to get rid of Mr. Lee?
All right. I'll try to come up with a way.
What happened to buying the building
where the dumpling diner is at?
Did you call the owner?
She said she won't sell it.
Even if we were going to give her
a hundred thousand dollars more?
Yes.
We were going to give her more than
the original price, so why won't she sell it?
What do we do?
She's going to sell it.
If she won't take $100,000,
we'll raise it to $300,000.
If she still won't sell it,
we'll raise it to $500,000.
Yes. We're going to give her so
much money. Why wouldn't she sell it?
There's no one who doesn't
crumble in front of money.
Yoo-jin, let's play slap-match here.
If we play downstairs, it'll get tiring
because of that woman's nagging.
Okay, Mr. Kim!
Okay then...
One, two, three, four, five. Here you go.
You get five. One, two,
three, four. And I get five.
You can go first.
Here I go.
What was that? The card unfolded!
Gosh, what's this? How can
this happen on the first try?
(We are looking for a person)
"We are looking for a person?"
(Name: Kim Dae-hoon)
Kim Dae-hoon?
(Blow Breeze)
Did you call yourself "mom" to Yoo-jin?
I think this paper is looking for me.
- You're not my daughter, right?
- Should I lock you up?
I'm going to tell father everything!
Honey! Are you really my husband?
Jang-go, can we meet?
- What is it now?
- I have a favor to ask of you. Please do it.
Jang-go...
Subtitles by OnDemandKorea