Subtitles by OnDemandKorea
(Episode 43)
What was that? The card unfolded!
(We are looking for a person)
"We are looking for a person?"
(Name: Kim Dae-hoon)
Kim Dae-hoon?
It's me. I'm the farting culprit.
Mr. Kim, I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I fart often, too.
I'm going to use the bathroom.
- I'll be back.
- Okay.
"We are looking for Kim Dae-hoon
who is from Pyeongyang?"
Oh, this ring...
This looks the same as my mother's ring!
What? Kim Soon-ok?
This is me.
Oh, Shin-ae! Take a look at this!
Someone is looking for
Kim Dae-hoon from Pyeongyang!
A photo of my mother's ring is on this, too!
What's this?
What is it?
Dad, where did you get this from?
This is the paper Yoo-sung
used to make the card.
But look.
The Kim Dae-hoon from
Pyeongyang is me, isn't it?
But who is looking for me?
Oh my gosh.
Dad, this isn't looking for you.
There are so many people named
Kim Dae-hoon in this world.
By the way,
don't you have to find that dumpling diner?
You said you had to pay them back.
Let's go find that dumpling diner right now.
Okay.
But I have to play slap-match
with Yoo-jin right now.
You'll get punished if you stole a
dumpling and don't pay them back.
Then when Yoo-jin comes
out of the bathroom, tell her
I'm giving these cards
to her as a present. Okay?
Okay, dad. Go downstairs and
get your jacket. I'll be down soon.
Okay.
Oh my goodness.
What are all of these?
These were floating around our house, and
we didn't even know it! What can we do?
Mi-poong made these, didn't she?
Yes. Mi-poong made these.
Oh my god. What do we do?
I saw that he had a whole box
of these! If Mr. Kim sees this, we're...
Just thinking about it...
Oh my god. What do we do?
Mother, I'll do whatever
it takes to take dad out of here,
so find all the cards in
the house and burn them all!
Then obtain similar papers
and fold them into cards.
You understand, don't you?
Yes. I understand. Oh my goodness.
What about Mr. Kim?
Yoo-jin, mommy has to go somewhere
with Mr. Kim, so we'll be going out.
So go and do your homework, okay?
Okay...
Good.
Did you call yourself "mommy" to Yoo-jin?
I did?
Yes.
When did I do that? You probably misheard.
And whether I called myself her aunt or
her mom, why is that important right now?
I thought for sure she called herself mommy...
She's right. That's not important right now.
Shin-ae.
Yes, dad?
About that paper that is
searching for Kim Dae-hoon...
Shouldn't we call the phone number on there?
Let's find out who's looking for me.
You have grandfather and me.
Who would be looking for you?
This won't do, Shin-ae. Let's go back home.
I need to look at that paper again.
Aren't you going to find that dumpling diner?
I am...
Then forget about that paper and check
if this is the right neighborhood or not.
This isn't the right neighborhood.
There weren't any big buildings like these.
- But Shin-ae...
- What now?
I really do think that paper is looking for me!
Get out of the car! Go to those
people who are looking for you!
Why are you getting angry?
You're scaring me...
Why don't you listen to me? I told you it's not
true! Why don't you listen to whatever I say?
I'm using my precious time to
help you find that dumpling diner.
You don't even know how I feel.
I'm so upset!
I'm sorry.
Let's go find that dumpling diner.
Where did it go?
I don't think he took it with him.
It's right here.
It's hot!
Where am I supposed to
find similar fliers like this one?
Gosh, he made a ton of these.
Ms. Ma, what are you doing?
Are you burning Mr. Kim's cards right now?
No. These are other papers.
Go inside! Don't come over here!
I heard you'll pee at night
if you play with fire.
My Yanbian mom told me that.
Hurry up and go inside!
And don't come down from the
second floor! You get in the way!
Got that?
Yes...
Gosh! Why did Hee-dong have to
bring her home? She's always in the way!
What does she mean by "Yanbian mom?"
Does that mean she has another mom?
Goodness.
Go ahead and try to find Mi-poong's
dumpling diner all you want.
It's one hour away from here.
What's wrong, dad? It's not this place either?
There's another dumpling diner in
the alley over there, so try finding it.
Okay.
Dad, it's over there.
Shin-ae-
Where did Shin-ae go?
My phone! It was in my pocket!
Shin-ae!
Sir, please help me find my daughter.
My daughter is gone!
- Her name is Park Shin-ae!
Please help me find her!
- Let go of me! You're crazy!
Shin-ae!
Shin-ae! Shin-ae!
Grandfather, something terrible has happened!
What? What do you mean Dae-hoon is missing?
Dad kept insisting we go find the
dumpling diner, so we came out,
but he ran off like he was out of his mind.
Ran off like he was out of his mind?
What do you mean by that?
Goodness. Poor me.
I'm folding cards at this age.
Is this the right way to do this?
This must be right.
It works now.
Hi, it's me.
What happened to the cards?
I saw similar fliers in
the newspaper, so I bought
a ton of them, and I'm folding them right now.
I'm almost done.
Then put them in that box and put it back
in grandfather's room. I'll be home soon.
All right.
Oh, my. When will I fold all of these? Oh, no.
Shin-ae!
Shin-ae...
Dad!
Shin-ae! Oh, Shin-ae!
Where were you? I've been
looking for you for a long time!
Why do you keep making trouble?
I thought you were following me.
I was following you,
but you went off on your own!
No, I didn't!
I was looking for the dumpling diner,
but you suddenly disappeared.
Dad, what's wrong with you?
Why do you keep saying strange things?
Why would I disappear?
You were running off on your own,
so I was trying to go after you,
but I ended up losing you!
I really did that?
I really ran off?
Yes!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Shin-ae.
Nam-yi's face will get worn out
since you keep staring at her.
I'm sorry. She's so beautiful,
so I couldn't help it.
Is my daughter that beautiful?
Well, Nam-yi is beautiful
because she takes after me.
When I was young,
I was much more beautiful than her.
I made so many boys cry.
When I think of them, I feel guilty.
What are you guys doing acting like a family?
This is a workplace!
Kim Won-bin, there is an elder present.
What do you think you're doing?
You must keep the promise you made with me.
The promise to love only one woman.
Go wait at the bakery.
You and I need to have a serious talk.
Hold on, Mr. Kim.
I need to speak with Won-bin, so can you
and Nam-yi give us a moment?
Mom, what are you going to say to him?
Nam-yi, go and drink coffee with Mr. Kim.
All right. Let's go, Nam-yi.
Won-bin, have a seat here.
Yes, ma'am.
Won-bin, do you hate Nam-yi?
No, I really like her as a friend.
However, I don't want her
to take my mom's spot.
So you want Nam-yi and your father to break up?
Yes.
But Won-bin,
there's nothing more horrible than
separating two people who love each other.
However, breaking a promise is horrible, too.
Father promised that he would only love my mom.
But isn't dating another
woman breaking his promise?
You're right. Breaking a promise
is a horrible thing to do.
However, if your father
has to only live with you forever
just to keep his promise to his late wife,
don't you think he'll be too lonely?
My father won't be lonely.
He has me and grandmother.
So if you meet a good woman in the future,
you won't be able to marry her
and you'll just have to live with
your father forever, all because of
the promise you made with your father?
That can't happen.
I'm going to get married early.
So you'll get married, but your father
will live the rest of his life alone?
See?
You won't be able to keep the
promise you made to your father either.
I found enlightenment toady.
I was thoughtless.
Yes. You're so smart. You understand
everything after just one explanation.
- Eat these dumplings.
- Yes, ma'am.
Are you coming home now?
Did Dae-hoon come home?
He didn't come home yet. What's wrong, Mr. Kim?
Dae-hoon got lost again!
Oh, dear!
- Dae-hoon!
- Father!
Do you know how worried I was when
I heard you that you went missing?
Why did you run off on your own
like you had lost your mind?
If you had gone to find the dumpling diner,
you should have stuck close to Shin-ae.
I'm sorry, father.
What were you thinking?
I don't know.
I was thinking about a paper
that was looking for me...
A paper looking for you?
What do you mean by that?
Father, on a piece of paper
that had been folded into a card,
it was written, "We are looking for
Kim Dae-hoon from Pyeongyang."
On top of that, mother's ring was on there.
So I was thinking about that...
Shin-ae, what is he talking about?
Grandfather, dad says strange things.
You saw that paper, too!
No. I'll show you myself.
- (Freshwater eel found in Gochang)
- That's odd. This isn't it.
Oh my gosh. He must have
thought that after he had seen this.
This is about freshwater eel though.
It's not about searching for people.
That's odd! This isn't it!
There was something that said,
"We are looking for Kim Dae-hoon!"
My mother's ring was on here for sure!
He must have thought
this curvy freshwater eel was a ring!
And it says " Freshwater eel found in Gochang."
He must have thought it said,
"We are looking for Kim Dae-hoon."
No! No! No!
No...
What do we do?
Mr. Heo...
It's clear that Mr. Heo has
something to do with that box incident.
But why would he do that to Mi-poong...?
Here you go!
I'll hold onto this, so you put the tape on it.
How did you know I was here?
Where there's a will, there's a way.
You can run, but you'll always
be in the palm of my hand.
Stop saying ridiculous things.
Did you put a tracking device on me?
I met your mother on the way here.
You should have called me
if you were going to do this.
Give me the tape.
Look. Right there.
Right there.
It's amazing.
What do you think?
Should you or should you not have a husband?
Anyways, I told you that I had to
talk to you. Why didn't you reply?
I was busy selling dumplings.
What did you need to tell me?
When you were working in Winner's Group,
did something happen between you and Mr. Heo?
Mr. Heo?
I only saw his face. I don't know him.
Why?
Really?
You didn't have conflicts
with him inside and outside of work?
I didn't.
Why would I have conflicts with
such a high-ranking person?
But what is this about?
It's nothing.
Are you just saying strange things because
you missed me, but had nothing to say?
How'd you know? I'm caught red-handed!
I need to put up the rest of
these fliers, so you go your way.
Why do you keep telling me to go
when I have nowhere else to be?
And I'm your father's son-in-law,
so I should help look for hm.
I saw many people over there.
- Where?
- There.
Give me the fliers. I'll hold them.
Grandma, are you okay?
Are you sick?
Yes, I'm okay.
Grandma!
Grandma.
Honey! Honey!
Who are you?
It's me, Young-ae.
Aren't you Kim Dae-hoon from Pyeongyang?
I think you got the wrong person.
Aren't you Seung-hee's father?
Mom!
Mother.
Mom.
I'm sorry.
I got the wrong person...
- Mom!
- Mother!
- Grandma!
Why didn't you tell me you were sick?
I'm fine.
What do you mean you're fine?
You have a terrible fever.
Where on earth can your father be?
What if we never find your father?
I wonder if he's able to
eat in this frigid weather.
Mom, father is a strong person.
He'll be fine.
Mother, take your medicine.
Okay. Thank you, Jang-go.
- Jang-go.
- Yeah?
What are you doing?
- Why are you spreading the blankets?
- I need to in order to sleep.
You're going to sleep here?
How can I go home
when your mother is very sick?
Think about it.
What if I hadn't been there today?
Because I was there,
I was able to carry her,
quickly bring her home,
and buy her medicine.
This is why there
should be a man at home.
I'm really grateful to you about today.
So you can go home now.
I can't!
What if your mother's fever rises
in the middle of the night?
I'll have to carry her to the emergency room!
Stop saying nonsense and go sleep!
Jang-go.
Yes, mother!
I'm fine.
Just go home.
Your mother will be furious if
she finds out you're staying here.
See?
My mom wants you to leave, too.
And if there's an emergency, I'll just call for
an ambulance, so don't worry and just go home.
Do as she says.
Okay.
- Go already.
- Call me if something happens
during the night. I'll come as soon as I can.
I will.
- My car key...
- it's right there.
- Bye.
- All right! I'm going!
(Veteran Hair Salon)
- Excuse me.
- Yes?
The hair salon sign changed.
I'll be running this place
starting from tomorrow.
Then where did the previous owner go?
I don't know.
Yeah.
What am I going to do if I find out
where she went anyways?
Baby.
Hee-ra, I'm sorry. I'm late, aren't I?
The play practice ended just now.
I'll hurry up and go clean.
It's fine. You seemed to not care
about the store, so I hired someone.
You hired someone?
Come out.
Yes, Ms. Jo.
Hello.
Hi.
This isn't it.
This paper isn't the one Yoo-sung gave me.
Dad.
What are you doing up here and not sleeping?
Shin-ae, why are you lying?
What do you mean I'm lying? What are
you talking about? What's wrong with you?
You saw the paper that said they
were looking for Kim Dae-hoon.
You saw my mother's ring.
So why did you lie that I saw something wrong?
I really didn't see it.
Why are you saying weird things?
That was just your imagination.
No! It isn't my imagination! It's real!
If you keep this up, it gets tiring for me.
Grandfather is having a hard time, too.
So enough already!
I think you're the strange one here.
Why do you keep saying I'm saying
weird things? Why do you lie?
You definitely saw that paper!
Dad.
If you keep doing this, I'll have no choice
but to send you to a mental institution.
What did you say?
You keep saying weird
things that give grandfather and
me a hard time? So how can
we continue to live with you?
So listen to me carefully.
If I said it's not true, it's not true.
You got that?
You're not my daughter, are you?
You're not my daughter, right?
Are you saying that again?
If I'm not your daughter, whose daughter am I?
Do you really want to be locked up
in a mental institution?
Should I really lock you up?
You terrible wench!
You're a mental patient!
A mental patient who says strange things!
I'm going to tell father everything.
I'm going to tell father everything
you just said right now!
You're not my daughter!
- No! You can't go!
- Let go of me!
Dae-hoon! What's wrong with you?
Father, don't do this! Why are you doing this?
- Dae-hoon!
- Don't do this!
Father!
- Oh my god! What's going on?
- Hurry up and come here!
Let go of her!
- Dae-hoon!
- Shin-ae!
Shin-ae, what happened?
Shin-ae, are you okay?
Oh my god! Look at this bloody bruise!
Oh my god! This is ridiculous!
How can he bite a person?
Shin-ae, that wench, isn't my daughter.
She's a terrible wench!
So kick her out at once!
She's not my daughter!
Dae-hoon, what's wrong with you?
Grandfather, dad is being so strange!
He suddenly came up to me and bit my arm!
You said you were going to
send me to a mental institution!
Everything she says is a lie!
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
Oh my goodness!
Thank goodness he bit her pajama!
If not, he would have ripped her skin off!
It was very painful, wasn't it, Shin-ae?
I'm okay. But what do we do about dad?
They're all lies! All of them!
Dal-ho, take Dae-hoon to my bedroom.
Yes, sir. Dae-hoon, come with me.
Dal-ho, you believe me, don't you?
- Right?
- Of course.
- It's okay.
- That terrible wench!
It's okay. It's okay.
Hee-dong, please take care of Shin-ae.
I will.
Hold on.
Mom, I'm going to get medicine.
Mr. Kim, here's your water.
Um...
Mr. Kim...
I know you have a lot on your mind right now,
but I thought I should still tell you this.
What is it?
Shin-ae's father...
bit my arm yesterday.
What?
Did Dae-hoon do this?
I wasn't going to tell you this because
I thought you would get upset if I did.
However, I had to tell you
when Shin-ae got bitten earlier.
Oh my goodness.
Since I'm home all day long,
so I spend the most time with him.
But he must be seeing strange things.
He keeps saying he saw weird
things and says strange nonsense.
When I told him that's not true...
Mr. Kim.
He had definitely eaten already, but he keeps
saying he didn't and asks for more food.
Even if I told him you
had gone to work, he says
that isn't true and keeps searching for you.
What are you talking about?
Those seem like dementia symptoms.
Dementia?
Grandfather, what if dad really has dementia?
Memory loss can get better over time...
but if he has dementia,
won't he lose all of his memories?
No way.
Are you sure Dae-hoon did that?
Yes!
He was trying to run out of the house
yesterday, and when I stopped him, he bit me.
Grandfather, this won't do.
Let's admit dad into the hospital.
Let's get him proper treatment.
Shin-ae, the two of us should take
your father to the hospital tomorrow.
Let's test for dementia right away.
She can go with me! Shin-ae, go with me!
No, Shin-ae, go with Hee-dong. He'll help you.
Yes, father.
Let's do that, Hee-dong.
If I can use the rest of my life
to let Dae-hoon get better,
I would die right this instant.
My poor Dae-hoon. What do
we do about my poor Dae-hoon?
Yoo-jin!
I need to tell you something.
What is it, Mr. Kim?
Come here for a moment.
Yoo-jin, when you go to school,
you can see Yoo-sung, right?
Yes.
Bring a card from Yoo-sung.
A card?
Yes. I really need Yoo-sung's card.
And this is a secret.
Okay, Mr. Kim. I'll make sure to bring it.
Thanks, Yoo-jin.
Yoo-jin! Yoo-jin!
Dad. Dad.
What are the two of you doing here?
What are you two talking secretly about?
- It's nothing.
Yoo-jin, you need to hurry up and go to school.
See you later, Mr. Kim!
Bye.
Father, it's time to go to the hospital.
Okay, Hee-dong! I'm going to go with Hee-dong!
Let's go.
Mr. Kim Dae-hoon's image examination...
- (Blood Test Results)
- and blood test...
are both fine.
He doesn't have dementia.
Really?
Yes. Dementia is a disease where
the brain cells are slowly destroyed.
However, Mr. Kim Dae-hoon
has partial memory loss from shock.
Shin-ae, I'm so glad.
Yes, Hee-dong...
However, due to his memory loss, he may be
unemotionally stable and can act unpredictably.
So you need to make sure
he doesn't receive stress.
Yes. We understand, doctor.
Father, I'm so glad.
Hee-dong, he said I'm not lying, right?
Doctor, I'm not lying, right?
Yes, you're not lying.
Hee-dong, can you take my dad outside?
Sure. Father, let's go get something to drink.
Sure.
Doctor, sometimes, my father
gets uncontrollably aggressive.
Please prescribe a strong sedative
for us to use in emergency situations.
How nice is it that he's sleeping so calmly?
I'm glad you went to the hospital today.
The doctor prescribed it to him.
Who will say anything about it?
Hi, Mr. Heo.
How about we send
Mr. Lee Jang-go to train abroad?
Train abroad?
Yes. There's a program at our company
that sends employees to train abroad.
How about we send him to
a faraway place, with the exception
of nearby countries like China
and Japan, like America or Europe?
I couldn't even fire him
because of my grandfather.
Sending him to train abroad
seems like a good idea.
Yes.
But I heard that the deadline to apply
to train abroad has already passed.
I can get a spot open in Britain.
Really?
Then take care of that immediately.
Yes, I'll do that.
Did you apply to go train in Britain?
Pardon? Train in Britain?
No, I didn't apply.
Is that so?
Then that's odd.
I heard that Mr. Gong was
supposed to go train in Britain this time,
but you've been selected to go.
Me?
Are you sure you're not misinformed?
No. The human resources team
made the decision right now.
They said you've been
selected to go train in Britain.
Look here.
Is that true?
Is Jang-go really going to train in Britain?
Yes. Are you that happy?
Chung-ja, thank you so much!
I was so upset because of Jang-go
lately because he didn't get a divorce.
Your son didn't get
a divorce? Didn't you say
last time that he went to
the court to get a divorce?
You don't even know the half of it.
He didn't go to court.
Really?
But if he goes to train in
Britain this time, he won't be able
to see her. Out of sight,
out of mind. This is great news!
That Mi-poong girl must
have held your son back.
You must have been so upset!
What's the point of talking about it?
Anyways, I'll make sure
to separate them this time.
Chung-ja, thank you.
But how did Jang-go get such an opportunity?
My daughter-in-law said there was a spot
available, so I quickly recommended your son.
Chung-ja, thank you so much!
What are friends for?
Besides, you and I are in-laws, too.
Please be good to Hee-ra!
Oh, don't you worry about her! I'm taking
care of her like she's my daughter!
Kim Yoo-sung!
What is it, Yoo-jin?
Do you have cards?
Cards? Yes, I do.
Then can I have some? Mr. Kim
told me to bring the cards you made.
Okay, but he must really love cards.
Yes, he loves them a lot.
First, take these. I have more in my backpack.
Okay, thanks.
Mr. Kim! Mr. Kim!
You're home, Yoo-jin?
Were you taking a nap?
I don't know.
Strangely enough, I feel
sleepy even if I keep sleeping.
Yoo-sung gave these to me, Mr. Kim.
Did Yoo-sung really give these to you?
Yes, he did.
That's strange.
This isn't it.
There really was a paper
that was looking for Kim Dae-hoon.
My mother's ring was on it, too.
This isn't it...
Mr. Kim, what's wrong?
This isn't it.
Mr. Kim, are you crying?
Yoo-jin...
I must really be ill...
Don't cry, Mr. Kim.
You're not crazy at all.
Yoo-jin...
Come in.
Mr. Jo...
Hi, Yoo-jin. Did you have
a good time at school?
What's wrong?
Mr. Kim is crying.
My father-in-law is crying?
Yes.
He wanted cards from Yoo-sung,
so I brought them to him,
but after he unfolded them, he started to cry.
He said he thinks he might be ill and cried.
My father-in-law is a bit sick.
Why?
He went through something traumatic
in the past, and after that, he's been ill.
I'll play with him a lot so
that he won't get lonely.
You're so kind.
Hi, mom.
What are you doing here?
You're bothering my son.
It's fine. She's not bothering me.
I need to talk to you.
What do you need to tell me?
Why do you keep Yoo-jin here?
- Why are you suddenly asking me that?
- Suddenly, whatever!
Aren't you two going to have a baby?
Why aren't you thinking about having a baby?
Why are you only thinking about Yoo-jin?
Mom, why are you being like this to her?
Please treat her nicely.
I'm going to raise Yoo-jin like she's my child.
Oh, you caused this trouble!
Anyways, I can let you do that,
but you can't adopt her. You better
not put her on the family registry!
Mom, Yoo-jin will hear you.
Okay, fine! I'll be good to her,
so hurry up and have a baby!
I'm saying this because I'm worried you two
aren't going to have a baby because of Yoo-jin!
Mom, don't worry.
We're making a lot of effort right now.
Look at this. Shin-ae
is waiting for our baby, too.
Really? She is?
Of course.
Okay.
Oh, dear. I wonder what you'll have
to do to quickly have a baby!
Come in.
Mr. Jo.
Hi.
This is the persimmon punch we'll be
giving out during the winter season. Try it.
It's not that sweet. It's good.
Okay then.
Hold on.
Is Ms. Joo doing well?
She opened up a dumpling diner,
and it's starting to settle down now.
A dumpling diner?
(Father's Dumplings)
(Congratulations on opening up your business)
- I'm back.
- Hi.
Where'd you get that plant from?
It was in front of the diner.
There's a ribbon to congratulate us, too.
I wonder who left that there.
Is it Jang-go, by any chance?
Mom, would Jang-go have just left it here?
If it was Jang-go, he would have showed off
about it and asked, "Mother, do you like this?"
You're right.
Mom, this plant is small but pretty.
Since there's a green plant here,
it seems like the diner got a lot brighter.
I think we'll have a lot of blessings.
I know.
I wonder who had left it here.
It would have been nice
if he or she could have
come in for some dumpling soup.
Is it someone's birthday today?
I don't think it is. What day is it today?
Why did you prepare a feast?
Jang-go is going to go train in Britain.
- Britain?
Oh my gosh. Isn't that where Ha-yeon is?
Yes, it is, Nam-yi.
What do you mean Jang-go is going to Britain?
His company is going to send him
to train so that he can study more.
Hee-ra's mom said she helped him out a lot.
My mom?
- I'm back.
- Hi.
Hey, Jang-go, is it true
that you're going to Britain?
No, grandma.
What do you mean no?
The company said they were
going to send you to train there.
I did get the offer,
but I told them I couldn't go.
Did you really?
There are so many people who want to go there!
Why? Why can't you go?
Mom, I have a lot of things to do here.
What? Things to do? What kind of things?
What kind of things are you
doing here that won't allow you to go?
Everyone else is trying so hard to go there!
Why would you reject such a great offer?
Is this because of Mi-poong?
Stop it, please.
If you feel so bad about it, then you can go.
- I'm going to my room.
- Oh my goodness!
Mother. Nam-yi. Am I the wrong one here?
How could he refuse such a great offer?
Jang-go said he has a lot of things to do here.
He must have some kind of plan.
Oh my god. This is unbelievable.
Grandma.
Jang-go, sit down for a moment.
Jang-go,
it's great that your company is offering
to send you to train abroad in Britain.
Are you refusing to go because of Mi-poong?
Then how about you two go together?
The two of you can go live there together.
Just think of it as moving out of the house.
Go, study, and work together.
You can live a happy
newlywed life there with Mi-poong.
Grandma, Mi-poong won't go.
She's searching for her father right now.
How could she go so far away?
Just bring it up.
She won't find him overnight.
There's no guarantee he's even here either.
Ask her about it, okay?
- Okay, grandma.
- Good.
How could he give up such a good opportunity?
And all because of that wench, too!
She's the worst enemy out there!
Disgusting.
Oh my goodness.
(Father's Dumplings)
What brings you here again?
I didn't come here to argue with you today.
I have something to tell you.
Please sit down.
Jang-go has the opportunity
to go train in Britain.
Did you hear about that?
No, I didn't.
Yes. I assumed he didn't tell you.
But Jang-go said he won't go.
I think it's because of you.
Mi-poong, you've worked at a
company before, so you know how it is.
Not everyone is given the
opportunity to go train abroad.
With the company's support,
he can study more and gain
more experience.
It'll be a good opportunity for him.
Shouldn't Jang-go go to train
abroad for the sake of his future?
But why are you telling me this?
Please help me.
Please help him go train abroad.
If I was harsh to you all this time,
please forget about it.
Please persuade Jang-go.
Please help me so that
he can be free from you...
So that he can have a bright future now...
What are you doing here?
I stopped by because I had
something to discuss with Mi-poong.
Mi-poong, I'm begging you. Okay?
Mi-poong, why did she come here?
What did she do to you this time?
It's nothing like that, mom.
What on earth did she say to that makes
you look so lost? Hurry up and tell me.
Mom, it's nothing like that.
Mom, I'm going out for a little bit.
- Mr. Han.
- Yes?
About training abroad in Britain...
I don't think I'll be able to go. You should
give the opportunity to someone else.
You're going to reject such a good opportunity?
Are you sure?
Yes.
All right.
(Little Tadpole)
Jang-go, can we meet?
Oh, Kim Mi-poong!
What a surprise. You asked to meet me first.
It's lunchtime, so why did you
want to meet at a coffee shop?
Let's go eat lunch.
I'll buy you something delicious.
Jang-go, I didn't come here to eat lunch.
What is it now? You're being scary.
You're lowering your voice, too.
I have a favor to ask of you.
You must do it for me.
A favor?
Mi-poong, don't say a word.
I'll never do this favor for you. Got it?
I said I'm not going to do it. I don't want to!
You don't even know what it is,
so how could you say no right away?
You're the one who made me this way.
Don't you remember?
You did this last time, too.
It was the same.
You lowered your voice
and made everything moody, too.
"Please do this favor for me."
And what favor was it?
You asked for a divorce!
When I think of that, my heart still...
No. I'm never going to do it for you.
Don't even bring it up.
- Jang-go.
- Whatever.
Jang-go!
What is it? What is it that
it's making you so serious?
Tell me. Let me hear about it.
Go to Britain.
Good opportunities like
that don't come every day.
Did you meet my mother?
Did my mother say something to you?
It's not like that.
She was nice about it when she asked me to
persuade you to go to Britain to train abroad.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
And your mother is hundred percent right.
If I had a son and he refused
a great opportunity
because of a girl, I would get mad, too.
Anyways, Mi-poong,
that offer is off the table now.
I already told the company I wouldn't go.
Already?
Why did you do that?
If you did that because
you're worrying about me, don't.
I'll be well until you finish
your studies and come back.
So go back to your company
and tell them you'll go!
Where would I go without you?
I want to stay by your side.
Mi-poong! Kim Mi-poong!
Mi-poong!
What's wrong?
I'm so grateful and sorry to you.
How much more are you
going to make me feel sorry?
What did I say? Married couples
are one in body and soul.
Did you ever see the body and soul separate?
Married couples shouldn't be thankful
to each other because it's natural.
So there's nothing to feel sorry about either.
Don't be delusional!
I still haven't changed
my mind about divorcing you.
If I don't agree to the divorce,
we can't get one! You'll have to sue me!
Do you know how hard it is to sue someone?
If it was me, I'd rather just live
together instead of suing my partner.
I don't want to talk to you! I hate lawyers!
It's freezing.
Hold still.
Kim Mi-poong, what's the point of
becoming rich and successful by myself?
I'm going to live as a stupid fish
next to you for the rest of my life.
Hold still!
Let go!
Soo-jung!
Did Soo-jung discharge from the hospital?
It's not that...
This early morning...
Pardon?
Soo-jung was very kind and angel-like.
(Kang Soo-jung)
Mr. Lee Jang-go!
Hold on!
Thank you for coming.
My daughter liked you a lot.
Before she died, she told me...
that I was the coolest dad in the world.
I don't think I should be
shameful dad to my daughter in heaven.
I'll tell you the truth now.
Pardon?
It was hard to refuse
Ms. Park Shin-ae's offer because
of the surgery bills for
my one and only daughter.
We failed to falsely accuse
Ms. Kim Mi-poong for the box incident,
but in the condition that I didn't reveal
Ms. Park Shin-ae was behind this,
I received money.
It's late, but please tell Ms. Kim Mi-poong
that I'm sorry I tried to falsely accuse her.
I'm sorry.
Jang-go, what's all this?
Jang-go, is this Mr. Kang from last time?
Then he committed the box incident because
she wanted to falsely accuse me on purpose?
Yes.
If what we heard is true, it's certain
that Ms. Park Shin-ae is behind this.
What did you say? Why would she...?
(Blow Breeze)
Why is the Golden Spoon of Pyeongyang doing
this to a mere homeless one from the north?
I brought fresh tangerines- oh my god!
I was doing leg exercises like this.
Sorry!
I'm going to sell him off to the shrimp boat!
All I can do is sleep, father.
Dae-hoon!
- There isn't "you and I"
in married couples. It's "us."
- Married couples?
What do you mean you
want us to empty the diner?
Who are you?
- You little...
- Mi-poong!
Jang-go! Jang-go!
Subtitles by OnDemandKorea