Subtitles by OnDemandKorea
(Episode 46)
Why do you keep treating
me like I'm a little kid?
Just stay put!
Why are you giving me a hard time?
Please just stay stuck at home!
No matter how much I think of
it, you're not my daughter.
I told you not to say that.
If you keep doing that, I'm going to
lock you up in a mental institution.
I'm going to throw you away
where no one can find you!
What...
did I just hear?
Father!
What?
Lock him up in a mental institution?
Throw him away where no one can find him?
Did you just say those things
to your father right now?
T-That's because...
he wasn't listening to me and
kept insisting he would go out.
I must have said those things because
I was so upset. I'm sorry, grandfather.
How could you say such cruel things to your
father who helped bring you into this world?
No matter how mentally insufficient he is...
how could you say those things to him when,
you're not a stranger, but his child?
Do you not feel pity for
your father who returned from death?
I'm sorry, grandfather.
I'm sorry. I'll never do it again.
If you...
act cruelly to your father...
one more time...
I won't be able to forgive you,
even if you're my granddaughter.
Do you understand?
Yes, grandfather.
Go.
Okay.
Father...
Yes, yes. It's okay now. You're okay now.
He didn't hear that I was
an imposter, did he?
If he had, he wouldn't have
just ended it with this.
Dae-hoon,
it is completely Shin-ae's fault
for mistreating you like this,
but you also need to make an effort
so that she can't do that to you.
You're Shin-ae's father.
As a father, you must keep your dignity.
Don't pester her like a little child.
You didn't hold onto
her hand, so you got lost.
That's why she's getting angry at you.
No, father. I don't want
to hold hands with her.
Dae-hoon.
I think Shin-ae is an imposter.
- What?
- Ms. Joo and Ms. Chun
said that Shin-ae is an imposter.
What?
An imposter?
Who said such a thing?
Shin-ae said I shouldn't tell you this.
It's fine, so tell me.
So the truth is, father...
the old woman who lived here before
said that Shin-ae is an imposter.
But they said she had misspoken
because she had dementia...
But I still think Shin-ae is an imposter.
What does all of this mean?
Chung-ja, are you in here?
Oh, yes, Mr. Kim.
What brings you here?
Did your mother have dementia
while she was staying at our house?
Pardon?
No, she didn't.
I heard that you and your mother
had said Shin-ae is an imposter.
What is that all about?
According to Dae-hoon, your mother
had said such a thing.
Imposter?
I have no idea what you're talking about.
You mean she has never said that before?
Did she, perhaps, go
around saying that Shin-ae
isn't my granddaughter
because she disliked her?
Oh, that!
The truth is, my mom was
showing signs of dementia.
I hid the fact from you because
I felt awkward telling you about it.
That's why she went to the countryside.
He must have heard my mom
saying strange things.
Then...
are you saying she called Shin-ae an
imposter because she has dementia?
I think so.
Or else, how would she say
such a thing in her sane mind?
That wouldn't make any sense.
You got the results that Shin-ae is really
your granddaughter through the DNA test.
All right.
Oh my gosh. I don't think I'll be able
to live long because of that idiot!
Honey! Young-ae! Honey!
Honey, where are you?
Can't you appear in front
of me one more time?
Then I'll never lose you again.
(Home Shopping Consignment Contract)
You made the right decision.
All you have to do now is sign the contract.
All the details we had requested
for are clearly written in here.
Mi-poong, sign here.
The first impressions are important, and
I have a great feeling about this one.
There will be good results.
(Kim Mi-poong)
Here.
Here you go.
Please take good care of us.
- We should be the ones saying that.
- Please take good care of us.
Are you that happy, mother?
I'm more fascinated than happy.
It seems like yesterday
we had been running away
from being caught doing
business by the subway.
Mom, this feels like a dream to me, too.
Now we'll appear on home
shopping, find father,
and hit jackpot on our dumpling business.
Just thinking about it
makes me very, very happy.
Jang-go, thank you so much.
This is all thanks to you.
No way, mother.
How is this thanks to me? This happened
because of your delicious dumplings.
No. We were able to come this far
because you stayed by our side.
You became a cane by our side.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
So Jang-go, I was thinking...
we could have dinner here
with your family tonight.
Mom, that's a great idea!
- Right?
- Should we?
- Should I give them a call?
- Yes, go ahead!
Hi, grandma. Hold on. You can
talk to my mother-in-law.
Oh, hello, ma'am!
Hello!
Really?
Oh, that's great!
Congratulations!
I'll pray for your success.
Thank you, ma'am.
I was calling you because I wanted
to ask if you and your family would
like to come over to my
diner for dinner tonight.
You're inviting us to celebrate something
good, so of course we'll come.
I'll bring my entire family over tonight.
Okay. See you later. Bye.
What are you so happy about?
Were you invited somewhere for dinner?
Yes, well, the thing is...
Something great has happened,
so you can congratulate them...
and use this opportunity to get rid of
your pent-up antagonism towards them.
Let's go together. Okay?
Antagonism?
Mother, are you...?
Yes, yes.
To celebrate their home
shopping contract, Mi-poong's
family has invited our
family over for dinner.
That woman is so strange.
She invited us for dinner?
Is she insane?
My goodness. Why would you speak so rudely?
Aside from everything else, they
worked so hard all this time.
What's wrong with eating dinner with them to
celebrate something good
that has happened to them?
Mother, don't go there.
What?
It's fine if you don't go, but
why tell me not to go either?
Are you ordering your mother-in-law around?
Why would you go there, mother?
What do we have to do with them?
We're strangers now.
We're not strangers yet.
I beg your pardon?
They're still in their consideration period.
So Mi-poong is still this family's
daughter-in-law. If something good
has happened to our in-laws, we should
definitely go congratulate them.
How dare you tell me not to go.
My goodness.
If you keep this up, I...
can't live with you!
You insolent thing!
You no-good-at-all wench! Fine!
Let's split up! Split up!
I don't want to live with you either!
Mr. Kim, are you okay?
Hi, Nam-yi.
Won-bin, I told you that I
don't want to come here.
I'm going now.
Tell your father not to use
you to call me here again.
Nam-yi, my father was
wrong yesterday, but you
should still talk to him to work things out.
Go ahead and talk. I'll be going now.
Like I told you yesterday, I really
don't think we're meant to be.
I'll be going then. Good-bye.
We're...
meant to be!
Oh, my.
Is that the ring that went
into your mouth yesterday?
Yes, you're right! It's the
ring you prepared for us!
But where did you get that ring from?
You had definitely eaten it yesterday!
Did you...?
No way.
How...?
Have you been well, Mr. Kim?
It's been a while, Mr. Cha.
What brings you here?
I have some business with the law firm here.
I was going to contact you anyways.
Why?
Is there something I should know about?
It's about your granddaughter
entering into your family registry.
There's a procedure, so the earliest
I can get it done is in a month.
All right.
I know you wanted it done as
soon as possible. I'm sorry.
What do you mean?
I never said that.
Pardon?
Mr. Jo's wife, who lives with your
granddaughter, called me directly.
She said that you're in a hurry,
so she wants me to enter your
granddaughter into your family
registry as soon as possible.
What?
I think Shin-ae is an imposter.
Ms. Joo and Ms. Chun said
that Shin-ae is an imposter.
Mr. Jo's wife, who lives with your
granddaughter, called me directly.
She said that you're in a hurry,
so she wants me to enter your
granddaughter into your family
registry as soon as possible.
Does Shin-ae want me to die quickly?
(99.99% Match. Kim Dae-hoon and Park
Shin-ae are father and daughter.)
I must have become doubtful
because of my old age.
She's my one and only granddaughter.
My bloodline.
Shin-ae is getting very
stressed because of Dae-hoon.
Yes, yes.
I should understand.
By the way, Yoo-jin, is
Shin-ae nice to you nowadays?
Yes, she is.
Really?
She doesn't get angry at you?
No. As long as I call her
mom only when it's just the
two of us, she neither scolds
me nor gets angry at me.
Is that so?
But Mr. Kim,
you didn't tell anyone that
Aunt Shin-ae is my real mom, right?
Of course I didn't.
I promised to keep this a secret.
I won't tell anyone, so don't worry.
Father.
What do mean?
Yoo-jin.
What do you mean
Aunt Shin-ae is your real mom?
T-That's...
N-No, Hee-dong.
We didn't say anything.
Yoo-jin isn't Shin-ae's daughter.
She really isn't.
Right, Yoo-jin?
He's right!
I'm not my mom's daughter. Really!
Yoo-jin.
It's not true.
If my mom finds out about this...
I mean...
If Aunt Shin-ae finds out about this,
I'll be in big trouble!
Yoo-jin is...?
Yoo-jin, what do we do?
This secret was only supposed
to be between the three of us.
If Shin-ae finds out we were caught by
Hee-dong, she won't just sit and watch. Right?
Then Mr. Kim,
should I call mom and confess to
her that we got caught by Mr. Jo?
Oh, no! You can't! You can't, Yoo-jin!
Do you know how scary Shin-ae is?
If Shin-ae finds out about this, you
might really be kicked out this time!
Really?
Mr. Kim, I don't want to be kicked out!
I don't want to be separated from you!
Mr. Kim!
Don't cry. Don't cry, Yoo-jin.
I don't want to be
separated from you either.
So don't cry.
I don't want to go back to the orphanage.
Don't cry, Yoo-jin.
I'll protect you.
I'll take care of everything, so don't cry.
Just trust me. Okay?
How?
Yes, come in.
Hee-dong...
can I come in?
Of course, father. Come on in.
It seems like you have something
to tell me. Go ahead.
I have a favor to ask of you.
You must do it for me, okay?
What favor? I should do it.
So, the thing is, Hee-dong...
About what you heard earlier...
About Yoo-jin being Shin-ae's daughter.
You can never tell anyone, okay?
Pardon?
Why?
That was a secret between
Yoo-jin and Shin-ae.
But I found out, and Yoo-jin got in trouble.
And Yoo-jin almost got kicked out
of this house because of that.
So if you act like you know about it, she
might really be kicked out this time.
I couldn't even tell my
father because of that.
Anyways, you'll keep this
a secret, won't you?
You can never tell anyone
about it, all right?
Yoo-jin, I'm here. What are
you doing here by yourself?
Come with me. A great man came today.
You can say hi to him and-
I can't see you.
Go, Hee-dong.
What do you mean you can't see me?
Did someone tell you not to see me?
Since Shin-ae and Yoo-jin are
wearing the same headbands...
they look exactly alike.
They're like mom and daughter.
Joo-ri, do you have a boyfriend?
Are you still single?
I'm a divorcee.
Oh. You were married before.
What about kids?
I have a daughter and son.
Oh, really?
I thought you were single!
Who would think you have kids already?
Thank you for seeing it that way.
There's nothing I have to worry about.
She's twelve years older
than Jang-soo, and on top of
that, she's a divorcee with a
daughter and a son already.
Hi, Jang-soo!
What? Go where with you?
Wasn't Jang-go going to get a divorce?
I won't go there.
The one who is planning to get a divorce but
invites her in-laws to dinner is a fool.
The one who accepts the invitation
and goes there is a fool, too.
Did they decide to cancel the divorce?
Gosh. My mother-in-law was waiting
anxiously for Jang-go to get divorced.
She must be disappointed.
- Be careful.
- Be careful. Whoa!
- We should turn the gas on.
- Yes.
Mi-poong, take these.
Aunt Nam-yi!
- Welcome!
- Thanks. Hello.
Hi!
My mother told me you opened up this
diner, but I get to come here now.
Your business is doing well enough to
enter home shopping. Congratulations.
- Here's cake.
- You didn't have to bring anything. Thank you.
Wow! It's cake. What kind of cake is it?
I picked the strawberry cream cake.
Is that okay?
Yes, it's okay. I love strawberries.
- Please sit here.
- Sure.
Why did you make so much?
- It's no joke, right, aunt?
- Right.
Please eat.
But Mi-poong, how did you think
about entering home shopping?
Oh, no. I didn't think of it.
Jang-soo, you got it wrong.
Home shopping found out
about these dumplings and
came to look for them.
Oh, really?
Of course.
At the senior center I go to, one
of the old ladies' son was trying
so hard to enter home shopping,
but in the end, he couldn't.
I heard it's like trying to pluck a star
from the sky. You're amazing, Ms. Joo.
The only thing I know how
to do is make dumplings.
This happened because Jang-go helped us.
Oh, no. It happened because
the dumplings are delicious.
I hope everything works out
and that you'll succeed.
I hope you'll find your husband as well.
Yes. Thank you.
Then to congratulate Mi-poong's
family's entrance into home shopping...
Cheers!
- Cheers!
- Good luck!
- Congratulations!
- Thank you. Please eat a lot.
If you act cruelly to your
father one more time, I won't
be able to forgive you, even
if you're my granddaughter.
Yes.
No matter how much I hate Kim Dae-hoon,
I can't make grandfather doubt me
until I'm on his family registry.
I need to get along with him, as if
we're really father and daughter.
- Yay! Cookies! Cookies! Cookies!
- Cookies!
Dad, say ah.
How is it?
It's very, very delicious, Shin-ae!
- Really?
- Yes!
Yoo-jin, you, too. Say ah.
Wow! Aunt, it melts right in my mouth!
Right? It's really delicious, isn't it?
Yes, Mr. Kim!
This is the first time I'm
eating such a delicious cookie.
- Really?
- It's so delicious.
Dad, I'm sorry for what
happened in the morning.
I'm sorry.
No, Shin-ae.
My father said I'm an adult, but I pestered
you like I was a little kid. I'm sorry.
I won't do that anymore, okay?
No, dad. I'm sorry.
Thank you, dad.
What are you guys doing over there?
Grandfather!
Father, did you have a good day?
Yes.
We were making cookies.
- Cookies?
- Here.
Try one.
How is it? It tastes
extremely delicious, right?
Yes. It's very delicious.
Wow. The smell of something
delicious is filling the air.
Oh my goodness! You made cookies!
- Yes, mother.
- Shin-ae made cookies.
You can't compare these to the
ones you buy at the market.
Your daughter is the best. She
made cookies just for you.
Honey, say ah. Try it.
Forget it. I'll eat it myself.
Everyone is here but Hee-dong.
Did he say he'll be late today?
No. He'll be home soon.
Save some for Hee-dong.
Yes, mother.
Yoo-jin, let's make a hundred of these.
The test results are out.
(DNA Report)
(DNA Report of Test Results)
(DNA Test Results)
(99.99% Match. Park Shin-ae and
Kang Yoo-jin are mother and daughter.)
Mom.
Are you eating rice in water?
With just kimchi?
Goodness. We ate our fill of meat, stir-fried
glass noodles, and dumpling hot pot.
Hey. Try this at least.
Ms. Joo packed this food for you.
Why would I eat this?
Then don't eat it.
Your loss.
Come on, grandma. Don't be like that.
Mom, she packed it for you. Try it.
Look. These stir-fried glass
noodles are very delicious and the
mung bean pancakes are to die for.
Totally North Korean style.
Try it-
Jang-soo, do you really want
to go there and be like that?
Don't you know that your
brother got a divorce?
How could all of you be so thoughtless!
Yes. You're so noble with
your thoughts, so you
should eat rice in water
with just that kimchi.
Jang-soo, put all of these
in the refrigerator.
I'll eat them deliciously by myself!
I'll put these over there.
The wind is blowing so hard,
and it's freezing out here!
Why did you want to come here?
Mi-poong.
Are you cold? Come here.
How come your ways to get
physical contact are
becoming more and more
sneaky as you get older?
You want to hug and kiss with
every opportunity you get.
Just say what you have to say.
I'm freezing to death.
Kim Mi-poong, close your eyes.
Why do you keep telling me to close my eyes?
Just say it. I'm cold.
Hey! How can you be so tactless?
If a guy tells you to close
his eyes to create a
mood, don't you have the
sense to go along with it?
Any other man would've ran
away a long time ago.
I'm the only one willing
to stick around you.
If you're going to keep being so
ridiculous, I'm going to leave first.
Okay, okay!
All right. All right.
Take out your hand.
- Why?
- Just hurry up and take out your hand!
What's this?
Can't you tell? It's a ring.
It's to commemorate a fresh start
for you and a new beginning for us.
I was going to propose to you by saying
that we should never separate again.
It's all ruined because of you.
Jang-go.
What?
All this time, I was really struggling.
But I was able to endure it because of you.
I was really mean to you.
Thank you for not leaving
me and staying by my side.
At least you know.
If you had done this from
the beginning, I would've
put the ring on you and
we would've kissed. How nice-
Gosh, it's cold!
The season silently leaves
I'm silently crying
I miss you, I miss you so much
The one person who crashes into the empty air
The one person
What happened?
Did Hee-dong not come home last night?
Is he sleeping in his studio?
He didn't even call me.
He has never done this before.
The person you are trying
to reach is unavailable.
He's not answering his phone.
Did he get into an accident?
Hee-dong.
Where were you?
Where did you sleep last night?
Hee-dong, did something happen?
Hee-dong.
Hee-dong, what are you doing?
Are you going somewhere?
Hee-dong, why are you doing this? You need
to tell me so that I know what's going on.
Shin-ae.
Let's get a divorce.
What did you say?
A divorce?
Why...?
Hee-dong, what's wrong with you?
What's this?
(99.99% Match. Park Shin-ae and
Kang Yoo-jin are mother and daughter.)
Yoo-jin is your daughter, isn't she?
Hee-dong...
I don't think I'll be able
to live with you anymore.
Hee-dong! Hee-dong...
I don't want to hear any excuse.
I don't want to know why you abandoned
Yoo-jin in the orphanage to deceive me.
My feelings for you are all broken now.
I won't be able to understand any
of your excuses, so don't stop me.
Hee-dong...
H-hee-dong!
Hee-dong! Hee-dong!
I'll call you as soon as the
divorce papers are ready.
What are you talking about? Divorce papers?
Mom, I'm going to divorce her.
Just know that. I'll tell
you the details later.
Hey...Hee-dong! Hee-dong!
Hee-dong! Hee-dong-
What happened to you two?
What does he mean divorce?
Did you two fight?
Why is Hee-dong suddenly acting like that?
Does Hee-dong have another woman?
Is he having an affair?
It's nothing like that.
Of course not! Hee-dong would
never do such a thing!
Then what is it?
Did you do something wrong?
Of course not!
Then why would Hee-dong mention divorce?
For what reason?
I nagged him about going on a
business trip. That's why.
What? You nagged him?
Goodness. He wouldn't bring up divorce
for such a reason. Don't be ridiculous.
Hold on.
Is there something you're hiding from me?
What would I hide from you?
Then why is Hee-dong acting that way?
This is strange.
Yoo-jin, did you tell Mr. Jo
Hee-dong that I'm your mom? Did you?
I didn't tell him myself.
He overheard Mr. Kim Dae-hoon and I talking.
What?
That's why I told you not to
tell anyone that I'm your mom.
I told you to be careful!
What are you going to do now?
Do you want Mr. Jo Hee-dong to find
out everything and divorce me?
No.
No. I'm sorry.
It's okay. Everything will be okay.
I'm sorry.
(Father's Dumplings)
- Here, mom. Let's try these.
- Okay.
It's so strange.
We made it the same way we make it in the
diner, so why does it taste different?
It's because the factory
make it in massive amounts.
What can we do?
Mom, the biggest problem we
have is the smell of pork.
If we want to get rid of it,
shouldn't we put in more ginger?
That would be a good way,
but people don't like it.
We can dice the ginger into tiny
bits and put them in there.
Our dumplings are aromatic and chewy,
but how come these aren't like that?
Are we missing any ingredients?
Or did we leave something out?
Give me the recipe.
Mi-poong, look here. It was this.
We mix dried bean curd and tofu
together, but here, they only used raw
tofu, so that's why it didn't have
that aromatic and chewy taste.
Oh, I see. I'll go to the factory
and tell the factory manager.
Don't worry.
(Breakdown of Purchasing Funds of
Winner's Group's Hope Welfare Center)
I'm Lawyer Lee Jang-go from
the Inspection Division.
(Please approve this/Inspection Division)
Please give this to the chairman.
Sure.
(Please approve this/Inspection Division)
Hi, mom.
Your friend wants legal advice?
All right. I'll be on my way.
You were desperate, so I
arranged this meeting,
but I don't know if I should be doing this.
It's not like your son and your
daughter-in-law are completely over yet.
Don't even mention her.
They're over already.
Anyways, I'm doing this
because I trust you, so
make sure you don't put me
in a troubling position.
Oh, all right. Don't worry.
But is she really such a fine young lady?
Yes.
Dr. Yoon's father is the director of a
famous hospital in Gangnam, and she owns
several properties in Gangnam, so she
doesn't care about the man's wealth.
To be honest, Dr. Yoon isn't someone
who would come to such a meeting, but
she is a divorcee, like your son, so
that's why she's coming out today.
Doctor. Daughter of a hospital director.
Building.
Anyways, this family
doesn't look at money.
Only the personality. Your son
has a fine personality.
Of course! He's kind,
amiable, and good-looking!
Jang-go won't lose to anyone.
She said she needed legal advice, so I
used that as an excuse to bring her here.
Thanks, Young-soon. You're the best!
Hello.
Have a seat.
This is Lawyer Lee Jang-go's mother.
She's my friend.
We came together. That's
okay with you, isn't it?
Of course.
Hello.
I hope you get good legal
advice from my son.
You can get more comfortable
with each other,
and it'd be great if you
two became good friends.
- Mom.
- Hi.
Hello. Hello.
You know my friend Ms. Lee
Young-soon, don't you?
Of course. Hello.
This young lady is Ms. Lee's
best friend's daughter.
She said she needed legal advice, so
Ms. Lee asked me to ask you for help.
Is that okay with you?
That's fine.
Jang-go, give her good legal advice, for
the sake of me and my friend. Okay?
Okay.
Hey, we should go grocery shopping.
Yes.
- Have a good counseling session, Dr. Yoon.
- Okay.
She's more calm and pure than
you told me she is. I like her!
I told you so. Besides being a divorcee,
she doesn't have any other flaw.
Anyways, I hope it works out well. If
it does, I'll buy you a nice dinner.
All right, but I still
feel guilty about this.
Their divorce isn't final yet. What will
we do later on if something goes wrong?
Their divorce will be finalized once
the consideration period is over.
I'll go with him this time if I have to and
make sure he gets divorced, so don't worry
All right.
Let's go.
You bought land in Jeju-do to build a villa?
Yes, but there's a cemetery on that land, so
they said I can't construct anything there.
The one who sold the land to me said
he can't return the deposit to me.
What can I do in this
situation to get it back?
Did you bring the contract with you?
No, I couldn't because I came
straight from the hospital.
Then can you send me the contract?
I'll examine it and try to find a solution.
Yes. I'll find the contract
and send it to you.
Okay.
What would you like to eat?
No. I'm fine.
You're giving me legal advice, so if you
go without eating, I'll feel too guilty.
I'll buy you lunch as a
means of thanking you.
I'm really fine though...
Please give us Course A.
Are you serious?
She really likes Jang-go?
Really?
She likes how thoughtful Jang-go is?
Oh, I hope it works out well!
Okay. Bye.
Hey.
Did something good happen?
Yes. I heard good news.
What good news?
Jang-go is going to have a good woman.
A woman who is far better than Mi-poong.
Dream on.
Jang-go and Mi-poong will never break up.
Jang-go and Mi-poong exchanged rings
yesterday and decided to start over again.
So wake up from your silly dream.
What? Exchanged rings?
Mother.
It's that ring, the one
you got from Jang-go.
You-
Mi-poong, I don't want to
get angry at you anymore.
Let's talk with the facts.
You and Jang-go broke up.
You said you were going to divorce him.
Then you two should start new lives.
Jang-go needs to meet a good woman.
You should meet a new
man, too. Both of you should
go your own ways in life.
Why would you exchange rings?
You and Jang-go can't be together.
So give me that ring.
Take it off. Take off that ring.
Mother, Jang-go gave me this ring.
I can never take it off.
What?
You can't take it off?
Take it off right now.
- Take off that ring right now!
- Mother, why are you doing this?
How can you be so stubborn?
Did you or did you not promise to separate
from Jang-go after getting the $50,000?
Is $50,000 not enough?
Why are you clinging onto Jang-go? Why?
How much more do you want from him?
- Give me that ring!
- Why are you dong this?
Goodness! Why are you being like this?
Why are you here again
upsetting my daughter?
If you have eyes, you
should take a good look.
I don't want to drag this out anymore.
Just take that ring off her
hand and give it to me.
I'm sorry, but I can't do that.
Jang-go and Mi-poong are both grown adults.
Why do you keep meddling into their affairs?
Does it look like I can't meddle?
I didn't want to say this, but it's all
Mi-poong's fault that Jang-go got hurt!
He got hurt because Mi-poong's
fortune has widowhood and a
white tiger in it, so she's
bound to destroy a man's life!
But you want me to leave my son to be
with her? She's going to destroy him!
What? What did you say?
Who destroys who?
How can you say such crude things?
If you really don't want Jang-go
and Mi-poong seeing each other,
then you can tie him up at home!
I don't have the confidence
to stop Jang-go from coming
to see Mi-poong, so you
stop him from coming here!
Mom!
Outrageous!
So that means the both of you are
going to ruin my son's future.
What stubborn creatures you are!
- Give me that ring!
- Why are you doing this?
Let go of this hand!
How dare you push me!
- What's wrong with you?
- Why are you doing this?
- Give it to me!
- What do you think you're doing at my diner?
- Get out!
- Mom!
- If you come here one more time,
I'll call the cops on you!
- Mom!
What the heck do you think you're doing?
My goodness. What does
she think she's doing?
Are you all right?
I didn't ask for you to come here
so that I can give you an excuse.
But I wanted to tell you why I did that.
When Yoo-jin first came to Korea,
I didn't care about other people,
but I was scared you would
find out about her.
I was scared you would get hurt like this.
So is that why you sent
Yoo-jin to the orphanage?
You lied to everyone.
You even made little Yoo-jin lie.
For what reason?
Why?
Because you would be disappointed in me.
I didn't want to tell you
about my pathetic past.
I love you so much.
That's why I did that.
Hee-dong, please believe that.
I don't understand you.
And I can't...
believe anything you say anymore.
Let's meet at court as soon as possible.
Hee-dong.
I don't want to divorce you.
Hee-dong, forgive me just this once.
Hee-dong, trust me just this once.
If grandfather finds out, he'll
be disappointed and doubt me.
Mother won't just sit still. What do I do?
Still, Hee-dong won't tell anyone the
reason of our divorce for Yoo-jin's sake.
Never.
I have to make sure he can never say it.
Yoo-jin, what are you doing?
Let's watch a cartoon movie.
I'm sorry, Mr. Kim.
Watch it by yourself.
What's wrong? Why are you packing your bag?
Are you going somewhere?
I'm going to go back to the orphanage.
What do you mean?
You said you didn't want
to go to the orphanage.
I think my mom and Mr. Jo are going
to get a divorce because of me.
What?
That's why I must leave this house.
That way, mom and Mr.
Jo won't get a divorce.
Shin-ae and Hee-dong are going
to get a divorce because of you?
Hi, it's me.
Father, it's an emergency!
Hurry up and come home! Hurry!
Emergency?
What emergency?
Because of Yoo-jin, Shin-ae and
Hee-dong are going to get a divorce.
So Yoo-jin is packing her bag
to go back to the orphanage.
So come here quickly and make
sure Shin-ae and Hee-dong can't
get a divorce! And make sure
Yoo-jin can still live with us!
I can't live without Yoo-jin, father!
And since Yoo-jin is Shin-ae's daughter,
doesn't that mean she's my granddaughter?
Dae-hoon, what are you talking about?
Yes?
Grandfather.
Have a seat.
Okay.
Shin-ae, why didn't you tell me?
Why did you hide it?
What do you mean...?
I heard Yoo-jin is your daughter.
Grandfather...
If Yoo-jin is your daughter, then
she's my great-granddaughter.
How can you hide this from me?
I understand you hiding this from everyone
else, but you should have told me.
I'm sorry, grandfather.
I couldn't tell you because I
knew you would be disappointed.
How can you say that? I'm not a stranger.
I'm your grandfather.
I'm your grandfather who can
embrace all your flaws.
Why didn't you tell me? Why?
I'm sorry.
Fortunately, I had brought
Yoo-jin home that time.
What if I hadn't brought her? She would
have still been at that orphanage.
That was why I was going to adopt her.
What? What do you mean adopt her?
How can you say such a thing?
You were going to adopt the
child you gave birth to?
Grandfather, I love Hee-dong.
I did that because I was scared Hee-dong
would be disappointed and leave me.
Grandfather, please help me.
Hee-dong wants to get a divorce.
I can't live without Hee-dong.
Grandfather, please stop Hee-dong.
Hee-dong, why are you suddenly
talking about divorce?
Do you have another woman?
No, right? Then why do you
want to get a divorce?
Hurry up and come home before
your father or Mr. Kim finds out.
Mother.
I'll tell you the reason later.
- I'm sorry.
- Seriously, what's wrong with you?
Do you want to see me die?
I can endure everything else, but I
can't see you go through a divorce.
Even if you won't be able to get
in touch with me, don't worry.
No, Hee-dong!
You can't find a woman like
Shin-ae anywhere in this world!
Shin-ae was very good to you.
She's very good to me, too.
Hey, look at this necklace.
Shin-ae bought it for me.
Hee-dong, I can't live without Shin-ae.
- If you divorce her, I'll bite my tongue and die!
- Mom.
Mr. Kim's inheritance will all become yours
later on. Are you going to give that up?
Do you want me to continue living with
Shin-ae just for grandfather's inheritance?
That's not all...
You like Shin-ae. You love her.
How can love change?
Hi, grandfather.
Right now?
All right.
Does Mr. Kim want to see you right now?
Shin-ae must have told Mr. Kim.
Now that Mr. Kim stepped in,
I won't have to worry about divorce.
Hee-dong,
must you get a divorce?
I'm sorry, grandfather.
She suffered through all sorts of
things while escaping North Korea.
This was something that had happened
in her past before she met you.
I know it might be hard, but can't
you understand her just this once?
Didn't you want to adopt Yoo-jin, too?
My heart breaks when I think of Yoo-jin.
I feel so sorry for her.
But...
everything is so difficult for
me right now, grandfather.
I feel like all the time I
spent with Shin-ae is a lie.
Everything seems fake.
Can't you forgive her just
this one time for my sake?
So...
you're saying that Yoo-jin is a kid that
Shin-ae had with another man, right?
That's what you're saying
right now, isn't it?
How could she deceive all of us?
How could this happen?
I'm sorry, grandfather.
Hee-dong! Hee-dong! Hee-dong!
Hee-dong! Hee-dong!
How can this happen?
How? How can this happen? What
do I do about my poor Hee-dong?
How can Shin-ae lie to me as well?
I'm her grandfather.
Hi, Mr. Choi.
There's something I must urgently
report to you about your granddaughter.
What?
About my granddaughter?
This is a report of Ms. Park
Shin-ae's embezzlement.
And this document is about the slush
fund she has asked Mr. Heo to prepare.
What?
Slush fund?
Embezzlement?
My granddaughter did those things?
Why is Shin-ae preparing a slush fund?
For what reason?
Like Dae-hoon had said, is she
not my real granddaughter?
Are you saying your mother called Shin-ae
an imposter because she has dementia?
Or else, how would she say such a thing in
her sane mind? That wouldn't make any sense.
You got the results that Shin-ae is really
your granddaughter through the DNA test.
The only ones who know about
Shin-ae's DNA test is Dal-ho and me.
How did she know about that?
Hi, Dal-ho. It's me.
Hello, Mr. Kim.
About Shin-ae's DNA test last time...
Did you tell your wife about it?
No. We had decided to keep
that between ourselves.
Are you sure?
You really didn't tell anyone?
What's wrong?
Dal-ho, come home at once.
Something is wrong.
Oh, my. Mother, what's wrong?
Mother, what do you think you're doing?
Tell me yourself.
Is Yoo-jin your daughter?
I thought this was about something else.
Are you like this because of that?
You wicked wench! You dirty wench!
How could you hide your
child and marry Hee-dong?
You deserve to die! My kind
Hee-dong didn't know she was
your real daughter. He hugged,
carried, and played with her!
If I think of that, I won't be
able to rest in peace when I die!
Yes. Yoo-jin is my daughter.
But that happened in the past
before I had met Hee-dong.
Tell anyone who has never had
a past before to come out!
And did I have an affair while
I was living with Hee-dong?
How dare you talk back!
How dare a nobody like you barge into
my home and break my son's heart!
You dirty wench!
I'm going to reveal that you're not
Mr. Kim's real granddaughter!
It's the end for you!
Do whatever you want!
Do you think I'll go down by myself?
You'll go down with me!
If I go under, do you think you'll be safe?
Go ahead and reveal that
I'm an imposter if you can!
What?
S-shin-ae... i-is an imposter?
She's... not... my granddaughter?
(Blow Breeze)
Get out!
I'm not going to leave even if I die!
I really do love Hee-dong.
Who said I wanted to hear such a thing?
Let's be honest.
The entire inheritance will
be split directly in half!
Please open this door.
I promised to prove your innocence.
Here.
It's so delicious. I can tell
this is going to be a big hit.
Father, let's make sure we meet.
Subtitles by OnDemandKorea