Subtitles by OnDemandKorea
(Episode 47)
Mother, what do you think you're doing?
Tell me yourself.
Is Yoo-jin your daughter? Is she?
I thought this was about something else.
Are you acting like this because of that?
You wicked wench! You dirty wench!
How could you hide your
child and marry Hee-dong?
You deserve to die! My kind
Hee-dong didn't know she was
your real daughter. He hugged,
carried, and played with her!
If I think about that, I won't be
able to rest in peace when I die!
Yes. Yoo-jin is my daughter.
But that was from the past
before I had met Hee-dong.
There isn't anyone without
a past in this world!
And did I have an affair while
I was living with Hee-dong?
How dare you talk back!
How dare a nobody like you barge into
my home and break my son's heart!
You dirty wench!
I'm going to reveal that you're not
Mr. Kim's real granddaughter!
It will be the end for you!
Do whatever you want!
Do you think I'll go down by myself?
You'll go down with me!
If I go under, do you think you'll be safe?
Go ahead and reveal that I'm
an imposter if you can!
Shin-ae is an imposter?
Why would I die? Did I pretend
to be his granddaughter?
You should be struck by thunder!
Don't you dare curse at me!
You don't deserve to curse at me!
I'll just...!
- Father.
- Mr. Kim.
- Father! Father!
- Ms. Ma! Ms. Ma!
Father!
Shin-ae, father collapsed!
Father! Father, open your eyes!
Grandfather! Dad, what's wrong with him?
Grandfather! Grandfather, wake up!
What are you doing? Call 119!
- Mr. Kim!
- Dal-ho.
- Is this 119? Please hurry up
and come here. Hurry!
- Father.
- Grandfather!
Father!
Hello?
What? You have information
about James Kang?
Someone who fits James Kang's
description has showed up.
His name is Kang Kyeong-cheol,
and he's thirty-nine years old.
He's been in jail four times for fraud.
It seems
like he's the James Kang
you've been searching for.
Where is he right now?
He was witnessed in
Beijing not too long ago.
- Beijing?
- Yes.
But someone else has sued him for fraud,
so they're still investigating him.
I'll contact you as soon as we catch him.
Please help me.
- Mom!
- Yes?
- The samples of our frozen dumplings are out.
- Really?
I hope it'll taste right this time.
- Let's hurry up and steam this,
so we can taste them.
- Okay.
Wow! It's delicious.
It tastes exactly like
your dumplings, grandma.
Really? Do they really
taste the same, Yoo-sung?
- Yup!
- Mi-poong, what do you think?
I think they do taste similar.
It's not exactly the same as our
handmade dumplings, but it's similar.
Yes!
I think we'll be able to sell our
dumplings on home shopping now.
- Is it good?
- Mom, we should tell our customers to try some.
Sure.
Hello. This is for free. Please try them.
- Is this a new kind of dumplings?
- No, these are the
frozen dumplings that will be
sold on Rainbow Home Shopping.
Oh, really?
- It's so delicious.
- It's really good!
- It is?
- Yes.
They don't seem like frozen dumplings.
- Thank you.
- Enjoy.
Father.
Mr. Kim didn't faint after
he heard us talking, did he?
No, that's not it. He fainted
a lot of times before, too.
Yes. He just fainted like last time.
If he had overheard
mother and me talking, he
would've barged into the
room and started screaming.
But that old man seems to be in
a critical condition this time.
Father...
If he passes away, then what
happens to all that inheritance?
That sly fox isn't even on
his family register yet.
Does that mean that idiot
gets the inheritance?
Father.
What happens if grandfather
passes away now?
What will I do?
How can I quickly get the
inheritance in my hands?
Dal-ho, why isn't my father coming out?
Please call the people who
took my father in there.
Tell them to bring my father out quickly!
Dae-hoon, Mr. Kim fainted a few times,
but he has overcome all of them.
He'll be safe this time as well.
Just wait a little bit longer.
Will my father really be all right?
Of course!
Of course, Dae-hoon!
Doctor, the surgery...?
Thanks to your quick response, the
cerebral hemorrhage surgery went well.
However, because this was a
spontaneous hemorrhage due to the
cardiovascular disorder that he
had, he's not completely safe yet.
Does he need another
cardiovascular surgery?
Anymore surgeries would overtax him.
Dr. Yang is doing his best in the cardiovascular
area, so let's wait for the results.
All right.
Dal-ho, didn't the doctor say
that the surgery had gone well?
But why isn't my father opening his eyes?
- Father, open your eyes. Father...
- Sir, you can't do this here.
The patient needs complete
rest, so only one person
should stay to take care
of him for the night.
All right.
Father.
Chung-ja, take Shin-ae and Dae-hoon
home with you. I'll stay here.
Okay.
No. I'm not going to leave. I'm
going to stay here with father.
I won't cry.
I won't talk either.
Don't tell me to leave, Dal-ho. Please?
Dad, go home with us. We
can come back tomorrow.
No! I'm never going to leave! Never!
I'm going to protect my father.
Father.
All right. You can stay with me.
You can go home with Shin-ae.
All right.
This is for the better.
Yoo-jin,
from now on,
I won't let you go through
a hard time by yourself.
Grandfather didn't hear everything
mother and I said, did he?
No.
Even if he did, there are the DNA results,
so he won't suspect me as an imposter.
You terrible...
What's wrong with you, mother?
If you don't want to humiliate yourself
in front of your daughter, follow me.
I don't even know what Hee-dong is doing
right now, but you're here with your child?
I don't even know who her father is, yet
you took care of her in my son's room!
You wicked thing!
It's enough that you tempted me and
made me do all the dirty, evil work!
How can you dirty my son's life as well?
Mother, you should talk straight,
no matter what the situation is.
You teamed up with me because
you coveted grandfather's
inheritance! I never
tempted you into anything!
What did you say?
I'm letting you slide this time
because of Hee-dong, but if
you do something like this
again, I won't hold back then.
I won't hold back anymore!
You imposter!
Fine!
What are you going to do if you
can't hold back? What will you do?
I can't forgive a stubborn one like
you either, so get out of my house!
Get out! Get out! I said get out!
I can't leave!
I told you that I would
never leave this house as
long as I'm alive! I'll
never leave even if I die!
So if you don't want to
see me, you get out!
You!
I'm the crazy one! I deserve to die!
I'm the fool for being used
by a spiteful wench like her!
Who would I blame for this?
Goodness! My poor Hee-dong! What will I do?
Get out! Get out this instant!
The person you are trying
to reach is unavailable.
After the tone, please leave a message.
Why is Hee-dong's phone off?
How did he end up meeting a woman like her?
No, no. This is all my fault.
Hee-dong won't be thinking about doing
something harmful to himself, will he?
Hee-dong, it's all my fault.
I'm sorry, so please hurry home.
Dal-ho, please rest here.
No.
I'm not going to sleep.
Until my father wakes up,
I'm never going to sleep.
Dal-ho.
You heard what the doctor said
when he dropped by earlier.
Mr. Kim underwent such a big surgery that
it'll take some time for him to wake up.
- So, Dae-hoon...
- Father, I'm sorry.
If only I hadn't called you, you
wouldn't have collapsed like this.
This is all my fault.
A call?
What did you call him about?
The truth is, today, Hee-dong found out
that Yoo-jin is Shin-ae's daughter.
Pardon?
Hee-dong said he was going
to get a divorce, so I
called my father to tell
him to stop Hee-dong.
This is why my father collapsed.
Because he was shocked.
Dae-hoon, Yoo-jin is Shin-ae's daughter?
Yes.
So then Hee-dong said
he would get a divorce?
Yes.
Hello?
Hello, sir.
Yes, thank you.
All right.
(Missed Calls)
Hee-dong, your grandfather-in-law
has collapsed.
Hello, dad? What do you
mean grandfather collapsed?
Mi-poong.
Where did you get that ring?
I never saw it before.
Did Jang-go give it to you?
Yes, mom.
I see.
So you decided to not get divorced?
Then what else do I do?
Jang-go sticks to my side
like gum and won't leave.
Good. You made the right
decision, Mi-poong.
When the consideration period
ended at the end of this month,
I thought you would go to
court again, so I was scared.
But mom, I don't know if I'm really
doing the right thing or not.
My mother-in-law still doesn't accept me.
You did the right thing. When
your mother-in-law sees you and
Jang-go living happily together,
she'll open up her heart one day.
Mother! Yoo-sung!
Speaking of the devil...
Isn't that Jang-go?
It's cold!
Welcome, Jang-go! It's cold outside,
isn't it? Did you eat dinner yet?
It's so cold, mother.
But did something good happen?
You look really happy.
Oh, really? Was it obvious?
Of course!
What is it?
Jang-go, thank you for changing
Mi-poong's mind. Thank you so much.
I should be the one who
is more grateful to you.
Even though I come here every
day, you always welcome me.
That's why I brought your
favorite strawberries.
Hi, Mi-poong.
What about Yoo-sung?
He's asleep.
What are you doing here at this hour?
You should go home early and sleep.
What? Mother, you heard her, didn't you?
Please scold her!
You little...!
- Jang-go, have a seat.
- Okay.
How does it taste?
It's so delicious.
These are really the frozen
dumplings from the factory?
Yes. I brought them from the factory today.
Wow! Mother, I can see these are
going to be a big hit already.
- Really? Are they really delicious?
- Yes, they are!
Did you get the broadcast date?
This Friday at 5:00 p.m.
Friday at 5:00 p.m?
It's the time when people would be hungry.
It's a good time.
But will the factory be able to
meet the supply demands by Friday?
The factory manager said he would
do whatever he can to meet them.
Oh, poor Mi-poong. You'll have to live
in the factory for the time being.
That's why I'm worried.
My mother will have a hard
time at the diner by herself.
Oh,dear.Don't worry about me.
I can manage alone.
Why are you alone?
You have me. When I'm done with
work, I'll come to the diner.
Goodness, no. I can do it by myself.
Don't worry about it.
Mother, I'm really fine.
Use me like I'm your servant!
Okay, Jang-go. Thank you
for your kind words.
Mother, this is really good.
What did you need to tell me?
The police caught James Kang.
- James Kang?
- Yes.
You mean the con-artist who said
he had bought my designs from me?
Yes.
He was spotted in China. He's being investigated
right now, so just wait a little bit.
Jang-go...
were you investigating this all this time?
Of course.
I promised you I would
prove your innocence.
Jang-go, thank you.
What's up with you?
You're hugging me first.
I'm just grateful to you for everything.
You can't live without me, huh?
Then don't just express
yourself with just words.
Here.
You got a call.
I don't have to answer it. Hurry!
Don't pucker your lips whenever you want.
Just quickly answer your phone.
Gosh. Who is calling me
during this important time?
Hello? This is Lee Jang-go.
You sent the contract?
All right. I'll check it.
Bye.
Who is it?
It sounded like a woman.
Oh, I'm doing legal advice
for her as my mom's request.
What? Are you jealous?
Yeah, right.
It's late, so go home!
All right. I'll go. Why do
you keep telling me to go?
I'll go after we finish what we started.
Finish what?
What else?
Hurry up and go home.
Gosh. I just had to get
a call at this time.
It's too bad.
- I'm home.
- Jang-go, why are you so late?
What about dinner?
- I already ate.
- Wait, Jang-go.
What is it?
About Dr. Yoon...
You must have given her
great legal counseling
because she called
Ms. Lee to say thank you.
I did?
She didn't even bring the contract,
so I didn't do anything for her.
She didn't bring the contract?
Then you'll have to meet her
again with the contract.
She sent it to me by e-mail,
so I said I'd check it.
Good. Check it carefully and
give her good legal advice.
Don't treat her in such
a business-like manner.
Eat dinner and drink tea
with her, too. Okay?
Why should I go that far?
Mom, did you...?
Did I what?
I'm just saying. This is my
friend's request, so you should
be extra nice to Dr. Yoon so
that I won't be embarrassed.
Be good to her for my sake.
All right. I'll be going in now.
It's true that Yoo-jin
is Shin-ae's daughter?
Yes.
How...?
I didn't think Shin-ae was like that.
How can she deceive the
entire family all this time?
That's right.
Yoo-jin calls Shin-ae her aunt.
Then Yoo-jin doesn't know
that Shin-ae is her mom?
Did Yoo-jin know everything, too?
She knew and pretended
Shin-ae wasn't her mom?
It wasn't enough that she
deceived you from the beginning.
It wasn't like she secretly hid Yoo-jin.
She lived with Yoo-jin.
Yet, how could she make
that child lie like that?
About Shin-ae's DNA test...
Did you tell your wife about it?
Did he tell me to come
home to tell me this?
But why did he suddenly
bring up the DNA test?
What are you talking about?
Huh?
Oh, it's nothing.
Father...
you promised to live with
me for a long, long time.
So please don't die.
You can't die, just like mother did. Okay?
Mother,
please save father.
Father is very sick.
Mother, you'll save him, won't you?
Mother...
Father...
I can't bring myself under
in order to drag her down.
Then it'd be too unfair.
Right!
What is it?
We need to talk.
Aren't you going to drink the tea?
I just made it.
I didn't put any poison in
it, so you can drink it.
I know what you're going to say.
You do? You're quick-witted.
I'm sorry for deceiving you
and Hee-dong all this time.
I had no choice to do that because I love
Hee-dong and I didn't want to hurt him.
I truly do love Hee-dong.
Love?
Because you love him?
Love...
Did I say I wanted to hear that from you?
How dare you say you love Hee-dong!
I dare you to say such
a thing one more time!
Did you bring in another man's child into
Hee-dong's life because you loved him?
Love? Love!
You little...
Let's be honest.
Fine.
Go ahead and talk.
You frightening nine-tailed fox!
If you want to make a deal
with me, don't curse at me.
Fine.
Anyways, since things turned out this way,
I'll allow Yoo-jin to live in this house.
However, you can never adopt
her under Hee-dong's name.
Got that?
And once you become the
heiress of Winner's Group,
all of the inheritance will
be divided exactly in half.
If you agree, I'll keep
my mouth shut until then.
If you don't agree...
I'll reveal everything.
What will you choose?
Fine.
We'll do that.
It's great that you're cool about this.
Let's write a contract.
A contract?
Yes.
Why would I just trust your words?
Hold on.
You better be careful so
that you won't get caught.
Speak for yourself.
"The Contract."
"Superior: Ma Chung-ja."
"The superior will get
half of the inheritance."
Oh my goodness!
I should've done this sooner!
Hee-dong, take your father-in-law to eat.
I'll stay here.
All right.
Father, you should eat.
I'm okay. I'm not hungry.
Dae-hoon, you'll get sick at this rate.
Go eat with Hee-dong. I'll stay
here, so you don't have to worry.
The two of you can go eat.
- Doctor, why isn't my father waking up?
- Yesterday, you said the surgery went well.
There are some cases of patients who undergo
brain surgery to gain conscious late.
It might also be because of his old age.
For now, let's wait and see.
Yes, doctor.
Dal-ho, what if my father doesn't wake up?
Father...
Oh, Hee-dong!
When did you come here? Do you
know how worried I was about you?
I came yesterday.
But Mr. Kim hasn't woken up yet?
The surgery went well, so
why isn't he waking up yet?
This happens sometimes for patients
who went through brain surgery.
That's right! My friend's
mom went through brain
surgery last time and didn't
wake up for ten days!
Grandfather...
We need to talk.
Did you know?
That Yoo-jin was Shin-ae's daughter?
I didn't know either.
How would I know something
you didn't know about?
Did Hee-dong tell you he
would get a divorce, too?
When I think about how
Shin-ae deceived us and
made us into fools, I
get extremely furious,
but isn't divorce the wrong answer?
She lied like nothing was wrong.
We don't know
what she'll lie about next.
We can't trust her.
Gosh. If she wasn't
Mr. Kim's granddaughter...
But thinking about it from
a woman's point-of-view,
I guess I can understand why she did that.
She did that because she liked Hee-dong
but was afraid to disappoint him.
Honey, we should at least understand her.
Hee-dong got very hurt this time.
Time will heal all the pain.
Anyways, they can't get a divorce.
Don't get in the way. Let
Hee-dong take care of it.
Still!
I told you to bring clothes for Dae-hoon
and me. Did you come empty-handed?
Oh, no. I forgot.
Where's your head?
Okay, I'll go bring it right now.
The kids can never get a divorce. Okay?
It's that ring. The ring
that Jang-go gave you.
I'll take that ring out no matter what.
Oh my goodness. She's such a headache.
She better not block
Jang-go's future this time.
Geum-sil.
What brings you here?
Geum-sil, I'm going to rest here.
Oh my goodness. I'm so exhausted.
What would you be exhausted about?
Does your
son or daughter-in-law
give you a hard time?
There's no one else with
a better life than you.
Gosh, I'm sorry for complaining when
I have a better life than everyone.
What's wrong?
Did you fight with your husband again?
Mr. Kim collapsed.
Really? Is he okay?
We don't know yet.
He had a surgery for a brain
hemorrhage, but he didn't wake up yet.
Then I should go visit him
with my mother-in-law.
Do you want to do that? Then we
can go together in my car later.
That's great. It's cold outside.
Geum-sil, I'm hungry. Do
you have anything to eat?
All I had was a cup of coffee
in the morning, so I'm dizzy.
You didn't eat anything yet?
- Yes.
- Oh, my. Hold on.
Oh my goodness.
Look at this beef stock.
Hey, where are these dumplings from?
They're delicious.
- Did you make them?
- No, Mi-poong did.
Since you said it's delicious, I
guess it really is delicious.
Their diner became famous, and now
they're appearing on home shopping.
Home shopping?
Yes. They're going to appear on home shopping
to sell dumplings and find her father.
What?
Find her father?
Won't home shopping be broadcasted
all over the country?
That's right.
I saw her father when I was in Macau, too.
They were living well there. Why did they
have to escape and get connected with us?
- My goodness.
- Wait a minute. Geum-sil, did you
see her father's face, too?
Yes. Jang-go and Mi-poong
went to the same school.
Her dad had these big and bright eyes. When
I see him, I'll notice him right away.
Mother.
You came again.
I'm glad you're here.
Mr. Kim collapsed. You're going to
visit him at the hospital, aren't you?
Oh, he did? Then of course I should go.
We can go in my friend's car.
That's great. It's cold outside.
Excuse us, please.
Geum-sil, I need to go. There's
an emergency I must take care of.
Chung-ja, we're supposed to go
with you to visit the hospital.
No, don't come. It's cold.
- We have many visitors at the hospital.
Don't come, okay? Don't come!
- Chung-ja.
We should just go together. What's wrong?
Don't come!
What's wrong with her, mother?
Goodness. She's a strange one.
She has a few screws loose in her head.
My goodness.
All of us hope that
Mr. Kim will recover soon.
Thank you for coming.
Thank you.
Going down.
First floor. The doors are closing.
Hee-dong.
Thank you.
Grandfather is family to me, too.
I came for him, not for you,
so don't get any thoughts.
I know.
You probably don't want
to see me right now.
However, aside from everything else,
stay by my side, for the sake
of grandfather and Yoo-jin.
I'm begging you.
We'll talk about our issue
once grandfather wakes up.
Hi, mother.
Where are you right now?
We're in big trouble!
Big trouble?
Mother!
Is it true that Mi-poong is going to
search for her dad on home shopping?
That's what I heard.
Home shopping is broadcasted all
over the country, isn't it?
That's not the problem right now.
Geum-sil said
she knows what Mi-poong's dad looks like.
Her family said they would
come visit the hospital.
Shouldn't that idiot not
be in the hospital then?
If Geum-sil sees him, it's game over!
What do we do?
- Pork made 100% in Korea.
- Along with beef made 100% in Korea.
- They're excellently mixed in
a perfect ratio along with...
- Wow. Looks delicious.
This is soft and delicious
grilled short rib patties.
Father, when are you going to wake up?
Hurry up and wake up so that
you can buy me that. Please?
South Korea has many interesting shows.
Home shopping!
Hey! Why did you turn that off?
I was watching that right now!
Dad, why would you watch home shopping?
It's no fun.
Why else would I watch it?
Because it's fun.
When I see food with my eyes, it feels
like I'm eating it, so I get happy.
Hurry up and turn it back on.
Dad, let's go out. I'll buy you
grilled short rib patties.
No.
I can never leave father alone.
My father-in-law and Hee-dong are
going to come back in a bit.
They're going to come right back
after they pay the hospital fee.
Yes, Dae-hoon. I'll stay here, so go and eat
grilled short rib patties with Shin-ae.
Grilled short rib patties just melt
in your mouth! They're so delicious!
No. I'm just going to watch
TV and stay with father.
I had bread a while ago,
so I'm not hungry at all.
Dad, come with me.
I don't want to eat them! So why
do you keep trying to take me?
Are you really not going to listen to me?
I told you that I wouldn't let you
go if you don't listen to me.
Shin-ae, why are you doing this again?
You promised to not act
like this to me again.
My father is listening
to everything right now.
When my father gets up, I'm not going
to let you get away with this.
Dad, to be honest, it's because of Yoo-jin.
Yoo-jin?
What about her?
She's sick.
That's why I'm not bringing her
here, but she wants to see you.
Yoo-jin is sick?
Really?
Yes.
All right.
Father, I'm going to go home for a bit.
I'm going to see Yoo-jin
and come back soon.
Shin-ae, let's go.
See you later.
He's easy to coax because
he's like a child.
My goodness. That was close.
Gosh. Now I can live.
- Yoo-jin! Yoo-jin! Yoo-jin!
- Yoo-jin isn't back from school yet.
Wasn't she sick?
Dad, she must have felt
better and went to school.
She went to school, so why did
you lie that she was sick?
No, dad. I didn't lie.
Yoo-jin was sick earlier, wasn't she?
Yes...
I'm going to go back to the hospital.
Hurry up and take me back to my father.
Hurry!
When Yoo-jin comes home, play with her.
Then I'll take you there after work.
No! I'm going to go there right now!
I'm going to go to my father!
I'm going to go by myself.
I have the card, so I can
take a taxi by myself.
Dad, what's wrong with you?
Shin-ae, why are you doing this again?
- That's mine, so give it back.
- Go to your room right now!
Right this minute!
O-Okay...
Stay here until I come back from work!
- You got it?
- Y-Yes...
Make sure you watch my dad so
that he doesn't go anywhere.
All right...
Gosh, what's wrong with her?
It doesn't matter if he lost his memory
and became a child. He's still her dad!
Isn't she being too mean?
That evil witch!
Shin-ae definitely isn't my daughter.
When father wakes up, I'm
going to tell him everything!
Father...
hurry up and wake up.
Our produce are great! You
can trust and use them.
Mister, we can't use these.
It might be troublesome, but please
take this back and bring us a new one.
- Why?
- What do you mean why?
Look. The tails are festered, and
the heads are turning yellow.
No. That can't be. They were
just picked last night.
No way. I don't know what happened,
but these bean sprouts are old.
If we use these, the dumplings will
smell and be too tough to eat.
Come on. You're being too picky.
Everyone else just let it slide.
I don't know about other places,
but we can't use such produce.
Half of the taste comes from ingredients.
Even if we have to pay more,
please bring us the best produce.
All right. I'll be back in an hour.
Yes. Please bring us your best.
Mister, I'm going to check very thoroughly.
Please bring us clean, fresh bean sprouts.
All right.
Bye.
Will you be able to meet the
supply demand by this Friday?
You don't have to worry about such a thing.
All the factory machines
are fully working on dumplings,
so that shouldn't be a problem.
Is there any way we can help?
The dumpling recipe has been finalized.
We'll call you if anything happens, so
just make sure you answer your phone.
Don't worry about that.
We'll be ready 24/7.
When you call us, we'll be here right away.
Then we'll put our faith in you.
Are you sure? It's this week?
I'm sure. It's scheduled to be
on air this Friday at 5:00 p.m.
Mr. Heo, don't ask me why. You need to stop
Kim Mi-poong's program from going on air.
If the program is aired, you
and I are both screwed.
So stop it no matter what!
Yes. I'll block the program
using whatever means I can.
Should I have visited the hospital, too?
You should have brought me with you.
You're working here.
I went, so it's fine.
Goodness. Poor old man.
He found his son and granddaughter. It would
be nice if he lived happily with them.
- Do you think he'll pass away?
- How would I know that?
The heavens choose the man's fate.
If he's destined to live, he'll
live no matter what. If he's
destined to die, he'll die no matter what.
That's what life is.
It's about time for Mr. Kim to come.
But why are you still here?
You said you were going to end things with
him because he ate your proposal ring.
I decided not to.
He found the ring.
What?
He found the ring?
How did he find the ring that he ate?
Oh, I don't know. Don't ask me.
Hey. So it went in here
and went out there...
Oh my god. How repulsive!
Don't think about it, mom!
Nam-yi!
Hello, ma'am.
Nam-yi, I brought your favorite ice cream.
But if Mr. Kim passes away, what will
happen to that enormous inheritance?
Will it be given to his granddaughter
who is Chung-ja's daughter-in-law?
Come on. He found his son.
His son is alive, so how can it
be given to his granddaughter?
That's right! He had a son! I forgot.
But I didn't see his son
in the hospital room.
The thing is, Mr. Kim's son has
a bit of a mental problem.
What problem?
Pretend you don't know anything.
The truth is, Mr. Kim's
son's mind comes and goes.
Because of the trauma he
received from the gunshot while
escaping, he lost his memories
and thinks he's ten-years-old.
- Oh my goodness!
That's why Chung-ja is about to go mad!
He's an old man with white hair, but
he acts like a ten-year-old kid.
He acts like he's the owner of that house
and gives Chung-ja such a hard time!
Really?
I guess it'd be troublesome to
live with someone like that.
What if he's not able to inherit that
money because he's mentally unstable?
You know, things like being
declared incompetent.
Geum-sil, since your son
is a lawyer, ask him.
In this case, would it be the father or the
granddaughter who gets the inheritance?
That's right. I think I
heard something about this.
Oh my goodness! Chung-ja might hit jackpot!
But Chung-ja seemed like she
was dying at the hospital.
What's wrong with her? Is she
worried about something?
Hey. The elder she served her
entire life might lose his life.
Of course she's serious.
Yeah, right! It makes more sense that she's
anxious he won't pass
away this time either!
Oh, come on! How can you say that?
By the way, did your son mention
anything about Dr. Yoon?
Dr. Yoon? Who's that?
Geum-sil kept pestering me, so I
arranged a meeting for her son.
She's the daughter of the
director of a famous
hospital in Gangnam. She's a dermatologist.
So what happened?
Nothing happened. They just met once.
I hope things will work out
between them this time.
Goodness. I heard they're going to meet
up again. I don't know what will happen.
Father...
Um...
You must be hungry.
Eat this.
No.
If you don't eat, I'll get in trouble.
I'll leave this here, so please eat.
This won't do.
If father wakes up, and he
doesn't see me, he'll worry.
Mister, is this really the
way to Saetbyul Hospital?
I told you that it was. How
many times are you asking me?
I see.
My card! Card wallet!
Shin-ae took it from me.
Mister, I don't have my card.
Can I pay you when my father wakes up?
Are you joking? Get out right now!
Okay...
Mister, my father is very wealthy.
- Get out.
- Okay.
Where am I?
I don't have my cell-phone or my card.
Where the heck am I?
Ma'am! Ma'am!
Ma'am, where did my dad go?
He's not in there?
He's not! That's why I'm asking you!
I told you to watch him carefully!
Where are you going?
My dad is missing.
Again?
What if he went to the hospital?
Hello?
Yes. That's my grandfather.
Where?
I'm sorry, Shin-ae.
We're going to the hospital, aren't we?
You're taking me to my father, aren't you?
Gosh, he's so darn disobedient!
Open the door! Open the door!
Good job. Here.
Shin-ae! Ms. Ma!
Please open this door for me.
Don't open the door for him, except
for when you're going to feed him.
Don't worry. I'm going
to stick by his side.
Shin-ae! Ms. Ma!
Please open the door! Please!
Please open this door! Shin-ae!
Shin-ae, I'm sorry. Okay? I won't do
it ever again, so open this door!
Open this door!
I'm going to go to my father!
Open this door, Shin-ae!
Ms. Ma!
Mother. Yoo-sung. Watch carefully.
Mi-poong, I'm going to start.
I heard there's a deep story
behind these Father's Dumplings.
Oh, yes.
To be honest, my mom and I
are North Korean defectors.
When we escaped, my father suffered a
gunshot wound, so we thought he had died.
Not too long ago, we saw
that he was alive in Seoul.
Wow. That's shocking news.
Please tell us about your father.
Okay.
My father's name is Kim Dae-hoon.
He has big and bright eyes. He's of medium
height, and he speaks in
a North Korean accent.
If you've seen someone like
that, please contact us.
Please help us find my father.
All right. Your father might be watching this
program, so please say something to him.
Father...
I'm Seung-hee.
Mother, Yoo-sung, and I are all
desperately waiting for you.
Until we meet again,
please be healthy.
Father, let's meet again.
Wow, you're really good, aunt!
You're amazing!
Yoo-sung, if your aunt speaks like that, do
you think your grandfather will call us?
Yes, he'll definitely call us.
Good job. Do exactly this tomorrow.
Jang-go, I'm so nervous. It's a live
broadcast tomorrow. What if I mess up?
Not again.
You did well. Just keep going.
- Right, mother?
- Yes. You did well.
One more time?
One more time.
- Ms. Ma!
- Oh my goodness.
Go and do something about him!
How can he not get tired?
- What did he eat that he has so much energy?
- I'm going to go to my father!
Anyways, Mi-poong's
program is going to be on
air soon. What are you
going to do about that?
Goodness. There's obstacle after obstacle.
He still didn't find a way to stop it?
This can never happen! If
that program is aired,
my husband, Hee-dong, or
anyone else could see it!
Then Mi-poong becomes the
real granddaughter, and
you'll be revealed to the
world as an imposter!
Mother! Watch what you're saying!
What if someone
hears us outside? What will you do then?
Fine! I'll be careful!
Hi, Mr. Heo. Did you find a way?
How can you still be looking for a way?
Find it right now! Right now!
Open this door...
I'm going to go to my father...
I'm going to go to my father.
Shin-ae.
Open this door.
Father...
- Father...
- Ma'am?
What's this sound?
The thing is...
Shin-ae...
What's that?
Is Dae-hoon locked in there right now?
Who the heck did such a thing?
Where's the key?
Your wife and your daughter-in-law...
What?
Park Shin-ae!
Ma Chung-ja!
Isn't that your father-in-law?
- Hey!
- Oh my gosh!
What the hell did you do?
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry.
- Where's the key.
- Here...
Honey. Honey!
Dal-ho!
Yes, Dae-hoon. You're okay now.
You're safe.
Dal-ho!
How could you do such a thing?
He snuck out and got lost again!
That's why we did this!
- It hasn't even been an hour
since we locked him up in there.
- Hey, Ma Chung-ja!
Do you want to die?
Is he a criminal or a beast?
How could you do such a thing?
Shin-ae, you shouldn't do this. How
could you do this to your dad?
I had an important meeting,
but my dad got lost again...
Do you think that makes any sense?
Was that meeting so important? Was
it more important than your dad?
You're a really nasty piece of work!
Father, you're being too harsh.
What? I'm being too harsh?
Would you act this way if he really
was your biological brother?
Is it okay with you if my dad gets lost?
Will you take responsibility
if he gets lost?
Yes. I'll take responsibility!
Dae-hoon, let's go.
Father!
Father, I'm here.
Father, I missed you.
Father.
Father...
Are you going somewhere looking like that?
Do you have an audition?
Oh, it's not an audition.
Something similar to that.
Yeah, right.
Mother, Jang-soo is going
to become a dumpling-eating
model for his ex-sister-in-law
at home shopping!
What? Is that true?
Are you crazy?
Jang-soo, are you ready? Let's go.
Are you going to Mi-poong's
home shopping broadcast, too?
They asked us to be models who eat
dumplings, so we're going over there. Happy?
Ridiculous.
Mother!
What?
We're family, so we should
help out when we can.
I won't ask you to come
with us, so stop nagging.
Make sure you watch Rainbow
Home Shopping at 5:00 tonight.
Check if I look pretty or not.
- Hey, let's go.
- Okay. Mom, Mi-poong's program starts at 5:00!
I really don't want Jang-soo to
come out in something like that!
- I'm going crazy! Oh my god!
- Does he really want to do that?
How much is it for these abundant amounts?
Yes, well...
There are three packs of Father's
Dumplings and three packs
of kimchi dumplings. A total of
six packs are all for $29.90.
If you want to make dumplings at home,
you need to make the skin and insides.
That's a lot of work.
You don't need to worry about such thing.
If you buy these Father's
Dumplings and put them
in the fridge, you won't have any problems.
We'll arrange the sets how you
like, so don't worry about it.
Please order right now.
Cut! Okay!
He said it's okay!
You did so well, Mi-poong!
- Really? I wasn't awkward?
- No! You weren't awkward at all!
You did very well!
- Mother, you look beautiful on screen.
- Really?
Grandma, you seem like a real model.
Do I really look okay?
- Of course!
- I need to eat prettily.
Jang-go, what about me?
- Of course you look cool!
- Yes!
I have no idea what I just said!
I must be out of my mind. I don't
remember anything I just said!
Mother, you did really well.
You just need to
do the same thing during
the live broadcast.
Should we do a cheer before the live show?
- Yeah, let's do that!
- Yes.
Go Father's Dumplings on one, two, three.
Go Father's Dumplings!
We're going to start!
I tried these. They're so big that you'll
feel full from just eating one of them.
- That's right.
- Not only is the taste guaranteed.
The price is, too.
The price is great. It really was
hard to meet the supply demand today.
You have the chance to be able to get
five kilograms of these for just $29.90.
- You must take this chance.
- Consumers definitely
know a good product when they see one.
The calls are coming in.
If you would like to order
- quickly, please use the home shopping app.
- Father,
after the Jeju oranges are sold,
they'll sell dumplings next.
I want to eat dumplings.
(Father's Dumplings)
Five minutes before we go on air!
(Rainbow Home Shopping)
(Five minutes later, Father's
Dumplings will be on the show)
(Blow Breeze)
Here we go!
- Let's do our best thinking that
father will be watching this show.
- Okay.
She's the chairman's granddaughter.
What do you mean I'm fired?
Are you crazy?
Yes! You two are driving me crazy!
What are you going to do about this?
Geum-sil, I'm sorry!
What's wrong with my father?
- Father!
- Mr. Kim!
What's the point of saying
that to someone who's dead?
"Someone who's dead?"
I recorded everything.
He was doing a background
search on me all this time?
Then, by any chance...?
Subtitles by OnDemandKorea