Subtitles by OnDemandKorea
If you die,
I'm going to die as well.
Father.
Dae-hoon.
Father, can you see me?
- Dae-hoon.
- I'm Dae-hoon.
Father!
Dae-hoon.
Father! Father! Father! Father!
Doctor! Doctor!
- (Episode 49)
- Congratulations on becoming
the president of Winner's Group.
Thank you, but I'm only the
acting president right now.
That's true,
but you still got up there.
And you know who you should thank for that?
Of course. I know it's all
thanks to you, mother.
I feel like I'm fishing for compliments,
but I'm grateful you know that.
So from now on, as you much as you've
done wrong, be good to Hee-dong.
That's all I want.
Yes, mother. I'll always be good to
Hee-dong and live as a good wife to him.
Later on, you shouldn't
coax my innocent son into
adopting Yoo-Jin as his child.
That can never happen.
You better keep that promise.
I will. Don't worry.
But mother, what will we do
if Hee-dong keeps refusing
to come home and insists
on getting a divorce?
He must be awfully upset to do that.
Think about it in his shoes.
What if Hee-dong had a hidden child? Wouldn't
you feel like your world fell apart?
I'm sorry.
If, like you said, your feelings for him are
sincere, then he'll come back later on.
Tell him you can never get a divorce.
Please meet Hee-dong and convince him.
All right.
Thank you, mother. Please eat a lot.
Mr. Kim is still lying there unconscious.
Now he just needs to pass away.
After we send that fool to a
hospital somewhere far in
the countryside in America,
won't it be our world now?
The steak tastes very delicious today.
- Eat some more.
- Go ahead and eat.
You're getting a call.
Why is he calling me?
Hi, dad.
What did you say?
Grandfather woke up?
What are you saying?
He's still unconscious.
Is it true that he woke up?
If he really had woken up earlier, then the
chances of him recovering are very high.
It's a good sign.
Let's wait and see.
- Thank you, doctor.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
Hey!
Is it true Mr. Kim woke up?
Did you make a mistake?
What's this?
N-No. I didn't make a mistake.
It's the truth!
My father really had woken up.
He even called my name.
Goodness. Don't lie. If he had woken
up, why would he be like this?
Look! He's the same as ever!
Because of you, we had
to run over here without
eating the expensive steak we had ordered!
What's this? My goodness! How annoying!
How could you be so annoying?
No, it's the truth!
He really had woken up! I'm serious!
How dare you yell at me.
- Dae-hoon.
- Dal-ho! Hee-dong!
You said Mr. Kim had woken up.
What happened?
Grandfather.
It's no use. He's the same as ever.
The doctor came by a while ago, and
he said Mr. Kim is still unconscious.
What?
That's what he said, father.
Dae-hoon, what did you mean
when you said Mr. Kim had woken up?
The thing is, he really had woken up.
He woke up and said my name, too.
Whenever you speak, it's a lie.
Just look at him! He's like
the boy who cried wolf!
I understand that
he wants Mr. Kim to wake up,
but he made all of us come
here when we were busy.
No.
He really had woken up.
He really woke up and said my name.
You have so many tears.
You always cry. Do you think
crying will solve everything?
Be quiet!
I told you to stay here
because I had an errand
to do. But you let Dae-hoon
here all by himself?
Well, I was only gone for a moment.
I'm telling the truth, Dal-ho!
I'm telling the truth, Hee-dong!
If that's what you say
is true, then it's true.
Don't worry. Grandfather will wake up soon.
Okay.
Hee-dong, we need to talk.
Hee-dong, I won't ask you to forgive me.
But after grandfather
collapsed, your father and my
dad have been sleeping at
the hospital every day.
The house is empty and scary.
Besides getting a divorce, I'll
do anything you want me to do.
So can't you come home now?
If you hate me, do it
for your mother's sake.
Or...
for Yoo-jin's sake.
Fine.
You can call me shameless, and
I can't argue against that.
But you brought Yoo-Jin.
I didn't want you to
ever find out about her,
but you were the one who brought her home!
I don't want to talk about this with you.
Like I said last time, we'll talk about
this after grandfather wakes up.
And what if my grandfather wakes up?
Will we get a divorce then?
When my grandfather wakes up, we're going
to present him with our divorce as a gift?
Hello.
What do you mean?
Yoo-Jin left me a letter and disappeared?
Yoo...
Yoo-Jin disappeared?
What happened?
To Mr. Jo Hee-dong.
I'm going to return to the orphanage.
So please live a happy life with my mom.
That's my wish.
From, Yoo-Jin.
Oh, no!
Oh, no...
- Stay home, please. Yoo-Jin might come back.
- All right.
Hey, kid. Are you going somewhere?
Are you alone?
Yoo-Jin!
Hi, Shin-ae.
You got a call?
Where is she?
I'm closer, so I'll head over there first.
Rock-paper-scissors.
Yoo-Jin!
Mr. Jo!
Where did you go?
Thank you.
I'm glad I met her.
- Yes. Thank you.
- Bye, kid.
Yoo-Jin, why did you do that?
Do you know how worried I was about you?
You and mom will live happily if I'm gone.
Yoo-Jin.
Take me to the orphanage.
I'm okay.
Yoo-Jin, I told you.
It's not because of you.
Then can't you live happily with my mom?
I really want you and my mom
to live happily together.
All right.
I'll come back home,
so don't ever run away from home again.
Do you understand?
Really?
Yes, really.
Okay.
I'll never do this again.
Promise me, too.
(Motel)
Mom, this is the cheapest place.
It's fifteen dollars per night.
But it's very shabby.
That's fine. We just need a place to stay.
Let's go inside.
Okay.
Grandma, are we living here now?
Yes, we'll be staying
here for the time being.
I don't like this place.
There's no bathroom.
Of course there's a bathroom.
It's right outside.
That bathroom is stinky and scary.
I'll go with you.
You're a good boy, aren't you?
Did I pack Yoo-sung's cold medicine?
Mom, can you and Yoo-sung
stay here by yourselves?
Why? Where are you going?
I'm going to look for work.
We need to pay for the bank debt,
private loan, and living expenses.
I need to start work as soon as possible.
Mi-poong, I'm sorry.
This is all because I'm
incompetent and foolish.
Why would you say that?
You're making me upset.
I shouldn't have agreed
to go on home shopping.
I thought we would be able to
find your father that way.
Goodness. What on earth is going on?
We lost our security deposit, and
our successful diner went bankrupt.
How will we be able to pay
back that enormous debt?
Mom, we can start over again.
If we gather our strength
and work hard, we'll be
reunited with father, and
a good day will come.
I'll work hard, so cheer up. Okay?
Okay.
Yes. We need to gather
strength and start over again.
We need to find your father, too.
I should search for a job in the area.
Make sure you lock the door.
I'll be back soon.
Be safe.
- Bye.
Grandma, don't cry. I don't need a bathroom.
Okay.
Kim Mi-poong.
What are you doing here?
Jang-go...
The season silently leaves
I'm silently crying
I miss you, I miss you so much
The one person who crashes into the empty air
Please come again. Oh, hi, mom.
Hi. Oh my goodness.
You must have had a lot
of customers today, too.
- Yes. Oh my gosh.
Let's lie down here and rest.
- Sure.
- Oh my goodness.
- Goodness.
But...
Where is Jang-go?
Did he eat?
Goodness. It's freezing outside, but he's
not even coming home. Is he dead or alive?
Mom, why would you talk like that?
He won't die just because he got a divorce.
This is all my fault.
If I hadn't written a guarantee, then
they wouldn't have gotten a divorce.
Come on, mom. That's not true.
You were trying your best to get them
back together and to help Mi-poong out.
They got a divorce because they were meant
to get a divorce, so don't feel that way.
I wonder how Mi-poong is doing.
I can't even meet up with her.
She'll live somehow, so forget about her.
But mom, I had a strange dream.
What? About Jang-go?
No. Remember I had a dream about that
phoenix who came into our house?
In my dream, that phoenix flew
around our house and then left.
- The phoenix left our house?
- Yes.
Now that I think about it, I had that
dream when Mi-poong moved into our house.
Isn't it strange that I had that dream on
the day Jang-go and Mi-poong got a divorce?
Is that phoenix meant to be
Mi-poong, and not Hee-Ra?
Gosh. You just had a silly
dream, that's all. My goodness.
I guess that's true. There's no
way Mi-poong can be the phoenix.
Mother. Nam-yi.
I made a reservation at a
restaurant for tonight.
How about we go together and
eat something delicious?
Why out of the blue?
You two seemed unhappy
because of Geum-sil's oldest
son's divorce issue, so I
want to restore your health.
Let's hurry up and go.
Did you get all your things?
Don't leave your phone
or wallet behind just to
use that as an excuse
to cling onto Jang-soo.
I never clung onto him.
Here. I paid you until today.
Let me say a word.
Don't live such a pathetic life
following your ex-boyfriends around.
Let me say a word, too.
You better be good to Jang-soo.
Or else, I might come back.
Jang-soo isn't someone you can
treat so disrespectfully.
He's a gem, so treat him right. Got it?
Hey! Who are you to tell me
to treat my husband right?
How dare you, you disrespectful wench!
Hee-Ra! Hee-Ra! Hee-Ra! Move!
Don't do this, Joo-Ri! Hee-Ra, are you okay?
Jang-soo...
Joo-Ri!
Song Joo-Ri!
You jerk! Why did you follow me?
Don't worry about me.
Hee-Ra loves me.
I love her, too.
Joo-Ri, I hope you'll live well, too.
You must live well!
Are you going to disobey me again?
Shin-ae, why are you doing this again?
Did I or did I not say I would punish
you if you didn't listen to me?
I'm your father. So why
are you doing this to me?
Mr. Kim,
I...
did another DNA test on Shin-ae.
I'm sorry for doing this
without your permission.
The result stating that she was your
real granddaughter already came out.
Am I being suspicious for no reason at all?
I feel like she's not your granddaughter.
I feel like something is wrong. So I...
I'm sorry.
Mr. Kim, please wake up now.
Wake up and please scold
either me or Shin-ae.
Hello?
Yes, I'm Jo Dal-ho.
Pardon?
The test results are out?
I'll be there right away.
The test results are out.
Thank you.
(Kim Dae-hoon and Park
Shin-ae are not related)
"Kim Dae-hoon and Park
Shin-ae are not related?"
How could this be?
Then what about those results that
confirmed she was the real granddaughter?
Where did things start to go wrong?
Yes. She's an imposter.
She's Mr. Kim's fake granddaughter.
Park Shin-ae.
Everything was planned from the beginning.
Dae-hoon.
Yes, father.
D-Did you just call me?
Dae-hoon.
Father! Father, you really woke up, right?
- Father.
- My son.
You won't close your eyes again, will you?
You can't fall asleep again, father.
Okay, Dae-hoon.
- Hee-dong.
- Yes, father.
- My father woke up!
- Pardon?
My father woke up!
Grandfather, do you recognize me?
My Hee-dong.
Grandfather.
Dal-ho, my father opened his eyes!
Look! Look!
He opened his eyes, didn't he?
Mr. Kim.
Do you recognize me?
Dal...
Dal-ho.
Mr. Kim!
Yes...
I'll bring the doctor.
Okay.
- Mom.
- Yes?
Grandfather woke up.
Oh my goodness! Mr. Kim! You woke up?
Grandfather.
Shin-ae.
Shin-ae was praying so
much for you to wake up!
Grandfather, thank you.
Thank you for waking up.
How can such a miracle happen?
They said he was unconscious! What happened?
I don't know.
Usually, when someone gets a
brain surgery, they can't speak.
He speaks clearly, and his mind
is perfectly normal as well.
How can this happen?
Grandfather couldn't have
possibly heard everything
you and I said while he was
unconscious, could he?
Oh my goodness.
No way.
No, no. I checked earlier, and it
didn't seem like that was the case.
P-Probably not, or else he would've gotten
angry at us as soon as he had woken up.
Mr. Kim's length of life
is so tenaciously long!
Why did he have to wake
up and complicate things?
If he had just passed away,
we could've sent that fool
to America, and everything
would've been just fine!
H-He won't live for much longer now.
Do you think I'm scared
he'll live for a long time?
I'm just afraid he'll find Mi-poong.
She's really determined to find her dad.
Mother, how can you say
something so unlucky?
How would they be able
to find him when they're
wandering around bankrupt and homeless?
What are you getting mad at me for?
Did I wish for Mr. Kim wake up?
Father, I'm going to go eat.
All right,
- We'll be back.
- Let's go.
Dal-ho.
We have a big problem.
Shin-ae is...
Did you know, too?
That she isn't your granddaughter?
So, she really isn't?
She wasn't Dae-hoon's daughter.
She wasn't your granddaughter.
Oh, no.
I had my doubts.
How dare she do such a thing.
What happened to the DNA
test we did last time?
Did she hire an employee at the
lab to fabricate the results?
- I looked into it, but she didn't.
It's impossible to do so.
- Then?
I think she switched her toothbrush with
the toothbrush of your real granddaughter.
Then doesn't that mean she
knows my real granddaughter?
She probably does, which is why she knows
so much about the real Kim Seung-hee.
That's how she got the
ring and the toothbrush.
Yes... yes...
Now everything is starting to make sense.
I can't forgive her. I won't let
Park Shin-ae get away with this.
No, Dal-ho.
Not now.
We must chase her out right now!
We can never do that until we
find my real granddaughter.
And with such a witch like her, do you think
we can just end with chasing her out?
We'll have to make sure
she pays for her sins.
She's a frightening witch
who deceives blood lines.
If we act rashly,
my real granddaughter could
get bullied or hurt.
I understand.
But Dal-ho...
I think Chung-ja is
involved in this as well.
My wife?
The DNA test that was between us...
Chung-ja knew about it. She also
knew that Shin-ae was an imposter.
While I was in bed, I heard
Shin-ae and Chung-ja talking.
They said they were going to
send Dae-hoon to America.
They treated him like he
was a mental patient.
It makes me shudder.
Mr. Kim, is that true?
Yes.
Honey, I bought coffee!
Americano!
What do you think you're doing?
Why are you doing this to me?
Are you out of your mind?
How can you do this to me?
That man must be crazy! He's crazy!
Hey, Jo Dal-ho!
I'm going to make you regret this!
Dad.
Dad, we need to talk.
About what?
Sit over there.
Dad,
did you tell grandfather
about how my mother-in-law
and I scolded you a bit
when he was unconscious?
No, not yet. Why?
Don't tell him that.
Why not?
You and Ms. Ma had mistreated me so much.
When did we do that? Why are
you saying weird things again?
When did I mistreat you so much?
I just scolded you a little bit
because you weren't listening to me.
Still, does it make sense for
you to scold your father?
I'm sorry, dad. I won't do it ever again.
But if you tell this to
grandpa, he might get
upset and faint again
because he got stressed.
Dad, this is candy.
- Look at the colors! Red, blue, yellow...
- Wow! This is really pretty!
This is my gift to you.
Dad, this is my love for you.
I want to get along with you.
Dad, you'll accept my sincerity, won't you?
It's yummy.
Thank goodness he's ten-years-old.
Dad, let's go.
Grandfather, dad stayed at
the hospital all this time,
so I'll take him home tonight,
and he can wash up, too.
No! I'm not going! I'm going
to stay next to father.
Shin-ae, you worked hard,
so go home and rest now.
Yes, grandfather.
Then I'll be going home now.
Father, Shin-ae must take
me for a ten-year-old fool.
What do you mean?
Shin-ae gave me this
candy and told me not to
tell you about how she
and Ms. Ma mistreated me.
Shin-ae is really a terrible daughter.
She doesn't seem like my daughter at all.
Poor thing.
I'm sorry, Dae-hoon, for
not recognizing her as the
beast she is and claiming
she was your daughter.
I'm serious, father!
Shin-ae and Ms. Ma hit
me, pinched me, and...
Never mind.
You can't get stressed and collapse again.
I'm fine. I won't collapse.
And since I'm awake, no one will
be able to mistreat you anymore.
You're the strongest man in the world!
But Dae-hoon...
from now on...
don't go anywhere with Shin-ae by yourself.
Okay?
I don't want to go anywhere
with just Shin-ae either.
Good.
Wait until I find my real granddaughter.
Park Shin-ae, I'll never forgive you.
So what you want me to do
is follow this Park Shin-ae
woman here to find out where the
real Kim Seung-hee is, right?
Please find all the people
who came from North
Korea who Park Shin-ae has contacted so far.
Mr. Kim's real granddaughter
should be among them.
Kim Seung-hee's safety is our priority,
so please be as stealthy as possible.
All right. I understand.
No one can find out about this.
Don't worry about security.
I'll do my best and find
the real Kim Seung-hee.
Please do.
Here you go.
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
Please give us more radish kimchi.
Sure.
Yoo-sung, are you all right?
Grandma, I try to hold it
in, but I keep coughing.
Oh, no, Yoo-sung. Why isn't
your cold going away?
Wait just a little bit longer. When
I'm done, we'll go to the hospital.
Yes, grandma.
What are you doing? The
customers are coming in!
Mom, I bought Yoo-sung's medicine.
Ever since last night, he won't stop
coughing, and his fever won't go down.
Yoo-sung, let's take your
medicine before you sleep again.
So you were hiding here.
What are you doing here?
What am I doing here?
Do you think I came here
because I wanted to?
You bitch. I couldn't get in touch with you.
Who told you that you could move without
my permission when you borrowed my money?
I'm sorry. I'll definitely
pay you back the interest
by the end of this week.
Please give me some time.
If you didn't have the money to pay the
interest, why did you borrow my money?
No! You can't take that! I
have to pay for the room!
Hey, take that ring from her.
You little bitch!
You can't even pay the interest, but
you were wearing such a big ring.
I'll pay the interest! How
can you take my ring?
Lady.
Take off that ring.
I-I can't give you this ring, even if I die.
- No! You can't!
- Give it to me!
What's this? Is this a silver ring?
- Gosh.
- Damn it!
This is a temporary phone.
Make sure you answer.
If you don't answer, and I find
out you disappeared, you're dead!
Yoo-sung, it's okay.
Goodness! I can't do this anymore!
You don't have to
pay for the late room rent,
so leave here right now.
- Ma'am.
- Ma'am...
Get out this instant, or I'll kick you out!
Yoo-sung.
Yoo-sung, are you okay?
Hang on, okay?
Yoo-Jin is home.
I'm back.
Hi, Yoo-Jin.
Yoo-Jin! Hee-dong! Put
your backpack away, and
hurry up and come here so
that we can play a game.
Okay.
Let's go.
I thought Hee-dong would divorce Shin-ae
because of the issue with Yoo-Jin.
I think he came back because you had
fainted and also for Yoo-jin's sake.
Can we allow that witch to be
next to our kind Hee-dong?
Shouldn't you reveal Shin-ae's
true identity to Hee-dong now?
Sir, I don't want Hee-dong
to find out about that.
Hee-dong sincerely loved her.
If he finds out Shin-ae was pretending
to be your granddaughter all this time,
I think he'll be really heartbroken.
Because of that beast, the
house has become a mess.
I'll talk to Hee-dong and
convince him to get a divorce.
All right.
Let's do that.
- Father.
- Hey, Hee-dong.
Let's talk.
Sure.
Hee-dong, what are you
going to do about Shin-ae?
Did you decide to get
back together with her?
That's not it.
I'm thinking about it. I'm
worried about Yoo-Jin as well.
You might think I'm
cold-hearted for saying this.
Yoo-Jin isn't your child.
You're attached to her,
so it might be difficult,
but you have to end ties that must end.
Shin-ae is a frightening woman
who deceived you and tried
to adopt her own daughter
she had with another man.
How many times has she lied to us?
I can't trust her. I don't like her.
I'm scared of her.
That's why I want you to get a divorce.
What are you saying?
Divorce?
Are you insane?
You should help the kids live well, but
you're persuading him to get a divorce?
Hee-dong, you can't get a divorce!
Never! Don't listen to your dad!
Get out!
Oh my goodness. Why are you yelling?
Hey, Jo Dal-ho!
Don't tell me to get out! You get out!
I don't have any lingering
attachment to you either!
- What?
- Mom.
Hee-dong, don't listen to a word your dad is
saying! He's out of his mind! He's crazy!
Do you know what your dad did to me?
He slapped my cheek in the hospital hallway!
What?
Why? If you didn't, say so!
Who are you slap my cheek?
Even my mom never slapped me once!
But who are you to slap my cheek?
I hope you'll think about this
carefully and make the right choice.
Where are you going? Tell me the
reason why you slapped my cheek!
Dad!
If you don't know why you were
slapped, you're not even human.
What the hell is he saying to his wife?
Hee-dong, if you upset me, too,
I really won't be able to live!
You can't get a divorce!
The day you get a divorce is the day I die!
Do you understand?
You can't!
Hey! How can you have an
appetite at this moment?
You made your son get a divorce!
You don't even
know where he is and if he's
sleeping or eating properly!
He said he needed to get some fresh air.
He needs some time to think, too.
You wicked, spiteful wench!
- Jang-go.
- Oh, my baby. Jang-go.
Oh my goodness. What happened to your face?
You lost so much weight.
Did you eat?
I'm hungry.
Okay, I'll make you food.
No, I'll do it. Jang-go, I'll make
you food, so just wait a little bit.
Good, good. Your mother made your
favorite hot and spicy beef stew.
Eat that and shake everything off.
Somehow, you'll be able to survive.
That's life.
I got rid of her dressing
table and belongings.
You two got a divorce. It's
over between you two, so
it would feel strange to still
have her things around.
The food is ready, so come out and eat.
Yoo-sung, are you sleeping?
Mom!
Hi, Mi-poong.
Did you wait a long time? Is Yoo-sung okay?
My work at the restaurant ended late,
so I couldn't take him to the hospital.
- I did buy more medicine though.
- You did?
Check his fever.
Mom, what's wrong with Yoo-sung?
His body is burning up!
- We need to give him
the fever reducer first.
- Yes, let's do that.
Yoo-sung.
What's wrong with him?
Yoo-sung. Mom, Yoo-sung is a bit strange.
What's wrong with him? Yoo-sung!
- Yoo-sung, it's me, Aunt Mi-poong.
- Yoo-sung, open your eyes!
Yoo-sung!
Hang on, Yoo-sung.
(Emergency Room)
Excuse me.
Doctor, please check my grandson.
Please save him.
Doctor, what's wrong with my grandson?
Doesn't he have a cold?
I think he has cerebral meningitis.
Cerebral meningitis?
Pardon?
Oh, dear. I didn't even know that...
Doctor, please save my Yoo-sung.
In the case it's just a virus, he'll be
fine as long as the fever is reduced,
but if he has cerebral
bacterial meningitis and his
treatment is postponed, then
his life could be in danger.
Pardon?
He must be admitted and treated.
He needs to take a cerebrospinal
fluid examination
for the exact diagnosis,
so we'll do that first.
Excuse me.
Miss, please go to the first floor
and sign the papers. As soon as
that's done, he'll be put into a
hospital room and the exam will start.
Mi-poong, what do we do?
Where can we get the money?
Mom, I'm going to go to
my part-time job and ask
my boss for an advanced pay.
I'll be back soon.
He went to a house of morning?
When is he coming back?
I don't know.
I would like an advance pay.
Is there anything you can do?
I'm just a part-time worker.
What do I do about Yoo-sung?
(Deokcheonok)
Ms. Joo.
Hello.
Hello. What brings you here?
It's cold. Come inside.
No. I was just passing by...
But is something wrong?
Um...
M-Mr. Jo...
Yes, go ahead.
I'm very sorry for asking for this favor...
but can I borrow some money from you?
Ms. Joo...
A thousand dollars.
Please let me borrow a thousand dollars.
Sure. Hold on.
I happen to have the amount.
Thank you.
I'll never forget your kindness.
But may I ask you what's wrong?
Mr. Jo, I'll make sure to repay you.
I promise.
Thank you so much.
Ms. Joo!
Yoo-sung.
(Call List Analysis Report)
That is what I got from investigating
Park Shin-ae's surroundings.
After investigating her
phone, e-mail, and SNS,
I find out that the people she
contacted who are from North Korea
are twenty-eight-year-old Kim
Mi-poong and her mother Joo Young-ae.
Kim Mi-poong and Joo Young-ae?
Yes.
Kim Mi-poong and Joo Young-ae are the
only people she has been in contact with?
Yes, that is correct.
I checked a few more times, but in the
end, there were only the two of them.
And in my opinion,
Kim Mi-poong might be the
granddaughter Mr. Kim is searching for.
Kim Mi-poong?
It's not her.
I already know Kim
Mi-poong and Joo Young-ae.
They're not the ones I'm looking for.
Currently, this is all I have.
I'll investigate some more.
Sure. Please do that.
Yes, sir.
- Kim Mi-poong!
- Yes!
Still, just in case, how about you meet Kim
Mi-poong and Ms. Joo
Young-ae and talk with them?
Sure, let's do that.
Let's meet them first.
Yes, sir.
The number you have dialed does
not exist, so please try again.
You can't get in touch with her?
Ms. Joo Young-ae isn't
answering her phone either.
Why not?
You can't get in touch with either of them?
Actually, a few days ago, Ms. Joo
Young-ae came to borrow money from me.
What?
She came to borrow money from you?
Yes, she seemed very urgent.
She asked to borrow $1000, and I had a
check at the time, so I gave it to her.
I was worried about her,
and I thought something
was strange, so I went
to the dumpling diner,
but according to others,
she had gone bankrupt.
Then call Mr. Kim and ask him
to track down the check.
Yes, sir.
Please don't put up an ad.
Aren't you curious about your son?
My father is your son, too.
(Motel)
- Mom, how much do we get
for folding one of these?
- Fifteen cents.
I hope I can fold many of these.
- Do I do it like this?
- Oh, leave it.
You must be tired after working.
Who can it be?
Grandfather?
Hello.
Mom, grandfather is here.
Please come in.
Father, how did you know we were here?
It's a bit shabby, but
please have a seat here.
Here.
Um...
I'm not your father-in-law.
I'm fake.
Pardon?
What do you mean you're fake?
I know I shouldn't have done that, but I
received a thousand dollars and lied to you.
Then you're really not my grandfather?
After I did that to you, I couldn't sleep
comfortably, since I deceived blood lines.
I felt like I would go to hell after I die.
Why did you do that? Why?
I did it because I was desperate for money.
Now that I think about it,
I think the people who hired
me to lie to you was trying
to prevent you from meeting
your real grandfather.
Who? Who hired you to do such a thing?
I don't know their names.
It was some woman and a young lady.
But I have a phone number.
Here.
I'm sorry.
Sir...
What on earth is he talking about?
Who would do such a thing?
Give me the phone number.
Mom.
Who on earth won't let us
meet Mi-poong's grandfather?
They even made up a fake one.
Who is it?
Hello?
Excuse me, but do you
know Mr. Kim Han-cheon?
Mr. Kim Han-cheon?
No. You got the wrong number.
Then what about Mr. Kim Bok-dong?
No, I don't know him.
You got the wrong number.
You really don't know him?
Where are you prank-calling from?
I don't know him!
Hold on!
By any chance, are you Mr. Jo's wife?
Who are you?
You are Mr. Jo's wife!
No, I'm not! You got the wrong number!
She used the money she
borrowed from you to pay for
Yoo-sung's examination
for cerebral meningitis?
I think that was why she
urgently borrowed money.
Then the hospital should
have her phone number.
I tried the number, but
it doesn't exist anymore.
Goodness.
How can we not get in touch with her?
It can't be Kim Mi-poong.
Dal-ho, let's go to the North
Korean Defector Center.
Kim Seung-hee from North Korea
could be searching for Dae-hoon.
All right.
I'll contact the center.
Oh, he's on the list.
What?
There's someone looking for Kim Dae-hoon?
Yes, there is. There's a video as well.
Kim Mi-poong and Joo Young-ae
are searching for Kim Dae-hoon.
- Mr. Kim!
- W-Who?
Kim... Kim Mi-poong?
Dae-hoon...
Father. It's Seung-hee.
It's been a long time, right?
I'm living well here in South Korea using
the name that you gave me, Kim Mi-poong.
Kim Mi-poong. Do you remember
the name you gave me?
All this time, mom and
I thought you had passed away.
So we didn't think of finding you.
But we think we saw you here in South Korea.
The person we saw is you, isn't it?
Father, you're alive, aren't you?
I miss you so much.
Dad...
Let's make sure we meet.
(Blow Breeze)
They were looking for us all this time.
I'm sorry.
Will your wrist break if you pour a drink?
I should just-!
Mr. Jo's wife!
You mean Shin-ae's mother-in-law?
- How could you do that?
- I had no choice...
I'll look for a way to stow away.
You promised to stay by
my side no matter what!
- Where is she heading?
- I think Shin-ae did this.
Is Mr. Kim your grandfather?
Where is she? Let's go.
Subtitles by OnDemandKorea