Subtitles by OnDemandKorea
(Episode 50)
Mom, I'll do it.
Father.
it's me, Seung-hee.
I'm living well here in South Korea
using the name, Kim Mi-poong, you gave me.
Kim Mi-poong.
Do you remember the name you gave me?
All this time, mom and I thought you had passed away.
So we didn't think of finding you.
But we think we saw you here in South Korea.
The person we saw is you, isn't it?
Father, you're alive, aren't you?
I miss you so much.
Dad...
let's make sure we meet.
I'm sorry.
I didn't recognize you.
Kim Mi-poong.
Mi-poong.
You were my granddaughter.
Dal-ho.
She's really my granddaughter, isn't she?
Yes, Mr. Kim.
She is.
How could this happen?
My granddaughter was next to me all this time, but I didn't know.
My Mi-poong.
My Yoo-sung.
My daughter-in-law.
Where do I find you?
Hello, Mr. Kim.
Is that so?
All right.
Mr. Kim, he was able to locate Mi-poong and Ms. Joo's location
from the hospital where Yoo-sung had been admitted at.
Really?
Where is it?
Let's go. Quickly!
(Motel)
What do you mean they left? When did they leave?
It hasn't been long.
Are you here for the debt as well?
Debt? What debt?
We're not those kind of people.
He's the grandfather of the young lady who was here.
Do you know where they went?
I wouldn't know. They were behind on the room rent, but those
loan sharks came barging in here suddenly, so I chased them out.
Loan sharks barged in here?
Don't even get me started. It seemed like the little one was sick.
Yet, those loan sharks took all the money, even the room rent.
They even took the ring on her finger and kicked the door loudly. My goodness!
Mr. Kim!
They were in such a rush that they ran out of here without even the time to think!
Since you say you're her grandfather, take these with you.
(We are looking for a person)
My goodness.
They were looking for us.
I didn't even know that.
Mr. Kim, Mi-poong would never do such a thing.
If that's what you're here to discuss, please go back.
Mr. Kim!
Please help her this one time. I can't let her
be unjustly accused for something she didn't do.
Mr. Kim, please help her just this once.
Ms. Joo, if one did something wrong, then one should receive the punishment.
Do you know how much damage Kim Mi-poong had caused to the company?
If we accommodated you this much, you should be grateful.
How can she be so shameless?
Pardon?
No matter how hard it is to live, there are things you should do and shouldn't do.
You tried to get help from another woman's husband, and
your daughter sought after illegal funds from her workplace.
How can you live any way you please?
You should try to live hard with your own efforts.
Where did you learn such terrible things from?
Mr. Kim, what are you talking about?
I'm sorry.
Who on earth won't let us meet Mi-poong's grandfather?
They even made up a fake one.
Who can it be?
Hello?
Excuse me, but do you know Mr. Kim Han-cheon?
Mr. Kim Han-cheon?
No. You got the wrong number.
Then what about Mr. Kim Bok-dong?
No, I don't know him.
You got the wrong number.
You really don't know him?
Where are you prank-calling from?
I don't know him!
Hold on!
By any chance, are you Mr. Jo's wife?
Who are you?
You are Mr. Jo's wife!
No, I'm not! You got the wrong number!
Wasn't that Mi-poong's mom?
Kim Han-cheon? Kim Bok-dong? That's that old man from last time!
Why is she asking me about that old man?
Did she find out he's the fake one?
What do I do?
It's definitely that woman.
Mom.
- Mi-poong! - Did you call the number?
Mom, what's wrong?
Mi-poong, this number seems to belong to that woman! Mr. Jo's wife!
By Mr. Jo's wife, you mean Shin-ae's mother-in-law?
Yes!
Mi-poong, stay with Yoo-sung. I'm going to check this out myself.
If it really is that woman, I'm going to demand for an explanation.
Mom, let me go with you.
No. Stay with Yoo-sung. I'll be back soon.
Mom...
No way. Why would she do such a thing?
There's a big problem, Shin-ae!
Mi-poong's mom called me to ask if I knew who Mr. Kim Han-cheon was.
Who is Mr. Kim Han-cheon?
You know Mi-poong's fake grandfather! We gave him that name!
Mother! Someone will hear you!
No one is home!
How does she know that old man, and why did she call you?
Did she call knowing that Mi-poong's real grandfather is Mr. Kim?
What do we do then?
That's not true.
If she knew that, would she have called to ask if you know that old man?
That's true...
Oh my gosh.
Hello? Go on.
What? She's heading towards our house right now?
- Right now? - All right. I got it.
Who is heading towards our house right now?
Mi-poong's mom is on her way to our house right now.
I think it may be because of that.
So you were keeping an eye on Mi-poong's family all this time?
Go outside and meet her. If she asks you about that
old man, firmly tell her you don't know anything!
Me?
Then do I go? She called you!
If I got out an explain, then she'll get suspicious!
Really?
It's that woman! It's her! What do I do?
What do we do if she runs into grandfather or dad?
Mother, hurry up and go out and take her far
away from here! Do something about this! Hurry!
I'm coming!
Hurry!
S-She didn't come here knowing everything, did she?
You don't know?
This is the phone number that the old man gave me.
It's your phone number, isn't it?
You still don't know?
I don't know how he gave you my phone number, but I don't know him.
Fine.
Then let's bring that old man and have a three-party encounter.
Okay, fine! I did it!
What?
How could you do such a thing?
Why did you make up a fake grandfather to prevent us from finding the real one?
You know who Mi-poong's real grandfather is, don't you?
How would I know that?
You do know him! If we find her real grandfather, it'll be a
disadvantage towards you! Isn't that why you did such an awful thing?
Oh my gosh! What are you talking about?
Why would it be a disadvantage for me if you found Mi-poong's grandfather?
Then why did you do this? Why?
You...
You don't know why I did this?
You tenacious woman!
What?
You shameless woman!
You stole my husband and ruined my family, and
yet, you want to find your father-in-law?
If there was still a law against adultery, I
would've locked you up in a prison a long time ago!
That's why I wanted to put you through trouble! So what?
Since you ruined my family, you deserve this punishment!
- What do you think you're doing? - Hey!
Hey, you crazy woman.
How could you do such a terrible thing?
Have you ever considered the feelings of people
who live with the hope of finding their family?
I want to kill you with my own bare hands, but I
don't want to dirty them, so I'm just leaving.
How terrifying! She said she wants to kill me!
Oh my goodness. What did she say? I'm speechless!
I'm utterly speechless!
What did you say?
You ended up confessing that you were the one who did it?
Yes.
Mother!
I told you to deny it, but how could you confess that you did it instead?
I had no choice.
She was going to do a three-party encounter. What else was I supposed to do?
Do you think she's going to let this slide?
She'll definitely suspect me now.
Then she'll realize that my grandfather is actually Mi-poong's grandfather!
No, she won't.
I told her the reason I did that was because I
was angry at her for bewitching my husband.
It seemed like she believed me.
Would you believe it if you were her?
It's possible...
Hi. It's me.
Nothing strange happened at the new motel she was staying at, right?
Then send me the phone number of the loan sharks they borrowed money from.
Why do you need the loan sharks?
What are you going to do?
Do you have a way?
This won't do. I need to make sure Mi-poong's family is far away from here.
This is the money that Kim Mi-poong owes.
I put in enough money for the interest.
You're paying her debt back for her?
I heard you have a request to ask me.
This is a service fee.
Make sure Kim Mi-poong doesn't appear in Seoul again.
If you can prevent her from coming here for one year, I'll pay you double the amount.
That's not hard at all.
We're professionals in that area.
We'll definitely take care of that for you.
Sounds good.
She really said that? But does that make any sense?
She's a crazy woman.
She came into our house last time when no one was home.
Are you serious?
She's insane.
But mom, that old man said that an older woman and a younger lady had come to see him.
Shin-ae?
Or that woman's daughter?
Something isn't right.
I'm going to go to work.
You had work?
I called an employment agency, and they said if I fill in for someone for
the day, I would get paid double the amount, so I quickly took the job.
All right. Be careful of cars.
I'll be back soon.
Why would Shin-ae...?
It can't be Shin-ae.
Mi-poong, we're behind on deliveries, so can you wash
the dishes later and go to a delivery right now?
Sure, I'll go.
- Detective. - Hello.
Is it true that James Kang has entered the country?
Yes, we have information that he has entered Incheon this early morning.
He's on the watch list, so it's only a matter of time before he's caught.
Really? That's good.
Please call me as soon as he gets caught.
Sure. I'll call you as soon as we catch this rascal.
Thank you.
- You must be busy, but I'm always asking favors from you. - It's fine.
It's a bit early for dinner, but would you like to get rice soup with me?
- Should I? I was so busy that I didn't even get to eat lunch. - Really?
- Yes. - That's great. Let's get a bowl of rice soup then.
But rice soup is okay, isn't it?
- Of course it is. Let's go. - Okay.
What's wrong?
Go in first. I'll be there soon.
- Sure. I'll order two bowls then. - Sure.
If you leave the dishes out here, I'll come pick them up later. Enjoy.
What did you follow me here for?
It seemed like you had moved away.
You changed your number, too.
What's your new number?
Jang-go.
We were once a married couple,
but now we're divorced.
Isn't it common courtesy to ignore each other even
if we coincidentally run into each other like this?
Mi-poong, how do you expect me to ignore you when I see you living like this?
How am I living?
I don't know what it seems like to you,
but I'm living very well.
So you neither have to pity me nor sympathize with me.
All right.
I got it, so give me your new number.
Please just forget me.
That's all I want from you.
Also...
even if we coincidentally run into each other,
I hope you can just ignore me.
Bye.
(Dongbaek Restaurant)
- I'm back. - Good job.
It's that house.
This is where Mi-poong used to live?
Yes.
Call Mr. Lee.
Yes, sir.
Oh, isn't that Mr. Lee?
Hello.
Hi.
What are you doing here?
I came to ask you something.
Go ahead.
I heard you and Mi-poong got a divorce.
Can you get in contact with her?
Where is she right now?
We're not keeping in touch.
I don't know her number either.
Is there a way you can find her?
Why are you searching for Mi-poong?
Mr. Kim would really like to find her.
The truth is, I ran into Mi-poong by chance earlier.
You did?
Where did you see her? Where is she right now?
It seemed like she was working at Dongbaek Restaurant in Yeongdeungpo.
Is that true?
Yes. May I ask you what this is all about?
There's a reason why I need to meet with her.
- Thank you. Dal-ho, let's go. - Yes, sir.
Why is the chairman of Winner's Group looking for Mi-poong?
It's a fallen one.
I'm back.
- Jang-go is back. - Hi, Jang-go.
Hello.
Did Mi-poong cause trouble at Winner's Group again?
Did she do something like embezzlement?
Mom.
If not, why would the chairman look for her and not you?
It's not like they're connected in any way.
I'm going to my room.
What's all this about? Who's looking for Mi-poong?
The chairman of Winner's Group came to the front
of the house earlier to look for Mi-poong.
What? Are you serious?
My grandfather came in front of our house?
But why did he just leave without contacting me?
If he had come just to say hello, he would have called you, but
didn't he just leave because he had an important matter to attend to?
Did she really stir up trouble again?
Would the chairman really search for her himself?
Usually, in those cases, his subordinates would take care of it.
The chairman wouldn't get involved himself.
I don't know what this is all about, but what would
Jang-go have done if he hadn't gotten divorced?
The sparks would've flown at him again.
Don't make her into a terrible person without knowing the full story.
Mi-poong was afraid we would lose our house, so she
sold her diner and house to pay the bank back for us.
It's freezing outside, and they have a little one with them.
I wonder where they are and how they're doing when they have nothing with them.
- Goodness. - I know.
Jang-soo, do you really think Jang-go isn't contacting Mi-poong these days?
Yes.
Welcome.
- Excuse me, but I have a question. - Sure.
Does a young lady named Kim Mi-poong work here?
Kim Mi-poong?
We heard that she was working here.
Oh, that young lady?
She only came for today. She's gone now.
S-She's gone?
Yes. What's the matter?
Then do you have her phone number?
I didn't get her number, since she only worked here for a half a day.
Mr. Kim.
What on earth happened, Dal-ho? Where are we supposed to find her?
Mr. Kim, all we have to do is find her now, so don't worry.
What if that wicked brat bullies my granddaughter in the meantime?
Hi, Dae-hoon. It's me.
Why aren't you coming home?
I'm hungry.
If you're hungry, eat first.
I have something important to do.
No. I'm going to starve if you don't come home.
So hurry up and come home, father.
All right.
Yoo-sung, eat a lot.
I will. Grandma and Aunt Mi-poong, you guys eat a lot, too.
All right.
Yoo-sung, let's go eat dumpling soup tomorrow.
Mi-poong,
after we're done eating, let's go meet Mr. Kim Bok-dong again.
We can ask him for the details about that young lady who came with Ms. Ma.
Yes. Something is a bit fishy here.
What brings you here?
We're paying the interest on time, so why are you doing this?
This won't do. I feel anxious.
I don't know when you'll run away again, and paying back
your interest a little bit at a time isn't good enough.
I need the principal amount.
How will we be able to pay the principal amount now? Please give us some time.
We'll definitely pay you back.
And we don't have anywhere else to go, so we won't run away.
You guys will never be able to pay me back.
So I found a way for you guys to pay the principal
amount back, so hurry up and pack your bags.
What do you mean you found a way for us to pay
the principal amount? What are you doing?
Damn it!
I don't have time to explain, so hurry up and pack your bags!
Baby, eat your ramen. It's okay.
Pack up!
Where are you taking us right now?
Tell us where we're going.
Hey! Be quiet!
What are you going to do if you know? Jump out of this moving van?
Don't give me a headache, and let's go quietly. Got it?
Where are we going? I'm scared.
Yoo-sung, you have me and your aunt. Don't worry. It's okay.
(White House Night Club)
Where is this place?
We can't work at such a place.
What do you mean you can't? You need to pay my money back.
If you work here for six months, I'll take money off the
principal amount and interest, so stay here quiet as dead mice.
Then will we only be working in the kitchen?
Of course. Do you guys know how to do anything else?
But if you try to run away, I'll follow you to the ends of the
earth and let you feel my wrath, so don't get any funny ideas.
Got that?
Now go inside and work.
Then please write a contract.
What contract?
A contract that promises you'll take money off the principal
amount and interest if we work here for six months.
Gosh!
Fine. I'll write it.
I'll write it. You happy now?
Then go inside! Go in!
Get the bags!
Hurry up and go inside!
Hurry up and go in!
Come in.
Hee-dong.
What do you want?
I made dinner to celebrate grandfather's recovery and discharge from the hospital.
If it's okay, you should join us.
Sure.
And...
this is yours.
Open it.
I thought of you while knitting this myself.
Did you really think I'd wear that around my neck?
I don't know.
While I was knitting each stitch,
I prayed that we wouldn't divorce.
I prayed that you wouldn't leave.
I made it while praying for those wishes.
I'll join the dinner because of the other family members,
but you shouldn't expect anything else from me anymore.
It's fine if you curse me for being a shameless woman.
But can't you give me one chance?
Just once...
You promised me you wouldn't leave me no matter what happens.
You promised to stay by my side no matter what happens.
My dad returned as a little child.
You're the only one who I can rely on.
I'm a terrible woman,
but still, can't you stay by my side?
Hee-dong, I'm sorry.
Father, thank you for coming back alive.
Thank you so much.
Yes.
Dae-hoon, I'm very happy that I came back as well.
Shin-ae, I'll obey you from now on.
I'm very sorry that I was being stubborn and didn't obey you at the hospital.
No, dad.
You were the one who had suffered the most while grandfather was in the hospital.
Really?
Of course!
You were the one who did your best by his side and suffered the most.
You were the best!
All right. Then I'll sing a song to congratulate father's return.
- A song? Why a song out of the blue? - Yoo-Jin!
A song!
Start!
That shameless wench is taking charge of someone else's place.
She definitely knows where Mi-poong and Yoo-sung are.
Dae-hoon, I'll make sure to find your wife, your
daughter Mi-poong, and your grandson Yoo-sung for you.
I promise.
- Mr. Cha. - Yes, sir.
Quickly cancel the registration of Park Shin-ae in my family registry.
- Cancel? - Yes, and make sure you keep this fact a secret.
If Park Shin-ae or Ma Chung-ja calls you, just say it's still being progressed.
- Do you understand? - Yes, sir.
Have you investigated Park Shin-ae's slush fund?
Yes, sir. Everything will be found out by today.
- Really? - Yes, sir.
Good work. Make sure you find out about everything.
You can't miss a single penny.
And make sure you find a way to collect that back as well.
Don't worry, Mr. Kim.
Park Shin-ae, I'm going to chase you out with nothing.
These are the documents Ms. Park Shin-ae have
authorized as the acting president while you were away.
(Dismissal Notice)
The dismissal of Lawyer Lee Jang-go?
This wicked wench.
Look here.
Take this.
Oh, my! Oh my goodness!
Oh, my.
Oh, what kind of dream is this?
Is it a dream that brings money?
That's amazing.
What kind of dream was that?
What's wrong?
I must be having spring fever lately.
I was taking a nap when I had a dream where
an enormous, golden pumpkin came into my lap.
- Really? - Yes.
But that pumpkin was so bright that I thought I was going blind.
I was so thrilled, but I woke up.
What does it mean?
Mother, something good must be happening in our family!
I guess so.
It seems like a conception dream, too.
Jang-go, are you going somewhere?
Yes, to my colleague's office to help with his work.
Your colleague's office?
Hello, this is Lawyer Lee Jang-go.
Pardon? The chairman?
All right. Thank you.
What was that about?
The chairman of Winner's Group is looking for you?
He gave me my job back.
- Oh my gosh! Are you serious?  - My goodness! How grateful!
He wants me to come see him, so I'll tell you the details later.
- Sure! Go ahead! - Sure!
Mother, that pumpkin dream must have been about Jang-go getting his job back!
- You're right! - Mother!
Oh my goodness!
- What's wrong with you? Do you feel unwell? - Yes, mother.
The coffee tastes like tonic, and I feel nauseated as well.
What's this? The pumpkin dream is a conception dream?
A conception dream?
I heard you reinstated me to my position.
Do you know the reason why Ms. Park Shin-ae dismissed me?
I know everything.
Then I'll speak comfortably.
Even if I come back, I'm going to investigate Kim
Mi-poong's incident of the leaked design until the end.
If you won't allow me to do that, I won't return.
That won't happen. I promise you.
The reason why I reinstated you to your position is because
I want you to thoroughly investigate that incident.
Yes, sir. I understand.
There must be someone else behind this.
Make sure you get that evidence.
Yes. I'll make sure to reveal the truth.
Good. Please do.
And when you get in touch with Mi-poong, let me know right away.
Yes, sir.
Make sure you keep an eye on Park Shin-ae and follow her.
She definitely knows where Mi-poong is.
Tail her quietly. Bye.
You, over there.
Yes. What is it?
Not you, your daughter.
Me?
Yes, you. Come over here.
Why?
What do you want Mi-poong for?
- If you need to talk to her, talk to her here. - I won't eat her.
Stop worrying.
Come out here. It's okay. Come here.
There are many customers today, and we're very busy, so go out there and serve.
Serving?
No, sir! Didn't we come here to work in the kitchen?
Mi-poong has never done such a thing before, so she can't do it.
No one does it right the first time. Everyone learns it first!
And during busy times, you do different kinds of jobs.
Follow me.
Sir!
It's fine. It's fine.
It's a lot easier than kitchen work.
Sir!
You get tips, too. You don't know anything.
I've never seen her before. She's fresh. Just my style.
Sit here next to me.
What am I doing? Excuse me.
Have a good time.
You just came. Where are you going?
Are you a student?
How old are you?
Why are you pretending to be innocent?
- Don't be like that and pour me a drink.  - I don't know how to do these things.
I'll be going now.
Just pour me a drink.
Let go of me!
Damn it!
Who do you think you are, you bitch?
- Who do you think you are, you bitch? - Hey!
You trashy bastard! Do you not have a younger sister?
- Let go! - Hey, manager!
- Get out of here! - What the hell?
We're sorry. We're sorry.
Go inside!
You're making me lose my mind here.
Why can't you do it like the other girls?
Will your wrist break if you pour him a drink?
I should just-!
We're only supposed to work in the kitchen!
Doing kitchen work and serving out there is the
same damn thing! Why are you arguing with me?
Hey.
If you cause trouble among the customers again, I won't let you get away with it.
Got that?
Damn it.
- Yoo-sung, it's okay. - It's okay.
Mi-poong, I think we came to the wrong place.
They made you do something like that. I can never watch you do that.
Mom...
Mi-poong...
let's...
run away from here.
What?
Let's run away and hide.
Let's go live somewhere where they can't find us.
Mom, hurry up. Come out.
Hey! Those wenches! Get them!
- Let go of me! - Mom!
- Mom! - You bitch!
Mom!
Sir, we're really sorry! We won't ever do it again!
- Please spare her! - Get up!
- Sir, we're sorry! Please spare her life! No! - Get up!
No! Please don't!
Mom!
We're sorry!
Hey.
What did I tell you?
I told you I would get you if you tried to run away.
I dare you to try running away again.
I'll sell you off to an island!
Got it?
You little-!
Hey, drag them inside!
- Mom! - Get up!
What?
They got caught trying to run away?
Watch them carefully.
Make sure they can't run away.
Make sure they can't come near Seoul.
Do you understand?
Gosh, I'm bored.
Should I call up my friends for lunch?
Oh, it's Geum-sil.
What is she doing here?
Ms. Ma, give me some juice.
Go the kitchen and tell the housekeeper to get you some. My friend is here.
Oh, no! I must be out of my mind!
Ma'am! Oh! What are you doing? Why are you grabbing my arm?
My friend is coming, and she'll be here soon. Stay in your room.
Why do I need to stay in my room if your friend is here?
My friend gets shocked when she sees men, so go to your room!
I'm going to drink juice!
- I'll tell the housekeeper, so go in! - Chung-ja, I'm here!
All right! Don't push me!
- Oh, hi, Geum-sil! Go to my bedroom! - What are you doing over there?
- Well... - Give me juice!
Bring some juice to Mr. Kim's room!
Hey, Geum-sil, go inside!
Give me some juice!
Sit down.
Goodness! What's the matter with you?
It's nothing.
I'm just so tired of that man.
Is he Mr. Kim's son?
Did you see his face?
Not exactly because you were pushing him into the room.
But he's younger and more normal than I thought he was.
Normal, my foot.
He has the body of an old man and the mind of a little kid.
You must be stressed out.
Don't even get me started.
What brings you to my house? And what are these?
Chung-ja, thank you for giving my son his job back.
These are bracken from Jeju-do and traditional honey.
What? Giving him his job back?
What do you mean?
My son is working for Winner's Group again.
I thought it happened because you had talked to Mr. Kim about it.
No. I didn't know about this.
Oh, my. How did he get his job back?
I don't know.
Mr. Kim had come to the front of our house a few days ago.
Mr. Kim went to your house?
Yes.
But back then, he had been searching for Mi-poong
and had asked my son for her phone number.
So I assumed Mi-poong had caused trouble again.
Mr. Kim asked for Mi-poong's phone number?
Yes. Why are you so surprised?
No, I'm not.
I was just a bit confused that he went to your house.
Anyways, I was so grateful that he gave Jang-go his job back.
Geum-sil, I was in the middle of getting ready to go out.
Really? Then go ahead and get ready. Let's leave together.
Pardon? Grandfather is searching for Mi-poong?
Yes. A few days ago, he went to Lee Jang-go and asked for Mi-poong's phone number.
What if he's searching for Mi-poong because he found out you were an imposter?
No way.
If that was true, with his temper, would he have just let me be?
That's true.
But Shin-ae, lately I've been having nightmares, and I'm so nervous that I can't live.
Instead of keeping Mi-poong in the countryside, can't you send her somewhere
far away to a different country where we won't be able to see her?
Why would grandfather be searching for Mi-poong?
I know!
This is so strange. I have a bad feeling about this.
Hello. I'm calling you to report that Ms. Park Shin-ae
is leaving Seoul and heading over to the countryside.
Where is she headed?
I think it's Dongducheon.
Dongducheon?
Ms. Joo! Mi-poong!
Ms. Joo, what's this? Why-
Ms. Joo, your face...
Shin-ae.
If you were having such a hard time that you had to
get a private loan, you should've just come to me.
Then I would've helped you.
We don't even know how we ended up like this.
I didn't even know you were here. I was searching everywhere for you.
Why?
Did something happen?
I found Mi-poong's father.
Are you serious?
You found my father?
Where is he right now?
Until a few days ago, he was here in Korea, but
he left to China to search for his family.
Because of the gun wound he received while
escaping North Korea, his memories aren't stable.
An acquaintance of mine met him in China, so hurry up and go meet him.
Is that true?
Yes.
But what do we do?
We're not in the best situation.
Shin-ae, can you help us?
Ms. Joo, listen to me quietly.
I'll look for a stowaway ship.
You won't be able to get on the plane because of
the loan sharps, so you'll have to ride a ship.
I'll do whatever I can to help you escape and
go to China, so please wait a little bit.
Okay. Thank you, Shin-ae. Thank you so much.
It's not a problem.
I have to repay you for your kindness.
Ms. Joo, please wait a few more days.
All right.
Why isn't he contacting us?
But why did Shin-ae go to a nightclub?
Who's there?
Mr. Kim is tailing Shin-ae, so he'll call us soon.
They might be there.They're there.
Hey. What if Mi-poong is over there, like Dae-hoon once was?
- Let's go there first. - Yes, sir.
- Mr. Kim. - What is it?
This is...
Mi-poong was here!
- Let's go there right away. - Yes, sir.
Get the car ready. We're leaving right now. Tell the guards to come as well.
Mom...
about Shin-ae...
Why is she suddenly offering to help us meet father?
When we asked her for help to find him, she rejected us.
First, she told us to go to America, and now she's telling us to go to China.
I don't feel right about this.
And how did she know we were here?
We don't have cell-phones, and we were dragged
here out of the blue by the loan sharks.
Mom, I think there's something strange going on.
I think that lady is strange, too.
When I went to Yoo-jin's house, she came looking for me at
home and told me I would go to jail for stealing that ring.
I didn't steal it though. Yoo-Jin gave it to me.
Yoo-sung, what are you talking about?
Oh, that's right. I'm not supposed to tell you this.
They told me not to tell you this.
Yoo-sung, tell us. You can tell us.
There was the same exact ring that grandma wears on her finger in Mr. Kim's room.
That's why Yoo-Jin gave it to me, so that we can play house.
Then? Then what happened to that ring?
I lost it.
You lost it?
I think I put the ring in the pocket of my pants...
Or maybe not...
Anyways, I lost it.
But that lady and the scary older lady came to our house and said that if I
ever tell grandma and aunt about this, the police would take me to jail.
Yoo-sung, are you telling the truth?
Yes.
Yoo-sung, was the same ring as mine really in Mr. Kim's room?
Mom.
Was it Shin-ae that made you faint in the
park last time and stole the ring from you?
Those rings are between grandmother and grandfather, so how could the same ring exist?
That's right.
I thought that was strange as well.
My ring was definitely on my finger that day.
It was so strange how I had lost it at the park,
but it had somehow appeared under the closet.
I think Shin-ae is the one behind this.
Why would she?
Is...
Mr. Kim your grandfather?
"Cheon!"
Mr. Kim's name is Kim Deok-cheon!
I think the young lady who came out with the older
woman who the old man talked about is Shin-ae.
Mom, even if we go to China, let's check the ring with Mr. Kim first.
Yes, let's do that.
- Yes. - Let's definitely check it out, Mi-poong.
Hee-dong.
Hee-dong, where are you?
Oh, in front of the school?
It's Yoo-jin's birthday today. How about we go eat her favorite pasta together?
With my dad, too?
All right. I'll leave at once with my dad.
Bye.
Dad, how do I look?
Am I pretty?
Yeah.
Thanks, dad. You look really handsome today, too.
- Really? - Yes.
- Do you mean it? - Yes, I do.
Dad,
I'm sorry about before.
I'll be really good to you from now on. I won't get mad either.
Do you mean it?
Yes.
All right then. From now on, let's not fight and get along, okay?
Promise.
Shin-ae, let's hurry up and go. Hee-dong and Yoo-Jin are already there.
Okay, let's go.
Mom! Grandpa! Over here!
Yoo-Jin! Hee-dong!
(White House Night Club)
Boss, the women who live in the storage room are gone!
Hey, wake up!
- Hey! - Run!
- Yoo-sung. - Hurry up and run after them!
Yoo-sung.
Stop right there!
Mom!
- Hey, drag them away. - No!
We need to go to Seoul and check something important! Please let us go!
Mister, we'll make sure to pay you back. Please let us go just this once!
- We need to find my father and grandfather! Please! - Enough with the nonsense!
- Mister!  - Come here!
- Mister! - Hurry up!
Please help us out just this once!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
- Let go of me! Damn it! - Hold still!
Let go!
Mi-poong!
Grandfather?
Are you my grandfather?
Grandfather...
Mi-poong! Yoo-sung!
Mi-poong, I'm your grandfather!
- Grandfather! Grandfather! Grandfather! - Mi-poong!
I'm your grandfather!
Grandfather!
- Grandfather! - You're my granddaughter!
You're my granddaughter!
(Blow Breeze)
Who on earth is this woman?
Hello, Mr. Jang-go. What do you mean China?
Mr. Heo, it's me. I have a favor to ask of you.
There's something you must know.
- Mom. - I want to go to the beach, too.
It would be so nice if all of us could live happily together forever.
How can she do such a thing?
Everything is true.
- I'm going to check myself. - Where are we going right now?
Hello?
You found your real granddaughter, didn't you?
Congratulations.