Subtitles by OnDemandKorea
Park Shin-ae. Park Shin-ae!
Yes, Hee-dong.
Don't forgive me.
I can't forgive you. I won't forgive you!
I'm going to kill you.
Hee-dong, I'm not worthy
enough to die in your hands.
I'm not human. I even abandoned my child.
Hee-dong.
Don't commit any sins
because of a woman like me.
If you tell me to die, I will.
I'll die. I'll die by myself.
I'll die.
Hey! Do you think it's all over if you die?
Then what about me and Yoo-jin?
Why did you do it? Why
did you do this to me?
What was I to you?
I was so good to you.
My name is Kang Mi-jung.
I'm thirty years old.
My mom's name is Kang Bok-soon.
I don't know who my father is.
The only thing I remember from my
childhood is that I was hungry every day.
I was always hungry.
My mom died from starvation because
she fed me first to keep me alive.
I was a poor homeless child in North Korea.
Who on earth gave the beautiful name "kotjebi"
to pathetic homeless children like me?
At first, I stole food.
Then I stole clothes.
After that, I stole money.
I stole everything I could.
That's how I managed to survive.
I wasn't a human being.
I was a beast.
But...
after I met you, I was
happy for the first time.
I realized that this is how
you live like a human being.
For the first time, I started to live
like a human being rather than a beast.
Everything was a lie.
My name. My hometown. My age. Everything.
I shouldn't have loved you.
I should have left you, but I couldn't.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
Thank you...
for loving me.
I won't forget this even if I die.
If you had any sincere feelings for me,
live and get your punishment.
- (Last Episode)
- The weather is great today.
- Dae-hoon, are you good at golfing?
- You can teach me, father.
- Have fun.
- Thank you.
Have a good time.
Young-ae, learn how to play golf so
that you can play with Dae-hoon.
Yes, father. I'll do that.
Honey. Mi-poong. I'll be back.
Let's go in.
Ms. Joo.
Mi-poong.
I'm sorry.
I've committed a grave sin.
Please forgive me.
Do you think you'll be
forgiven if we forgive you?
I went to the beach to die...
but I couldn't and just came back.
I've committed such a grave
sin to you and Mi-poong.
If I had just died like that, I felt like
I was committing an even graver sin.
And I don't think I should commit anymore
sins for the sake of my innocent Yoo-jin.
That's why I came back.
I'm so sorry.
We want to forget about you. We
don't even want to think about you.
Mi-poong, let's go.
Park Shin-ae.
You are arrested for embezzlement, fraud,
kidnapping, confinement,
and attempted murder.
You have the right to remain silent.
You have the right
to an attorney. Anything you
say can be used against you.
Take her in.
You're going to leave?
Yes.
Must you really leave?
Grandfather, I'm going to
forget about everything
on my trip and experience a lot of things.
All right.
If that's your plan, I can't stop you.
Please take care.
I don't know what you think,
but to me, you've always
been my reliable grandson.
So don't forget about me, and
don't be away for too long.
All right?
Yes, grandfather.
Good.
Take care.
- I'll call you.
- Okay.
How is your dad doing?
Are there any women around his vicinity?
Make sure you watch him well.
Many gold diggers will flock around
him because of the inheritance.
Got it?
Mom...
don't be shocked.
Why?
Hee-dong left.
W-what? Hee-dong left?
No way.
How could he...?
How could he leave Korea
without seeing me first?
It's not true, right?
You're lying, aren't you?
Mom, he really left.
But don't get shocked.
He took Yoo-jin with him.
Why would he do that?
Just looking at her must drive him crazy
because she reminds him of Shin-ae!
It seems like Hee-dong is going
to raise Yoo-jin as his own.
That's ridiculous!
That can never happen as long as I live!
Why does he have to raise
that wench's daughter?
Hee-dong, I'm sorry!
- Hee-dong!
- Mom!
- I need to get out of here! Hee-ra!
- Hee-ra, I'm so sorry!
- Mom!
Mom, stop it! Don't hit my mom!
The defendant Park Shin-ae...
in order to be Kim Deok-cheon's
fake granddaughter,
has injured Joo Young-ae and
committed robbery from her and
kidnapped and confined
Kim Deok-cheon's son Kim Dae-hoon.
She has committed many
unforgivable crimes as a person.
Therefore, according to
criminal law code 37,
defendant Park Shin-ae is
sentenced to ten years in prison.
Look here.
Hey, you.
Be quiet.
Big Boss is reading here.
- Quit your crying!
- Do you want to be beaten up again?
What the hell is she crying for?
Do you think you're the only one
here who has kids? Shut your mouth!
Stay quiet in that corner right over there.
Don't even dare breathe.
That's right.
Don't even breathe!
Here.
- You have one more roommate,
so don't fight and get along with her.
- Yes, ma'am!
Bye!
Where do you think you're sitting?
Come over here.
Hey, you. She's calling you.
Hey, look at that glare.
Wow, you're so frightening.
Hey, you. Stop glaring at her.
Damn it! She told you stop glaring!
You horrible...
- Hey, inmate 4949, what did you just say?
- Mother...
You!
They say you'll run into
your worst enemy at the
worst place and time. I'm glad you came.
You wench!
You deserve to die! My life and my
son's life are ruined because of you!
- You wench! You made me get a divorce!
Give my son's lie back!
- Stop her!
- Guard!
- You wench!
- Stop!
- I can't forgive you!
I decided to get back together with Jang-go.
We came to officially tell you that.
State it clearly here
that you'll get divorced.
I, Kim Mi-poong, will divorce Jang-go.
I'll never go back on my
words or change my mind.
If you don't keep your promise,
you're not even human.
Mi-poong and Jang-go can never be together.
Whose car is that?
There's no one in my family who
would ride such a nice car.
Isn't she Mi-poong's mom?
Oh, my. Jang-go and Mi-poong are back
together again. Is that what she's here for?
I think you came here because you
needed to tell me something.
Did you come here because
of Jang-go and Mi-poong?
Yes.
I'll be honest with you.
Yes, go ahead.
I don't want Mi-poong to get
married into this family again.
Thinking of Jang-go breaks my heart,
but still, I don't think this is right.
I witnessed Mi-poong going through
such a hard time in this family.
Would she have left the
house and offered to get
a divorce if things hadn't been so terrible?
She did those things even though
she loved Jang-go so much.
That's why...
I can't give permission.
What do you think?
If I'm wrong, please tell me so.
No, not at all.
I understand how you feel.
Mi-poong met her grandfather and father now.
I want Mi-poong to forget all about her
sufferings and just live a happy life.
Don't worry.
I'll talk to Jang-go.
Ms. Joo, I'm so sorry.
I'll apologize instead.
I'm sorry.
No. I'm the one who's sorry, ma'am.
Ma'am, it's cold outside.
Please don't come out.
No. You're my guest. I should
at least walk you out.
She's opposing Jang-go because of me?
What do I do?
I didn't see you come in.
Oh, now I see. You were
hiding back there like
a rat and eavesdropping on our conversation.
Good for you.
You must know what kind of
mess you've created again.
Because of you, Jang-go is about to
cry tears of blood again, you brat.
You want to make your child
walk on a path of flowers?
Fine. Was this a path of flowers for you?
You broke your child's
heart, not once, but twice.
Goodness. Our poor Jang-go.
He was cursed with a horrible mother.
What will he do now?
Mother, I'm sorry. Mother! Mother I'm sorry.
Mother, I'm sorry...
How does it feel working? Aren't you tired?
Not at all. I won't get
tired even if I have to
work straight for days
because it's so much fun.
You're amazing. I thought
you would be tired.
Oh, it's right here.
What's wrong?
I just feel a bit strange.
I had once lived here, but all those events
seem like they had happened a long time ago.
Mi-poong.
Thank you.
For what?
Just everything.
I'm grateful you came
back here with me again.
Gosh, what's wrong with me?
I'm nervous, like it's my first time here.
They know you already. It's not like
you're here for the first time.
Let's go in. They'll welcome you.
Grandma, Mi-poong is here!
Oh, my.
- Mi-poong!
Aunt Nam-yi. Jang-soo. Hee-ra.
Mom! Grandma! Come out! Mi-poong is here!
- Goodness.
- Grandma.
Who's this? Oh, my. Mi-poong.
- Mi-poong.
Have you been well?
Oh, come on. Why are you tearing up?
- Sit down.
- Let's sit.
My goodness.
I'm so happy for you.
I heard you reunited with
your grandfather and father.
Yes.
In the end, everyone will be reunited.
Come on, mom. That's not all. Her
grandfather isn't a normal man.
He's the chairman of Winner's Group.
- Congratulations, Mi-poong!
- Thank you, Aunt Nam-yi.
Hee-ra, what are you doing?
Prepare some tea and fruit.
Me?
Yes, grandma.
Hold on.
This is yours, grandma.
This is yours, aunt.
These are from Mi-poong.
Oh my goodness. What's this?
Oh my gosh! This is so pretty!
I always wanted a red wallet!
And this is for Jang-soo and Hee-ra.
Oh, what's this? Did you
buy something for us, too?
Hee-ra, Mi-poong brought us a gift!
Thanks, Mi-poong!
These are couple sunglasses!
I've always wanted these!
- What do you think? Do I look great?
- Yes.
You have great taste, Mi-poong!
Where did mom go? There's
a gift for her as well.
She's not home. She went out.
What is taking you so
long to bring some tea?
I'm almost done. I'll be there soon.
You guys, go to your rooms. I need to
talk to Jang-go and Mi-poong alone.
Go, Jang-soo and Hee-ra.
Okay, grandma.
Let's go, Hee-ra.
Bye.
Mi-poong,
thank you for not forgetting
about me and coming to see me.
But don't come here again.
Today is the last day.
Grandma, what are you talking about?
Grandma, did I do something wrong?
No. That's not what I mean.
We were the ones who did wrong.
You've done wrong to us.
But why are you telling me not to come?
I want to see you as often as possible.
You two got a divorce.
Then you two must go your different ways.
Grandma, I decided to get
back together with Jang-go.
That's why I came to greet you, mother,
and the rest of the family members.
I, too, wished you two would
get back together again,
but you've suffered so much in this house.
It would be ridiculous for you to be
this family's daughter-in-law again.
I did have hard times,
but I was happy as well.
You always protected and loved me.
And I've forgotten all about the past.
I found my grandfather again,
so I won't be a burden to Jang-go anymore.
That's exactly why! I feel too guilty!
Even if that's the past, do you think it's
something that could be forgotten so easily?
If things hadn't been so terrible,
would your kind and calm mother
have come here to see me
and requested me to keep you
two away from each other?
My mom came here?
Grandma, is that true?
So meet another good man
and start a new life with him.
Go home now.
Grandma...
Jang-go.
I'm sorry.
I had no idea my mom would come here
and say such things to your grandma.
I understand your mother.
I think I was too selfish.
Jang-go, you can't think about
breaking up with me, okay?
Okay.
Let's make an effort together.
Mi-poong, you're home?
Mom.
Is it true you asked Jang-go's
grandma to separate Jang-go and me?
Why?
Was it wrong to do so?
How can you ask his grandma to do that?
Then what was I supposed to do when you said
you're going to go back to that family?
You suffered so much
while staying with them.
I saw it with my own two eyes.
It wasn't enough that your
mother-in-law disrespected you.
She forced you to make a
hundred cabbages into kimchi.
You had to go to work, but she
forced you to make breakfast.
She flipped over the tables.
That's not all.
She came to the dumpling
diner, tried to take
your ring, and said all
those harsh words to you.
I can never forget those
things she did to you.
But you want me to send
you back to that house?
Mom, his mother won't do that to me anymore.
Yes. Of course she won't.
You're the granddaughter of
the chairman of Winner's
Group now. She won't dare
give you a hard time anymore.
She won't change. She's a
materialistic woman who
is determined to find a
rich daughter-in-law.
I'm not saying that I got back together
with Jang-go because I like his mother.
I can't give Jang-go up.
I hate the idea of having
such a woman as an in-law.
Time will help you forget everything.
So meet another man in the future
and have a clean start with him.
Mom.
I will never allow you and
Jang-go to be together.
When I think about how much you suffered
under his mother, I still get nightmares.
What's all this about?
Father.
Grandfather.
Is all of that true?
Did she force you to make kimchi
in that freezing weather,
flip the tables,
wrecked havoc in the dumpling diner,
and threatened you to divorce her son?
Did your mother-in-law really
do such things to you?
Yes, father. That's why they got a divorce.
My goodness.
How dare she do those
things to my granddaughter.
It's not like that.
If it's not, are you saying that the
things your mother said are untrue?
Oh, well, they are true,
but Jang-go tried to help
mom and me until the end.
Because he was trying to help
us, he almost lost his house.
So I begged him for us to get
divorced, which is why we did.
Mom, if you're going to
tell grandfather what
happened, you should tell him everything.
Jang-go tried not to get a divorce with
me, and he helped us until the end.
Am I opposing this because of Jang-go?
Mi-poong, listen to me carefully.
I can never allow you to get married
into such a family. End things with him.
Grandfather.
How could she have been so cruel to you
when the two of had gotten married already?
She disrespected you for being
a poor North Korean defector.
I can't be in-laws with such a family.
Grandfather...
End of discussion.
Dad.
Did you cry? Is something wrong?
Dad...
What is it? Tell me. I'll
solve everything for you.
Really?
Of course.
Because I'm your father.
And...
you're the only one who I'm telling this to.
I'm the most powerful person in this house.
That's why I'm telling
you that I'll solve it.
What do you mean by that?
You thought your grandfather was the most
powerful one in this house, didn't you?
But your grandfather can't say no to me.
That's why I'm the most
powerful one in this house.
Got it?
Got it.
I'll tell you everything, so
you must solve it for me.
I will.
Tell me everything.
What can I do about Mi-poong?
Since my father and wife are against this
relationship, I'll have to meet Jang-go.
So if I like him, I'm going
to fulfill Mi-poong's wish.
Who can it be?
(Yoo-jin)
It's Yoo-jin!
Yoo-jin?
Why did Yoo-jin text you?
Yoo-jin and I are friends.
Grandfather Dae-hoon, I'm in Cuba with
Mr. Jo Hee-dong.
The weather is great, and
everyone here is so much fun.
But Mr. Jo Hee-dong doesn't smile.
Don't worry. I'm going
to make him smile again.
Yoo-jin is so smart.
He seemed like such a good person.
He just had to meet the wrong woman.
It's okay.
Even if I don't remember the past,
I'm still living happily like this.
Hee-dong will be happy again soon.
Let's look at it together.
- She sent you pictures?
- Cute, right?
Who is it? Huh?
Who the hell is snoring?
Hey! Quit your snoring!
Oh my stomach...
My stomach...
Mother, are you okay?
Hey, you damn, evil wench!
How dare you use violence!
Do you think you don't snore? You
better apologize to my mother-in-law!
- Apologize to her at once!
- I think I'm done sleeping tonight.
You young, little thing. You con-artist.
Let go of her hair.
I'm going to change the order of your ribs!
You con-artists from a messy family!
What? Con-artists? From a messy family?
Yes, that's what I said!
Hold tightly onto her!
If you treat my mother-in-law disrespectfully
one more time, I'll get you.
Okay, I'm sorry, girls.
Let's get along well from now on.
She's my daughter-in-law.
Daughter. In. Law.
Mother, lie over there.
Yes, come here! This is the warmest spot!
Come here.
The new Big Boss should
lie down next to her.
Please lie down.
You can relax your eyes now.
- Turn off the light.
- Yes, ma'am!
- Turn off the light!
- We must turn off the light!
Good night.
It's too cramped here! Move over! Gosh!
Shin-ae.
Mother.
Come in.
Ms. Joo, the mother of
Lawyer Lee Jang-go is here.
Who?
What brings you here?
Well...
I heard Mi-poong...
found her grandfather and father.
I sincerely congratulate you.
Did you come all the way here just for that?
The truth is...
I came for Jang-go and Mi-poong.
About Jang-go and Mi-poong?
They're divorced now. They
don't have anything to do with
each other. So what do you
need to tell me about them?
Mi-poong came over to my house,
but I was too ashamed to face
her, so I couldn't even see her.
I know very well that I have
no right to come here either.
Still, I mustered up the courage
to come here for the kids' sakes.
"Kids' sakes?"
Um...
I'm the one who's at fault here.
You know very well that Jang-go
didn't do anything wrong.
Just think of me as a dead person.
Can't you allow them to get re-married?
Did you forget what you did to Mi-poong?
What did you do to my daughter?
You couldn't possibly have
forgotten all about it.
Even now, I remember how you tossed out
all her belongings to the front yard.
I can't forget how you
yelled at her to get out.
But now you want me to allow
them to get remarried?
Look here!
Get out of here before
I say harsher things to you.
Housekeeper!
- Yes, ma'am.
- Tell this woman to get out of here at once.
And don't ever open the
front gate for her again.
Ms. Joo...
I've committed a grave sin.
I'll severe mother-son ties with Jang-go.
I'll cut ties with him and live somewhere
far away. That works, doesn't it?
I'm really regretting what I've done.
I was blinded by greed,
so even though I knew
Mi-poong was a nice woman,
I pretended not to notice.
I'm sorry.
It's late, but I'll apologize now.
I was wrong.
I'll apologize! I'm sorry!
Please forgive me, Ms. Joo!
I've committed a grave sin!
I'll cut ties with him!
Please forgive me!
I've committed a grave sin, Ms. Joo!
I'm sorry! Please forgive me!
Ms. Joo, I've committed a grave sin!
I'm sorry!
No matter how much I think of
it, I can't understand why your
grandfather and mother would
be against you and Jang-go.
From what I see, he seems
like a good person.
The truth is,
it's not because of Jang-go-
I know. It's because his
mother was mean to you.
But it's you and Jang-go who are
getting married. Why does that matter?
Right?
Of course. So don't worry about it.
I'll solve everything for you.
But what do you like about Jang-go?
He's good at playing slap match.
He's pretty good-looking.
More importantly, he's fun.
I hate people who are no fun.
But Mi-poong, why must you marry Jang-go?
During my most shabby and difficult
times, he was there for me.
When I was falsely accused, he
was the one who believed in me.
When I was searching for
you, he helped me, too.
Father, the only one I want to
marry in this world is Jang-go.
I see.
What fun things are you
talking about without us?
Jang-go.
Son-in-law.
I can call you that, right?
Yes, father.
Mi-poong said she wants to marry you.
Do you feel the same way, too?
Say it like a man.
Do you want to marry my daughter?
Yes, sir!
Do you have the confidence
to make her happy forever?
Yes, I do!
Is that so?
Then...
I shall grant you permission
to be Mi-poong's husband!
Really? Do you mean it?
Thank you! Thank you, father!
I'll be really good to her!
Father, have a hot dog.
Thank you.
Wow, grandpa! You're the best!
I'll open it for you.
Sure.
Mom.
Where did she go? The market?
To my dearest son Jang-go,
I'm sorry.
No words can justify my actions.
I thought I was doing the best for you,
but now that I look back,
it was just for my greed.
- Come out.
- Don't you ever come near Jang-go again!
- Hurry up!
- I'll get you then!
I think I'm going to get
sick just looking at you.
So can't you leave Jang-go now and
take your family out of my house?
I'm sorry I was such a greedy, flippant mom.
Jang-go, pretend I don't exist. I hope
you'll live a happy life with Mi-poong.
Mother, I'm very sorry.
Please be healthy.
Jang-soo.
Hee-ra.
I'm sorry.
From, your terrible mother.
Mom...
Grandma! Aunt!
Hi, grandma.
What did you say?
Okay. I'll be home soon.
Bye.
Jang-go, what is it? Is something wrong?
No, it's nothing. Take your father inside.
Yoo-sung, see you later.
Bye, uncle.
Good-bye, father.
Bye. Let's play a game next time.
Sure. Bye.
- Drive safely.
- I will. Go on in.
Father, have some tea.
- Sure.
- We're back.
- Grandfather.
- Oh, you're home, Yoo-sung?
- Welcome! Weren't you cold?
- Where did the three of you go?
We went to the amusement park with Jang-go.
Jang-go?
Mi-poong, your grandfather and
I told you very clearly that
you can't be with Jang-go. What
do you think you're doing?
Honey, what are you saying?
They love each other, so
why are you opposing them?
Dae-hoon, stay out of this. Let
Young-ae take care of this.
Father, I'm Mi-poong's father, so why
are you telling me to stay out of this?
There's a reason for that. That's why
Young-ae and I are against this.
Father, let's settle this once and for all.
Is Mi-poong my daughter or yours?
You should be the one to stay out of this!
Honey, if you're going to oppose this as
well, then you stay out of this, too!
You don't know what's going on.
What do you mean I don't?
I know everything, too!
I know Jang-go's mother criticized
Mi-poong and hated her a lot.
But the one who criticized Mi-poong
was Jang-go's mother, not Jang-go.
So why are being like that to him?
Honey. Dae-hoon-
I'm not finished yet!
In my opinion, Jang-go did nothing wrong.
Also, I heard Jang-go
helped you and Mi-poong
out a lot when you were having a hard time.
You shouldn't be like that.
If you received help, you should
know how to return the favor.
The worst people in this world are the
ones who don't know how to be grateful!
Father, am I wrong?
Well, you are right, but...
I'm not wrong.
Mi-poong, listen to me carefully.
I shall give you permission to date Jang-go!
Um... dad?
I think mom is very angry. What will you do?
Dae-hoon, you're in big trouble now.
I didn't say anything wrong!
So don't you worry about such a thing!
Honey.
Honey, are you really mad at me?
Think about it.
What if my father was against
us, and we had to break up?
How would you feel?
I hate it when Mi-poong is sad.
I want her to be very happy.
Still, how could you yell at me and
make me into an ungrateful person?
I'm sorry, honey.
I didn't mean it like that.
Instead, take this, and
don't be mad anymore.
What's this?
A gift for you.
I felt bad for going to the amusement
park without you, so I bought it for you.
So take this, and please
don't be mad anymore. Okay?
Honey!
How can you laugh right now? You could
have knocked me down with a feather!
Honey, are you okay?
I must have gotten punished
for having done wrong to you.
Honey, I'll listen to you from now on,
so don't be angry anymore, okay?
You smiled.
Since you smiled, you're going to give
permission to Mi-poong, aren't you?
- I don't know.
- Thank you, honey.
Hi, Jang-soo. What about mother?
I searched the saunas and even called her
friends, but no one knows where she is!
I'll search for her, too, so the one who
finds her first should contact the other.
Mom.
Jang-go.
Do you know how worried I was?
It's late. Let's go back together.
Thank you, Jang-go...
for coming to find a terrible mom like
me and offering to go back home with me.
Why would you say that?
I'm your child. Your son.
I can't go.
Why not?
I know how you feel, so
let's go back together.
I know very well that you'll understand
and forgive me since you're my son.
However,
I can't forgive myself.
I've done something horrible
to you and Mi-poong.
Jang-go,
I feel too guilty right
now to go back with you.
When I get the courage to go back...
When I get the courage to
smile and meet you again...
I'll come back then.
Can you understand me?
All right.
You'll come back, won't you?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, Jang-go.
I'm sorry, Jang-go.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
Mi-poong!
Jang-go!
My grandfather and mom
allowed us to be together.
- Really?
- Yes, my father solved everything.
Did you already know about it?
Yes.
What's this?
Do you remember this?
Of course!
Jang-go, that music room
legend must be true.
You still didn't find it yet?
What's the rush? We have plenty of
time, so I'm going to take my time.
But Kim Seung-hee, be honest.
You didn't come here to
find something, did you?
Did you come here to check the legend?
Well, the thing is...
I wanted to check if we were
destined to be together or not.
I had my doubts, but I was right?
Mi-poong,
I thought I would never
be able to see you again.
But when I saw you in Seoul again,
I felt it then.
We were destined to get
married from the beginning.
Jang-go...
Shin-ae!
- Ju-no!
- Shin-ae, I brought my grandmother with me.
I brought my grandfather with me.
Where?
Grandfather!
Grandmother!
- Jung-hee? Are you Jung-hee?
- Yes!
- Jung-hee!
- Honey!
Grandmother.
- (Seoul Bumpkin, Pyeongyang Delinquent)
- In the end, they met.
Those elders were husband and wife in North
Korea. Does that mean you guys break up?
No. My character was adopted, remember?
I'm not her real grandson,
so it's all right.
Really? How fortunate.
But it's so sad. Did they
meet after 65 years?
Goodness. What's the point
of North Korean families
reuniting in dramas? They
should reunite in real lie.
- That's true.
- What are our politicians doing
not solving such a matter?
If they're living off of taxes,
they should at least do such a thing.
Everyone must self-reflect.
Does it make sense that families
can't meet each other for 65 years?
- It doesn't make sense at all!
- At least they reunited in the drama.
Your mom really wanted
to see you appear on TV.
Can she watch TV in the temple, too?
- Hye-sung must be cold.
- Yes, it's because he's cold.
Let's go see your grandma, Hye-sung.
Hye-sung, what's that?
Venerable sir.
- Hello.
- Welcome.
Where's my mother-in-law?
Mother!
Oh, you're here?
Yes. Hello.
Did you pick some vegetables?
Do they come out already?
Yes. I was going to send some to you, but
you can take them while you're here.
Thank you.
What brings you here?
We just wanted to see you.
You should go back with us today.
Oh, dear. You came here for vain again.
I like being here.
I feel comfortable here.
- We feel sorry.
- There's no need to be sorry.
What about Jang-go and Hye-sung?
- Mom!
- Jang-go!
Oh, my adorable puppy!
- Let's go to grandma.
- Oh, my! You grew a lot!
Why are you crying? Didn't you miss me?
I put money and Yoo-jin's photos in there.
Buy something good to eat.
Is Yoo-jin doing well?
She's doing well.
Right now, she's in Cambodia
building houses for the needy.
Hee-dong is smiling a lot, too, nowadays.
Dad, don't come here anymore.
I'll come again, Shin-ae.
Hee-dong lost a lot of weight.
He's building houses for the
needy in Cambodia right now.
Crazy fool.
He should be thinking about
coming back, getting re-married,
having kids, and living
happily ever after with them.
He's raising someone
else's kid while building
homes for someone else in
someone else's country.
What did I eat to give
birth to a fool like him?
Mother, don't you realize
why Hee-dong is doing this?
He's paying for our sins instead of us.
What did you say?
Why does my son have to pay
for your sins instead?
If he hadn't met you, why
would he be living like this?
It's all your fault! My life
is ruined because of you!
My son's life is ruined because of you, too!
It's all your fault! Your fault!
Guard! Guard! Guard!
What now?
Let me go to a different room!
I think I'm going to die if I'm with her!
I can't live with her!
Inmate 4949, last time we
moved you to a different
room, but you begged us to take you back to
this room because you couldn't live without
inmate 3894, so you had
gone on a hunger strike.
I take it back! Let me use a different room!
- I can't live with that wench!
- Let her change.
Go ahead and change rooms.
Get out! Get out! Get out!
- Get out! Take your shoes!
- You get out!
- I'll carry it, honey.
- Thank you.
(Happy Birthday)
Mr. Kim, we're here!
- Hi, Dal-ho!
- Hi!
You came?
- Have you been well, Young-ae?
- Yes.
Young-ae, I brought griddle
pancakes and glass noodles.
Oh, you didn't have to!
"Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday to grandpa.
Happy birthday to you!"
Happy birthday! Be healthy!
(Let's definitely meet
when the countries unite!)
Yeong-cheol!
My son Yeong-cheol!
I'll go to see you!
I'll go to you!
I'll make sure to go, Yeong-cheol!
Soon-ok.
Yeong-cheol.
I'll come soon.
Just wait a little bit longer.
(Thank you for watching "Blow Breeze."
We hope a wonderful breeze
will be blown in the world.)
Subtitles by OnDemandKorea