(Episode 6)
It's that way.
-That way? -Yes.
Be careful.
Oh, are you the new tenants?
-Yes, grandma. -I see.
Yes, we are. Hello.
I don't know how to express my gratitude towards you for helping us out like this.
But is this all that's in your family? Is there anyone else?
No, it's just us three.
I see.
-This is the key for the back gate. -I see.
The previous tenant said it was uncomfortable for her to
use the same gate as us, so she always used the back gate.
You can use the same front gate as us, but it'll
be comfortable for you to use the back gate.
Yes, I understand.
Thank you.
Oh my goodness. Unlike most people nowadays, you guys are very courteous.
My goodness. You guys will live well.
Oh, go on and move your belongings.
-Yes, excuse us. -Of course.
Let's go in.
They're extremely courteous.
But what did you mean by you wanted me to pretend
not to know you in front of those people?
Let's go in. I'll tell you inside.
What is it?
They don't have any place to go, so they are
going to pay their security deposit later.
I thought their pride would get hurt if they
know this is my house. I know them personally.
My goodness. Why would you lie about that?
It's only a matter of time before they find out that you live here.
That's true, but I will explain it to them later on.
Or else, with their pride, they wouldn't have moved in here.
Goodness. They don't have a place to go, so what's the point of having pride?
Anyways, for the time being, you can't let them know I live here, okay?
Okay, I got it.
That's not hard to do at all.
We're done.
Okay.
-Thank you. -Thank you.
Good-bye.
Thank you.
Take care.
Oh!
Do you like the house?
-We love it! -We love it!
Mr. Lee, thank you so much.
It's clean and cozy, and there's plenty of sunshine.
I don't know how I can thank you for finding such an amazing house for us.
I'm getting embarrassed because you keep saying that.
All I did was ask the house owner to let you move in.
Who would do such a thing for people like us?
We really won't forget your kindness.
Oh my goodness! I'm sorry for embarrassing you, Mr. Lee,
but I'm so grateful that I keep thanking you.
Come to think of it, Mi-poong takes after you.
She talks a lot, just like you do.
Excuse me.
Hello?
Okay.
I'm sorry, but something came up, so I think I'll have to leave now.
You don't have to apologize. You helped us even when you're so busy.
No matter what we do, we won't be able to pay you back for your kindness.
I see. I'll be going now.
All right.
-Good-bye. -Bye, Mr. Lee.
-Good-bye. -Thank you.
Mom, since you keep doing that, Mr. Lee is getting embarrassed.
What can I do when I'm so grateful to him?
Anyways, is this really our home, Mi-poong?
Is this a dream or reality?
This feels like a dream for me, too.
Yoo-sung, pinch your grandma and me.
Pinch us.
It's not a dream!
-Really? It's not a dream? -It's not a dream?
Here. This is the $5,000 you need.
I'm sorry that I keep borrowing money from you when I haven't paid anything back yet.
I'll pay this money back to you very soon.
You can take your time. It's not like I have to use it anytime soon.
You're not the type to run away and not pay my money back.
Of course not.
Thank you for understanding me, Geum-sil.
The coffee is cold now because I went to the bank.
Should I order another cup?
No, you don't have to.
Anyways, I hope that your daughter and my son
will like each other when they meet tomorrow.
Right?
Yes.
If it goes well for our kids and we become in-laws, we'll become a family,
so there's no burden when we have to borrow money from each other.
Just thinking about it makes me happy. What about you?
Oh, dear. Geum-sil, I'm sorry, but I have to go now.
Okay, I have to go, too.
It's tomorrow at the Prince Hotel at noon. Make sure to tell your daughter.
Oh, I'll pay for the coffee.
Geum-sil is letting me borrow money from her
because she wants to set up our kids together.
I fell into that trap.
Thank you.
Geum-sil is sly and scary.
But Geum-sil, dream on.
That'll never happen.
Here you go.
Thank you!
Don't live your life like that.
There's something called affection between people.
I treated you like that because I felt comfortable
with you, like you were part of my family.
You ratted out on me to my father and made me into
some nasty person who doesn't pay her workers.
I'm so disappointed.
-It's just that it happened more than once- -Is this a dishcloth or a rag?
Before you demand for money, make sure you do your work right!
Inconsiderate woman!
Because of her, I have to ask around for favors!
Mom, I'm home.
Hi.
You're coming home now, sweetie?
I need to talk to you.
Talk to me?
What is it?
Tomorrow at the Prince Hotel at noon, just eat lunch and come home.
Why do I have to meet your friend's son?
I told you I won't go on blind dates anymore.
Use that smart brain of yours to hear me out.
It's not a blind date!
Just eat lunch and come home. Pretend like you're on a blind date.
Why the heck do I have to do that?
I have my reason.
Don't ask me about it.
Hold on. Does she have your weakness?
It's nothing like that.
I'm doing this because it would be nice to be close to a lawyer.
So to simply put it, you want me to go out tomorrow, just eat
lunch, and dump him while telling him he's not my style. Right?
My smart little girl. My cutie pie.
You got it!
Fine then. I'll do it one condition.
I'll go out tomorrow and pretend it's a real blind date,
buy me a bag. A new one just came in.
What? A bag?
No.
Then forget it.
This.
Come on, mom! This is too much!
-I don't have any money. Just help me out this once. -This is the last time.
-Gosh, mom. -My cutie.
What's going on? Where's the phoenix?
It was a dream?
It must have been a dream.
But what kind of dream was this?
What kind of dream is so vivid?
Am I winning the lottery?
Phoenix dream.
It's right here.
A dream of a phoenix coming into a home means that a precious guest will be coming.
If a single person dreams of this, it means they'll meet a wonderful partner.
Geum-sil. Geum-sil!
Geum-sil, I hit jackpot!
A huge jackpot!
What is it?
After work, I must have been so tired, because I fell asleep.
But do you know what I dreamed of?
Hurry up and buy my dream!
Why? Did you dream of pigs?
How dare you compare pigs to my dream!
You know what a phoenix is, right?
A dazzling gold phoenix came right into our front gate!
Just now!
A gold phoenix came into our house?
That's right!
It was so vivid that I searched up phoenix dreams,
and it said that we'll either get a precious guest or,
if you're single, you'll meet a wonderful partner.
This is Jang-go's dream!
Are you sure it was a phoenix dream?
It wasn't a chicken?
You don't think I can tell the difference between a chicken and a phoenix?
I thought it was a dream for Jang-go, so I was going to sell it to you, but forget it.
No, no. I'll buy it.
I'll buy it.
Okay.
Here. A hundred dollars. Happy?
Okay!
Then is she the phoenix?
What do you mean?
Tomorrow, Jang-go and my friend's daughter is going to meet.
Geum-sil, that's it.
Tomorrow, they're going to like each other,
and she's going to become part of our family.
I wish everything worked out just like you said!
Goodness. It's been a while since you came home
from work, but you haven't even changed your clothes yet.
What are you two up to lately?
What is it?
It's nothing.
You don't have to know.
I dare you to say that to me again!
I'll rip your mouth off!
-Mom. -Nam-yi.
I should wash and sleep.
I gave the key to the back gate to the new tenants today.
What are they like?
They're very courteous. It's just a mom, her daughter, and her grandson.
If there's anything you need to tell them, you should go see them now.
You and Jang-go already met them. I can meet them later.
Maybe the owner is here.
Hurry up and answer the door.
Mr. Lee, what are you doing here?
Oh, you're here.
Come on in.
Come in.
Pardon me.
No problem.
Mr. Lee, what's that?
This?
I wonder what it is.
Ta-da!
I bought it for you.
It's the jelly that I like!
Why would you give such a thing to him at night?
If Yoo-sung gets cavities because of this, will you take responsibility for it?
I thought he would like it.
It's just one time, so it shouldn't matter.
He bought it for Yoo-sung.
Yoo-sung, thank Mr. Lee before you eat it.
Thank you, Mr. Lee!
But don't eat too much, okay?
I'll get in trouble by your aunt.
But what are you doing here?
While you were moving in, I noticed that there was a hole in the screen.
So...
There are many mosquitoes at this time of the year.
Oh, my!
You came because of that?
We're troubling you too much.
We have nothing to serve you.
Oh, Mi-poong! Go and buy a bottle of juice. Mr. Lee must be thirsty.
No, I'm fine.
I'm not thirsty.
I'll just do this quickly and go.
Still...
Thank you.
It's done.
Not even one mosquito will be able to come inside now.
I'll be going now.
We haven't finished unpacking yet, so we can't even serve you a cup of tea.
I feel so bad.
No, it's fine. You can give it to me next time.
Okay. Make sure you come again, Mr. Lee.
Thank you for today.
-Bye. -Bye.
See him out.
Okay, mom.
-I'll say hello to the owner, too. -Okay.
Seung-hee...
Why do you keep calling me Seung-hee?
At this rate, my mom will find out that you're Jang-go.
Sorry.
Anyways, I need to talk to you.
Okay, talk to me.
I can't talk to you here. Let's go out.
What is it? Why are you hesitating?
Is it something bad?
Did something go wrong with our security deposit?
No, it's not that.
That's not it.
Then what is it?
The truth is...
that's my house.
What?
What do you mean by that?
So the thing is...
that house you moved into today is mine.
It's your house?
Are you serious?
Yes.
I'm sorry for not telling you the truth.
I thought you would have said no if I had told you the truth.
Of course I would have!
How could you fool me like this?
Are you joking? Do you think we're easy?
How could you do whatever you want?
Seung-hee. No. Mi-poong.
Calm down and listen to me.
Do I look like a fool to you because I lost my security deposit in a fraud?
You thought it was okay that you can do as you please
with me because I'm a poor North Korean defector, huh?
Kim Seung-hee.
That's not it!
We'll move out tomorrow.
To where?
Do you even have money to move?
Or will you return to that storage room again?
Will they even accept you? What if they don't?
Are you saying you and your family will go out into the streets?
How can you only think of your pride?
Don't you think of Yoo-sung and your mother?
They had to go to the emergency room because they were sick!
But how can you say that?
It was nice to see your mother and Yoo-sung so happy after you guys moved in.
I just found out today that your mother is a talkative person.
I understand how you feel.
I do understand,
but you should realize that this is the best for now.
Receive your security deposit first, make a lot of money,
and then you can move out if a better house appears.
My mother and your mother know each other.
My mother will faint if she finds out.
I told my mother that you're my friend's sibling's family.
I thought I wouldn't have to bring it up on purpose.
Just like your mother didn't recognize me, my mother won't recognize you guys, too.
We'll tell them when the time is right.
When your security deposit is returned to you, and
you still feel uncomfortable, you can move out then.
Let's do that, Seung-hee.
I mean, Mi-poong.
Okay?
Let's go in.
Hold on.
Jang-go...
I got it.
If you're so grateful, buy me a meal next time.
Just so you know, I really like black bean noodles.
Okay.
I'll definitely buy you black bean noodles.
Let's go in.
Aunt, this place is so nice!
The water is really warm, and the bathroom isn't cold at all.
Yoo-sung, did you take a bath?
Let me see.
You're so cute, Yoo-sung!
You took a bath, so you're all clean and shiny!
Did you say hello to the owner?
I thought it was too late, so I just came back.
Oh, really?
Just leave it.
We already greeted the grandmother already.
We can greet her later.
But, if you didn't go see the owner, were you with Mr. Lee all this time?
Did you two drink tea?
Of course not, mom.
We just talked a bit.
About what?
Nothing much.
Just about when we'll get our security deposit back.
I see.
About Mr. Lee, Mi-poong...
Is he interested in you?
Mom! What are you talking about?
He's not!
Then why else would he be so nice to us?
Come on, mom.
He's just helping us out because we're pitiful. Don't imagine nonsense like that.
It makes me feel sorry to Mr. Lee.
I guess.
Mr. Lee has a good career, good looks, and a good personality.
He must have a girlfriend, right?
I have to finish unpacking.
Come in.
Mom. What about Jang-soo?
I don't know. He must be drinking somewhere again.
I'm so upset.
Drink this. It's red ginseng.
You should drink it.
Hurry.
You work outside.
Thank you.
You saw my text, right?
Tomorrow noon at Prince Hotel.
I saw it, but what is it for?
You saw it, but why didn't you reply?
I was busy.
Since you didn't reply, I already told them you were okay with it.
Mom, is it...?
Yes.
My friend and I won't be there. You'll be meeting her daughter alone.
Come on, mom.
How can you make such a plan without asking me first?
You should start dating now.
All you've done is study and work so far.
Aren't you going to get married?
I'll take care of that.
And my office isn't even stable yet.
You can do that after you get married.
And more than anything else, my friend's daughter
is lively and honest. I really like her.
I really don't want to lose her.
Mom, I really don't like such meetings.
Then just this once.
Just do it for my sake this once. Please, Jang-go?
I already arranged the meeting. Are you going to embarrass me like this?
Fine.
Good. Thank you, Jang-go.
You can't go wrong if you do as I say.
Thank you.
Gosh, seriously.
Although I'm just going to eat, but if you want to eat
with me, you need to wait at least fifteen minutes.
What the heck? It's that psycho from last time!
Why must he be here out of all places?
How annoying!
Hello?
I'm Lee Jang-go, the one you're supposed to meet today.
Oh, yes. Hello.
I'm here already.
Where are you?
I arrived here just now.
Jo Hee-Ra?
Lee Jang-go?
Gosh! Is mom crazy?
How can she tell me to eat with that psycho?
I can't let this one slide!
Damn it.
Damn car.
Look here, mister!
You can't just go.
What is it?
You just hit my car's door.
Look! Look at that!
It's dented!
How dare you accuse an innocent person.
Oh my god. You hit my car's door just now so how can you play innocent?
I saw it with my own two eyes!
So why would you park like that?
Park properly from now on. Got it?
Mister, if you don't solve this and just leave, I'm going to call the police.
Police? My god.
What are you doing?
Let go. Let go of me!
You little-
What are you doing?
Who are you?
Let go.
Mind your own business and piss off.
You put this woman in danger with your car keys.
Criminal law code 260 article 1: in the case
you assault a woman with a dangerous object,
you'll be charged with a special assault offense, so think before you act.
What are you?
Would you like me to tell you the law code for
running away after you damaged her car door?
I wasn't running away.
I'm sorry.
Contact me after you get the quote from a car center.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
In such a situation, you shouldn't irritate the person.
Next time call your car insurance first.
Excuse me.
Thank you for saving me.
It was nothing.
And I'm sorry about last time. It was my fault.
It's all in the past anyways. Don't worry about it.
I came out today because my mom forced me to,
but if you ask me out on a second date, I will accept it.
So, for example...
if you ask me to watch a movie with you, I will.
I'm sorry. I have an appointment with a client.
What does he mean?
Is he saying that he doesn't want to watch a movie with me or
that he has no time right now so that we should meet later on?
Which one is it?
I'm so curious what they'll be doing right now.
It's daytime, so they won't be drinking.
I know. I wonder what they do on blind dates nowadays.
Wouldn't it be the same as the old days? Eat and watch a movie?
But since he's not back yet, I guess they're getting along great!
Why are you back already?
Did you just eat with her?
You should have drank tea, too.
Mom, what are you doing here?
Why else would she be here? She couldn't stay home
because she was curious about your blind date.
Mom, don't ever do this again.
I don't want to meet women that way.
Why not? Did she not like you?
You asked her for a second date, but she said no?
Mom, I'm very busy today. Aunt, you can go home early with mom today.
Okay.
Oh, Mr. Kim!
That woman!
Father, if there's a document you need, you should tell me or Dal-ho to get it.
You don't have to do it. It'd be tiring.
How can I ask you guys to get it when I'm the only one who knows about it?
I'll be back.
Good-bye, father.
Good-bye, Mr. Kim.
Did you catch a rat and eat it?
Pardon?
You're a maid. What's wrong your lipstick color?
It's bloody red, just like you ate a rat.
Is there someone you want to look nice for at my house?
What are you talking about?
My daughter gave this lipstick to me, so I tried it on.
And I told you so many times not to go into my father's room.
But you go in whenever you have the chance and even shut the door.
On top of that, you giggle at everything when you're next to him.
What are your true intentions?
What do you mean by true intentions?
Mr. Kim asked for a cup of tea, so I-
I told you to call for me at those times!
I forgot. I'm sorry.
It won't happen again.
Don't wear that red lipstick at my house!
It doesn't suit you at all!
I dare her to go into father's room with the door closed again! I'll just fire her!
She makes me uneasy!
Mom! Mom!
Oh, sweetie!
You must have really just ate lunch!
-Mom. -Yes?
We need to talk.
-Why? -Hurry!
What did you say?
You asked him to watch a movie?
Yes, but he didn't give me a clear answer whether he'll watch it or not.
Oh my gosh, Hee-Ra! What's wrong with you?
Did you forget I told you to just eat with him and reject him nicely?
I was going to do that at first, too, but out of all the guys
that I met so far, he seems to be the best one.
You are out of your mind!
What's so good about him?
The pure and honest look in his eyes?
He's manly.
Anyways, he's different from the other guys I met so far.
What in the world are you talking about?
He went from rags to riches!
He has a windowed grandmother, a widowed mother,
a divorced aunt, and a jobless brother!
You shouldn't even look his way!
Then why did you tell me to meet him?
Didn't you tell me to meet him because he's a good man?
Mom, call your friend and ask her what her son
thinks of me and whether he liked me or not.
How can you hate all those wealthy men with potential
and like empty fools like him instead?
Your life is going to get messed up!
Maid!
Get her a glass of cold water so that she can drink and wake up to reality!
God! Mom is no help at all!
That's right!
Her phone number is...
Geum-sil.
I've been on quite a few blind dates before,
but I have never been the first one to ask the
man on a second date to go watch a movie before.
All right. I understand what you mean.
You must have felt very upset.
But Jang-go didn't answer to your second date request because he doesn't like you.
It was because he was shy.
It didn't seem like that. He seems like the type
to say what is on his mind. He was manly, too.
Huh?
Oh, well, of course he's manly because he's a man who fights against injustice.
But Jang-go is a fool when it comes to women.
I thought it was because he had a girlfriend.
Of course not. That's not true at all!
To be honest...
Remember I told you about that weird psycho I met in the parking lot?
That person was actually Jang-go.
Oh, really?
Yes, but truthfully, it was my fault that day.
That's why I think Jang-go did that because he's disappointed in me.
So that's what happened.
I guess it would be a bit iffy then.
Jang-go is a bit inflexible.
Right, Ms. Hwang?
He doesn't have a good impression of me. What do I do?
Hee-Ra,
what do you like about Jang-go?
Compared to other guys, I think Jang-go is a hot brain.
Hot brain?
What's that?
A man with a sexy brain.
He's not just sexy. He's cool sexy.
A brain is sexy?
Oh my goodness! Young people's words are so funny!
Hee-Ra, then let's do this.
I'll talk about you nicely to Jang-go, so you just capture his heart!
How a man act depends on the woman.
This is the address of his office.
Go and visit him.
(Seoul Law Office. Lawyer: Lee Jang-go.)
This is my grandfather's building!
Oh, my! Are you serious?
Oh my goodness! What kind of fate is this?
I didn't know Jang-go's office was in your grandfather's building!
She is the phoenix.
The phoenix came in first. I should never chase it out.
Geum-sil, I really like Hee-Ra!
I only talked with her for a short while, but she was so cute and pretty!
But if such a pretty girl asked him to go watch
a movie, he should have quickly said yes.
Why would he say no and hurt her pride?
I know!
It's my friend Chung-ja.
Hurry up and answer it!
Hi, Chung-ja.
Geum-sil, I feel so bad about what happened with our kids today.
Huh? What do you mean?
My daughter said that your son is not her style.
Hee-Ra said she doesn't like Jang-go?
Oh, my!
Yes, Geum-sil.
I guess we're not fated to be in-laws.
Geum-sil, are you listening to me?
I feel so bad.
It's fine.
Okay. I'll talk to you later.
Geum-sil, what was that?
You just met Hee-Ra.
Chung-ja just forced her daughter to meet
Jang-go because I asked her to let them meet.
She acted all high and mighty because she has some
inheritance. In other words, she took us as fools.
Your friend is really ridiculous.
But there is no parent who wins over her child.
She likes Jang-go, so what will her mom do about it?
Don't you think so?
Hello, sir.
Oh, Mi-poong, are you going on a delivery?
Yes.
But why is this sewing machine outside?
Oh, I'm getting rid of it because I'm getting a new one.
Really?
Then may I take this?
Sure.
It's a bit old though, so you'll have to fix it.
You might have to grease it up, too.
It doesn't matter. Thank you, sir.
I'll come pick it up after I'm done with work.
Oh, my!
Why are you so surprised?
You came out of nowhere! I almost had a heart attack!
I did it on purpose so that you can have a heart attack. So what?
I'll get you back later.
Go ahead.
But what is this? Why is it so heavy?
It's a sewing machine.
A sewing machine? You know how to use one?
Of course. It's a piece of cake!
When I was in Pyeongyang, I made my dance costumes all by myself.
You know how to make clothes?
A little tadpole like you?
Wow. I can't believe this at all.
Then don't.
I never asked you to believe me.
And that was a long time ago.
Do you still see me as a little tadpole?
You should get your eyes checked out.
You need to wear glasses.
Jang-go, why are you coming from there?
I wanted to check if they moved in well.
Why would you care about them? Grandma already checked on them.
But Jang-go, Hee-Ra seemed to have liked you.
Hey, Jang-go.
Jang-go!
Why don't you like her, huh?
She's amiable and pretty. She studied abroad as well.
She's perfect for you!
How is she perfect for me?
I don't think so. So why did you arrange such a meeting?
Do you think I did that because I had nothing else to do?
If you want to become a successful lawyer, you need sturdy connections.
But we have neither money nor connections.
But later on, Hee-Ra will receive a tremendous inheritance.
If you became the son-in-law of such a house, you won't have to
be seduced by temptations, and you can work as much as you want!
If it's for such a condition, then I really don't want to be with her.
Jang-go, men must meet good women. That's why I did this!
Just meet her one more time.
How can you judge someone after just meeting them once?
Mom.
Do you not like Hee-Ra because of the parking lot incidence?
I heard all about that.
But do you know what she said?
She said it was her fault.
She's cool and doesn't hold any grudges.
Mom, I'm sorry, but no is no.
I don't want to fight with you about this.
I'm going to wash.
Oh, that stubborn fool!
I have two sons, but why are they both not listening to me?
Why doesn't he like her?
-Hey, Lee Jang-soo! -Song Joo-ri!
Song Joo-ri!
Joo-ri, where were you?
Do you know how worried I was?
Why didn't you answer your phone? Did you want to see me go mad?
And who is that man? Huh?
He's the father of my kids.
What?
I decided to get back together with him.
So, Jang-soo, you go your own way.
Why are you talking so much? Let's go.
Joo-ri, are you crazy? You divorced him because he cheats on you, beats you,
and never gives you money! But you want to get back together with this bastard?
You little!
You're dead today!
Stop it!
Are you crazy? Why would you hit my husband?
Are you insane? How can you just beat him?
Who are you to hit him?
Are you okay?
Did you get hurt?
He bit me!
Joo-ri.
Don't appear in front of me ever again!
Go! Hurry up!
Those jerks!
Jang-soo, are you okay? Did you get hurt a lot?
You fool! Why did you fall for her?
Joo-ri, I'm sorry!
I'm sorry.
Lee Jang-soo, why would you cry?
You shouldn't shed tears for such a nasty woman!
Go! Go!
I can't believe you got beaten up. Go!
I'm done making the curtains!
Peek-a-boo!
Is it really all done now?
Stand up and hold this.
Wow! It's pretty!
Grandma, aunt is done making the curtains!
Oh, my! It's beautiful!
Mom, what do you think? Do you like it?
I like it.
It's a very nice curtain.
Grandma, what's that smell?
This smells like burning mung bean pancakes.
Oh, dear!
Is it good?
-Yes. -Yes.
Eat a lot. There's more.
Where are you taking those?
I'm going to give them to the owner's house, and I want to say hi to her as well.
We met the grandmother, but we need to say hi to the other family members as well.
Stay here and eat with Yoo-sung.
I'll go with you.
Me, too.
Okay. Then let's all go and say hi.
How embarrassing.
How can you cry after being dumped by such a nasty woman?
I'm so frustrated!
This is all your fault!
Mom. Aunt. Grandma.
Go and tell Joo-ri that you allow her to be with me.
I can't live without Joo-ri!
Mom! Grandma!
Just die!
Mom! Mom! Mom!
Oh my goodness.
What on earth is going on?
What did her son do so wrong that she's beating him like he's a dog?
Use your words!
Mom!
Grandma, I'm scared.
Okay. This won't do. Let's go home.
Yoo-sung, come here.
Mi-poong, what are you doing? Hurry up and come here!
That owner must have a bad temper.
How can she beat her son like that?
Mi-poong, did we move into the right place? This looks like a strange house.
There must be something we don't know about.
I guess.
But it seems like the owner has many more family members than just the grandmother.
There was one man who called her "mom," so it seems like she has another son.
Let's go inside.
Honey.
There's no point in pretending you're asleep.
It's obvious that you're just pretending to be asleep.
What do you want now?
I'm suspicious about the maid.
When I'm not around, she wears red lipstick and goes into father's room.
That again?
When the maid is old, you say she's suspicious because she's old.
When the maid is young, you say she's suspicious because she's young.
Elder is 88 years old right now.
There's nothing suspicious going on at all.
There are many middle-aged gold diggers lately.
They seduce wealthy old men, get their inheritance
when they get dementia, and then throw them away.
Don't you watch the news?
So what do you want me to do about it?
I'm just saying.
If Elder meets a good woman, I'm going to clap for him.
It would be a great thing if he can live happily
with the woman he loves before he passes away.
You're crazy. For whose happiness?
Do you really mean that?
Yes, I do.
How can you have such foul thoughts?
When father gets married, it's the end for us!
The wrong catch! A pitiable condition!
Don't you know?
Enough with that crap!
Get out of the way!
You're the one who is talking crap right now!
I can allow everything else, but I will not allow father to get re-married!
He better not get re-married.
Hee-dong!
Over here!
Grandma.
Give those to me.
What happened?
I can't stay in the sauna any longer.
I feel so suffocated!
Do you want me to find a nearby motel for you?
Oh, no!
Motels are scary, Hee-dong.
Goodness! I feel like I'm alive now!
Grandma, I'll find a good timing to talk to mom about you.
So you know...?
I know. I know.
When I get caught, I'll get kicked out.
I'll bring you your meals, so be careful when you use the bathroom.
If Hee-Ra finds out, it'd be troublesome.
I know Hee-Ra has a big mouth.
I'll sleep on the floor, so sleep comfortably on the bed.
All right.
Oh, my baby.
I'm glad I carried you on my back and raised you when you were this small.
Grandma, here.
No way.
It's just a similar woman.
How could she be here when she's in North Korea?
(Lawyer Lee Jang-go)
I'm going to go home after I send these at the post office.
Okay, see you at home.
Okay.
Hee-Ra, what are you doing here?
This is my grandfather's building.
I was just passing by.
Hee-Ra?
The girl you met last time is her?
Hello. I'm Jo Hee-Ra.
I'm Jang-go's aunt.
Oh, I see!
Then go ahead and talk! I was just on my way out.
Geum-sil, Hee-Ra came to Jang-go's office just now!
Really?
Yes!
Geum-sil, she looks so pretty and cute!
I told you so!
She must really like Jang-go! She came all the way to his office.
Eavesdrop on them.
Okay! I'm so curious, too!
You didn't ask me out on a second date, so I thought you had rejected me.
But your mother said that you just didn't know how to express yourself very well.
My mother said that?
Yes.
If you ask me to go watch a movie,
I'll still go watch it with you.
I'm sorry.
I think there was a misunderstanding between my mother and me.
I don't have any time or will to be in this kind of relationship.
So you're saying that...
you don't want to go out with me?
Well...
I understand what you mean.
Nam-yi, are you serious?
I was so flabbergasted. Hee-ra's pride must have been really hurt.
What do I do?
Does Jang-go have a girlfriend?
Or else how could he do this?
No way. That can't be.
Okay, Nam-yi.
Oh my goodness.
Kim Mi-poong, get in.
It's fine. I'm almost there.
Just get in.
If you don't get in, I won't go.
What kind of threat is that?
How can I go alone when I saw you walking?
Get in. It's my order.
Fine.
Jang-go must have come home already.
Oh, my. Who is that girl?
Geum-sil, we're in big trouble!
Why? What's wrong?
Geum-sil, I was right! Jang-go has a girlfriend!
What are you talking about? That's not true.
Just like Jang-soo, he's bringing her home to introduce
her because we keep telling him to go on blind dates.
That can't be, Nam-yi!
That doesn't make sense when there's a girl like Hee-Ra around!
You must have made a mistake.
Geum-sil, Jang-go is entering our house right now with a girl!
What did you say?
No! This can't be true!
No way! This can't be!
Jang-go, who is this girl?
I'm asking you! Who is she?
(Blow Breeze)
Leave as soon as possible.
-I don't want to live here either. -(Yeongdong Job Center)
-What did you say? -Kim Mi-poong, don't mind who Jang-go meets.
I hope you meet a good person.
Hey! I don't like you either!
How much did you drink? I saw stars exploding in my head!
Are you saying my head is a rock?
It was you who ran into me!
Where did you go dressed so nicely? Did you meet your secret boyfriend?
That's the most ridiculous thing I ever heard!
When will you buy me black bean noodles?
Name the date.
Then buy it for me right now.