Subtitles by OnDemandKorea
(Episode 7)
Jang-go, who is this young lady?
I'm asking you. Who is she?
Is she your girlfriend?
No. She's the one who moved
into the back house.
She's the one who moved
into the back house?
Did you say you disliked Hee-Ra
because of this young lady?
Mom, what are you talking about?
Geum-sil, I was right, wasn't I?
What are you doing here?
You know her, too?
Yes. She's the young lady from
North Korea who came to our
office because she lost
her security deposit in a scam.
Young lady from North Korea?
Are you from North Korea?
Oh, my.
Mom!
Mi-poong,
what happened?
We met before, haven't we?
How can these people be in our house?
This is ridiculous.
Jang-go, what's going on?
So what you're saying is that
those people who live
in the back house are
really from North Korea?
He said they are. Come on, mom.
Were you even listening?
Long time ago,
the North Korean boy who fought
with Jang-go in Macau
is that woman's son.
Well, when they lived in Macau, you said
they were a wealthy family with nice cars.
How did they come down here
as penniless people?
I'm curious, too.
That's not important right now.
Jang-go, what is your reason
for fooling me and
secretly bringing those
people into our house?
Are you dating that girl?
No, mom.
I didn't mean to fool you. I was going
to tell you at the right time.
I didn't tell you who
they were, but they really
are the family of
my friend's younger sister.
Friend, my foot! Don't say that!
How can you think of bringing those people
into our house? It makes me uncomfortable!
Mom!
It does make us uncomfortable.
They're from North Korea.
We would be lying if we said
we weren't uncomfortable.
Long time ago, they used to arrest people
for just talking to North Koreans.
On top of that, we don't know what kind
of things they were doing in North Korea.
Grandma!
Jang-go, how can you be so rude
to your grandmother?
How dare you raise your voice at her!
Yeong-cheol was my friend in Macau.
We studied in the
same class, exercised together,
and played together.
Seung-hee, I mean Mi-poong, is like a
younger sister who spent those times with us.
But Yeong-cheol and his father were
killed while they were running away.
His mother and Mi-poong came to South Korea
with little Yoo-sung but got conned.
I found out that they were living in
a storage room because they had
nowhere else to go, so I couldn't
just let them live like that.
If our situations had been switched,
Yeong-cheol would have done the same for us.
So grandma, aunt, and mom...
please understand.
How can our situations be switched?
North Koreans come to South Korea.
We don't go to North Korea.
Don't you think so?
Hearing their story,
I do feel bad for them, but...
Goodness! Why does it have
to be our house of all places?
I can't believe Mr. Lee was
Yeong-cheol's friend back then.
You should have told me!
I thought you would
get upset if you found out.
Still...
How can you be so thoughtless?
How can you think of moving in here?
I didn't know this was
Jang-go's house either.
On the day we moved in, when I was
seeing Jang-go off that night, he told me.
At first, I thought it was ridiculous, too...
but we don't have
anywhere else to go, mom.
Still, isn't it better staying here
than as homeless people under that bridge?
Didn't you see that woman
looking down on us earlier?
It would be more comfortable living
under that bridge than living in this house.
Oh my gosh. Honey.
Did you see the way she looked at us?
She was looking down on us!
Oh my god.
She was acting
all high and mighty, so why
did she come to
our house out of all places?
I'll go out.
Come out. I have something to tell you.
I was so shocked that I can't be
calmed down even though I ate medicine.
What is it that you want to say?
Goodness. She still thinks
she's a wealthy madam.
Stop acting so graceful.
No matter how much I try to understand you,
I can't. I feel very offended.
How can you think of fooling me
and moving into my house?
- That's because-
- You didn't know?
Don't even try to lie.
My son's name Lee Jang-go
isn't such a common name.
You should have known right away
when you heard his name.
I really didn't know.
I don't really care
whether you knew or not.
It seems like my son brought
you and your family
here because he felt bad
about your pitiful situation.
When you can, as soon as possible,
look for another house and move out of here.
I don't have the slightest desire
to stay in this house either.
What... What did you say?
What I'm saying is that I wouldn't have
come here if I had known this was your house.
We had met a nice person
and had a place to go,
but your son gave us false hope by
claiming there was a house we could
move into without paying the
security deposit. That's why we came here.
We'll be getting part of
our security deposit back soon.
When we get that money,
we'll move out, so don't worry.
You really mean that, don't you?
I wouldn't live here
even if you begged me to.
This isn't such an amazing house, so I don't
know why you're acting all important.
If you have nothing else to say,
I'll be going in now.
How dare she act like that
when she has nothing!
This is ridiculous.
This is so ridiculous!
How dare she! Oh my goodness!
Goodness!
Mom, I'm sorry.
This wouldn't have happened
if I hadn't been conned.
I was wrong.
No, Mi-poong.
This all happened because
I wasn't competent enough.
Don't cry.
Let's quickly make money
and get out of this house.
Let's hurry up and get out of here.
It's okay. It's okay.
Don't cry. It's okay.
It's my fault, mom.
It's okay, Mi-poong.
It's okay. It's okay.
My Jang-soo. Yes, yes.
Good thinking.
Forget all about Ms. Song
Meet your friends and get
some fresh air. All right?
Keep in mind that if one bus leaves,
another bus will come soon.
Okay.
Hey, take this money.
It's fine, grandma.
You don't have money.
I have a lot of money,
so don't you worry.
He's going to go meet his friend.
Are you going out looking like that?
Shave that beard immediately!
What's so great about being dumped by
a divorcee with kids? My goodness.
Damn it!
Geum-sil, aren't you being too harsh?
If you're going to nag him like that,
then do it after you
give him thirty dollars.
Don't nag him for free!
Pardon?
He went through a big heartbreak.
You won't even comfort
him, and yet, you're putting
salt over his wounds.
Is Jang-go your only son
and Jang-soo just a stranger?
I'm doing this because I'm upset.
He shouldn't be wasting away
his youth over such a ridiculous woman.
He'll get over it.
He's doing this because he's young.
And Jang-soo is a late bloomer.
Who knows? He might be the
one who will feed you later on.
He doesn't have to feed me. I just want
him to be able to make his own living.
That woman...
No matter what I do, I'm going
to make Jang-soo succeed!
You better not mooch off
of him later on!
- Mom.
- Yes?
Sit up.
I have a present for you.
A present?
Ta-da!
Guess what it is.
What is it?
What is this?
Mom, don't you recognize Yeong-cheol?
He's your son, Yeong-cheol.
Yes.
My son.
Yes... my Yeong-cheol...
Where did you get this photo?
I got it from Jang-go. I told him we didn't bring
any photos from North Korea, so he gave it to me.
Oh my goodness.
I can't thank him enough.
Mi-poong.
Mom, Jang-go must be here.
Okay.
You were very surprised yesterday, weren't you?
I should've told you before. I was thoughtless.
I'm sorry.
You don't have to be sorry. I feel like
we put you in a difficult position.
We're sorry.
By the way, since you're Yeong-cheol's friend,
can I speak informally to you?
Of course.
I think your mother had
a misunderstanding.
Anyways, I think it's going to
be difficult for us to live here.
No, it's okay.
I'll talk to my mother again.
No, don't do that.
Just tell her not to worry because we'll leave
here as soon as we get our security deposit back.
I don't know how long it'll take,
but let her know that as long
as we're here, we'll make sure
she won't feel uncomfortable.
By the way, thank you very much
for Yeong-cheol's photo.
Lee Jang-go, why are
you coming from there?
Well...
Come inside.
An apology?
Why would you need to apologize to her?
She was surprised because of me.
I told her I was sorry about that.
You let them live here
without paying the
security deposit.
So why should you apologize?
They should bow down and thank you.
Mom, why are you being so unreasonable?
They were going to
give you the security deposit
later, and I did this
without Mi-poong knowing.
Why do you keep blaming her family?
Why do you keep defending
that North Korean girl?
You're acting so strange.
You're getting their security deposit back.
That should be
the end. But you lied to me
and moved them into our house.
You even drive that wench
around in your own car.
Jang-go, tell me the truth.
About what?
What is your relationship with Mi-poong?
Is there really nothing
going on between you two?
Yes.
Really? Are you sure?
Mom, stop it.
Fine.
If there really is nothing going on between
you two, meet Hee-Ra one more time.
Mom.
We were talking about Mi-poong.
Why are you suddenly bringing Hee-Ra up?
It's because I don't
understand you at all.
And Hee-Ra is such a great catch!
I really like her,
and if you had at least pretended
to date her, I wouldn't be this upset.
Later on, I'll bring a woman
that you'll really like.
If there's really nothing going on
between you and that North
Korean girl, and if you really
don't have a girlfriend,
then meet Hee-Ra one more time.
It's my wish.
Fine, I'll do that.
Really?
You'll really meet her
one more time, right?
Instead, don't make Mi-poong's family
uncomfortable while they're here. Okay?
Huh?
Fine.
All right. I'll do that.
I'm going to work.
This time, you call Hee-Ra first, okay?
You promised me! I believe in you!
Why is she calling me?
She made me sick and now she's giving me
medicine? Is she trying to comfort me?
She doesn't have to do that.
Hello?
Hee-Ra, you must have very upset, huh?
I heard what happened.
But Hee-Ra, I think there's
another misunderstanding
between you two.
What misunderstanding?
When you went to my son's
office that day, he had a
very important case that
made him sensitive and dazed.
That's why he had declined
your invitation to go to the movies.
Really?
My son said he wants to meet you again.
Well, if it was because of work,
I should understand.
Of course!
I love this side of you!
Other girls would have
hesitated because of
their pride, but you coolly
understand right away!
It's nothing.
Then have a good date with my son.
Jang-go will call you.
Really, Ms. Hwang?
You'll trip and fall down!
Do you want to break your leg?
Mom, how do I look?
Do I look okay? Is my make-up okay?
Is my dress too short? Check it!
Who are you meeting that
you're making such a big fuss about it?
Well I... I'll tell you
when I come back.
Later, later. I'm late.
Is she going to meet a man?
Is she going to meet Geum-sil's son?
I should call Geum-sil and ask her!
No.
She's mad because I told her
Hee-Ra doesn't like her son.
What if I call her and she tells me
to pay her money back?
I hope she's not going out
to meet strange guys.
Goodness! She must have gone out!
Oh, no. I heard you can get sick
if you hold back from using the toilet.
Oh my gosh! I have to pee!
Oh my gosh!
What was that sound?
Oh my goodness! I'm dying!
That sounds like my mom's voice.
Maid!
Yes!
Yes, ma'am?
Did you just shout,
"Oh my goodness! I'm dying!"
Did you fall?
No.
Then did you hear someone say
"Oh my goodness?"
No.
Okay. You can go back to work.
It sounded like my mom's voice.
But why did I hear that strange sound?
Mom should have called and complained
about having no money by now.
What's going on?
Did something happen to her?
What if she collapsed?
She's my enemy, not my mom!
I heard that if you break
your bone at my age, you'll die.
Oh my goodness. I almost died.
Oh, dear!
(My daughter Chung-ja)
It's Chung-ja!
What's that sound?
Hee-Ra and Hee-dong went out,
so no one is on the second floor.
How can I hear two bell sounds?
Oh my gosh. Do I have an ear disease?
Why do I keep hearing strange things?
It's me, mom.
Goodness. You called me first
this time. Thank you, Chung-ja.
Were you worried and curious about me?
No, I'm not curious at all!
I was going to call someone else
and pressed your number by mistake.
What?
You little wench!
Are you really going to do this to me?
Good-bye!
Hold on!
Chung-ja...
Yes, I was wrong.
I thought about it, and you had
every reason to be angry.
I really regretted it.
So-
So what?
So Chung-ja, let's meet up and talk.
Mothers and daughters should be able to
understand and forgive
each other for anything.
I'll come to your house
right this instant!
Where do you think you're coming?
Didn't you hear what I said last time?
I told you I was never
going to see you again.
Until you die, don't contact me.
Chung-ja!
Chung-ja! My daughter Chung-ja!
I miss you, Chung-ja!
Don't call my name!
I'm not your daughter!
Horrible wench! Spiteful wench!
I was the one who gave birth to her!
That rude wench!
Oh, dear.
Oh, my sacrum! Oh, my sacrum!
There's nothing wrong with them.
Thank you for your hard work, Mi-poong.
You're welcome. I'll see you next week.
Okay.
By the way, you said you were still
looking for more part-time jobs, right?
Yes!
Are there any?
This company is looking for
a fitting model. Do you want to try it?
Fitting model?
I never did that before.
It's not hard at all.
You just have to wear the
sample clothes and stand still.
It pays well, too,
so you should try it out.
Okay! Thank you!
The steak here is
slightly tough, isn't it?
I think it's fine.
The steak is much better at a French
restaurant I know. Let's go there next time.
Okay.
That's right! There's a famous steak restaurant
nearby! I totally forgot about that!
The beef stock there is amazing.
Each steak costs $300,
but you'll never regret it!
I see...
Just like mom said, when we leave the
house after getting our security deposit,
then things with Jang-go
will come to an end, too.
Kim Mi-poong.
You don't have to be concerned
about who Jang-go dates.
Jang-go, you're tall and
good-looking with a good figure,
so if you paid a little more
attention to your fashion,
you would look like a celebrity.
There are new shoes from Gucci,
and they're so beautiful!
If we don't hurry up, all the sizes
will be gone, so let's finish this and
go there. While we're there, you should
get a new suit and pick out a few ties.
I'll take responsibility
of your fashion from now on.
Later on, we'll change
your car to a cooler one.
If things work out between us,
we can ask my mom to buy the car.
Jang-go, you're like
a blank sheet of paper.
There are many things I want to change
about you, and I think it would be worthwhile.
You know those kind of people
who wear brand names
from head to toe
but don't seem like they do?
But for you, Jang-go,
even if you just change
your shoes, your fashion
would totally be better!
Um, Hee-Ra...
Yes?
I'm sorry, but I think
I have to tell you now.
Tell me what?
My mother really liked you, so I tried
to meet with you one more time,
but I don't think we'll work out.
What?
Why not?
We have different tastes and interests.
What are you interested in?
Work.
It hasn't been long
since I opened up my office,
so I want to focus on my work
until I can get settled in.
You said the same thing last time.
If it's for such a reason,
I can wait until you settled in.
No.
I have no wish to progress
my relationship with you.
I'm sorry.
Did you call and ask to meet me
today just so you can tell me that?
I hope you'll meet a good person,
since you're a charming woman.
Are you joking? Are you playing around?
Hey! You're so annoying!
I don't want to date you either!
(Employment Agency)
You graduated from Kim Il-sung University
with a foreign language degree.
You were an English teacher
in Pyeongyang?
Yes. I speak
a little bit of Chinese, too.
It was a long time ago,
but I lived in England, Macau,
and China for a while, so I know
some foreign ways, too.
Can I become an English tutor?
You want to tutor someone with the
English you learned in North Korea?
Ms. Joo,
you should forget about
your life in North Korea and
think as if you are starting
from the very bottom.
From the very bottom?
How can you still be working
on those? Are you here to play?
Hurry up, will you?
Yes.
Gosh, it's so busy here! How can
they send someone like her here?
Jang-go's phone is off. What happened?
He should have met up with Hee-Ra
earlier today. Is he still with her?
Should I call Hee-Ra?
No, no. They might still be together.
Hello.
Why are you coming from there?
Pardon?
I heard my mother-in-law gave you the
key to the back gate. Didn't you get it?
Oh, my mom has that key.
I'm sorry.
Aunt, what's wrong?
I need to talk with your aunt,
so can you go home first?
Yes, go on.
I'll be there soon.
I'm about to tell you this as someone
older than you, so don't feel too offended.
Okay, please continue.
I don't like the fact that you're hanging
around Jang-go. It concerns me.
Pardon?
Jang-go has a lot of
attachment like his father.
That's why he has to help
pitiful people when he sees them.
He's always been like that
ever since he was little.
So I don't want you to have
a weird misunderstanding here.
I know very well, too.
There's no misunderstanding.
Then I'm glad.
Jang-go went on a blind date
with a girl from a wealthy
family, and things
are going very well for them.
They'll be dating from now on,
and she'll visit our
house sometimes.
What if she finds out about you?
Jang-go will be misunderstood.
You're not wishing
that will happen, are you?
Of course not. How can
I wish for something like that?
Okay. Then I'll believe in your words.
By the way,
from now on, don't use this door.
Make sure you go through the back door.
Okay.
Yoo-sung!
Thank you.
Good-bye!
Lee Jang-go.
How dare he disregard me.
I'm Jo Hee-Ra. Jo Hee-Ra. Got it?
I got it. I said I got it!
Open sesame!
Are you disregarding me?
Joo-ri!
Do you want me to beat you with my head?
Oh shoot.
What the hell is this?
How much did she drink?
Hey, you idiot!
You're supposed to press this!
Did you just call me an idiot?
Yes, you idiot! You're supposed
to press this, not push the door!
What's this?
Where am I?
Yes, you idiot! You're supposed
to press this, not push the door!
Oh my gosh. What did I do?
Why am I lying here with that guy?
I'm so embarrassed!
It seems like both of you woke up.
Oh, my head.
Both of you fainted from shock. There's nothing
especially wrong with either of you.
Are you sure? How can there be
nothing wrong when it hurts so much?
If you want an image examination,
please let the front desk know.
Why was she laughing?
How much on earth did you drink that
caused you to smash my head like this?
What are you going to do about my head?
What did I do?
How dare you play innocent.
Don't you remember?
Or are you pretending not to?
You were the one who did this!
Well... I can't remember very well...
It's the first time
I saw so many stars at once.
I thought there was a firework of stars
exploding in my head! Bang, bang, bang!
What if I have a concussion?
Why does it hurt so much?
Look here.
Stop exaggerating!
Even me, a weak woman, is fine!
Are you saying my head is a rock?
About bumping into your head, did I
even ask you to open the door for me?
You opened the door out of nowhere
and caused me to fall!
Oh my god. Look here.
When something like this happens,
the first thing you should do is apologize.
You should tell me not to worry because
you protected my head from cracking
open on the ground and that I should
not worry about the hospital bills!
You're supposed to say
"I'm sorry and thank you" first!
But you're pretending like you don't
remember and blaming me instead?
You're a very ungrateful woman!
Sheesh! Fine! I got it!
- I'll pay the hospital bills!
- Of course you will!
You're a really pathetic cheapskate!
What? Pathetic? Cheapskate?
Me? Me?
Wow! This woman has no conscience!
Hey, you better wait.
You wait right there! Oh, that little-
What's wrong with my head?
Goodness.
I'm starving!
Is it because I'm only eating food
without anyone knowing about it?
Why am I always hungry?
I can't wake up Hee-dong again.
I'm so hungry!
Ghost!
- It's a ghost!
- Who are you?
It's a ghost!
Elder!
Father! Father!
Oh my goodness!
Who is she?
- Mother!
- Grandma!
Grandma, wake up!
Grandma!
Hee-dong...
a ghost...
He's not a ghost, grandma.
He's my grandfather.
Are you all right?
So you were hiding in
Hee-dong's room all this time?
I'm sorry.
Hee-dong, you should have
told me beforehand. What's all this?
I'm sorry.
I told him not to tell you.
Hee-dong did nothing wrong.
I'm sorry.
I caused you trouble.
I'm too embarrassed to face you.
Ms. Chun, you're welcome in our home.
Why did you stay here so uncomfortably?
You hid from Chung-ja as well.
That's because I made
many mistakes to my daughter.
So I was going to disappear without
a trace once I found a place to live.
I didn't want to trouble you or Dal-ho.
Honestly, I was going to only
stay here for a few days, but then-
Mom.
Still, how could you come in here?
How dare you coax my innocent
Hee-dong and show up here?
No, mom.
It's not like that.
Grandma said she didn't want
- to, but I forced her to come in.
- Jo Hee-dong.
I know your grandmother
better than you do.
Do you think I'll believe your words?
Mom,
if you really didn't
want to trouble anyone,
you shouldn't have
come anywhere near here.
Do you really want to
act like a stray cat?
Chung-ja!
How can you say that?
Would I say that
if things weren't this bad?
The tears I shed because of
you could fill up the Han River!
Chung-ja, that's enough.
It doesn't matter if you had a bad
relationship with her. She's still your parent.
How can you do that to her?
You're a mother yourself.
How can you not be as nice as Hee-dong?
Dal-ho.
The guest room
back there is empty, right?
Yes, it's empty.
Then give that room
to Hee-dong's grandmother.
Yes, I'll do that.
No, Mr. Kim.
I can't trouble you like this.
It's fine, Ms. Chun.
Don't say that.
Chung-ja is like my daughter-in-law.
I was inattentive all this time.
This is all my fault.
Since things turned out this way,
you should comfortably stay here.
Father!
It's late. Go back to bed.
Good night.
I should go back to bed. Good night.
Mother, come this way.
What do you think?
If it's very uncomfortable,
you can switch bedrooms with us.
No, it's great.
Mom.
If you have a conscience,
leave the house at
dawn without anyone
knowing about it! Got it?
All right.
That woman.
Mother, she'll get over it.
Don't worry about it.
No.
If Chung-ja tells me to leave,
I should leave. I don't have a choice.
Mother.
You know she's weak-hearted
even if she speaks like that.
I'll talk to her,
so please stay comfortably.
Okay?
Thank you.
Then good night.
Why would I leave?
There's nowhere else I can go!
It feels great
after the storm passed by!
I feel much better after I got caught.
Goodness. It's so comfortable.
Mom, why did you
come home so late last night?
Where did you go?
Oh, just there and there.
I was trying to look for a job.
You were looking for a job?
What job?
I'll be the one who's working.
I'm a mom, so how can
I let you suffer alone?
And we need to hurry up and work to make
money so that we can leave this house.
I like this house.
We're not moving right now.
We meant that we were going
to move to a better house after
we make a lot of money.
Oh, I see.
Here, Yoo-sung. Eat different foods.
Good boy.
Are you and Hee-Ra really over?
Yes, so stop talking about her.
How can you do that when
I begged you to be with her?
I'm off to work.
Why on earth do you dislike Hee-Ra?
You don't even have a girlfriend,
so how can you flatly reject her?
I just don't like her.
Must I have a reason?
Yes, tell me so that I can understand.
What on earth don't you like about her?
Mom, Hee-Ra wears $2000 shoes.
What? $2000?
Do you know what she talked
about while we ate?
What kind of designer bags she likes,
what clothes and shoes brands she only
wears, what brand is like at what mall,
and what different restaurants are like.
That was all.
Do you think I would be
compatible with such a person?
So what?
What about it? What's so bad about that?
It's not like she steals them.
She has brand-name bags and
expensive shoes because she can
afford them. So what's bad about that?
I want you to succeed,
wear brand-name clothes,
and live a good life in
a wealthy household.
Mom.
Jang-go, don't you have
any ambitions or dreams?
Are you going to end your life in a tiny
office taking on small, pathetic cases?
Mom, I do have ambitions and dreams.
But I don't want to marry a girl I can't
communicate with and mooch off my in-laws.
- What?
- I'm going to achieve my dreams with
my own strength. I have the confidence.
So don't arrange such meetings anymore.
I'll take care of my marriage.
- Bye.
- Jang-go.
Lee Jang-go!
Hey, Jo Hee-Ra! What happened to you
last night? You disappeared out of nowhere!
You drank alone again, didn't you?
Who are you?
Hello?
This is Hee-ra's phone number.
What the heck is this?
Darn it!
Did my phone switch with hers?
Oh, my.
Just like me, you have soft skin.
You're so pretty.
Grandma!
Yes, it's me!
Grandma, when did you come?
Yesterday.
Starting from today, I'm going to
live with you. Are you happy or not?
I'm happy.
Oh my lovely baby.
Hold on.
Why do you have a bruise on your forehead?
Did you bump into something?
Gosh. Last night,
I bumped into a rockhead-
What's wrong with my ringtone?
Is it not my phone?
Hello?
What's wrong with you? No matter how drunk
you are, how can you take my phone instead?
Did you take my phone on purpose?
Bring my phone to me right now!
What? What's wrong with you?
Fine! I got it!
It's good.
- Hold on.
- Okay.
We'll take a few photos.
Okay.
Relax. Be comfortable.
Okay, here we go!
Good.
Very good. Let's take a few more.
Okay, keep it up.
Can you change your position?
Okay.
Very good.
You have the right height and a good figure,
so you're a good fitting model.
Good job, Ms. Kim.
Thank you.
Help us again next time, okay?
Okay! Please call me anytime.
You can change your clothes.
Where's the chief?
She's upstairs.
Oh, my! Oh, no!
What do I do? What do I do?
Mi-poong, I'm sorry.
It's fine.
What do we do?
You didn't leave yet?
I wanted to say good-bye to you.
You could have just left.
I'm glad it wasn't hot coffee.
But you're wearing white. This won't do.
Hold on.
Change into this.
No, I can just wash my clothes at home.
Just wear it. Your clothes
got wet because of me.
And this fit you well earlier.
Just think of it as a bonus
for working hard today. Okay?
Thank you.
Enjoy. See you again.
Bye.
Since when have you been following me?
Come on. I wasn't following you.
I just saw you now.
But where did you go dressed so nicely?
Did you go meet your secret boyfriend?
That's the most ridiculous thing I ever heard of!
If you have nothing else to do,
just go home and sleep.
What?
Why are you laughing?
Was I that funny?
Well, I was just joking, but you took
it so seriously, so it was funny.
What?
It's fun to tease me, isn't it?
I'm going to go now, so laugh
all you want by yourself.
Stupid.
Hey, Kim Mi-poong! When are you going
to buy me black bean noodles?
Black bean noodles?
Come on. You said you were going
to buy black bean noodles.
All you do is say "Thank you."
Was that an empty promise?
An empty promise?
What's that?
Just set the date.
I can buy that measly
black bean noodles anytime you want.
You mean that?
Of course I do.
Black bean noodles is nothing.
Why would I lie about that?
Fine.
Then buy that for me right now.
Right now?
Let's see.
It's delicious.
Is it delicious because this restaurant
made it well or because it's free?
It's delicious.
If it's that delicious, eat a lot.
You should eat, too.
I'll eat a lot, too.
That's it. No more.
You should wipe yourself.
You have black bean sauce on you.
How can you get things on
your face like a baby does?
Do people know you're such a farthing?
Nope.
It was delicious,
but I feel kind of bloated.
Jang-go, what's wrong?
Did you get indigestion
from black bean noodles?
I thought you were eating fast.
It's not that.
I just feel guilty
because you paid for it.
I thought you were talking
about something else.
This won't do.
Since you bought
black bean noodles, tell me
whatever you want to do it.
I'll make it happen.
There's no such thing.
The black bean noodles is stuck
right here and won't go down...
Hurry!
There was something I wanted to do.
What is it?
To be honest, it's been almost
two years since I came to Seoul,
but I haven't been able to look around properly.
So I wanted to go to Seoul Tower.
Seoul Tower?
That's not hard at all.
Let's go.
What? Right now?
Yes, right now.
It's not a hard thing, so why delay it?
Thanks to you, I'll be able to
get some fresh air. Let's go.
I need to stop drinking.
I'll never drink again.
(Please press)
Here is your cell-phone.
Here's yours.
I had important plans today.
What's this?
I'm so annoyed!
Hold on.
What now?
It seems like you don't
have any plans anymore.
How about you have some beer?
Beer?
You didn't do it on purpose.
I was a bit harsh yesterday.
Since you paid for the hospital bills,
I'll buy the drinks.
Geez.
You do have some manners after all.
Cheers to seeing stars together.
Okay, cheers.
Cheers!
X! X!
He's a pathetic mama's boy!
It's a good thing you broke up with him!
Break-up wasn't even called for!
I just feel like I've been used
by that man and his mother.
That's why I feel offended. That's all.
My pride was hurt.
I'm saying it's a good thing!
Your pride doesn't have to be hurt over
a pathetic man who isn't even worth a penny!
At times like this,
my grandma always says this.
"Your ancestors have helped you."
Your ancestors helped you
break up with that man!
That's right! You're right! I think
you're right! Now I feel so much better!
Yes! To your ancestors!
- Cheers!
Thanks to you, I was able to
visit Namsan Seoul Tower today.
Kim Mi-poong has succeeded!
Thank you.
Hey Kim Mi-poong, until when
will you speak formally to me?
You should speak informally
like you used to.
Okay.
I'll try to fix it.
Like this?
Yes, like that.
But Mi-poong, can I ask you something?
What is it?
Go ahead and ask me.
Why did you change
your name to Kim Mi-poong?
My father gave me that new name
so that I can forget
all about my name in North Korea
and live a new life.
Seeds aren't spread by fierce winds
but by gentle breezes.
He wanted me to become
a gentle breeze like that.
That's what my father said.
That's why I really like
my name Kim Mi-poong.
Jang-go, do you still remember
everything that happened in Macau, too?
Of course.
Back then, I had taught you
Michael Jackson's dance, too.
I remember.
When I think about how
a little tadpole like yourself
criticized me for not being
able to dance the moon walk,
I still can't sleep
because I was wronged.
What do you mean you were wronged?
It was the first time I had
seen an awful dancer like you.
How can you not be able to do that?
I can do it.
I'm good at the moon walk now.
Really?
Of course!
When I was in the army,
one of the soldiers was a good dancer,
and I got special lessons from him.
Special lessons?
It seems like you don't believe me.
Want me to show you?
You wait right here.
Watch.
How can you not know how to dance that?
Are you sure you
received special lessons?
I wonder why you can't do this.
Watch me carefully.
You move your foot back like this.
Like this. Like this. Like this.
(Blow Breeze)
Mi-Jung.
Mi-Jung, that wench.
Give me my money!
We did sleep together,
but nothing happened!
I won't let this slide!
- We're not friends anymore!
- What?
I want you to pay me back by
$35,000 by the end of this week.
My motorcycle broke on the street.
Thank you so much.
You really know how
to make a dress shirt?
What's wrong with my heart?
It's acting up again like old times.
Subtitles by OnDemandKorea