Subtitles by OnDemandKorea
How can you not know how to dance that?
I wonder why you can't do this.
Watch me carefully.
Like this. Like this. Like this.
Hey, Kim Mi-poong.
What did you just do to me right now?
What do you mean what did I do?
I didn't do anything.
Didn't you grab and
pull my arm and waist first?
Well, I did that because I thought you
might fall down the stairs.
I tried to save you.
I know.
I was trying not get hurt either.
If you didn't want to get hurt,
you should have just
grabbed my hand.
Why did you have to hug my neck?
Was this a kiss by willful negligence?
What?
What do you mean?
What did I do?
Willful negligence.
You didn't intentionally
plan on kissing me,
but even with such
a highly probability that
it would happen,
you still danced anyways.
I'm right.
You did do that.
Yup.
So are you saying that I kissed you on
purpose but covered it up as an accident?
That's the only way I can
think of it in this situation.
No! That's not true!
That was just an accident!
I'm crushed that
you stole my lips like this.
I'm devastated.
Do you really think
that's what happened?
Acknowledge that this was an accident!
Our lips just bumped into
each other! It wasn't a kiss!
If you don't acknowledge that this
was an accident, you can never leave!
All I did was grab onto you
because I didn't want to fall!
Okay.
It's not like you can return
my stolen kiss to me.
Let's just say that happened.
Why are you talking like that?
Don't just say that!
Acknowledge that this was an accident!
I swear to God that
I wasn't doing willful negligence!
Kim Mi-poong, you were
a player in North Korea, weren't you?
Pyeongyang Player.
It doesn't seem like
you just did this a couple times.
How can you say that to a woman?
Now I see that you're not someone
I should be associated with!
If I associate with you from now on,
I'm not a person but a duck! A duck!
Hey! Mi-poong! Mi-poong!
I'm sorry. It was a joke.
Whatever.
Don't act like you know me anymore.
I'm sorry. Don't be mad.
I won't do that again.
What? Are you crying?
Mi-poong, it was just a joke!
Should we go eat ice cream?
Do you think I'm a baby?
You pumpkin head!
Fine! Okay, okay!
I'm a pumpkin head. I'm a pumpkin head.
So don't be mad anymore.
I'm sorry.
Fine! You can hit me once!
She really hit me?
You're not mad anymore, right?
Right?
That's enough. Stop.
You want me to stop?
There are still many more left.
Someone else is coming,
so stop washing the
grills, and start serving
in the hall tomorrow.
Okay.
But isn't the daily wage fifty dollars?
How can you expect getting all
fifty dollars when you worked like that?
You didn't even do half
of the work the others did.
My restaurant doesn't pay you by the hour
but by the number of grills you washed.
You'll be serving the hall tomorrow,
so make sure you put on some make-up.
Are you feeling better now?
Do you love teasing me that much?
Yes.
If I play a joke and there's
no reaction, it's no fun.
But you react right away, so it's fun.
If you do that again,
you'll be bleeding from both nostrils.
Bleeding from both nostrils?
Goodness.
Isn't it really fascinating?
What is?
You and I separated like that in Macau.
I was in North Korea, and you were
living here in South Korea.
Yet, we looked around
Seoul together today.
The more I think about it,
the more fascinated I am.
I feel like that, too.
You should be in North Korea, but here
we are eating ice cream together.
It's strange but fascinating.
But Mi-poong...
Never mind.
It's nothing.
You're curious about why
we ran away from North Korea, too.
That's what you want
to ask me about, don't you?
Yes.
When I say I'm from North Korea,
the first thing most people ask me
is why I ran away from there.
That must be what they're
most curious about.
They're suspicious that I must
have done something terrible.
Mi-poong, it's okay.
You don't have to tell me.
I'll tell you that story later.
I don't want to spoil this great day
with such a somber story.
Thanks to you,
for the first time, I felt like
I really belonged in Seoul
and became a citizen
of the Republic of Korea.
In heaven, my brother
will be very grateful to you.
Very good.
But...
it seems like your love wound...
is very deep, too.
Yes. It's very deep.
If I scrape my knee,
I can put medicine on it.
But when your heart hurts,
there's no medicine for that.
Love doesn't last forever.
You shouldn’t put your life
on the line for love, too.
Of course I won't!
You can love again,
but you only have one life.
You and I understand
each other pretty well.
To celebrate that, let's drink
one more bottle of beer. Deal?
Deal!
Excuse me!
Hello.
We're starting a couple event where you
have to compete to drink beer the fastest.
If you're interested,
you can participate in it.
What are the prizes?
First place gets twenty
free bottles of beers,
second place gets ten,
and third place gets five.
- Deal?
- Deal.
Where do we have to go?
Who will win first place for the
fastest beer drinking contest?
Are you ready?
Ready, set, go!
First and second couples are the fastest
so far! Which one of them will win?
The second couple is pretty fast!
Can the second couple win first place?
She got up!
She's drinking it! One shot!
They won!
Kim Mi-poong, you were a player
in North Korea, weren't you?
Pyeongyang Player.
How can you say that to a woman?
Now I see that you're not someone
I should be associated with!
If I associate with you from now on,
I'm not a person but a duck! A duck!
What happened to Jang-soo?
One, two. One, two. One, two.
- Mom.
- Yes?
Where did Hee-ra go?
Why? Isn't she in her room?
What?
Did that brat not come home
last night, mom?
Oh, I forgot!
Yesterday she said she was going
to sleep over at Hye-rin's house.
Really?
Of course.
Mom, tell Hee-ra not to
stay out overnight again.
It will become a habit.
Okay.
This little brat.
Oh, my!
She really must not have come home!
Oh my gosh!
She went out dressed so well yesterday!
I should cut off
all her hair or something!
What can I do about this brat?
Hello?
Where are you?
Me?
Where are you? Tell me!
I'm coming. I'm coming right now.
What happened?
Oh my goodness.
Damn it!
Just get on my back.
Where do you live?
- No! No!
- Darn it!
Why are you pushing me?
Hurry up and come out.
- Are you okay?
- Mister, where are we?
What am I supposed to do?
"Shy, shy, shy."
She's freaking heavy.
What was that?
Oh my god. How can
a woman snore like that?
Nothing else happened, right?
There was nothing more, right?
Why can't I remember anything else?
Where did my bag go? My bag.
It's right here.
Let go of me!
Don't you dare scream! You know
what will happen if Hee-dong finds out!
I dare you to scream, you little brat!
So what if he finds out?
I'll just be beaten to death!
Did you do something
you should be beaten to death for?
What did you do?
What do you mean what did I do?
Why do you keep yelling at me like that?
All I did was drink because I was upset,
and when I woke up, I was in a motel!
You slept in a motel?
With who? With who?
Tell me!
I don't know! I said I don't know!
You don't know?
You slept with a guy you don't know?
I did sleep with him,
but nothing happened!
What?
How can you do that to me
after I raised you?
Why are you hitting me?
Why?
Starting from today, you're not my daughter,
so pack your bags and leave!
Why would I leave? Why?
What did I do so wrong?
I told you that nothing happened!
You're ridiculous.
Enough talking.
I don't need a daughter
like you, so get out.
I won't leave. Whose fault is this?
It's all your fault!
What did you say?
Honestly, do you know how upset
I was because of your friend's son?
If I hadn't gone on
that blind date with your
friend's son, I wouldn't have
gotten upset and drank!
Why are you bringing him up right now?
It was all over!
No, it wasn't!
I was going to end it back then, too,
but Ms. Hwang told me to date her son.
She told me that her son is a simpleton
so that I should go see him first!
That's why I did that! But...
What are you talking about?
Tell me everything from the beginning
to the end without leaving anything out!
Tell me everything!
That's why I really
was going to end things,
but Ms. Hwang called me again and
said there was another misunderstanding.
That's why I thought he
was being serious this time,
but when I met him,
he said that wasn't true again!
That's what happened!
They were playing around with me!
Shouldn't your friend not do that for your sake?
How dare they toy
around with my daughter.
How dare they looked down
about me and my family!
I won't let this slide!
She's still lying down?
Just pretend you don't know anything.
I feel bitter like someone stole my money.
How would Geum-sil feel then?
You can't force your kids to
be in a relationship you want.
If you could, there would be
no problems in this world.
I guess so.
Then what was that phoenix dream about?
Was it just a silly dream?
What? What do you mean
by a phoenix dream?
The day before Jang-go went
on his blind date, I had a dream
that a golden phoenix came
right through that front gate.
It was so vivid.
That's why I thought it was
his dream and sold it to
Geum-sil for a hundred dollars.
I feel so bad now.
How can you get a hundred dollars
for a silly dream?
Give her fifty dollars back!
No way! Jang-go is the one
who kicked that phoenix out of his life!
I really don't understand him.
How could he reject the position
as the son-in-law of a wealthy household?
It's such a waste.
Geum-sil has every reason
to be depressed.
Who is that?
Hey! Hwang Geum-sil, open the door!
Who the heck is that?
- Who the heck is calling Geum-sil so rudely?
- Hwang Geum-sil, open the door!
Open the door!
- This is a female gangster!
- Mom, mom, mom!
- Wait.
- I think it's Geum-sil's 100 million dollar friend.
- Open the door!
- What? But why is such a wealthy
woman acting so unrefined?
- I'll break this open!
- So what if she has money?
Mom, what are you going to do?
Just stay. I'll go out.
What are you doing here
yelling in front of my house?
What am I doing here?
You don't know why I'm here?
How can you do this?
Are you even my friend?
You need to tell me the whole story.
If you just talk to
me like that, how can
I understand what you're saying?
I told you that we weren't
meant to be in-laws,
so you should have
just ended it at that.
You secretly met my innocent Hee-ra.
And you said what? That how the
man acts depends on the woman?
Did you or did you not tell
my daughter to seduce your son?
How can you do that to my daughter?
I thought you were talking
about something else.
Is that why you're throwing
a fit right now?
What? "I thought you were
talking about something else?"
Are you freaking serious?
Your daughter seemed
to like my son a lot, so
I told her to ask him out
one more time. Is that so wrong?
Do you think your son
is suitable for my daughter?
What?
You were so desperate to let
my daughter and your son meet.
That's why I allowed them
to eat a meal together.
My goodness. You should know
you're barking up the wrong tree.
I'm speechless.
I'm getting cursed out for
simply letting our kids meet up.
Hey. We need to make things clear here.
Your daughter liked my son,
but he didn't like
her, so they ended.
Let's just leave it at that.
He has nothing,
but he doesn't like my daughter?
He doesn't even have
the right to not like her!
Ma Chung-ja!
What?
What? "He has nothing?"
Then why did you borrow money
from me when I have nothing?
Oh, I see.
Now I know!
I thought I was wrong, but you were
so nice to me about lending me
money because you wanted my daughter
as your daughter-in-law. Right?
I thought you did that
because we were friends.
I don't want to see you ever again!
We're through!
Fine! We're through!
But you should pay back the
money you borrowed from me.
We're not friends anymore,
so you should pay back the
$45,000 you borrowed from me
by the end of this week.
Fine.
I'll pay you back.
I'll pay you back that
measly $45,000 so, Hwang
Geum-sil, let's not ever
see each other again.
Oh my gosh.
My goodness.
My goodness. You told us
that you didn't have a penny
and always complained
about not having any money.
Mom.
What do I do?
My goodness!
But how can I make $45,000
by the end of this week?
I can't make another private loan again.
Private loans are scary.
Hi, it's me, Chung-ja.
Young-soon, can I borrow some money?
Goodness, I don't have any money.
You know that my husband
is in control of it.
- I heard you fought with Geum-sil.
Did you need to pay her back?
- Goodness.
Forget it!
You don't have to lend it to me,
so stop asking me questions!
They're not my friends!
Fine.
That's the only way.
Hello.
Is my father here?
Is he in the office?
He's over there with some guests.
Really? Eat a lot.
Who are those people?
I have to talk to father
about money issues.
What are you doing here?
Oh, I was just passing by.
But who are those people?
They seem like workers.
Elder is going to give his
Yangpyeong orchard to charity,
so he's discussing the taxes
and process for that.
He's going to give the
Yangpyeong orchard to charity?
Are you serious?
Yes. Why?
What do you mean why?
We need to talk.
What is it?
You didn't do anything
when he said he was going
to give the Yangpyeong
orchard to charity?
And why didn't you tell me
such an important thing?
Why do I have to tell you that Elder
is going to give the orchard to charity?
Each square foot of that orchard
costs over two thousand dollars!
It's 3,000 square feet
so it's six million dollars!
You didn't do anything
when the six million dollar
orchard is being given to
someone else we don't know?
It's not being given
to people we don't know.
It's for students
in difficult circumstances.
It'll be given to a scholarship
foundation for those students.
Why couldn't you tell him
to leave that be
and give it to Hee-dong
and Hee-ra later on?
Chung-ja!
Stop barking nonsense like a dog!
Yes, I'm a dog! Bark, bark, bark, bark!
Can't you listen to
my nonsense for once?
Are you crazy?
Stop thinking such stupid things
and just go home and prepare food!
Elder has no appetite lately,
so he can't eat well.
Six...
Six million dollars...
There goes my six million dollars!
Twelve points. Let's see...
Maple leaf.
Why did that have to appear again?
I'm done for.
Oh, I was just bored.
I was trying it out for luck.
Mom, don't turn this
song on in my house!
I'm sick and tired of this song!
Are you scared I'll live
to be a hundred years old?
It hasn't been that
long since I've been living
here, and you're already criticizing me.
Goodness. I have an unlucky life.
What's the point of living like this?
Oh! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Chung-ja, how can
you drink like that? Hey!
Mom, I can't live like this.
I really can't live like this
for another day!
Chung-ja! Hey! Hey! Oh my goodness!
My head.
Why do I still feel nauseated?
I'm dying.
(Fastest beer drinking contest)
Oh, my stomach!
He must have had a hard time
because of me yesterday.
He must have felt disappointed
when he woke up and didn't see me.
Should I text him a "thank you?"
No.
It'd be better if I just call him.
The person you are trying
to reach is unavailable.
His phone is off.
I guess all men aren't wolves after all.
He could have done something
terrible to me if he had wanted to.
He seems like a good guy.
What am I thinking right now? Jo Hee-ra,
get a hold of yourself. No, no, no.
Where did my cell-phone go?
Oh, my! What's wrong with this?
Hello?
Hi, it's me. Where are you right now?
Well... what is it?
The thing is...
I think it will take some time for
your security deposit to come out.
What?
What do you mean?
Don't worry. The money is delayed,
but it will surely be returned to you.
Oh, all right.
Let's talk later.
I'm not in the situation to be
talking on the phone right now.
Why? Did something happen?
My motorcycle broke down in
the middle of the street.
What? Your motorcycle broke down?
Where are you right now?
What's wrong with it?
This won't do. I'll just have
to drag it to the mechanic.
Hold on.
The turn signals are coming on,
so it's not a battery problem.
It worked fine before.
Why is it suddenly not working?
Hold on.
I think this may be the problem.
What is that?
Fuse.
I think there was a wire here somewhere.
This will do.
Okay.
How did you do that?
It works, thanks to you!
I made it so that the engine can turn on.
This is just temporary, so hurry up and
take it to a repair center. Change the fuse
and check if there are any other problems.
Got it? You must do that.
I got it. I understand what you
just said. Do you think I'm a baby?
You're so clumsy.
That's why I'm doing this.
Oh, Jang-go.
What's wrong with your shirt?
When did this get on here?
This seems like a grease stain.
What do we do?
It's fine. Don't worry about it.
It's grease, so it won't
be easy to take off.
Your dress shirt is ruined.
I said it's fine. Hurry up
and go to the repair center.
No, I'll go with you. Lead the way.
No. You should go back to work.
I feel bad for taking up your time.
Jang-go, thank you so much.
I'll buy you yummy
black bean noodles again!
Hey, tell them to thoroughly check it!
Jang-go, thank you!
Will she be okay?
Drink slowly!
If you mix drinks tomorrow,
you'll get a bad headache tomorrow!
Hey, let's stop.
Mom.
I'm going to drink all
of this and then die.
Crazy wench.
How can you say that in front of me?
Mom...
I really can't live in
disgrace like this.
I didn't even tell you half
of how I lived so far.
Goodness, Chung-ja. You don't have to
tell me everything in order for me to know.
Do you think I'm a fool?
Sitting back and waiting
for something to happen is
the most miserable and
pathetic thing you can do.
It seems like it will happen,
but then it doesn't.
That is a very frustrating
thing to deal with!
So why would you just sit back and wait
for something to happen in the first place?
Still, I thought that if
I sincerely tried my best,
I thought I would
get something out of it.
But since that's not happening,
I keep thinking these awful thoughts.
- I keep wondering when that old fart will die!
- Oh my goodness!
Hey! You shouldn't say that!
What if someone hears you?
Father said he won't die
unless there is a union.
Mom, what do I do if there's no union?
Our wish is to have a union.
Our dream is also to have a union.
- "We sincerely want a union."
- Goodness.
- "Let's accomplish a union."
- You must be mad!
- Chung-ja, what's wrong with you?
- "A union that will save the people."
- "A union that will save Ma Chung-ja."
- Chung-ja!
Mom, this is my favorite song to sing.
So you must sing with me
with your utmost sincerity, okay?
"Our wish is to have a union."
"Our dream is to also have a union."
"We sincerely want a union."
"Let's accomplish a union."
"A union that will save the people."
"A union that will save this country."
- "A union that will save Ma Chung-ja."
- Mother.
What's wrong with her? What's all this?
Chung-ja drank quite a lot.
I tried to stop her, but she still...
Chung-ja!
Honey, you're home?
Look here, Jo Dal-ho.
Where is Elder who is
your God and Buddha home?
Did Elder come home, too?
How much did you drink?
Where are you going in this state?
I'm going to see the end of it today.
Let go of me.
I've got nothing to lose!
Father!
- Honey.
- Father.
- Chung-ja! Chung-ja!
- Honey! Honey!
Yeah, go ahead and fight!
How can you live so cheap like this?
She needs to undo the knots and squeeze out
the festering wounds. She has no other choice.
- Honey.
- Father!
What's wrong with you?
Have you gone mad?
Yes, I have!
I'm so mad that I can't
see anything right now.
- So move.
- That's enough!
Why? Are you going to hit me?
You act like you're so kind.
You act like you have no greed.
You act like you're so generous.
Hey, Jo Dal-ho, you're the worst.
Why is it so noisy?
Father!
I'm glad you came out.
I was waiting for you
until my eyes popped out.
Ta-da! And you came out!
What's wrong with Chung-ja?
Did you drink?
I'm sorry, Elder.
Let's go in.
I have something to tell him!
- That's enough!
- Let her be!
Okay.
What did you need to tell me?
Father,
I...
I'm so disappointed in you.
I'm so, so upset.
You give the Yangpyeong orchard worth
six million dollars to others so easily...
but why are you so stingy to us,
who is like your family?
When my father-in-law passed away,
you promised him...
that you would take care of Dal-ho...
like he was your biological son.
But right now...
I'm living in debt.
In debt.
Father,
I'm just your daughter-in-law by label.
I'm living a shabby life right now!
Why are you in debt?
What's so shabby about your life?
- What are you talking about?
- Enough.
You just stay still.
Father, can't you give us some of
your enormous inheritance in advance?
Is it because we're not
your biological family?
If we were, you would have already given
some of it to us and taken care of us.
Is it because we're
your distant relatives?
Please give us a little bit
of your inheritance.
If you give us just a little bit of it,
I'll be able to live in peace.
Father,
it's not like you're going to take
that enormous inheritance with you.
You think of us as strangers.
Right?
Or else you wouldn't
be able to do this to us!
If you had really thought
of us as your family, you
would've given us some
of your inheritance already!
Am I not right?
Chung-ja!
How dare you speak to him like that!
Why?
Did I say something wrong?
Tell me what I said that was wrong.
Tell me, you horrible man!
Jo Dal-ho! You're the worst! You're-
What do we do?
She should have gone easy on him
without crossing the line. Oh my goodness!
- Hello!
- Hi! Good job today! Bye!
It's grease, so it won't
be easy to take off.
Your dress shirt is ruined.
I said it's fine. Hurry up
and go to the repair center.
Jang-go!
Do you still go on the slides?
You should try it, too.
It's really fun.
But why did you call me out this late?
Is there something else
wrong with the motorcycle?
Is there another problem
besides the fuse?
No.
The motorcycle is working well,
thanks to you.
I didn't call you out for that.
I'm grateful to you for many things,
but I was only able to
buy you black bean noodles.
I felt bad for ruining
your dress shirt earlier.
So? Are you going
to make me a dress shirt?
How did you know that?
You were serious?
I was just joking around.
Of course I'm serious.
Do you think I'm lying?
I need to measure you so stand still.
Yeah, right. You really know
how to make a dress shirt?
Goodness. I told you to stand still.
Gosh! Stand still!
How can you be more
disobedient than Yoo-sung?
That's because it's tickles.
I didn't tickle you,
so why do you feel ticklish?
If I get the sizing wrong,
the shirt won't fit.
It's not like you're a baby.
I got your sizes, so I'll be going now.
Hey, Kim Mi-poong!
Wait for me!
How can you go home alone
after you called me out?
Mi-poong! Kim Mi-poong!
I said wait for me!
Lee Jang-soo,
what are you thinking about?
You don't need to think of that woman.
I bought her beer, carried her on my back,
patted her back because she was throwing
up, and slept with her at the motel just
in case something happened to her!
How can she disappear
without saying thank you?
Anyways, women can't be trusted.
They're the icon of betrayer.
Icon of betrayer!
Lee Jang-soo, what are you
mumbling about to yourself?
Gosh! I don't know.
Jang-go, give me your cell-phone.
Hurry!
The person you are trying
to reach is unavailable.
Darn it. Where did my cell-phone go?
What?
Did you lose your cell-phone?
Gosh. I don't know.
Nothing works out for me.
I'm going to wash.
Hey, Jang-go.
Do I look very dirty?
- Yes.
- Okay.
Gosh.
She better not make
an awful dress shirt.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, father.
I can't believe
I was drunk in front of you.
I must have been out of my mind.
I was very wrong.
Please forgive me this once.
All right.
How much is your debt?
Pardon?
Debt?
No!
I don't have any debt, father.
Tell me the truth.
No, I'll take care of it.
How will you take care of it?
Did you throw that fit yesterday
because you could take care of it?
Hurry up and tell me.
How much is your debt?
Yes, well, the thing is...
It's roughly around $30,000...
I don't want you to tell me an estimate!
Tell me honestly how much it is.
The truth is...
in order to cleanly repay all of it...
I need $50,000.
$50,000?
Are you sure it's $50,000?
Yes, father.
All right.
I'll repay that for you,
so make sure something
like this happens again.
Pardon?
Father...
but the thing is...
I swear to God...
that I was first in debt
because I had to send
Hee-ra money for her
living expenses to live abroad.
Then I was buying good things for
my family. That's why I became like this.
I never wasted money on strange things.
Please believe that at least.
Father...
I'm going to work.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry, father.
Honey, I'm really sorry.
So please don't be angry
and talk to father for me.
You'll do that for me, won't you?
Honey!
Welcome!
Did the buttons I ordered come out?
Of course they did. Hold on.
Here you go.
May I sew on the buttons here?
- Of course.
- Thank you.
You really made this?
So, do you like it?
Yes, I do.
I like the color, too.
Did you buy this
and lie that you made it?
No, I really made everything.
Can't you see that
I sewed on the buttons, too?
You were serious.
Then this is a
one-of-a-kind dress shirt.
Yes, that's right!
Awesome.
What are you doing right now?
I need to check if it fits or not.
What are you doing? Turn around.
You don't have to check.
The size should be just right.
What do you take my skills for?
I have to wear it to
check if it fits me or not.
What's wrong with my heart?
It's acting up again on
its own like old times.
Jang-go will be able
to hear my heartbeat.
You were right.
The arms are just right,
and so is the chest.
You can turn around now.
I knew it.
You look amazing!
It's not because you're good
at making clothes.
It's because I look good in any clothes.
What?
I mean, think about it. Would the shirt
look so good if the body didn't?
Fine. You have a great body.
Happy now?
Yes.
But seriously I think it's nicer
than the clothes I buy.
I love it.
I'm glad you love it.
This won't do.
Let's go eat dinner.
You gifted me a handmade dress shirt.
I should buy you dinner.
Dinner?
Yes.
- If you need anymore side dishes, let me know.
- Please give us premium ribs.
All right.
Ms. Joo, clean up over there.
Ma'am, please give us two
more servings of premium ribs.
Okay, please hold on.
- Welcome!
- Ms. Joo, get them two bottles of soju.
- Where?
- Over there.
- Enjoy.
- Ms. Joo, get them more side dishes.
Lady!
- What do I do?
- We're sorry!
Are you okay? We're sorry!
I'm going nuts!
- Forget it!
- I'm sorry.
How annoying!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'll clean it up.
I'm so stunned.
This is the first time
this has happened to me.
No more excuses.
Quit right this instant.
If I continue to work with you,
I'm going to get sick!
It's Mi-jung. Mi-jung, that witch.
Kang Mi-jung, that awful witch.
Hello?
Kang Mi-jung!
You witch! Give me my money back!
Someone save me!
Hey!
What happened?
You crazy bitch!
Who the hell do you think you are?
- I'm sorry!
- You're a psycho!
Webfoot octopus?
Yes, I'll let you taste some
delicious webfoot octopus.
It's a bit spicy, but it's delicious.
My mom and Yoo-sung
likes webfoot octopus, too.
Oh, really?
We can order some for
them and take them home.
Jang-go, why are you
being so nice to me?
It's because I'm Yeong-cheol's sister, right?
Who is it?
Hello?
Yes.
Joo Young-ae is my mom.
What? The police station?
How can she start a fight
in the middle of street?
Please take care of it.
You should just settle
an agreement with her.
Mom!
What happened?
What happened to your face?
Did that woman do something to you?
No.
It's my fault.
She didn't do anything wrong.
Then you really grabbed her hair first?
Why did you do that? Why?
The thing is...
Kang Mi-jung!
I thought she was her!
What are you talking about?
No.
I really saw her! I really saw Mi-jung!
I'm serious, Mi-poong!
I really saw her!
Mi-poong...
I really saw her.
I really did see Kang Mi-jung.
- Hello.
- Are you here for autumn clothes?
- Yes.
Many new clothes are over there.
Mom...
we decided to forget about Kang Mi-jung.
How can I forget that witch?
If it hadn't been for her, we wouldn't
have been living pathetically like this.
She stole our bag full of money,
which is why we're suffering here like this.
Still, how could you grab
someone else's hair like that?
I definitely saw Kang Mi-jung.
She must have been living well
with our money because
she looked Ike she was
some wealthy family's daughter.
I'm serious! I really saw her!
You made a mistake.
You couldn't forget Mi-jung
and keep thinking
about the past.
That's why this happened.
Same goes for today.
If it hadn't been for Jang-go,
you would've gone to prison for assault!
Mi-poong, take a look at this ring.
When your grandmother was alive,
she used to wear this on her finger.
You see this, don't you? You see
the symbol for "Cheon," right?
What does this mean?
Could this Cheon be part
of your grandfather's name?
Mom!
Don't you think there was a reason
why your father gave this
to me before he died?
Seung-hee,
think about it carefully one more time.
Your father told us to go find your grandfather
who lives in South Korea!
Did you really not hear that?
How many times do I have to
tell you that I didn't hear that?
It seemed as if you forgot about it,
but why do you keep doing this?
If I don't find Kang Mi-jung,
I'm going to find your grandfather.
I can't live like this any longer!
Seung-hee, why do we have
to live here like this?
Who are we?
We come from a heroic family that
everyone respected in North Korea!
But those people lower
than dirt disrespect us!
Mom, please stop!
If you were going to be like this,
why did you come here?
Why did you leave our home country?
I didn't want to come here either.
But I believed that there was a reason
why father wanted to leave home.
Are you the only one having a hard time?
I'm having a hard time, too.
Are you the only one being disrespected?
I'm disrespected every single day!
But...
I endure thinking of father.
I think it's self-respect for me to
survive here just like father wanted me to.
But I can't do this anymore either.
If you're going to be like this,
go back home, even if you might
die on your way back there. No!
You're going to die going there anyways,
so let's just die here together!
Seung-hee, no.
- No.
- Let go!
Seung-hee, I was wrong.
Okay, okay. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Just die!
I'm sorry. I was wrong.
Seung-hee, I was wrong.
Calm down, Seung-hee.
I'm sorry, Seung-hee.
I was wrong.
Oh, Elder.
What are you doing here in the darkness?
Are you drinking?
Yes.
I had something to tell you anyways.
Sit down.
Okay.
I'll pour it for you.
Dal-ho.
I'm sorry.
Why are you saying that, Elder?
Chung-ja was right.
All this time,
I said that I think of you as my child,
but I hadn't actually
accept you as my child.
I think I only thought
of you as a nephew.
That's why I'm sorry.
Come on, Elder.
It doesn't matter if
I'm your nephew or son.
I'm just grateful I can live with you.
And the incident with
Chung-ja was my fault.
I'm sorry.
No.
I think I did something wrong
to you, and I feel embarrassed.
That's why...
I wanted to...
officially...
adopt you as my son.
Pardon?
Adopt me as your son?
Adopt...?
Adopt him as a son?
(Blow Breeze)
Mi-jung stole that bag full of
money that my father left for us.
Is he really the second son
of Daelhyong Group?
It worked effectively!
I wouldn't lose to
a few glasses of soju!
Is that true? Are you serious?
Subtitles by OnDemandKorea