Subtitles by OnDemandKorea
- (Episode 9)
- That's why...
I was thinking of...
officially...
adopting you as my son.
Pardon? Adopt me as your son?
Adopt...?
Me?
Yes.
Adopt him as a son?
Does this mean he'll officially
put Dal-ho as his son
on the family registry?
Oh my goodness!
Elder...
Why are you suddenly saying this?
It may seem like the law and
family registry don't mean much...
but since our relationship right now
is a distant uncle and nephew...
I think I'm only treating you
as a nephew.
That's right! That's the reason!
Still... I never considered this before.
Come on! Why are you questioning this?
You just have to say, "Yes. All right."
Oh my gosh! He's so frustrating!
I understand.
I know this isn't something
you can answer right away.
Still...
I wish you would understand...
this old man's wish to
make a child before he dies.
All right.
I'll think about it.
Think about it carefully.
- All right?
- Yes, sir.
Did you hear that, mom? Father is
going to adopt Dal-ho as his son!
I heard it, of course!
You did well by throwing a drunken fit!
You got a fantastic
result from doing that!
If Dal-ho is officially
put on the family
registry, we won't have
anymore worries, mom!
Even if father gets dementia and
decides to give all his money to charity,
we can go to court
and get all of it back!
Now that you're really becoming
his daughter-in-law, be nicer to him!
You must really be nice to him
now instead of just playing pretend!
Okay, mom!
I'm really going to be good
to him from now on.
I was so sick and tired of pretending
to be nice to him all this time!
Chung-ja!
But...
what if Dal-ho stays mad at me?
He doesn't even want to see my face
because of all the trouble I caused with money.
Be obedient to him until
he isn't angry anymore.
You were flattering Mr. Kim all
this time. Can't you even do that much?
All right.
All right!
You witch! Give me my money back!
If I can't find Kang Mi-jung,
I'm going to find your grandfather.
I can't live like this any longer!
If you're going to be
like this, go back home,
even if you might die
on your way back there.
No!
You're going to die going there anyways,
so let's just die here together!
Seung-hee, no...
What are you talking about?
I thought she was Kang Mi-jung.
I saw Kang Mi-jung!
I really did, Mi-poong!
I really saw her!
It's me.
Hi, Jang-go.
How about your mother? Is she okay?
She's fine.
Thank you for today.
I'm always troubling you.
I write them all down, but I don't know
when I'll be able to pay you back.
Did you drink?
Why are you being so soft?
Ma'am, get me another bottle of soju.
What's that noise?
- Give me some eel, too.
- All right.
You're not home?
What? You're where?
Your mother was looking
for a woman named Kang
Mi-jung at the police station earlier.
Who is that?
Who is she?
If you don't want to tell me now,
you can tell me later.
She was a kkotjebi.
A poor kkotjebi.
Kkotjebi?
(Kkotjebi: Homeless kids
who go around looking for food)
- What's that?
- A kkotjebi.
Why are you glaring at me?
Is it the first time
you see someone eat?
If you don't want to die, piss off!
Ms. Joo.
Ms. Joo, it's me, Mi-jung.
Kang Mi-jung.
How did you come here?
What about your mother?
My mother starved to death.
Kang Mi-jung risked her life to
come find us all the way in Macau.
She must have starved for days.
It was the first time I had seen someone
stuff their mouth with so much food.
I wondered how starving
she must be to do that.
I had felt really bad for her.
We had lived together
in Pyeongyang, too.
Not even one year later, she had
stolen our money and ran away.
We forgot all about her and lived on.
I don't know what kind
of twisted fate we have...
but she came to us the
night before we escaped.
(Pyeongyang)
Dae-hoon, what about Yeong-cheol?
We're going to meet him halfway.
Let's hurry up.
Yeong-cheol will be waiting for us.
Ms. Joo, take me with you.
Take you where?
We'll be back, so stay here.
Do you think I'm stupid?
You think I don't know that
you're escaping right now?
What do you mean escaping?
What nonsense are you sprouting?
You're a crazy wench!
Crazy wench?
Did you just call me a crazy wench?
Fine. How about we ask everyone
who the real crazy one is around here?
Everyone! Listen to me!
Die!
Dae-hoon, you can't do this!
Dae-hoon! Dae-hoon!
Kill me.
Kill me!
It's the same thing as
starving to death anyways!
Kill me!
Go ahead and kill me!
Please!
Please take me with you!
Please! Please! Please take me with you!
- What's wrong with you?
- Take me with you!
That's why...
we took Mi-jung with us...
on that risky journey to escape.
What's that?
- Get down!
- Don't move!
If you move, we'll shoot!
Yeong-cheol! Yeong-cheol!
After my father and brother died
like that at Amnok River,
we didn't even have the strength to
hate Mi-jung for running away first.
(China Dandong: a city nearby
the border of the Amnok River)
We met Mi-jung again at the place
where we were suppose to meet our broker.
My mom and I had relied on Mi-jung
who had kindly taken care of us.
She had said that we would meet our broker
and live in South Korea like a family.
On the dawn of the day
we were supposed to meet our
broker who was going
to take us to South Korea...
The bag full of money that
my father had left us...
Mi-jung stole that money that
we were supposed to give our broker.
She's an ungrateful brat that
is worse than beasts!
Then how did you come here
from China without any money?
How did we survive?
How did we survive and
end up coming here?
I can't...
tell you that...
until I die.
Not until I die...
- Thank you! Come back next time!
- Good-bye.
Ever since you came to our store as
a manager, the sales has gone up a lot.
Really?
Even if rude customers come,
you still treat them kindly.
Thank you.
I'll take care of things here,
so go home first.
Okay. Then I'll see you tomorrow.
All right.
- Then I'll go home first.
- Bye. See you tomorrow.
Bye.
Is that man really the second son of
Daelhyeong Group? Are you sure?
Of course.
If things work out, I'll pay you more.
Okay. Good luck, Shin-ae.
Oh my gosh!
Are you okay?
Oh, no.
I'm sorry. My heels must have
been too high, so I tripped.
What do I do?
I'm fine.
You didn't do it on purpose.
If it's all right with you, I would like to
fill up your wine glass that I emptied.
Honey.
Hey. You're here.
I'm fine. My girlfriend is here.
Oh, all right.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
Oh, I wasn't doing that on purpose...
I was trying to get out of your way.
Damn it.
What's all this?
They're taking all of my money.
You can't get blood from a stone.
Where were you?
Were you in father's room?
No words can justify my actions.
You wouldn't be this angry at me
if I had confessed to you earlier.
Like I told father before, I swear
I didn't use that money for no good.
You believe me, don't you?
Turn the lights off.
And I'll never drink
and throw a fit again.
I promise.
But what did father say?
What did you two talk about for so long?
I said turn the lights off!
Okay, honey.
Are you okay?
Of course! I'm perfectly fine!
This won't do. Hold onto me.
I'm fine.
Do I look drunk to you?
I'm not the type of woman to lose
to a few glasses of soju!
Yeah.
Who could overcome your stubbornness?
If you fall, you'll scrape
your knee, not mine.
Oh, my. Isn't that Jang-go?
But why does he keep hanging out
with that North Korean girl?
Did they drink together?
You just came home?
You're late.
We need to talk.
About what?
Why do you keep hanging out with her?
What are you going to do
if your mom finds out?
What do you mean?
She had a bad day, so I drank with her.
So why would you drink with her?
What does her having
a bad day have to do with you?
What's so bad about neighbors
having a drink together?
Neighbors, my foot.
What if she starts sticking around you?
Aunt, how can you say that?
You should be glad I was the one
who saw you guys. If it was
your mom, she would've kicked
them out right away. You know?
What are you two doing out here?
Jang-go, why are you outside?
I was just getting some fresh air.
Give me that. I'll throw it away.
What's wrong?
Did something happen at work?
No, of course not.
Geum-sil...
Never mind. It's nothing.
Why did she stop talking?
That was weird.
What's this? It's the jackpot!
It's not green vegetable juice today.
Yeah. I mixed wood-cultivated
ginseng with honey.
It's for my father-in-law.
You just made one glass?
Can't you make one more glass for me?
Come on, mom. Just wait a little bit.
I'll get you real ginseng.
Happy?
Geez. Wood-cultivated ginseng
doesn't cost much anyways.
It's delicious.
Drink this, father.
It's wood-cultivated ginseng juice.
I put enough honey in it,
so it should be easy to drink.
Thank you.
Sit here.
Yes, father.
It's $60,000.
Pay back your debt with this.
Father...
Chung-ja,
make sure something like
this never happens again.
All right?
Yes.
This will never happen again.
Thank you, father.
I'm sorry, father.
Here. This is the $45,000
I borrowed from you.
Thanks for paying back without
dragging this out any longer.
You didn't get another
private loan, did you?
You must think we're on the same level
just because I didn't have enough living
expenses for the time being and had to
borrow a small sum of money from you.
Geum-sil, you're going
to have a difficult
time living in this world
without much tact.
Level, my foot.
Is that the brand name of an underwear
being sold at Dongdaemun?
You can't say that when you're going
around borrowing small sums of money.
It's the correct amount.
I wasn't going to say this,
but Geum-sil,
you're barking up the wrong tree.
You must be trying to do something
with your son's title as a lawyer,
but the world is overflowing
with lawyers lately.
You better not pull
this kind of stunt again.
It's my last warning as your friend.
Then let me give you
one last warning as a friend.
You must be acting like this
because of your Elder's inheritance.
That isn't the inheritance
you worked hard to
make and it's not from
your parents either.
It's the inheritance from your distant relative.
Aren't you being too stubborn?
You never know what will happen.
Your Elder's blood relatives
could pop out of nowhere.
Or your Elder can give all of his inheritance
away to charity before he dies.
So don't count your chickens
before they hatch.
You'll get disappointed.
Thanks for the warning, but you don't
have to worry about such a thing.
My husband is going to
become Elder's adoptive son.
Adoptive son?
We're not just relatives anymore.
We're going to be a parent and children.
No one will say anything
if we get Elder's inheritance now.
Right?
Geum-sil, I'll live according
to my standards now,
so you should live according
to your standards, too.
We don't have any more reason
to see each other now, right?
Oh my goodness! Oh, no! What do I do?
You little brat! Who told you that
you could do something like this here?
Yoo-sung.
What's wrong?
Why are you yelling at him?
Can't you see this?
What are you going to do about this?
This bean paste has
been stored for years now.
Yoo-sung, did you do that?
How can he come around here
and do something like this when you
guys are living here without
even paying the security deposit?
What are you going to do about this?
Don't you people have any
conscience? What are you going
to do about my bean paste?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
If you're careful with the broken pieces,
I don't think you have to throw it all away.
- I'm sorry. I'll clean it up right away.
- Forget it!
I don't even want to see you
right now. Take that kid
and get out of here.
Get out of here this instant!
I'm sorry.
What do I do about
this bean paste? Oh my god.
Will we still be able to eat
if I take the broken parts out?
I'm so upset!
Go inside.
Who told you to play ball in the owner's yard?
Huh? Who told you that you can do that?
Answer me!
Who told you that you can do that?
I'm sorry, grandma.
I'll never do that again, grandma.
Please forgive me, grandma.
I don't like you. I don't like you!
I hate you!
Go!
Yoo-sung...
It's okay, Yoo-sung.
No. No, Yoo-sung. It's all my fault.
It's all my fault, Yoo-sung.
Yoo-sung, it's okay.
Yoo-sung.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, Yoo-sung.
I was thinking of officially
adopting you as my son.
Father,
tell me what I'm supposed to do.
So have you thought
about what I told you?
Yes.
The thing is...
Talk comfortably.
There's nothing
we can't tell each other.
Then I'll tell you my honest thoughts.
All right.
I'm willing to do anything you want-
Deok-cheon! Deok-cheon!
- Deok-cheon, are you here?
- What is it?
- Deok-cheon!
- He's over there.
Oh! Deok-cheon!
Oh, Kyung-sik.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Have a seat.
So you were here.
What is it?
Look, Deok-cheon.
Don't get surprised
after you hear what I tell you.
You went to meet your younger cousin
in China. What's all the fuss about suddenly?
Do you remember Kyung-sook
who used to live in our village?
Ms. Soon-cheol's daughter Jo Kyung-sook?
Yes, I do.
About twenty years ago, my younger cousin
coincidentally ran into Kyung-sook.
Kyung-sook said she saw your wife
in Gaeseong in the summer you escaped.
What are you talking about?
As soon as I had escaped,
my family were assassinated
by soldiers during
the Third Battle of Seoul.
Does it make sense that she saw
my dead wife a few months after that?
He's right, sir.
We heard that there were
no survivors in both our families.
Yes, but your wife's brother
had only taken your wife away.
She had cried saying that she was the
only one who had a narrow escape from death.
Kyung-sik, are you telling the truth?
Are you serious?
That's not all.
Back then, your wife...
had been obviously pregnant.
Preg...
Pregnant?
Kyung-sik!
Is that true?
Elder.
If my younger cousin
is speaking the truth,
then your wife and
your child will both be alive.
Yes...
Soon-ok!
- Deok-cheon!
- Elder! Elder! Elder!
Elder! Elder!
Elder, are you all right?
I'm fine.
Dal-ho.
This isn't the time
for me to be like this.
He said my family had died.
I need to find that broker Mr. Kim.
Dal-ho, my wife could be alive.
I must find her.
No matter what, I must find her.
Of course!
You must find her.
You must find her no matter what.
I'll find her for you, Elder.
Dal-ho, thank you.
I told you that I was going
to adopt you as my son...
I can't do this again...
Why are you saying that?
If your family is alive,
you must find them first.
Elder,
I'll make sure to find them for you.
And if...
if you can't find them...
I'll become your son then.
Thank you.
Goodness.
We ate so many delicious foods
and went shopping, too.
Now we're getting a foot massage, too.
I feel a lot better now.
But mom, if Dal-ho ends up
on my father-in-law's family
registry, then will he have
to change his last name to Kim?
Why would you ask such
an obvious question?
Then he's becoming a Kim?
- Yes.
- He'll be Kim Dal-ho instead of Jo Dal-ho?
Oh my goodness! That's so strange!
Then our kids will become
Kim Hee-dong and Kim Hee-ra?
That's so funny and strange!
My goodness!
They'll still have to bear
with it even though it's strange.
His last name Kim is the stamp
that will get them the inheritance.
But still... Kim Dal-ho? Oh my goodness!
It's so funny, mom!
Mr. Jo.
Your story is great,
but you're lacking romance.
Isn't it better to simply go with this rather
than ruin it with the wrong romance?
That's what you think. There's no business
without romance these days.
I'm going crazy.
Mr. Jo, try dating.
Study women.
I'm surrounded by women.
Your grandma? Mom? Younger sister?
Be with women you want
to sleep with, not women
you eat with.
That's how business will do well.
Come on, sir.
Got it!
Darn it. I have no luck nowadays.
It's because I haven't
been practicing lately.
I need to make more of an effort.
I forgot about that.
Grandma!
Jang-soo, I'm glad you're here!
Play Go-Stop with me!
Sorry, grandma.
I'll definitely give you a lesson
in Go-Stop next time.
- What?
- I'll use your phone for a few days!
- Hey! Bring that back here!
- Thanks!
Did you lose yours again?
That little punk!
The person you are trying
to reach is unavailable.
Damn it. Where the heck is my phone?
It has to be that woman.
But she didn't seem like the
kind of woman to steal cell-phones.
Damn it! Where the
heck did I lose it then?
Hey, Jo Hee-ra. If you cancel on us again
today, you're out of our group. So hurry up!
Whatever.
What's up with him?
Why isn't he calling me?
I mean, we spent the night together.
Shouldn't he at least text me
to see if I got home okay?
Geez.
Where is my lipstick?
Where did it go?
Oh, it's over there.
It's right here.
What's this?
Why is this here?
Why do I have another cell-phone here?
Is this his?
But why is it in my bag?
My bag.
It's here!
Oh my god.
What do I do? What do I do?
To the person who has
my phone: please contact me.
What do I do?
Hello?
Now you're picking up?
Is it you?
Yes.
You're right. It's me.
Wow! Why would you take my phone? Why?
Is it your hobby to make me mad?
No!
It's nothing like that!
I just found your phone in my bag!
I'm telling the truth!
Whatever. Bring my phone
to me right now!
I charged your battery all the way.
I'm telling this to you again,
but I really didn't take it on purpose.
Then? Did you take it
because you were bored?
I really didn't take it on purpose
or because I was bored.
Look at this!
This happened because
our cell-phones look alike!
Think about it from
a woman's perspective.
When I woke up, I was in
a strange motel with you.
Do you know how surprised
and flustered I was?
I had no idea that your phone
would be asleep in my bag!
I guess that's possible.
All right. All right.
Anyways, it was
very uncomfortable for you
because you didn't have
your cell-phone, right?
What do you think?
Then I'll buy you beer
as a means of apology.
You don't have to buy it.
We still have our victory coupon,
so let's use this chance to drink together.
You still have the victory coupon?
Of course! It was hard
for us to win this.
Excuse me!
Good job today. I'll see you tomorrow.
Kim Mi-poong, you did
a good job today, too.
This is the company
that I did that modeling for.
(We're looking for
a new face for Zishen.)
(Zishen Symbol Contest)
What's this?
If you win the contest,
the prize is $10,000?
They'll even give you a chance
to work for the company?
Hi, mom.
I just finished up.
What?
Yoo-sung broke the owner's crock?
Yoo-sung.
What's wrong?
Why are you yelling at him?
Can't you see this?
This bean paste has
been stored for years now.
How can he come around here and
do something like this when you
guys are living here without
even paying the security deposit?
Are you from North Korea?
Oh my goodness.
My son seems to have
brought you to our house
because he felt pitiful
for your situation.
But look for another house as soon
as possible and move out of here.
Yes.
I can't stay like this for the sakes
of Yoo-sung and Mi-poong.
If we want to be respected
around here, we need money.
I will make money through
whatever means I have to.
Yes. Just watch.
I will survive.
Were you very sad because
your grandma scolded you?
Yes.
But Yoo-sung, your grandma didn't
scold you because she hates you.
Your grandma loves you so much.
I know that. I'm not stupid.
Of course not, my smarty-pants.
But next time-
I know.
I'll never play ball in
the owner's yard again.
Okay.
Yoo-sung, should I read you a story?
Yes!
This again?
Is this story that fun?
Yes, the owl family
is very nice. I like them.
All right. I'll read you this story,
so close your eyes.
"It's all right.
Since the deers can't move,
we'll have to borrow strength
from the owls."
"What? How can we help you?"
"You guys have bright night vision
and strong wings,
so you guys can deliver
the presents for me.
Please deliver these presents to the
children of the woods before morning comes."
Yes. That's it!
What, aunt?
Thanks to you, I have
a great idea for the logo contest!
You're so lovable, Yoo-sung!
What happened? Jo Hee-ra,
you're out of your mind!
Why did this happen again?
How could this happen
not once but twice?
This is ridiculous!
I'm saved.
Yes!
Jo Hee-ra.
What's up with you?
Where were you last night?
Why are you coming home now?
What happened was...
At my friend's house...
Mom! Father!
Okay! Okay! I'll tell you everything!
Hee-dong, please! I'm begging you!
Hee-dong, I'm sorry,
so please don't do this!
So...
you went to the motel with the
same guy twice after getting drunk...
but nothing happened?
Do you think that makes sense?
Well...
to be exact...
I didn't go to a motel.
When I woke up, I was in a motel.
You little...
My fist is crying...
Hey, Jo Hee-ra.
Are you insane?
How can you drink so much when you don't
even know what kind of guy he is?
What if he was a strange guy?
He's not.
I drank with him twice
and shared a lot of conversations
with him. Wouldn't I
at least know that much?
I really don't know what to say.
How can you go to the motel with
the same guy you don't know twice?
I didn't go to a motel!
When I woke up I was in a motel!
That's the same damn thing!
Are you kidding me?
But I'm asking you this
because I'm really, really curious.
Am I really not charming as a woman?
Why are you mentioning that right now?
That guy is strange!
Just like you said, does it make
sense that nothing happened?
We went to the motel twice,
so how could he treat me as if I'm a rock?
I mean, how can he just leave me alone?
- Hey.
- You're crazy.
You haven't come to your senses yet.
Since you didn't lie and told me the
truth today, I'll hold it in and let it slide.
But watch what happens
if you get caught staying out again.
As your brother, I will break your legs.
I'm warning you.
Oh my god.
Gosh. Is that guy still unable
to forget his ex-girlfriend?
Or maybe...
That boy is a eunuch.
No way.
He's a eunuch.
Grandma, how can you say that
about someone else's precious grandson?
I'm not making up anything.
Gosh.
Hey.
A man and a woman spent the night in
one room together, not once but twice.
But nothing happened.
Come on. Do you think that makes sense?
It doesn't.
- Hey.
- Why did he do that?
I don't know who
this friend of yours is,
but he definitely doesn't
know how to be a man.
In other words, he's a eunuch!
He's not a eunuch, grandma!
I swear he's the manliest of men!
Really?
Yes.
Then that boy was
trying to protect that girl.
In other words, he...
Hey.
Your friend must really like her.
No way.
You're right, but I don't even
think such men exist anymore.
Except for you, Jang-soo. Right?
- Right?
- Sure...
You're right.
Hi, it's me.
What are you doing?
Are you done with your work?
If you're not busy today,
buy me black bean noodles.
Black bean noodles?
Why do you keep asking me
for black bean noodles?
You can't afford it?
That's not it.
I don't know why, but black bean
noodles taste best when you buy it.
If I buy it alone,
it doesn't taste that good.
Don't lie. All black bean noodles
taste the same. There's no such thing.
What? So you won't buy it for me?
When I fixed your motorcycle, what did
you say to me? Did you or did you
not say you would buy black bean
noodles? Did you already forget?
I remember. I said I would buy it.
But I'll buy it next time.
I'm very busy today.
Really?
You're not lying because you
don't want to buy it?
I'm not lying! I'm busy because
I'm preparing for the logo contest.
Logo contest?
Do it here?
Yes.
You'll need internet in order to
research ideas and sketch them out.
That's true, but...
My aunt left work early,
and I need to go out to meet a client.
So go ahead and focus here.
Thank you, Jang-go.
Double the size of black bean noodles.
Okay.
But you're going to make
an owl the logo of a fashion
company. How did you
come up with such an idea?
While reading a story for Yoo-sung.
What do you think?
Do you think it's a good idea?
I'm not sure.
I think the idea is good.
In the west, owls symbolize Athena,
the goddess of wisdom.
In the east, they symbolize
wealth and fame.
First, I think it would be
best for you to create a
simple and approachable design
that anyone could like.
Hearing you talk, owls go back
and forth in my mind. I'll try my best!
What if you really win the
contest because of me?
Then double the size of
black bean noodles isn't enough.
- You need to buy sweet and sour pork, too.
- Okay.
If I win, I'll make sure you can never say
the words "black bean noodles" ever again.
You know how to use the
computer and printer, right?
I'll come back here after my meeting,
so let's eat dinner together. Do your best!
Good luck!
Where are you going?
To get a date.
A date?
Oh!
You're going to
get Dal-ho's adoption date?
You're so tactful!
It's an important date when
a parent and a child meets.
We need to get a good date for that.
You're right!
Let me come with you!
Hurry up!
His last name won't change.
It won't change?
It's going to be changed soon.
Don't be like that and
just tell us the good date.
How can I when it won't change?
It needs to change for me to get a date.
Goodness.
Why do you keep talking
about something else?
He's going to change
his last name from Jo to Kim.
So just tell us the good date
to change his last name.
How can it change when
something is stuck on you?
You can't change
family relationships so easily!
Why? Is there a problem?
What's stuck on us? A ghost?
Forget it. Let's go.
No. What is it?
- Let's go! Come out!
- Why?
Goodness!
You'll be wasting a lot of your time!
Hello!
Hello.
Have you been well?
Yes, thanks to you.
We troubled you but didn't
get to thank you properly.
This isn't much. It's very small.
These are socks for you and Mr. Kim.
It's my gratefulness.
Oh, you didn't have to.
Thank you very much for last time.
You're welcome.
I'll be sure to give this to Elder.
Okay.
Go on in. You should have
some noodles while you're here.
No, it's okay.
Wait.
It seems like you have
something to tell me.
Well...
is there a job I can do here?
A job?
Yes.
Yes, actually, we were
trying to hire someone!
Really?
Of course! Look here.
(Hiring worker)
Oh!
- Enjoy.
- You must be new.
Yes. Enjoy.
Noodles for table nine is out.
Okay.
Dal-ho, what happened?
Did you find the broker Mr. Kim?
I couldn't find him
with his old phone number,
so I asked for help from a new
detective agency, so they'll find him soon.
Please wait a little bit longer.
All right.
No.
Mr. Kim is a con-artist.
He's a con-artist who took my money
and lied that my family had died.
Dal-ho, think about it.
If Soon-ok hadn't died back then,
she would still be alive.
Then...
Then my child...
I must find Soon-ok.
I have to find her! There's no time!
(Blow Breeze)
Why did you just leave me alone?
Because I wanted
to protect you! I like you!
You're similar to my webtoon female character.
Can you be my model?
I don't meet men who have no money.
You should have said no.
How can you be so thoughtless?
Do you have feelings for Jang-go?
Lee Jang-go! Is she your girlfriend?
She's like my little sister.
I'm Bang Sung-sil.
Do you still see me as the little tadpole
who went to school with you in Macau?
I need to stop liking Jang-go
while he doesn't realize I like him.
Subtitles by OnDemandKorea