(Episode 10)
I told you to come home early, didn't I?
I left the meal here since it's too late.
Don't forget to take your medication.
This way.
Who is he?
Isn't he Ahn Dan Tae?
Who does he think he is?
How dare he?
Hey! Get up right now!
Hello, I'll be working as the chairman's secretary from today.
I'm the bright and cheerful Ahn Dan Tae.
What? Secretary?
(A week ago)
Dad.
I know I can't be forgiven.
But it's not me...
who kidnapped you.
I brought you home from the person who tried to kill you.
Then...
who kidnapped me?
Why on earth would he do that?
Dad.
Who am I?
I'll tell you everything when we meet.
I'll tell you the truth.
I'm sorry, Dad.
I suspected you.
I'm sorry. I know it's too late.
I'm so sorry.
After I tell you everything,
I'll pay for what I did wrong.
Okay, Dad.
Blue Sky Arboretum.
You mean that's where Ahn Soo Yong works at?
Yes.
Well, Soo Yong tends to keep things to himself.
I only recently found out about him.
I see. Thank you.
It's nothing. By the way, Staff Sergeant Yeom.
Now that you are...
the executive director of Star Group,
it must be inappropriate to call you Staff Sergeant Yeom, right?
What are you talking about?
It's absolutely fine.
By the way, why are you looking for Soo Yong?
Oh, that.
I owe him a favour from a long time ago.
I just want to repay his kindness.
Oh, my.
Long time no see, Soo Yong.
Staff Sergeant Yeom.
How did you...
I came here to see you. Aren't you happy to see me?
I'm getting upset.
I just wasn't expecting you, that's all.
By the way,
what brings you here?
I have something to discuss with you.
Why don't we sit down first?
If you're here to...
talk about that day,
you don't need to worry about it.
I didn't tell anyone.
I noticed that your son, Dan Tae,
became a lawyer.
Have you...
met Dan Tae?
(Way to Blue Sky Arboretum)
I was always on the run due to my debt.
So I haven't talked...
to Dan Tae for over 10 years.
Is that so?
Whatever you're worrying about won't happen.
How long have you worked here?
The air is so fresh here.
I only recently started working here.
(Dan Tae)
You said you haven't talked to him for 10 years.
But he's coincidentally calling you now.
What were you trying to tell him by lying to me?
There's no such thing.
Give it to me.
Soo Yong!
What are you hiding from me?
I'm not hiding anything!
How much did you tell Dan Tae?
How much does he know?
I said, there's no such thing!
- I didn't...
- Tell me!
You little...
Soo Yong!
Dad, what's wrong?
Dad!
Dad! Wake up!
Dad.
What happened? Wake up.
Star Group?
He had a huge impact to his head.
He's unconscious due to a brain haemorrhage.
But was there an assault?
He has some scratches on his neck as well as bruises.
He'll still live though, right?
We'll have to wait and see.
But the bigger problem is...
his brain tumour.
What?
He has brain tumour?
Yes. Didn't you know? I thought you were his son.
It's quite advanced.
I didn't know...
Then,
what will happen to him?
We'll have to wait and see,
but you should prepare for all possibilities.
The one that tried to kidnap me also tried to kill my father.
The suspect...
is within Star Group.
I'll find the suspect with my own hands.
No matter what happens,
I'll find out who you are.
Hello.
You scared me.
You're working so hard.
Here, have a vitamin drink, and have a great day.
Thank you so much.
- I hope it helps.
- Thank you so much.
- Be careful.
- Okay.
That's Staff Sergeant Ahn's son.
What is he doing?
- Have a good day.
- Bye.
He probably doesn't know what happened to his dad.
Whatever happened to him anyway?
Did he die or not? Gosh.
It's making me so uncomfortable.
Joon Soo is doing a lot better than we expected.
Due to the restaurant, our company's image became more youthful.
Our sales are up as well.
Okay. Keep watching over him...
instead of jumping to conclusions.
Yes, Ma'am.
Hello, Ma'am.
Lawyer Ahn.
It's been a while.
Yes.
Hello.
Hello. Long time no see.
Where have you been all this time?
You didn't even call. What brings you here?
I have a favour to ask you.
Sure, go ahead.
The thing is, I need some money.
I'm struggling to pay our firm's rent.
My aunt got a loan and...
Are you asking me for money?
No. I would appreciate it if you'd gave me a job.
You want a job?
Yes. I'll do my best in anything you assign me to.
I'd really appreciate it.
Isn't that Shim's sister?
Shim's sister?
Why is she running away?
Hello?
Are you okay? My goodness.
Hey.
Are you okay?
Why did you run away? I was happy to see you.
I never...
ran away from you.
Did you call me?
I was in a rush, so I didn't hear you.
Hey, do you work at this company?
Yes.
I recently got hired.
I see.
Shim recently got fired from...
Please. Let me say this while we're on the topic.
You know that Shim was fired on bad terms, right?
So I haven't told anyone that I'm her sister yet.
Is that how it goes?
Please don't act like you know me in front of other people.
Also, please don't tell anyone that I'm Shim's sister.
I'd appreciate it.
Okay. I won't tell anyone,
but I doubt the secret will last long.
You should just be honest and work in peace.
I plan on telling them soon.
Sure. I understand.
We're neighbours and all.
I can do you a favour.
Have a good day, then.
Bye.
Hey, Shim's sister!
Aren't you curious why I'm here?
My friend owns this company, you know.
Do you know Joon Soo? He's the heir to this company.
He's like my best friend.
I'll see you at home.
Lawyer Gong.
Yes. Hello, Director.
It's been a while.
Yes. How have you been?
Good. I didn't get to properly greet you since you started work.
I had the restaurant opening, then the deal with the United States...
along with the new product development. I've been very busy.
I see.
Are you free tomorrow?
I'm sorry? Tomorrow?
I was wondering if you'd like to have dinner together.
I didn't get to thank you properly yet.
Does tomorrow work for you?
Yes. It's good.
I'm going up.
I'll tell you the time and place later.
Okay.
Hello?
Ms Gong, are you in Seoul?
Yes.
I'm at the Jeju International Airport.
We were chasing the branch manager, but we lost him.
He just got on a plane.
Go to Gimpo International Airport and catch him.
What?
Just hold him for 30 minutes.
We'll take the plane over to Seoul right now.
Hurry, Ms Gong. We have to make him pay us.
Okay. I'm hanging up.
You scared me. Where are you going?
I have no time to talk. I have to go catch the branch manager.
The thief who never paid you?
Yes.
You have to hold onto him for 30 minutes at the airport?
Yes. Otherwise, he'll run away straight to China.
If he escapes, it'll be over for us.
How can you hold onto him? You're a small girl.
I thought you were going to help me.
You're in the taxi to the airport with me.
Why am I here?
Let's go.
Sir, please go faster.
(Arrivals)
It just landed.
(Ko Young Bae)
Right there. That man is holding a sign.
Ko Young Bae is the name of our branch manager.
You should watch the doors and see if he comes out or not.
What do you plan on doing?
I'm a police. Stay still. Stay still.
Give me the fake passport and the boarding pass for Ko Young Bae.
I'll let you go if you do. Hurry up.
You really won't arrest me?
No, I won't. Just give it to me.
This is everything.
Okay. Don't look and just leave.
(Ko Young Bae)
That's him.
The one with the black jacket and glasses.
I'm going to China.
You must be Ko Young Bae.
Hand it over.
What do you want?
My passport and the address to my accommodation.
Gosh, I forgot them in my car while I was rushing.
- What is it?
- I thought you were...
from Yanbian.
Did I surprise you?
People tend to look down on me with my accent, so I try to hide it.
I'm in a rush, so hand it over.
Let's go to the parking lot together then.
Let's go together.
(Min Jung)
I got him. Call me when you get here.
Hurry up and look for your car. I'm going to miss my flight!
Why are you so nervous?
What's your license plate number?
- Sir.
- I'll help you look.
Are you mad at me?
What's the license plate number?
You must be very nervous. What was it again?
Hold on. Let me call and find out.
Come to the 2nd floor basement parking lot near H4.
I don't really know the number.
Please wait a moment.
This must be the song Shim was talking about.
Shim? Gong Shim?
There she is.
- Stop!
- Wait right there!
- Go get him!
- Go.
Where are you trying to run off to?
Gosh. You jerk.
Give me my money.
You evil man!
You should be put in jail!
We'll beat you.
Give me my money.
(Office stationary)
What is he doing? Why did he make me wait out here?
(Director Seok)
Yes, Director.
Shim, where are you?
I'm just around my neighbourhood.
What's up?
I just didn't have anyone to eat dinner with.
Is that so?
Right, I got my first pay check.
Dan Tae is with me as well.
Really?
I'll come to your place then.
Okay. Let's have dinner together. It's my treat.
Okay.
You surprised me.
Why are you surprised? Who were you talking to?
Director Seok.
He doesn't have anyone to eat dinner with. He wants to go out.
You're free, right?
I have to go to the office.
Really?
He said he'd come to pick us up.
You guys should go ahead.
I'll join later if I can.
I should have asked you first.
I thought you'd be free.
What should I do?
Maybe I should ask him to eat another time.
There's no need.
Here.
Is it for me?
You drew me pictures before, right?
(I told you to come home early, didn't I?)
(I left the meal here since it's too late.)
(Don't forget to take your medication.)
It cheered me up...
when I saw your drawings.
I want you to continue to draw.
I'm your fan.
I'm sure even the most famous artist started with a single fan.
Thank you. I'll use them well.
Joon Soo.
Dan Tae.
Unfortunately, I have to go to the office. I can't come.
You two should enjoy dinner on your own.
I agreed to dinner without knowing that Dan Tae was busy.
Really? What should we do?
If it doesn't take too long, we can wait for you.
I don't think today will work for me.
We can go next time.
That's too bad.
Shim promised to treat me with her first pay check.
I'm thinking of going somewhere really expensive.
- What?
- It's going to be expensive.
You should get ready. You promised.
Gosh. Rich people are worse.
We can just get street food, then.
We can get gimbap, fish cake and tteokbokki.
Forget it. Gosh.
Enjoy your dinner. I'll be going.
Let's go.
Okay.
Be careful.
Aunt Ji Won.
Please take good care of Dad.
I'm sorry I had you working where we didn't make any money.
You should take this time to get some rest.
Okay. I understand.
I'll go see him everyday.
So don't worry about him.
By the way,
I heard you're going to work at Star Group.
How did you manage to get a job there?
It's my friend's company. I applied for an opening.
I see.
I was worried about you working as a driver at night.
I'm glad.
Make sure to be polite to your superiors. Okay?
Don't you worry. I'm not a kid.
This restaurant is expensive.
But I promised the director that I'd buy him dinner.
So I'll just skip dinner for a few days.
Are you Gong Shim?
You are.
I kept wondering if it was you.
Eun Jin?
It's so nice to see you.
This is the first time seeing you after graduation.
You're the only one I haven't heard from amongst our friends.
I know. Things just turned out like that.
Well, it's good to see you, too.
How are you doing?
What's your job?
Where do you work?
I'm still looking for a job.
So that's why I couldn't hear anything from you.
It's not like it's a crime to be jobless.
How can you cut off all contact?
Keep in touch, Shim.
Who is she?
She's Gong Shim, my high school friend.
Isn't she cute?
Shim, this is my boyfriend.
Hello.
Although you two are friends,
you're really different compared to Eun Jin.
Hello.
By the way, let me tell you.
Her sister takes after their mother.
So she's really tall, pretty and smart, too.
But Shim takes after her father, so she's short, ugly...
and cute. They were really famous at our school.
She and her sister went to the same school,
but they were the exact opposite of each other.
By the way, who did you come here with?
This restaurant is quite expensive.
Hello.
You must be Shim's friends.
My goodness.
Hello, Director.
Director?
I'm Lee Jung Ho, and I work in the Management Support Team.
- It's an honour, Sir.
- I see.
I guess you work at our company.
What a coincidence. Nice to meet you.
Is he the director of Star Group?
Yes.
Shim, is he your boyfriend?
No, he's not.
I thought so.
I like her.
Pardon?
I...
like this young lady.
I hope I didn't...
cross a line and make you feel uncomfortable.
To be honest, I know I shouldn't be saying this,
but I was really thankful.
She ignored me a lot back in high school.
Gosh, then I should've acted more manly.
That was more than enough. You looked really nice.
Choose your menu.
You have my stuff ready for me, right?
Yes.
I kept it ready for you.
You really are trustworthy.
Okay. Keep up the good work.
Dan Tae.
Don't you get sick of eating the same thing over and over again?
If I get hooked on something,
no matter what it is or what it does,
I don't easily get sick of it, and I keep liking it for a long time.
You can say that I'm full of pure love.
- Can I pay now?
- Okay.
I almost forgot.
There they are.
Thank you.
I had a great day thanks to you.
The dinner was nice, too.
Bye, Director.
I had a great time, too.
Good night.
Isn't he home yet?
The lights are on inside.
Did he leave the house with the lights on?
Did you just get back?
It would've been great if you came to dinner with us.
It was really delicious.
I thought of you while eating. You would've liked the food there.
The atmosphere was really nice, too.
You like those kind of places, right?
Gosh, anyway,
you missed out on great food today.
Let's go there together someday.
I'll treat you to dinner.
Okay then. Good night.
Be sure to buy me a meal next time.
I...
helped you get your first pay check.
Okay, I will.
Bye.
Why were you standing still?
What did you expect?
You should've come down quickly.
Secretary Doe, you did a great job supporting the chairman until now.
Thank you.
I heard you're the vice-president of the Chinese branch now.
What an unprecedented promotion.
Congratulations.
By the way, who will be the chairman's next secretary?
Has anything been confirmed?
I don't really know yet.
I haven't heard anything about it from the secretary office.
I'm certain she won't leave the position vacant.
My goodness.
The chairman should hurry up and hire a secretary.
Well, let's go in first.
Okay.
This way.
Who is he?
Isn't he Ahn Dan Tae?
Who does he think he is?
How dare he?
Hey! Get up right now!
Hello, I'll be working as the chairman's secretary from today.
I'm the bright and cheerful Ahn Dan Tae.
What? Secretary?
What kind of nonsense is this?
Who are you trying to fool?
You better leave before we call the security and drag you out.
What's going on here?
Why are you ordering my secretary to leave?
Sorry?
So this person...
Ahn Dan Tae is your secretary?
I hired him temporarily since we have a vacant secretary position.
If you don't do your work properly,
I'm going to send you straight home, so do things right.
Don't you dare try to slack off.
Yes, Ma'am.
But I don't understand.
Even if that's the case,
I don't think it's appropriate to hire him...
when he has no experience at all.
Seok Dae Hwang.
Did you become the president because you had any experience?
Well, in my case...
I need to get going. Get my bag, and come with me.
Yes, Ma'am.
What? Ahn Dan Tae is the son of whom?
Ahn Dan Tae is the son of Ahn Soo Yong...
who took Joon Pyo 26 years ago.
And you let him work here even when you knew that?
He doesn't know anything anyway.
He hasn't been in touch with his dad for a long time.
Besides, Soo Yong is pretty much a criminal, too.
He wouldn't have said anything to his son.
Whatever. Just know that it bothers me.
I hope you take care of things. I don't want to see him around.
I will.
Ahn Dan Tae.
You're not here to dig anything up, are you?
One more lap, here we go.
Look at me. I look so cool.
My goodness. What is he doing up there?
Make a curve.
- Hello.
(Secretary Goo)
Secretary Goo.
Calling me like this won't get you your job back.
My gosh. Your driving is really amazing.
Here we go.
Let's go.
Sir?
What are you doing here?
You're supposed to be working. Why... Why are you riding this?
- It's fun, isn't it?
- Nonsense.
Stop.
Anyway, if I tell you not to do something, don't do it.
- Hey.
- Yes?
You get a break when you're done cleaning this place, right?
- Yes.
- Then how about a final lap?
Okay.
- Let's go!
- Let's do this!
Faster.
Gosh, I didn't bring my mascara today.
Hello, it is very nice to meet you.
- Come in.
- Here.
I brought you all some sweet coffee.
- Thank you.
- You all should say hi.
He is the chairman's new secretary.
His name is Ahn Dan Tae.
I see. He used to be a lawyer, right?
I heard...
that he's extremely skilled.
Is he the one who saved Director Seok from...
being assaulted from violence last time?
Yes, that's him. You have a good memory.
- He is a great lawyer indeed.
- He is.
You see, that's really not a big deal.
Please don't hesitate to ask me anything.
I'm living on a lease, and it's my seventh month living there.
But the landowner suddenly told me to move out.
What should I do?
According to the law of Housing Lease Protection,
your lease should be protected for at least two years.
So your landowner can't kick you out that easily.
- He or she has no right to do that.
- Wow.
Really?
I thought I had to leave right away. I was worried day and night.
My goodness. Thank you.
If your landowner still forces you to leave, let me know.
I will take care of that for you.
You're amazing.
By the way, do you also...
clean the executives' offices and restrooms?
Not just that. We also clean...
restrooms and secretary offices. We take care of everything.
We do have our own areas to clean. But before they show up,
we just jump in and start cleaning together...
as soon as our chief janitor unlocks the offices.
I see.
If you need anything, let me know any time.
- Okay.
- Okay. Enjoy your coffee.
- Thank you.
- No problem.
- He is handsome.
- He is.
Hello, Director Seok.
You calling me that makes me feel awkward.
Where are you coming from?
I just found the shortcut to the cafeteria.
What made you decide to work here?
Well, it's kind of embarrassing.
But I needed to earn some money.
My aunt, whom I've been living with since I was young,
guaranteed her friend's debt, so we started struggling financially.
Did Dan Tae tell you what had happened to him...
lately?
I don't know the specific details.
But I heard he had some family issues.
I see.
Yes, so I called the chairman to ask for a job.
Good for you.
I'm glad that you became the chairman's secretary.
Really?
Then should I bring you something to drink?
We have iced Americano, lukewarm Americano, and hot Americano.
- No, thank you.
- Okay.
I want to celebrate your first day of work.
But I have an appointment today.
We should meet up soon though.
Yes, Director.
Please don't call me that when it's just the two of us.
Understood, Director.
Goodness.
Take care, Director.
Have a good day, Sir.
Thank you.
I'm happy to see you again, Shim.
But I don't know if I should be too happy about you being jobless again.
When did you come back?
It's been a week.
Doesn't it feel like we got dragged back here after becoming jobless?
Is this place a jail to you or what?
We get paid at this jail. I like it.
You guys are funny.
I hope you both get a proper job so that you can flee this place.
I want to run away from here.
Welcome.
- Welcome.
- You can park here. That's good.
How much gasoline do you need?
(Star Group Chairman, Nam Soon Cheon)
I heard...
from the chairman that...
you'll be attending the meeting instead of her...
and that you'll update her on what we talk about.
- That is correct, Sir.
- During the meeting,
you don't need to talk. Just stay quiet and listen.
Yes, Sir. The chairman also told me to...
just stay quiet and listen during the meeting, Sir.
You finished the refreshments already.
You shouldn't be sitting on the chairman's seat.
Move.
I should be sitting there.
Yes, Sir.
(Star Group President, Seok Dae Hwang)
Attention, please. The chairman isn't feeling very well.
Although it may seem odd,
her secretary was sent to attend the meeting instead of her.
So don't mind him, and let's start the meeting.
Executive Director Ha, you can begin.
Yes, Sir.
- My goodness.
- Oh, no.
My goodness, you're so careless.
What is this nonsense?
My apologies, Sir.
This pen is originally made of silver.
Why is the colour changing?
Hold on. Stop.
Don't drink your water.
I think there's poison in the water.
What are you talking about?
I need to check something right this instant.
Please don't drink your water.
Your water is not poisoned.
Next, please.
(Star Group Executive Director, Yeom Tae Cheol)
Okay, your water is not poisoned.
Next, please.
You two are the last ones left, Sir.
Let me check your water for you, President Seok.
Okay, your water is not poisoned.
Executive Director?
Now, I'm going to check with my water bottle again.
It is clearly poisoned.
- What? Who did that?
- What's going on?
How is this possible?
Everyone, be quiet.
Looking at this,
I feel like someone tried to pull a very dangerous prank.
You all should make sure no one outside of this room...
hears about any of this, okay?
If I see anything released by the press...
about what happened here today,
you all will have to take responsibility.
Make sure you maintain this confidential.
And I will investigate thoroughly...
as I maintain it confidential.
Was the suspect aiming for me?
I think Mi is too much of a perfectionist.
She can live easily, but she's too sensitive about everything.
No wonder she got sick.
She brings everything upon herself.
She's too greedy.
She should just live in peace.
Shim!
She's greedy because she's competent.
She has the potential, so she's just trying to become successful.
Shim!
What's up?
Here. This is porridge.
Go and give this to your sister at work.
What? Are you telling me to visit a place that fired me?
We need to go to a funeral in Daegu.
We already booked a train ticket, so please do us a favour.
She didn't tell anyone at work that she's your sister.
So be careful not to get caught, okay?
Mi will never be able to talk about her family at work.
Your mother beat the president's wife with a shoulder throw.
She'll never be able to talk about us.
Oh, dear. What should I do?
I should ask Dan Tae for help.
- Dan Tae?
Hi, Gong Shim.
Sorry to bother you.
No, it's okay. Is this it?
Yes. Please give it to her for me.
Isn't that Secretary Gong?
So I guess the two of them...
are quite close seeing that she's even giving him packed lunch.
I'll give this to your sister for you.
Thank you.
Hey, you don't look so well.
Is everything all right?
I'm fine.
Maybe it's because it's my first time working at a company.
It's tough to work at a company. Hang in there.
If you need any tips, feel free to ask me.
Understood, Ma'am.
See you.
There was poisoned water at the board meeting?
Well, the thing is,
I'm thinking that someone...
targeted your secretary, Ahn Dan Tae.
But because of Ahn Dan Tae, the other board members...
are feeling very uneasy and worried.
He requested for...
a pharmaceutical analysis on the poison that was in the water.
Apparently, it was potassium cyanide.
It wasn't a fatal dose. There was very little of it.
Who in the world did such a terrible thing?
We checked the security cameras.
But there were no outsiders near the meeting room that day.
Whatever.
Just know that it bothers me.
I hope you take care of things. I don't want to see him around.
Does that mean my brother is behind this?
Enhance the security at the company.
And find who's behind all this.
I will. I made sure to keep this confidential so that...
no one outside of the company will find out.
Do you remember?
When our husband was alive, someone was threatening him.
He almost died from that poison in his drink.
We rushed to the hospital and spent all night crying.
It was chaotic. My goodness.
That day, you cried more than I did.
You were crying for him even when he was cheating on you.
She was crying her eyes out. You have no idea.
My goodness, Mum. Here, try this.
- Is this good?
- Yes, try it.
- Let me try it then.
- Yes.
Who could it be?
Who's trying to get rid of me so soon?
It was definitely a new water bottle.
Was the potassium cyanide injected into the bottle?
- You can put it on like this.
- Hello, everyone.
- Hello.
- Hey.
- Welcome.
- You're here.
You should eat these while you rest.
My goodness.
I washed these nice and clean.
- So eat all you want.
- You're so kind.
By the way,
while you were cleaning,
did you happen to see a syringe in the meeting room...
or in any other places that you cleaned?
- See what?
- A syringe?
You mean, the one they use at hospitals?
Yes.
Did any of you see anything like that while cleaning?
- I haven't.
- Me neither.
Then how about a chemical or medical bottle?
I've seen a bag of medicine for a cold.
Well, if you happen to see a syringe or a medical bottle,
please let me know, okay?
The air among the board members is not pleasant these days.
Even when we drink a cup of coffee, we get paranoid...
thinking that it might be poisoned.
Ever since the chairman hired a strange man as her secretary,
things have become very awkward.
That secretary has no class, and he's also arrogant.
Anyway,
before anything worse happens,
I think we should let go of Secretary Ahn Dan Tae.
Let's all cooperate on that.
If all of us agree on this matter,
she won't be able to ignore our opinions.
She will be here tomorrow.
So everyone here should...
cooperate on firing Secretary Ahn Dan Tae.
Hand in your written opinions...
to the chairman.
I could get kicked out of this place like this.
Okay, thank you. Sure.
What?
Am I seeing things again?
I should go see a doctor.
Wait, this is real.
Hello, Sir.
Hello, Secretary Gong.
Yes, hello. Have you been well?
Of course. How about you, Sir? Did you stay well?
Since I don't get to drink your oolong tea any more,
I feel low and gloomy all the time.
Sir, it's not very funny.
Yes, this is it. This reaction.
This is the reaction I've been missing.
What? What just happened?
Get him! That jerk!
Now, they've started to harm people close to me.
This must be a warning.
Shim.
Are you all right?
Did you get hurt?
I didn't get hurt, but I was really surprised.
You must have been startled.
I was just surprised at first.
But now, I'm really scared.
Why would anyone do such a thing to me?
It really scares me.
I'll just put the clothes away.
Shim.
I know it'll be difficult for you to recall the moment,
but can you explain specifically what happened?
I won't let them get away with it.
Did you see the face of the man who threw the paint ball?
I didn't get to see his face since everything happened so suddenly.
He was on a motorbike wearing a helmet, so I couldn't see.
Did he say anything as he threw the paintball?
I'm not sure.
It all happened out of the blue.
Shim, try to calmly think it over.
I went to the company to give the porridge to Mi,
and that's when I met President Seok.
We hadn't met in quite a while,
so we were glad to see each other and were talking.
Then a paintball suddenly came out of nowhere.
You met the president?
Yes, I met him.
Dan Tae.
Is something wrong?
Shim, don't get too scared, and just relax here.
I'll be back soon.
Be careful.
(Star Group President, Seok Dae Hwang)
Why are you doing this to me?
What? Why are you doing this?
My gosh, Jong Chul.
Jong Chul, are you okay?
- Jong Chul!
- Secretary Goo?
Secretary Goo, it's you!
- She used to be my secretary.
She nagged me to give her job back saying that she was fired unfairly.
Hey, you.
How can you do this to me?
You must be the one who put poison in his water.
It was easy for you to sneak in since you were his secretary.
You even knew exactly where his seat was.
You were also aiming for him when you threw the paintball.
I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry. Please forgive me.
- Is that what it is?
I'm sorry.
President Seok, are you okay?
I think I am.
What a relief.
He should at least call me after leaving like that.
What if something bad happened?
It's Dan Tae.
Dan Tae.
Did you just arrive home?
Weren't you sleeping yet?
How did it go?
I caught the criminal. It's going to be all right now.
You can relax.
Shim, how are you feeling? Are you still scared?
I'm okay,
but you look very tired.
Me?
Well, I did have a busy day today.
I'll go back down then.
Get some rest.
Gosh, what if I can't sleep again tonight?
I'm worried.
(The next day)
President Seok.
Here are the written opinions of the executives...
stating that Secretary Ahn should be fired.
You can hand it to the chairman.
(Written opinions on firing Secretary Ahn)
The chairman...
will not be here today.
- What?
- What is he talking about?
We need to solve this problem.
Then,
should we go to her office?
Let's trust the chairman's judgement...
regarding Secretary Ahn Dan Tae.
But that crazy...
He's just so strange. We can't let him be the chairman's secretary.
This doesn't make any sense, does it?
- Don't you agree?
- You are right.
- This doesn't make sense.
- Why so suddenly?
Right now,
the chairman's secretary is Ahn Dan Tae.
The meeting is dismissed.
My gosh. Why is he acting weird again?