(Episode 11)
What's wrong with me? I need to cook rice first.
(Five minutes left)
Hey, Dan Tae.
What's all this?
It's your breakfast.
You need to get ready for work. Let's eat quickly.
Let me carry it for you.
Don't worry. Let's go inside.
Okay.
Here. Go ahead and eat.
All right.
Try this, too.
Shim.
Thank you for the meal. It was so good.
Drink some water.
Thank you.
I'm a lucky man.
Thank you so much.
If this is what you call lucky,
I can do this for you for a hundred more years.
Really?
Why is it so hot in here?
It is, right?
Yes.
Don't feel uncomfortable in front of me.
You can take your wig off.
Excuse me?
We're close enough. Don't worry.
You can take it off if it's too hot.
Let me help you.
Hold on.
I know we're close and all.
But how can I show you the big hole I have from hair loss?
Where is it?
Shim!
You hair grew back.
There is no hole any more!
Really?
Yes.
The hole is gone. It's now covered up with your new hair!
Oh, goodness!
Congratulations.
Wow.
Yes, I love you.
You love me?
Your rice is ready.
What?
I fell asleep?
Hey, Dan Tae.
Ahn Dan Tae.
I guess he went to work early today.
(I found this at the Yangpyeong arboretum. It looks valuable.)
How have you been, Sir?
Good. Come here.
Okay.
My dear Ho Joong. Are you doing well?
Yes. Thanks to you, I'm doing great these days.
You said you wanted to ask me a favour, right?
Can you please deliver this for me?
Of course.
Where should I deliver it to?
Please deliver this to Star Group's information desk...
about an hour later.
After an hour, deliver this to Star Group's building. Got it.
Don't tell anyone that I sent it.
Got it.
Thank you.
- I'll get going.
- Okay. Bye.
I don't understand.
He should've gotten a job at a cleaning company.
I don't understand why he started working as a secretary.
Shall we go?
Excuse me, Sir.
Someone delivered this for you.
What's this?
Isn't this the badge for our executives?
"I found this at the Yangpyeong arboretum."
"It looks valuable."
"I hope it get backs to the owner."
There is no such thing.
How much does he know?
I said, he doesn't know anything.
You little...
Tell me everything.
What is this?
Who in the world is careless enough to lose their badge?
President Seok.
Executive Director Yeom.
You two should lead a good example.
This badge wasn't some kind of gift for you to keep in your drawer.
You only wear it for the board meeting that I attend.
How many times did I tell you to wear it everyday?
I'm going to find out who this badge belongs to.
Yes, Ma'am.
Secretary Ahn.
Find out who lost their executive's badge.
An executive's badge?
It's a badge only for the executives.
Do you think someone who retired could've held onto it?
It was made a year ago when we changed our company logo.
And you're supposed to return it to the company when you leave.
There was once a fraud case by someone who picked up the badge.
Secretary Ahn.
Take care of this right now and report back to me.
Yes, Ma'am.
Secretary Ahn?
Thanks for your work, Sir.
What work?
I was just checking if you were wearing your badge.
(Check)
You scared me.
Secretary Ahn?
Thanks for your cooperation,
Director Moon.
I was checking if you were wearing your badge.
(Checked)
My goodness.
What's up with him checking our badges?
You'll get in trouble if you lend your badge to others.
- What?
That's what the chairman said.
That little...
Come in.
Hey, Secretary Ahn.
Hello, Sir. How are you?
I'm here to check if you are wearing your badge.
Are you?
Please leave if you're done looking. I'm quite busy at the moment.
Why are you just standing there?
It's here.
Where is it?
It's gone.
Where did it go?
When did you lose it?
I didn't lose it.
I have it.
You saw my badge this morning. You saw me, right?
My badge was right here.
No, I didn't see it.
You didn't?
May I ask where you went this morning?
I went to meet...
some people in the sports industry and...
some people from the Animal Protection Society.
I will go check if you lost it during those meetings then.
No, you don't have to.
I can check. I think I know where it is.
Once you find your badge, let me know as soon as possible.
The chairman is waiting for my report.
Okay, I'll let you know.
Where did it go?
Seriously.
- Go, go!
I don't think I dropped it here.
Where did I lose it?
Hey, Judy! Judy, come here.
My goodness. Judy.
Good.
You came here twice today.
Have you seen a little badge here?
It's a small badge I wear.
No, I haven't.
I'll let you know if I see it.
It's not here? I see.
This is not good.
I'll be in trouble.
Where are you going, Judy? Come here, Judy.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Are you hungry, Judy?
Let's eat then. Let's...
I found my badge.
Hey, Judy.
Did you find this? You kept my badge here. Wow.
I found it.
Good job, Judy.
He's not here.
Director Seok has gone out for a while.
Really? Where did he go?
I'm not sure about that.
Should I leave him a message?
I'm here to check if he is wearing his badge.
He is the last one I need to check.
Please tell him to call me once he comes back to his office.
How many have you checked so far?
I have only two left. Director Seok Joon Soo and...
Director Gwak Seung Jin who is in China for a business trip.
I checked everyone except those two.
Director Gwak, are you going to China now?
Yes, I'm heading to the airport now.
I have a board meeting to attend right now.
But I forgot to wear my badge.
Can I borrow yours today?
Of course. You should avoid getting scolded by the chairman.
- Here you go.
- Yes.
Thank you.
I'll give it back to you once you get back from China.
What should I do?
He's coming back from China tomorrow.
Excuse me, Sir.
Is everything all right with you?
Why do you care?
You look pale, that's why. I was just worried.
Thank you for your cooperation.
(Yongwangnim Nakji)
(Nakji character contest, Winner gets 50 nakjis for free)
A character drawing contest for nakji?
Gosh, riding a night train will be very romantic.
We can have boiled eggs with beer.
We're going to a funeral. Don't expect any romance.
We're going to Suncheon. We'll be back tomorrow.
Mi's on a business trip in Busan. Will you be okay home alone?
I'm not a kid any more. Have a safe trip.
When you were home alone last time,
a ghost came out from the ceiling like this. Ouch.
Don't scare her.
We'll see you tomorrow. Stay safe.
I saw the ghost from the ceiling.
- Stop. You're worse than a ghost.
- Okay, okay.
- She'll be home alone.
- Have a safe trip.
What was that?
Is it a ghost?
I'm scared.
It hurts.
Where is it?
Come on.
Shim? What's going on? What happened?
Open the door, Shim.
Shim!
Hey, Dan Tae.
I'm alive.
What's going on? Are you all right?
The power went off suddenly.
Can you fix it for me?
- The power went off?
- Hurry up.
Really?
Where is the fuse box?
My parents went to a funeral. They're coming home tomorrow.
And my sister is on a business trip. She's not here.
I was home alone, and I really didn't know what to do.
Do you not know how to fix it?
Don't you know how to get the power back on?
It has nothing to do with my major, so I don't really know.
Gosh, but what are you going to do?
You must be scared to be home alone.
That's why I need to fix this.
But my dad knows how to handle electricity...
even though he didn't major in sciences.
My school was coeducational.
Oh, okay.
Let me look it up on the internet.
I know that I need to find the fuse box, though.
Where is that?
Goodness.
You scared me. I almost had a heart attack.
You scared me more.
- Ouch.
- Are you okay?
You should've checked properly.
We almost went to the wrong funeral.
Take your shoes.
No, no. Don't go that way.
I can't believe this.
Why is it so dark in here?
Shim.
Are you already in bed?
The power went off.
Let me check the fuse box. Wait here.
Why did you come back so early?
You don't want to know. I'm still so angry.
He didn't pass away. There was no funeral.
The 97 year old man who almost passed away is doing well now.
He is fine. He recognises all of his family.
I was told that he won't make it tonight.
I'm pretty sure they didn't literally mean that.
The fuse box was off. Why didn't you do anything about it?
It... It went off just now.
I'm going back to my room.
Gosh, what is this? We went for nothing.
It only made me hungry.
It's me. It's me.
Let me tell you why they're back so early.
I heard them talk about what happened.
Right.
But why did I hide? I can't even leave now.
You're right.
But they could've asked me what we were up to in the darkness.
You missed the timing to leave. You can't leave now. No.
Then what should I do?
Please wait a little.
They will go to bed soon.
It won't take long, right?
They'll soon go to bed. Get some rest.
What's wrong?
I smell pork. Don't you?
Pork?
Are they really...
Are you hungry?
I can never hate you.
You said you were hungry.
You're so cute.
Cheers.
What are you doing at this hour?
What's wrong? We're just hungry.
I guess you're going to take your time.
We don't need to hurry. We'll slowly eat a lot.
Join us, Shim. You should eat, too.
Shim, what are you doing?
Have a seat. The samgyeopsal is so good.
Eat it with the lettuce. We just harvested them from the garden.
It tastes so fresh.
Samgyeopsal tastes best when you fry it in its own oil.
Open up.
How is it? It's good, right?
Yes, it's so delicious.
Hey.
Where are you going?
I was going to eat it in private.
Why would you eat that in private?
My daughter is quite unique.
Where are you?
Shim.
The smell of samgyeopsal is killing me. I can't stand it.
Eat this.
Is this all you brought?
Sorry?
You have two hands, don't you?
I'll be right back.
Hold on, Shim.
Put in a lot of meat, garlic and ssamjang paste.
And I want two layers of lettuce.
Got it.
Two layers of lettuce.
A lot of meat.
Garlic and...
Here we go.
- Why?
- You never eat raw garlic.
I'm lacking energy these days.
She's right. Garlic is a good energy booster.
Shim, invite Dan Tae over.
We have plenty to share.
You should tell him to come and eat with us.
Yes, go bring him down.
No.
I think he's really busy these days.
I'll go eat quietly in private.
Hey.
What's with her?
I'm not sure.
She's acting strange.
Why aren't you hiding?
I can't eat like this any more.
It's not like we did anything wrong.
I'm going to go out and eat confidently.
You can't. It's too late.
No. I'll go out there and explain what happened.
No. It'll make us look weird. It's too late.
We did nothing wrong. What's the problem?
I'm going.
You can't!
- You can't.
- Shim.
- No.
- I'm going.
- Come out and eat.
No.
Your sister will yell at you if you make her clothes smell.
Where did she go?
Honey!
He passed away just now.
- Are you serious?
- Of course.
He left peacefully.
What are we going to do?
It's too late for us to drive down now.
Did she go to the wash room?
We missed the last train already.
Are they for me?
Yes.
They'll find out if I keep going back and forth.
I'll stay outside.
Please hang in there even if it's hard.
Okay.
(Please make a lot of money.)
Please make a lot of money.
(Stupid)
You're so stupid.
(Crook)
You're a conman.
(Should I tell him I like him?)
Should I tell him I like him?
I'm sorry. It must've been hard to stay in here.
Can I go out now?
Yes. They went to bed since they have to leave early in the morning.
Thank you for the samgyeopsal.
I'm sorry.
Don't be. Sleep well.
I'll get going. Good night.
Okay.
It's the 3pm flight.
I'll ask you one more time.
Should I go...
or not?
You should go, Shim.
Fancy running into you here.
Where are you going at this hour?
I'm going to work.
Right, it's time to go to work.
How's working at the office?
It's all right.
Why are you following me?
I'm not. I'm just going my way.
Dan Tae, do you like mulnaengmyeon or bibimnaengmyeon?
Mulnaengmyeon.
Okay.
I'll have it ready for you when you get home.
I think I'll be late today.
Why didn't you tell me that you'd be late?
You just asked me now.
If you finish early by chance, let me know.
Okay.
Go earn a lot of money.
Director Gwak who is currently on a business trip in China...
and Director Seok who is off site haven't been confirmed yet.
When is Mr Gwak coming back?
He's scheduled to come to the office this afternoon.
We'll...
find out who lost the badge today.
Yes. I think so.
We'll see Joon Soo later.
It must be Mr Gwak who lost it.
Chairman,
do you plan on scolding him?
Go and check on it right away.
Yes, Ma'am.
Are you here?
I have to leave right now for an environmental union seminar.
What? You're busy again?
Why is it so hard to have lunch with you?
I'm sorry. It'll get better after today.
Why don't you ever wear that expensive jacket?
It's all wrinkly now.
You never wear anything I buy for you.
I've been saving it for important occasions.
You've become sly lately.
She's here.
Come on in.
Are you meeting someone here?
Hello.
Lawyer Gong.
I wanted the three of us to get lunch.
Sorry, I have to go for a seminar at the hotel.
It's quite all right.
It's just the two of us again.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Joon Soo, are you taking the company car?
No, I'll drive over.
I see.
Lawyer Gong, please take good care of her.
She'll soon be the most powerful person in the company.
Yes, Sir.
Did you follow me here to talk nonsense?
Are you leaving now? I have to go.
Let's go.
(Uncle Tae Cheol)
Hey, Uncle Tae Cheol.
No, not yet.
That document?
It's probably in my office.
I'll get it for you before I go.
Okay.
Yes, Uncle Tae Cheol.
Oh, you found it?
It's okay.
All right.
If we count Director Seok out, Director Gwak is the only one left.
Age and home town...
He doesn't seem like he has any relations to my father.
Executive Director Yeom borrowed your badge?
Yes. He came to me two days ago before I left for my business trip,
so I lent it to him.
You never got it back from him?
No.
Hello.
Executive Director Yeom.
Did you borrow this badge from Director Gwak?
Thank you for lending it to me.
I left my badge at home on the day I had a meeting.
Don't tell the chairman that I borrowed the badge...
before going into a meeting.
Okay?
That document?
It's probably in my office.
I'll get it for you before I go.
Okay. Thank you so much.
I already took care of the surveillance cameras.
My bag!
Why did I leave my window open?
The drawings that you gave me...
really cheered me up.
I want you to continue drawing.
I'm your fan.
Even the most famous artist must have started with a single fan.
(Gong Shim)
(Director Seok)
Hello?
Yes, Director.
Yes, I'm at home.
What?
What will you do? You lost all the documents?
Right now?
Yes, I understand.
I'll be right there.
Director!
I'm so sorry I called you suddenly.
What happened? Why didn't you call your colleagues?
Actually, I'm trying to become independent from the company.
Become independent?
Why?
I don't like hearing that I got everything from my family.
I was preparing my own business without telling my family.
I'm scheduled to do a presentation for my potential investors,
but I lost all my documents along with the bag.
I've delayed the meeting for two hours for now.
Two hours? What should I do?
I told the office that I have a seminar to attend...
to go to this meeting.
I can't call my colleagues since I'm doing this in secret.
All I could think of was you.
Can you help me?
I don't think now's the time to talk about that.
What should I do? Just tell me what to do.
I have all the sources on my cloud.
I need you to fix the presentation material.
Okay.
- Let's start.
- Okay.
(Developing private-label products,)
(currently in discussion with franchise convenience stores)
(Joon Soo's Great Series)
Here you go.
You saved me.
Thank you, Shim.
It was nothing.
I don't have time right now, so I'll call you later.
Okay. You should go.
Thank you so much.
That was hectic.
My nakji!
- Sir.
- Yes?
The contest isn't closed yet, right?
The character contest?
You can put it on that table.
Okay.
(Nakji character contest)
Why are there so many?
(Gong Shim)
Do you know how many people applied?
I think it's about 100 people.
100 people?
A lot of students from arts and design seem to have applied.
I didn't mean it to get so huge.
I see.
- Bye.
Even this isn't easy.
Lawyer Gong, I don't know what it is about you.
I always enjoy it when I eat with you,
and it's fun when I go shopping with you, too.
It's because you're nice to me.
It feels like I have a new friend. I'm having a great time.
I'm glad you think that way.
- There's the car.
- Yes.
My goodness! What should we do?
My goodness.
Gosh. My goodness.
Ouch, that hurts. Oh, my back.
Try to get up.
- Gosh.
- Ouch.
Including my wrist and my back, I'm in a lot of pain.
I'll have to go to the hospital.
Give me 5000 dollars right now for the doctor.
Here.
Right now I don't...
Hold on, Ma'am.
- Don't give him anything.
- What?
Who are you?
First of all, the black box on the car captured...
you jumping into the car.
I'm sure the car over there also captured it.
It'll be obvious when we look at the clips.
Who are you?
Should I call the police?
Go ahead.
(Lawyer Gong Mi)
A lawyer?
We were driving at a low speed when you purposefully...
jumped in to hit it with your wrist.
According to the constitution's Act 39 Article 347,
you'll either get 10 years in prison or a penalty under 20,000 dollars.
On top of that, you could get up to 15 years if you're an ex-convict.
What would you like to do? Do you want to go to the station?
I'm okay.
What? What's with him?
Is he a habitual offender?
How can this happen?
You must have been surprised.
My goodness, you're such a doll.
I knew it when she helped Joon Soo before.
What a sweetheart.
Mother, do you like her?
Of course.
She's perfect.
Lawyer Gong, do you have a boyfriend?
I'm sorry?
No, not yet.
What's wrong with all the men in this world?
How can someone like her not have a boyfriend?
What do you think about my son, Joon Soo?
Sorry?
You two should date.
Yes. They're perfect for each other.
You two would look great together.
What do you think?
I'll help you out.
Well, I...
I don't think it's up to me.
That must mean that you're interested...
as long as Joon Soo agrees.
Right?
My goodness.
My daughter-in-law and my great-daughter-in-law!
You two will get along so well.
How adorable.
(Gong Shim)
Yes, this is Shim.
Did you get home all right?
Yes, Sir.
How did the presentation go?
Shim.
The investors agreed to invest in my idea.
Really?
I'm so glad to hear that.
Congratulations.
It's all thanks to you.
Thank you so much.
I didn't do much.
I'm hesitant to ask,
but have you found a job?
Not yet. I'm just doing part-time work for now.
I want to help you.
I'd be happy to get your mental support.
If I introduced you to a job,
would that hurt your pride?
I want to be like you and try to find something...
on my own.
I understand.
I'll look forward to it.
Okay. Bye.
Dan Tae,
you should go now.
Aren't you tired?
I'm sure you're more tired than I am.
I get to do my own work aside from the visiting hours. It's okay.
Aunt Ji Won.
He'll wake up, right?
Even if it's for a moment, he'll wake up, right?
I still have a lot to talk to him about.
Of course.
Welcome.
You're here.
You look really tired.
Goo Nam.
I think I'll be less tired if I have a certain something.
Can you guess what it is?
I'm really sorry.
We're out of King Lunchboxes.
Goo Nam.
Didn't I tell you to save one for me?
I'm sorry. People knew that I was hiding it and asked for it.
I had no choice.
I'm disappointed in you.
How can you give them my King Lunchbox?
You're not betraying me, are you?
No way.
Gosh.
You're here.
Were you waiting here?
It's nice and cool up here.
You asked Goo Nam for the King Lunchbox, right?
I bought it before you.
Sit down.
I thought I had a new enemy,
but it was you.
Enjoy.
I want to try it, too.
Here.
Thank you for the food.
Thank you.
It's good.
Since when did you like King Lunchboxes?
Ever since they released it.
What else do you like?
Banana milk, sausages, and iced...
But...
why are you asking me that?
I'm just curious, that's all.
You're not wearing flip-flops today.
You seem to wear that white dress shirt a lot.
Do you wear it because you know girls like it?
Not at all.
Do you call your dad often?
How is your aunt?
Come to think of it, I haven't talked to your aunt in a while.
Do you take after your mum or your dad?
You didn't look like your dad when I saw him last time.
Am I wrong?
I guess you look like him in some ways.
Your mum must be really beautiful.
Shim, I'm sorry. I'm going to head in.
You didn't even finish it.
Are you feeling sick?
I'm just tired.
(Should I tell him I like him?)
Do you take after your mum or your dad?
Why am I living as Ahn Dan Tae?
If I'm not Ahn Dan Tae, then why am I Dan Tae?
What's wrong, Dad? Dad!
Dad!
Who am I?
No one applied for a new badge as of yet.
Other than one person, everyone else proved that they have it.
Who is that one person?
It's Director Seok Joon Soo.
Joon Soo?
Yes. We didn't get to check with him yesterday...
because he had gone to a seminar.
When I called him, he said he would come here himself.
There you are.
Joon Soo,
where is your badge? Do you have it?
Well...
I'm sorry.
I lost it when I went to a seminar at a hotel.
You lost it at a seminar?
I took a jacket my badge was on,
but it was stolen.
What?
It was stolen?
Your jacket got stolen?
Yes, along with my bag.
I think they wanted my wallet and my laptop.
But my jacket was with my bag,
so I ended up losing my badge with it.
It sounds like a huge bag. How did you lose it?
Did you try looking for it?
Yes.
A bag thief?
Did the person follow Joon Soo to get his bag?
He mentioned the seminar was at the Shindeahan Hotel.
Yes, this is Shindeahan Hotel.
There was a seminar there yesterday held by Star Group, right?
Is it possible to check your security footages?
We didn't have any seminars here yesterday from Star Group.
Then...
could you check if someone by the name Seok Joon Soo...
ever booked your seminar room?
Hold on one moment.
No, he didn't.
No?
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
All right. Thank you.
What's going on?
- Look at that.
- Excuse me.
- Who is Gong Shim?
- I feel jealous.
(First Prize Winner: Gong Shim)
Did I really win?
It can't be.
What should I do?
That Gong Shim is me.
I'm Gong Shim.
It's me. I'm Gong Shim.
I drew this picture. I did it.
Thank you. Thank you.
Welcome, Dan Tae.
I'm sorry if I surprised you with my visit.
No, that's okay.
I just have been really busy lately.
How was your seminar?
It was great.
Didn't you go through any trouble because of your lost bag?
Your laptop was in that bag.
How can you go to a seminar without any materials?
It was fine. I didn't need any materials.
I mostly listened to the presentations, so it was all good.
Wasn't it hosted by our company?
I somehow managed to skip my turn.
Dan Tae, I have to work on something right now.
Right, of course.
Then how about some beer after work?
Beer sounds good. Good idea.
All right. I'll see you at the pub in front of the building after work.
Why don't we go to your place instead?
I like it there.
Okay, sure.
I'll bring the beers and snacks.
Okay. I'll just go without buying anything then.
- All right. See you then.
- Okay.
Why is he lying to me?
Did he really lose his badge or is that a lie, too?
(Khong Shim)
Yes, Shim.
Dan Tae. When are you coming home tonight?
I'm busy tonight.
Are you?
Are you coming home late? I've got something to show you.
Sorry, I'm afraid I can't see you tonight because of an appointment.
I see. That's too bad.
Aren't you going to ask what it's about though?
I'm really sorry, Shim. I can't talk for long.
Oh, I'm sorry. I'll hang up now.
Wait.
Please call me even if you come home late, okay?
Okay, I will.
All right. Bye.
Why is he talking so seriously?
It's Dan Tae.
Dan Tae.
Ta-da.
(First Prize Winner: Gong Shim Prize: Voucher Worth 50 Nakjis)
What is this?
What happened?
A restaurant down the street held a character drawing contest.
So I participated.
And I won the first prize.
Really?
Wow. That's amazing.
That's really good to hear.
When did you participate? You didn't even tell me anything.
I really wanted to tell you,
but I was afraid I might fail.
So I was going to tell you if I win.
And I actually won!
Good for you.
Congratulations, Shim.
You're really amazing, Shim.
I'm really happy.
Never have I ever came in first place for anything...
my whole life.
I'm...
really happy.
Why are you about to cry when it's a good thing?
Don't cry, okay?
Thank you.
It's all thanks to you, Dan Tae.
What did I do?
It's all because you did well.
I gave it a try because you cheered me up and encouraged me.
When I think about it,
you're always the person who cheers me up.
You're the one who told me I'm pretty.
You're the one who saw my picture...
and cheered me up by telling me that you're my fan.
Every time I'm going through a hard time,
you're the one who always stood by me and kept me company.
It was always you, Dan Tae.
Shim.
I want to be that kind of person for you too, Dan Tae.
Shim. Just because...
Well, just because you're thankful,
it doesn't mean you have to...
You don't need to do this.
Remember what you said?
You said you're glad that you can see me anywhere at any time.
I feel the same way.
I keep thinking of you.
From early morning as I open my eyes...
to late at night before I fall asleep,
I keep thinking of you.
I often see you in my dreams, too.
I...
I like you, Dan Tae.
Shim.
I'm sorry.
I...
I can't accept your heart, Shim.
So please don't like me any more. I'm really sorry.
What do you mean?
Then what about...
everything you told me last time?
What I said last time...
Back then,
things were very different.
But Shim, right now...
Dan Tae.