(Episode 12)
I keep thinking of you.
From early morning as I open my eyes...
to late at night before I fall asleep,
I keep thinking of you.
I often see you in my dreams, too.
I...
I like you, Dan Tae.
Shim.
I'm sorry.
I...
I can't accept your heart, Shim.
So please don't like me any more. I'm really sorry.
What do you mean?
Then what about everything you told me last time?
What I said last time...
Back then,
things were very different.
But Shim, right now...
Dan Tae.
Joon Soo, what are you doing here?
Oh, that's right.
We were supposed to have drinks together, right?
Gosh, I'm really sorry,
but can we meet some other time?
All right.
I'm so sorry.
I don't feel so good today.
I understand.
I'm sorry. I'll see you later.
(Don't forget to take your medication.)
(I told you to come home early, didn't I?)
(I left the meal here since it's too late.)
Here you go.
Visit us again.
Hello.
It's not as aromatic.
- It's a bit bitter.
- My goodness.
Our tofu always tastes the same. What do you mean?
I'll take two packs. It's made of beans from Paju, right?
Why do you ask when you already know?
Goodness, pay for what you eat.
My gosh, you'll be rich soon.
All right. Enjoy the food.
- It's seven dollars, right?
- Yes.
All right, enjoy.
Sir, did this just come in today?
Shim, I've know you since you were in middle school.
When did I ever give you bad fish?
Give me two of this and that.
And please give me a discount. They don't look so fresh.
All right.
But what's with you today?
Shim.
I'm sorry.
I...
I can't accept your heart, Shim.
So please don't like me any more. I'm really sorry.
What do you mean?
Then what about...
everything you told me last time?
The number you're calling is currently not...
(Khong Shim)
- What about Secretary Ahn﻿?
- We should ask.
- My gosh.
- It's him!
- Secretary Ahn﻿!
Secretary Ahn﻿!
- Hello!
Hello, everyone. You're so hard at work.
It's nothing.
Hey, you should tell him.
Okay.
Hey.
Do you...
Gosh, I'll tell him myself.
Okay.
The thing is, Secretary Ahn﻿,
we're having a team dinner tonight.
We were wondering if you'd like to join us.
We have a lot to say to you, and we'd also love to hear you sing.
Yes, that's right.
What should I do?
There's somewhere I really have to go to tonight.
I knew it. You're busy, right?
I told you he'd be busy.
I wanted to hear you sing.
I promise to attend the next one.
Since I can't make it tonight, I'll give you a preview.
Tell them I can't make it
To the team dinner tonight
Gosh.
- All right.
- Good luck.
Hello, Sir.
Joon Soo.
That's unexpected.
I'm sorry?
What do you mean? What's unexpected?
A lot of things.
I guess you're close...
with the cleaners.
Oh, I see.
Did you see me dance?
I don't understand.
I'll be going.
Joon Soo.
I made a mistake.
It wasn't a suitable thing to do at work. I won't do it again.
Bye.
Joon Soo.
Did you find your lost bag?
Are you curious about the bag...
or the executive's badge?
I'm curious about the bag,
but I'm more curious about the badge.
I told you, I lost it.
Isn't that enough?
Why are you so hung up on it?
Why are you so curious?
There must be something you're not telling me.
All right.
Shim.
Why did you make so much?
My goodness, you're too generous with food.
We're going to eat it all anyway.
This is still too much.
It won't taste good if it's kept in the fridge.
I'll eat all the leftovers.
What's with you?
Can't I just say that there's a lot?
(Pervert Lawyer)
The number you're calling is currently...
Shim, are you going to put all these in Mi's room?
Yes.
Did you talk to her about this?
She never mentioned anything about it.
What's there to talk about?
This used to be my room anyway.
How can you do this without telling her?
She'll have a fit.
Tell her to go ahead.
I'm going to live like a human now.
Hey...
Shim!
There.
Shim.
That's it, right?
You won't bring all of her clothes and shoes in here, will you?
I am.
I'm going to get a bed.
What? A bed?
I'm getting a bed tomorrow.
When I get it, can you put it together for me?
You put Mi's together, too.
But...
What am I going to do?
I think they'll have a huge fight.
Gosh, I need more beer.
Don't forget to come to the reunion today.
Of course I'll be there.
I think I'll be late.
What time was it again?
- It's at 6pm.
There will be enough drinks at the reunion.
(Director Seok)
Yes, Director.
Shim, are you all right?
Yes. What is it?
You don't sound so good.
My throat is a bit hoarse. It's fine.
Really?
Let's have dinner tonight.
I have a reunion to go to.
How about tomorrow, then?
Tomorrow works.
I'll treat you instead.
I'll choose the menu, too.
All right.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Have fun at the reunion.
Okay.
See you tomorrow.
- Let's go.
- Go!
- One.
- Two.
- Three, four, five.
- Six.
Seven, eight.
By the way,
why is Shim here? She never came before.
Is she getting married?
I hear people come out to reunions to hand out wedding invitations.
Why would she drink like that if that's the case?
- One more pint please.
- Okay.
Attention please.
I would like to take this chance...
to propose to a beautiful lady today.
She's the one who made me believe in love at first sight.
My first love, Jee A.
Kim Jee A.
Will you marry me?
Do a love shot!
- Love shot!
- What?
- What is she doing?
Congratulations.
- Live happily ever after, okay?
- Thank you.
Cheers!
Congratulations.
Hey, Kid.
What are you looking for?
Let me help you.
Well, have you ever seen...
a lady with a wig like this?
Are you playing hide-and-seek?
Yes.
She is so good at this game.
I can't find her anywhere.
Got it. Why don't you have my candy?
It's too late. You need to go home.
Let me find her for you.
- Thank you.
- No problem.
Shim.
Oh, no. You found me.
But how did you find me?
You're the one who dumped me.
Did you drink a lot?
That is not what's important right now.
Hold on for a second.
After I got dumped by you yesterday, I got so mad.
So I made a list of things that I hate about you.
Listen up.
First of all,
you're broke.
You live in a rooftop that costs 250 dollars a month.
And secondly,
you're messy.
You know what I mean, right?
Look at this picture.
There is always dust in between your toes.
Also, you eat food that was dropped on the ground.
Right?
Now the third one is...
This one is the best one.
You're so cheesy.
Like this.
That wink is so cheesy.
You know that, right?
And the fourth one is...
Well, I can't read this out loud.
I'll stop here.
Shim. Let's go.
Dan Tae.
Don't you want to know what the fourth one is?
The fourth one is that you're...
broke, messy...
and even cheesy.
It's hard to be like that.
All right. It's time to go home.
Dan Tae.
Tell me why you don't like me.
Is it because you don't like girls with hair loss?
Or is it because I am dumb?
Is it because I am still terrible with the multiplication table?
Or...
is it because I'm jobless?
I'm sorry.
It's nothing like that.
It's not?
Then...
is it because I almost killed you...
with my plant when we first met?
I told you. That was an accident.
Or is it because the rent is too expensive?
I'll give you a 20-dollar discount.
Shim.
Wait, now I know.
Is it because I pull your hair whenever I get angry?
No.
No, it's not that.
Is it because I once went into your room after I got drunk...
and ate your soap and brushed my teeth with it?
Is it because I pushed you for not eating the dumplings I got you?
Gosh, there are too many.
You don't like to see me drunk, either. Right?
Is it because I'm not pretty enough?
I'm truly sorry about that.
I can't do anything about that. I'm so sorry.
Shim. You're drunk. Let's go home.
Get up.
Hold on.
Please tell me why you dumped me.
Then I'll go home.
It's because...
No, don't say it.
Wait. I want to know, so tell me.
No, no. Don't say it.
I'm ready.
Tell me.
Shim.
Actually,
I...
Don't ever tell me why you dumped me.
I don't want to hear it.
Hello.
Get on.
Okay.
You don't know each other, do you?
I'll introduce you.
He's the secretary for the chairman, Lawyer Ahn Dan Tae.
Lawyer Gong Mi works in our legal department.
Nice to meet you.
Yes, hello.
Hello.
Have a good day. This is my floor.
Okay.
Excuse me.
I heard you helped my mother...
when you were with her in her car.
Oh, the blackmailer?
Thank you.
It was nothing.
My mother and grandmother can't praise you enough.
Actually, they told me to visit from time to time.
I didn't know how you would take it, so I haven't dropped by yet.
I like hanging out with the elders.
It's fine with me.
You can visit any time.
Okay.
"Hot video from Yangpyeong arboretum."
"High quality video."
What is this? I didn't get a spam text in a while.
At an arboretum?
I wonder how awesome it is.
Don't click on things like that.
You have to delete it right away.
Of course.
Let's go.
What are you doing? You should just delete it.
I'm still curious.
Director Gwak, did you get the Yangpyeong arboretum spam text, too?
Yes.
I opened it, and it's nothing.
It's just a spam.
You already clicked on it?
Gosh.
Did everyone get...
the spam text?
I guess all of us got it.
But...
isn't it weird?
How did they get all of our executives' numbers?
You're right.
Yangpyeong arboretum?
Did you get it, too?
Wow.
Did all of our information leak?
- Director Gwak.
- Yes?
Did you end up clicking on it?
Yes. I opened it.
But there isn't much.
Listen to him.
Why are you so noisy?
Let's start the meeting.
Yes, Ho Joong.
Dan Tae. I sent around the spam text...
like you asked.
Thank you.
Good job.
No problem.
Ho Joong, can you send me one, too?
I'll send you one now.
Okay.
(Ho Joong)
(Hot video)
(Do you want to open this link?)
(Original clip for 300,000 dollars, Tomorrow at 5pm at the arboretum)
He'll have no choice but to bring the money.
The one who shows up is the murderer.
(Two days ago)
Dad, you have to wake up.
Dan Tae.
Aunt Ji Won.
Here.
These are the clothes he was wearing when he was...
transferred here after the accident, right?
That's right.
I washed them already.
What do you plan on using it for?
I need it for something.
What is it?
It's not something dangerous, is it?
No, don't worry.
I'll be going.
All right.
Don't forget to eat.
I won't.
Dad! What's wrong?
Dad!
Dan Tae!
Hey.
Dan Tae, what do you think about him?
His build is a lot like Dad's.
Good. I think he'll be perfect.
I'm glad.
He's my uncle.
Hello.
Thank you so much for coming here.
No problem.
Could you change into these?
Sure.
- Ho Joong.
- Yes?
Thank you.
I know it's not easy to help.
I feel bad.
Don't be like that.
For friendship.
You scared me.
Sir.
We can see too much of your face.
Can you look down?
That's good.
Ho Joong.
My face won't show, will it?
We'll blur it, so don't worry.
- Ho Joong.
- Yes?
Take a video as well.
Okay.
What should I write in the text?
Well?
What?
I'm thinking, okay?
Hot video...
from Yangpyeong arboretum.
Make sure you put three dots.
High quality video available.
(High quality video available.)
Put in some hearts.
Hey, colour the middle heart red.
Should we add a link?
Yes. Let's try clicking on it.
Yangpyeong arboretum video.
Direct dealing for the original video.
(Yangpyeong arboretum video)
Price is 300,000 dollars.
Tomorrow at 5pm...
at the arboretum.
(5pm at the arboretum)
That's good.
(Tomorrow at 5pm at the arboretum)
- Hey.
- Tell me!
You little...
What is this?
Someone was filming then?
Tae Cheol,
is this really Ahn Soo Yong who looked after Joon Pyo?
I'm sure of it. It's Ahn Soo Yong.
This place in the picture is exactly...
where I met with him.
This means someone was recording everything while...
you and Soo Yong were fighting.
I think so.
He must have found my badge there and mailed it to the company.
He's trying to scare me.
Are you going to give him the money...
to get the original clip?
Of course.
The one who sent the text...
is only blackmailing me for what I did to Soo Yong.
We should end it with money.
If this video gets leaked on the internet and the police...
end up investigating me,
they will ask about our relationship.
That'll end up revealing that I once kidnapped Joon Pyo.
Could this be a work of Dan Tae?
Didn't you say that he's Soo Yong's son?
He could have easily reported me to the police.
Why do you think he didn't do it?
It's because he doesn't know.
Soo Yong probably didn't tell his son about it...
since he was partially responsible.
If it were you, would you tell Joon Soo?
Whatever.
Anyway, I just hate the fact that Ahn Dan Tae works as a secretary...
for the chairman. I hate seeing him around the company.
I'll get rid of him soon, too.
Prepare 300,000 dollars so I can pay the blackmailer tomorrow.
Okay?
Will you save 300,000 dollars and lose everything instead?
Gosh, I get it.
I'll prepare the money in cash.
Where should I give it to you?
Joon Soo.
We should talk.
All right.
Something feels different between us, don't you think?
If you felt that way too, then I guess things really have changed.
Because I was feeling the same way.
What do you think is the reason?
Maybe it's because we're not honest towards each other.
If we were honest,
then we wouldn't suspect or misunderstand each other.
Then shall we ask each other questions and answer them honestly?
Then it'll be up to ourselves to decide...
how honest we're going to be.
You've got a point.
Only ourselves would know whether or not we're telling the truth.
Ask me first.
No.
I want you to ask first.
All right. I'll be the first to ask.
Then...
could you check if someone by the name of Seok Joon Soo...
ever booked your seminar room?
No, he didn't.
Did you really...
attend a seminar at the Shindeahan Hotel last time?
No.
I told you that I attended a seminar at the hotel, but it was a lie.
Then did you also lie about losing your badge?
No.
I really lost my badge.
I parked my car on the side of the road to buy coffee.
And I lost my bag with my badge.
Are you sure you didn't give your badge to another executive?
No way.
Is it...
my turn to ask, now?
Yes. Go ahead and ask.
Is there another reason why...
you're looking for the owner of the badge?
It's not just to find the person who lost the badge, is it?
What's the true reason behind all this investigation?
It's to find Joon Pyo.
That's why I couldn't tell you everything.
What did you say?
When you lost your bag,
are you sure you lost the jacket that had your badge on, as well?
Yes.
I would know better than anyone.
Then the person who took your badge...
is the criminal of Joon Pyo's case.
The person who took the badge...
is the criminal?
Why?
The person who sent the badge to the company...
left a small note with it.
It was about Joon Pyo.
The note said that the owner of the badge was the one who took Joon Pyo.
That's why I was looking for the badge.
Is that really true?
Yes, it is.
Let me ask you one more thing.
Okay.
Where were you really on the day you said you were at the seminar?
I'm preparing to run my own business.
I'm trying to run an independent business...
outside of the family company.
I went out to meet investors.
That's why I couldn't tell anyone in the company.
I see.
Shim knows about it, too.
She came and helped me that day.
She did?
I like Shim.
I want to make things work with her.
I want her to be happy.
I feel just the same.
We may have answered each other's questions,
but I'm not sure if we've become more comfortable with each other.
We'll find out in time.
All right, then.
Let's find out.
I'll be going.
Gosh, it's really spicy.
It wakes you up, doesn't it?
My tongue feels numb.
You really can't eat spicy food, can you?
No, not really.
When people feel irritated and stressed,
they often eat spicy food to relieve their stress.
But I guess you never really needed to do that before.
Stop teasing me.
I asked you to have dinner with me...
because I felt irritated and stressed.
Is it because of your new business?
No.
It's because of the people around me.
People around you?
Exactly who?
Ms Gong Shim.
The nakji character you drew is really popular.
Our customers really like it.
That's good to hear.
By the way, one of the customers...
asked for your phone number.
He wants to ask you for a character drawing, too.
Can I give him your number?
Yes. It's fine.
Character drawing?
Shim, what is he talking about?
Didn't she tell you anything about it?
Sir, that's enough.
Look. This is the character I'm talking about.
Shim won first prize in our nakji character drawing contest.
Really?
Is it true, Shim?
Yes. I received 50 nakjis for the prize.
Wow. You got 50 nakjis?
That's really amazing.
Sir.
Can I please have a new one?
All right. I will give you one.
What are you doing? It's nothing special.
It was just a small contest.
What are you saying? I really mean it.
I'm not exaggerating. This is really amazing.
Come on. That's too much.
You can have as many nakjis as you want.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
Shim, here.
Pardon?
Can you sign it for me? I'm going to keep it.
Don't be like that.
I'm serious.
Sign it for me.
I don't really have a signature.
(Yongwangnim Nakji)
(To Mr Seok Joon Soo)
(From Gong Shim)
(To Mr Seok Joon Soo, From Gong Shim)
I didn't write your company title.
- I'll keep it well.
- Thank you.
It's good to see you smile.
Pardon?
Shall we go to the cinema?
Or do you want to go shopping?
What do you want to do?
Sorry, I can't. My new bed is coming today.
A new bed?
Really?
Thank you for the nakji.
I can eat 43 more nakjis for free.
Call me when you want to eat something spicy.
Okay, I'll call you.
You should go before your new bed arrives.
- Okay. I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
- You should leave now.
- Okay.
Bye.
Oh, my.
It looks so delicious.
Why haven't you assembled Shim's new bed yet?
Let me eat first.
- Aren't you going to eat?
- I had it already.
Go ahead and eat.
I'll go and make room for my new bed.
Okay.
Eat well before you assemble her bed. It won't be easy.
Of course.
There's a lot.
Hey, I should invite Dan Tae over to come eat with us.
- Sure. Tell him to come down.
- Okay.
You surprised me again.
I didn't intend to.
I was really just on my way home.
Really?
Have you eaten yet?
No, I haven't. What about you?
Join me then. Please come in.
I'll just eat by myself today.
Why are you turning me down?
You used to bone a fish for me.
It's okay. Come in.
I'm really fine.
Come on, let's go. It's okay.
- I...
- Let's go in. It's okay.
- Let's eat.
- Oh, dear.
There we go.
This will do.
Dad, should I open that box for the bed?
Shim.
Can you give him a bowl of rice?
It's a bit spicy, but it's good.
What are you doing, Shim?
Give him some rice to eat.
Okay.
Thank you.
Go ahead and eat.
Thank you for the meal.
Shim won this nakji...
as a prize for a character drawing contest.
Hey, Shim.
Bring us the dish mat.
The one you got from the nakji place.
That's right. Let's use the mat. Get three of them.
Look at this.
Isn't her drawing amazing?
Where are you going, Shim? Join us.
Sit with us.
When she was in middle school,
she wanted to go to an art academy.
But we couldn't afford that.
So instead, we just scolded her...
by saying that she wasn't talented enough.
If we let her learn art, she would've had a different life.
Now she's just doing part-time jobs.
I'm so sorry, Shim.
It's all my fault.
My business failed.
I'm crying because this nakji is way too spicy.
Thank you for the lunch. I'll get going now.
You ate so fast.
Wait.
Can you assemble the new bed? It'll help with your digestion.
- Pardon?
- Right.
That's what young people should do.
I feel so guilty when I ask your father to do house chores for me.
Can you help us?
Of course, I can.
Shim, go and get him our tool box.
Help him in case he needs a hand.
Can you hold that for me?
Here?
Yes.
Dan Tae.
Yes?
About last night...
Yes. What about it?
I mean, last night...
What about it?
It was an accident.
Did you hear me?
It was like a car accident.
I never expected that would happen.
It was an accident that was never supposed to happen.
Was it?
Okay.
Let's say it was a mistake on the both of us.
There was no victim or assaulter.
Are you looking at me now?
You don't want another accident to happen.
It wasn't an accident.
I did it because I wanted to.
I'm not going to care about what you think...
from now on.
I don't care if you accept me or not.
I'm not going to worry.
I'm just going to...
cook for you whenever I feel like it.
I'm going to draw your face whenever I want to.
And I'm going to talk to you...
whenever I want to.
That's what I'm going to do.
So you shouldn't care about what I do, either.
You can just keep doing things your way.
I'll do the same.
Even if you don't give me the green light,
I'm just going to go straight ahead.
And that's not how you assemble a bed.
Let me do it.
Joon Soo.
Let's eat dinner and go to the movies together tonight.
Sorry?
We used to do that. I feel so distant.
Let's have some mother and son time.
If you have a plan, cancel it. Do your work tomorrow, too.
I'll buy movie tickets and make a reservation for dinner.
I'll take care of the tickets and the reservation.
Stay home.
I'll get off work early to pick you up.
Will you do that for me?
Okay.
My son is the best.
Have a great day at work. Thank you, Joon Soo.
I'll see you later.
- I'll see you later.
- Bye.
My goodness. There you are, my son!
My son.
What's going on, Mum?
Hey, let's go on a date.
Let's go to the movies and have dinner together tonight.
My goodness. What?
Just play that game on your phone.
What do we have for breakfast?
Hey!
- Yes, Father.
- Joon Soo.
Did you hand me the proposal for the outlet management?
I did. I gave it to you yesterday.
I guess you can't find it since you have so many documents.
Just wait a little bit.
I'll go upstairs and help you find it.
Okay.
I'm almost there, Dad.
You found it?
It's okay. All right.
Joon Soo, are you taking the company car?
No, I'll drive over.
(Uncle Tae Cheol)
Uncle Tae Cheol.
No, I'm still here.
That document?
It's probably in my office.
I'll get it for you before I go.
Yes, Uncle Tae Cheol.
Oh, you found it?
It's okay.
Then the person who took your badge...
is the criminal of Joon Pyo's case.
Did my uncle...
No, it can't be true.
Hi, Joon Soo.
Hi.
By the way, do you remember anything about your lost bag?
No, not really.
Are you coming back from something?
The chairman had to go out. I'm coming back from the lobby.
It's time to eat lunch already.
The menu is handmade pork cutlet, curry,
hamburger steak and galbitang. I wrote it all down.
It's always hard to decide on what to eat.
Aren't you going for lunch?
I have something urgent I have to do.
Enjoy your lunch.
Okay.
(Chairman Nam Soon Cheon)
Yangpyeong Blue Sky Arboretum?
(Blue Sky Arboretum)
The arboretum in the spam text...
was the same place where the executive's badge was found?
Does that mean the person in the video dropped the badge?
Is the sender...
trying to blackmail him by sending the spam texts?
Then if I go to Blue Sky Arboretum tonight at 5pm,
will I be able to see Joon Pyo's kidnapper?
(Do you want to open this link?)
Wow.
Did all of our information leak?
Uncle Tae Cheol.
Are you going somewhere?
Joon Soo. What brings you to my office?
Did something happen?
No. I wanted to get coffee with you.
I have an important appointment today, so I have to get going.
I see.
I'll come back another time.
You funny boy.
All right, I'm leaving.
Okay.
The suspect must have left by now.
It's impossible for him to sit still if he saw this text.
(Five minutes later)
(Three minutes later)
Welcome. How much would you like to fill?
- 50 dollars, please.
- Okay.
(Blue Sky Arboretum)
The person who shows up here...
is the suspect that kidnapped my brother.
(Blue Sky Arboretum)
Mother?
No.
It can't be.
It's not possible.