(Episode 13)
The suspect must have left by now.
It's impossible for him to sit still if he saw this text.
(Five minutes later)
(Three minutes later)
Why is he so late?
- My gosh.
-  Excuse me.
- Are you all right?
-  Watch your driving.
You almost killed us all.
Here.
I'm... I'm so sorry.
I admit that it was 100 percent my fault.
I'll take care of the entire hospital fee.
But I have to go somewhere urgently,
so can I pay for everything later?
Yes, it's about 3 to 4km away from Blue Sky Arboretum.
Please come here quickly.
No, you can't just go now.
If you leave, it'll be a hit-and-run.
He's injured because he got hit by your car.
You should come with us to the hospital.
This is an accident. Shouldn't we call the police first?
We need to take pictures of the scene first.
Maybe we should call the insurance company first.
All right, all right. I get it.
Let me just make one phone call.
I'm begging you.
Please hold on for a second.
Tae Cheol, what's the delay about?
Tae Hee, I don't think I can go right now.
Why? Then what about me?
I was almost there, but I got involved in a small collision.
I'm stuck here.
My gosh. Then what am I supposed to do?
Since I can't go there,
you should go to the arboretum instead.
It's almost time, so hurry up and go.
If the video goes viral online, I'm dead.
You won't be safe, either.
You're not that far away, so hurry up and go.
All right. I'm hanging up.
My goodness.
The person who shows up here...
is the suspect that kidnapped my brother.
Mother?
No.
What's going on?
Is the suspect not here yet?
Someone told me to hand you this.
"Direct dealing has been cancelled."
"Leave the scene immediately."
Did you hand her the note?
Yes, I gave it to her.
Thank you so much.
What's going on?
Is the suspect not going to show up?
Should I hide and watch?
The suspect didn't show up.
What should I do now?
Come in.
Hey.
Joon Soo.
How are you feeling?
I have a headache, and my whole body hurts.
I was supposed to go to the movies and have dinner with you.
I feel terrible.
Did you take some medicine?
Yes.
Don't think it's over just because I couldn't keep my promise today.
Promise me you'll set another date for us to spend time together.
Okay.
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
Get some rest.
All right. You should eat dinner.
I have to go somewhere.
Don't skip your meal, Joon Soo.
All right.
Why didn't the suspect show up today?
I was sure that the suspect would appear today.
(Director Seok)
Why is he calling at such a late hour?
Hello, it's Shim.
Hi, Shim.
I'm sorry for calling at such a late hour.
It's okay.
It's too late, isn't it?
It's okay. Don't worry about it.
Shim, I'm a little drunk right now.
I shouldn't be calling you.
Sorry.
Are you not at home?
Are you alone?
I just...
had a few drinks.
Are you all right, Director?
I just felt like calling you. That's all.
Shim.
Excuse me.
I'm hanging up now. Sorry.
Hello?
What's going on?
(Gong Shim)
- Yes?
-  Director Seok, it's me, Shim.
Where are you right now?
Director Seok.
Hang in there.
Taxi.
Director, get in.
You should get in.
I want to take you home.
It's okay. You should go home and get some rest.
Get in.
It's late. I can't let you go home alone.
Please get in.
Come on.
Then we'll go to my neighbourhood first.
But you have to go home right away, okay?
I will. Get in.
Hey, Director.
I bought you some water, so drink...
Director Seok?
Are you sleeping?
Gosh, what should I do?
Hello, Shim.
Hey, Dan Tae. Can you help me?
What?
What's going on? Where are you?
I'm at the park in our neighbourhood.
Director Seok is drunk right now.
I'm stuck here.
You're with Joon Soo right now?
Yes. Please come and help me.
Okay. I'll be right there.
Come quickly.
What happened?
I don't know what's going on.
But he drank a lot by himself today.
He was already drunk when he called me.
I came out because I was worried about him.
Once I arrived, he was more drunk than when I called him.
I tried to send him home by getting a taxi for him.
But he insisted on bringing me home first.
That's what happened.
You took a good care of him.
Honestly, I'm so uncomfortable right now.
Help me.
Here we go.
Joon Soo.
Joon Soo?
I think he's completely blacked out.
We should take him home.
Can you help me put him on my back?
Okay.
Let's go.
- We need just half of it.
-  Okay.
- Ready?
-  Yes.
Please watch his head.
He must be uncomfortable.
Thank you for helping.
No problem. You must be tired.
I wonder why he drank so much.
Me too.
Get some rest.
Thank you. See you.
Where am I?
(Visit Dad at Hyuan Memorial Park)
(Lawyer Ahn Dan Tae)
This Dan Tae's place.
Joon Soo is not up yet.
He's not?
What's this?
It's detox juice. I tried making some.
Good morning.
Are you feeling all right?
Yes, I'm good.
Do you remember what happened yesterday?
Was it you who brought me here, Shim?
Yes, it was me.
Try this. It'll help with your hangover.
Drink this and wait a little.
I'll bring over some hangover soup I made for you.
No, it's okay, Shim.
I need to get going.
Why? Have some hangover soup.
I need to go somewhere.
Thank you for last night, Shim.
Sorry for troubling you, Dan Tae.
I'll get going then.
I'm worried about him.
You already made a visit today?
Yes, we went early in the morning.
- Have a safe drive.
-  Have a safe drive.
All right.
Have a seat, Mum.
That old lady really is unfortunate.
On the anniversary of her son's death,
she's visiting her son all alone.
It would've been much better if she had her grandson by her side.
Then she wouldn't be that lonely.
However much we ask her to go together,
she says she doesn't want to go with us.
That's why I call her an obstinate old lady.
My goodness.
But I can't believe it's already been over 20 years since...
Joon Pyo's father died from a car accident.
I'm home.
- Joon Soo.
-  You're home.
You shouldn't sleep out no matter how much you drank. I was worried.
You look pale.
I'm fine.
How are you feeling?
I feel good now. I'm not sick any more.
Joon Soo.
You know it's the anniversary of your uncle's death today, right?
It's the day when Joon Pyo's father passed away.
- I remember.
-  You should...
go and visit him, too.
We already paid him a visit early in the morning.
Okay, I will.
By the way, the name of the charnel house is...
Hyuan, right?
Yes. It's Hyuan Memorial Park.
What's wrong, Joon Soo?
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
(Visit Dad at Hyuan Memorial Park)
His father?
Hyuan Memorial Park?
What's going on here?
Aren't you going to eat the eggs?
Gosh, I'm allergic to eggs.
Same here.
My father is severely allergic to eggs and so am I.
This is really odd.
Don't you feel like we connect quite well somehow?
Is Dan Tae...
Joon Pyo?
(Seok Young Jin)
(Ha Eun Jeong)
Joon Soo.
Grandmother.
Are you all right?
Oh, goodness.
Lean on me.
Chairman.
Please take her to the hospital.
- Yes, Sir.
-  I'll follow you.
Don't worry.
There's no need to go see a doctor.
I feel better now.
I just felt dizzy a while ago.
Are you sure you're okay?
I just need to get some rest.
Why don't you go see a doctor just in case?
All right.
Go visit your uncle, okay?
- I will.
-  Please go and get some rest.
Okay.
Oh, dear.
Grandmother.
Joon Pyo.
It was so close.
You almost ran into Joon Soo.
I'm glad that didn't happen.
It was all thanks to you.
You don't think Joon Soo came knowing everything, do you?
I don't think so.
I think it was just a coincidence.
Joon Pyo.
Until when do we need to meet in hiding?
Grandmother.
You promised not to call me Joon Pyo yet.
Until you're able to call me your grandson, Joon Pyo,
please call me Dan Tae.
Okay.
I will, Dan Tae.
It doesn't matter whether you're Joon Pyo...
or Dan Tae.
I finally found my grandson.
Ever since I found you,
I feel like I'm living in a dream.
When you told me you were Joon Pyo,
I thought...
I could die without any regrets.
Ma'am.
How have you been?
(15 days ago)
You look tired.
You disappeared for about a month.
What happened?
Ma'am.
Tell me.
I think...
I found Joon Pyo.
What?
What did you say?
You found Joon Pyo?
Is that true?
Ahn... Ahn Dan Tae.
Tell me.
Did you really find my Joon Pyo?
Where is he now?
Say something, Dan Tae.
(Genetic Test Results)
This is the genetic test I requested.
That's right.
This is the result...
you received earlier.
And this is the...
confirmation of the blood relationship...
according to Joon Pyo's genetic test results.
And it matched?
So you're saying...
he's my grandson?
Where is he now?
I think...
I am Joon Pyo.
(Nam Soon Cheon, Ahn Dan Tae)
Grandmother.
Joon Pyo.
Where have you been all this time?
My goodness. You were so near me, Joon Pyo.
Oh, goodness.
Joon Pyo.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry, Grandmother.
Joon Pyo.
Don't ever leave me again.
My Joon Pyo.
Joon Pyo, don't ever leave me again.
I won't.
I won't go anywhere.
All right.
I won't go anywhere, Grandmother.
Until we find the suspect,
no one should know that I'm Joon Pyo...
apart from you and me.
We have to keep it a secret no matter what.
Okay.
Since you insist on catching the suspect, we'll have to do that.
The person who kidnapped me is in Star Group.
In order to find him,
I need a position in the company.
All right.
I need to be active inside of the company with no restraint.
In order to do so, I'll need your support.
I think being the chairman's secretary will do the job.
Okay.
Then I'll appoint my current secretary to somewhere else...
and make a vacant position. Does that sound okay to you?
Yes, Grandmother.
Why are you ordering my secretary to leave?
Sorry?
So this person...
Ahn Dan Tae is your secretary?
I hired him temporarily since we have a vacant secretary position.
Grandmother.
Why do you keep crying?
Every time I think about the day you told me you were Joon Pyo,
I can't help but cry.
Grandmother.
I thought the suspect would show up at the arboretum.
But no one did.
Joon Pyo.
I don't need to find the suspect any more.
I'm already grateful to have you back.
I'm more worried that you might be put in danger...
while looking for the suspect.
I just...
want to tell everyone...
that I found Joon Pyo.
I want to live with you...
and go everywhere together.
Sorry, Grandmother.
Please wait a little longer.
The suspect not only kidnapped me,
but he also made my mother die in a car accident.
And he's also...
the same person that put my dad into a coma.
I have to...
catch the suspect no matter what.
So please wait a little longer, Grandmother.
All right.
It must be so hard on you.
Do you...
have any good news?
Grandmother.
Something...
has been on my mind lately.
Really?
Yes.
There's a girl I really like.
Is that so?
Who is she?
You should introduce her to me.
My heart is beating so fast.
Joon Pyo.
I'm dying to know who she is.
I really like her.
But I can't tell her that I do.
It's torturing me, and I feel sorry.
To be honest,
I can't tell if I'm Joon Pyo or Dan Tae any more.
I assume I should live as Dan Tae until I catch the suspect.
Also, the father that raised me...
is at a state where he could pass away any moment.
Grandmother.
I don't want the girl I like...
to know about...
all the mess I'm going through.
I want to treat her in all honesty.
But if I can't tell her everything about me,
how can I accept her feelings?
I like her,
but I can't say it.
It's so tough.
What will you do if she misunderstands and leaves you?
That's what I fear the most.
I don't want to lose her.
I'm sorry...
that you have to go through...
so much heartaches.
Dan Tae.
It's open.
You're home early.
Yes, I just got in.
(The Odd Couple)
I have movie tickets.
The nakji restaurant owner gave these to me.
I think he gave them to me because they expire today.
You should go see it. Otherwise, it'll go to waste.
- What?
-  You should go see it.
You can go, but you don't have to.
Here.
Don't be pressured, and take one.
I have a lot to do today, so I don't think I can go.
You should give it to someone else.
He didn't fall for it.
It's okay. Just throw it out.
It's fine with me.
Wow, it's hot.
Bye then.
I'm not going to care about what you think...
from now on.
Even if you don't give me the green light,
I'm just going to go straight ahead.
There's still time until the movie.
Should I just forget everything and go watch it?
No.
It won't end with the movie.
I won't be able to keep my feelings in any longer.
There. Like that.
Where could it be?
I won't know this way.
It's Shim.
What should I do?
Forget this.
Where is it? Where?
Where did it really go?
Where is it?
Shim, are you watering the plants?
Yes. I'm going to give one to the nakji restaurant.
Out of this and that, which do you think is better?
This one.
This one? Okay. I'll give this to him.
Shim, about that movie ticket...
It's okay. I already told you it's fine.
Don't worry so much.
If you don't want to something, you can just tell me.
I'd prefer that.
I'm completely fine.
Take care, then.
Wait.
No, it's not that. What I wanted to say was...
You don't have to feel sorry. It's nothing.
It just means that I failed today.
I'll get going now.
I'm the one who failed.
Where are you going?
To get a haircut.
Really?
I always wanted to point out your hair. That's good.
I have to get my hair done, too. I'll come with you.
Do you go to the salon for your wigs?
No, my real hair. Let's go.
I'm going to a barber shop.
- Really?
-  Yes.
You're so mean.
Come on.
Hello. Please follow me.
Okay.
Come this way.
- Hello.
-  Hey, Dan Tae.
Are you here for a haircut?
No, I'm here for a treatment.
My daughter suggested that I should take care of my hair.
Shim's such a good daughter.
Please give my father a lot of nutrients for his hair.
Okay.
As for this guy, if you cut his sides too short,
he ends up looking like an old man.
And if his bangs are too long,
he looks cheesy, so that won't do. But then if it's too short,
it'll make him look dumb.
And this part here. He has too much hair here, so it's puffy.
It makes him look shabby.
So please give him a good haircut.
How would you like your hair?
Just like what she told you.
Okay.
Hold on!
Don't cut too much of his sides.
- Let's shampoo your hair.
-  Okay.
- This way.
Yes, Mum.
Oh, right.
I'll be right there.
It'll take me five minutes.
- Dad.
-  Yes?
I have to go buy summer sheets with Mum.
- I have to go.
-  Okay.
Hey, Dan Tae.
Did you hear?
Shim is going on a business trip to draw.
A business trip?
That owner from the nakji restaurant...
introduced her to a sashimi place in the suburbs.
She's so excited to earn money from her drawings.
That's great news.
But my wife and I have to go to the hospital for our check-ups tomorrow.
I feel bad about not driving her.
She must have a lot of baggage.
I'll go with her then.
I told her that she should ask you,
but she told me that you've been really busy lately.
Luckily, tomorrow is pretty open for me.
Is that so? I'd be so thankful if you did.
Okay, then I'll go with Shim tomorrow.
Thank you.
No problem.
I'll be fine going alone, right?
Should I ask Dan Tae to go with me?
No.
He'll be busy for sure.
Goo Nam.
I don't need a King Lunchbox today.
Do you have dinner plans?
I'll pass for today.
Let me know when you need it.
Get lost.
Are you leaving now?
We'll hit traffic if we don't hurry.
- What?
-  You're going on a business trip.
How did you know that?
Your dad asked me to go with you.
Are you really coming with me?
You?
Well, your dad asked me a favour.
I don't have anything else to do, either.
Do you like sashimi?
I'm going to a sashimi restaurant.
The owner promised me a lot of free sashimi.
It wouldn't have tasted as good if I went alone. I'm glad.
We'll be late for the bus. Let's go.
Hold on.
Let's take this car.
I brought it from the office.
Isn't it tiring to drive?
It's okay.
If you're sleepy, take a nap.
I'm okay.
It's rude to sleep when someone's driving.
I stayed up late drawing up some drafts.
Gum.
This gum is waking me up.
Gosh, seriously.
I have to stay awake.
Please...
Gong Shim...
Ouch.
I'm sorry. I dozed off, didn't I?
You should be careful.
I borrowed this car from the office.
I thought you broke the window.
I'm sorry.
Wake up.
Should we stop at a rest area?
Should we?
I'll help you.
Gosh, this is really heavy.
Wow.
- Give me that.
-  No, I'm okay.
Just give it to me.
There we go. All done.
- You're 32 years old?
-  Yes.
I wish you were my son-in-law.
My daughter's perfect for you.
My younger daughter is 32 years old, too.
Her name is Bae Eun Sol.
She's a pretty one.
Stop that.
It's rude to say something like that to a stranger.
Instead of Eun Sol, our eldest has to go first.
That's true. What do you think about older women?
My older daughter's name is Bae Eun Chae.
She's a little older than you.
She's 39 years old.
Honey.
Were you helping this couple?
Yes.
We should go, Honey.
- Bye.
-  Bye.
Let's go, Honey.
Let's go.
Get on, Honey.
Hey.
I only called you "Honey"...
because I thought you were in an awkward position.
I was just trying to help.
I wasn't trying to make a move on you. I promise.
Please don't misunderstand me.
I won't.
Okay, then.
Let's go!
Let's go.
Are you free tomorrow?
Pardon? Tomorrow?
I wanted to have dinner with you.
I didn't get to thank you properly.
Director Seok's dad and grandmother all love me.
His mum loves me even more.
You ruined it all by beating up his mum.
Mi, don't worry.
I can't help you, but I won't drag you down.
I'll meet with Tae Hee...
No. I'll see Director Seok's mother and sort it out.
What are you going to do?
Beg on my knees.
There's nothing to it.
I'll just go on my knees and beg until she forgives me.
I have no pride.
I'll do anything for both my daughters.
Then when should the parents meet each other?
We're not that serious yet.
What? You're not?
- No.
-  Then why did you bring it up?
I begged on my knees a million times in my head just now.
You hurt my pride.
I didn't have to imagine begging to Tae Hee.
Gosh, my pride.
Next time, be more specific.
Hello.
Yongwangnim Nakji's owner sent me here to draw your mural.
What?
We have another one?
Why did you ask so many people for recommendations?
What a mess.
You're a troublemaker.
Sir.
We left Busan last night to come for this.
You came from so far away. We should go with you.
I broke my leg this morning, but I came anyway...
with my crutches to keep my promise.
You risked injuries to come here.
We should go with you.
I'm sorry about this.
I guess you have no choice.
Okay.
Honey.
I'm sorry.
It's because you married an incompetent man.
You're always working day and night. I'm so sorry.
My goodness.
When we get enough money,
let's have a proper wedding.
Honey.
Gosh.
Shim.
The only reason why I called you "Honey" was because...
I thought you would lose the job after coming all the way here.
I know. I'm thankful for what you did.
Draw it here like this. Okay?
Thank you for letting me draw.
I'll do my best.
Stop staring at her. She'll wear out.
You're a lucky man.
Your wife is a good catch.
Right?
How did you two meet?
I chased her around because I liked her.
Can you pass me the eraser,
Honey?
Sure.
Here.
Thank you.
Sir, can I start painting it?
Didn't the owner of Yongwangnim Nakji tell you?
I have a gathering happening here tonight.
I asked him to tell you that you should paint after they're gone.
No, I didn't get that message.
I left some food for you in the room. You should eat.
Okay.
It's delicious.
Help yourself.
It's really good.
Sorry, I think they'll be here for a while.
Come with me. Eat this later.
- Turn the stove off.
-  What?
Good. Follow me.
- What is it?
-  Just come along.
It's okay. It's okay.
They're newly-weds from Seoul.
They came here to draw our mural.
Have a drink.
I'm okay. I have to drive later.
Just take one.
I have to draw.
You guys are boring for your age.
Then sing us a song instead.
If they're good, you'll let them draw at your restaurants, right?
- Of course, of course.
-  Yes.
- Sing!
-  Sing!
-  Come on.
Applause.
I feel like you might pop if I touch you
- Awesome.
-  Nice.
I'll call you a flower
I miss you so much that I can't handle it
And the feeling spreads in my heart
- Great!
-  Wow!
Your shy
Confession
My heart's burning inside
My heart is like a volcano
That's about to erupt
- One more time!
-  One more time!
- Cheers!
-  Cheers!
Cheers!
I hear you two are a great match.
But why don't you have any kids?
If they take after you, they will be so beautiful.
You should have a kid even if you don't have money.
Do you know how happy those little toes make you?
They can make one tonight.
That sounds good.
- Make one.
-  Make one.
We're going to be really loud today, so don't mind us.
Here.
Get up.
- Good luck.
-  Good luck.
- Make one.
-  Make one.
Come in.
Sir, when can we start painting?
I think they'll stay a while longer.
I don't think you can paint today.
- What?
-  What?
Sleep for tonight,
and we can start tomorrow.
You only need one set of bedding, right?
Sir.
Do you have another room?
No. Of course not.
This won't do.
Didn't you hear everyone?
Good luck tonight.
See you tomorrow.
Shim. Instead of standing up,
you can lie down on this. I'll set it out for you.
What?
That's not what I meant.
You just look really uncomfortable.
It's okay with me. You can take it off.
What?
No, it's not that.
I meant that you should take off your wig.
Do you want to shower first?
What?
I'm sorry.
I don't know why I keep making these mistakes.
What's wrong with you, Dan Tae?
Forget it.
I'll set the blankets and lie down first.
What?
I'm going to go out for some fresh air.
Okay, go ahead.
It's hard for me to fall sleep at a new place,
so I won't be sleeping. Take your time.
- Okay, I'll be back.
-  Bye.
Wow, it's so hot.
Shim.
Wake up.
Shim, you should lie down and sleep.
Shim.
I'm sorry.
Thank you for liking me all this time.
Shim.
Can you stay a bit longer...
and wait for me?
Will you?
Shim.
Did you wake up?
When did you wake up, Shim?
A while ago.
Do you need help with anything?
Then...
can you please draw the octopus' eyes...
more clearly with thicker lines?
All right.
It's finished.
This looks great.
This looks really amazing, Shim.
Well done.
Thank you, Dan Tae.
Honey.
What a masterpiece!
I really love it, Shim.
Please take this.
Okay.
Thank you for your work.
Thank you.
Honey?
Why don't we take a photo in front of your drawing, Honey?
Shall we?
All right, here we go. In 1, 2, 3.
It's done.
You should take a photo with your husband, too.
Stand there.
Why are you so awkward when you're married?
You should be hugging each other like this.
There you go. In 1, 2, 3.