(Episode 14)
Hey, Shim
You're sitting in the passenger seat, so you should do your part.
Play some music or talk to me.
Okay.
Dan Tae.
Thank you.
By the way, your singing was impressive.
I will call you a flower
You should go and sing trot songs for the elders.
What about your dancing?
You danced...
like this.
You were like a leader of a women's association.
- Stop teasing me.
-  What did I do?
We're home.
Thank you for the ride.
Thank you, too.
Your drawing was great.
Get some rest.
You too.
Joon Soo.
Where are you coming from?
What are you doing here?
I came over thinking you'd be home since it's early in the morning.
I was out of town.
Please come in.
You've been here before, so you know my place is not spacious, right?
Please make yourself comfortable.
- You can sit here.
-  Okay.
Right. Hold on.
I should give you something to drink.
Oh, dear.
I don't have any drinks.
Let me go to the store and buy something quickly.
- It won't take long.
-  It's okay. Don't worry.
Wait here.
Dad.
His father is alive.
Then...
whose father is he?
Hyuan Memorial Park.
That's also where the urn of Joon Pyo's father is at.
It's the same memorial park.
This is strange.
Your drinks are here.
In summer, it gets really hot here because it's a rooftop house.
Here, have a drink.
Thank you.
I saw your family picture.
Oh, that.
I don't know if it's appropriate to ask you this,
but why aren't you living with your family?
My mother passed away when I was in high school.
And my father normally lives abroad.
I see.
Where does he live?
He lives in the Philippines.
In the Philippines, I see.
(Visit Dad at Hyuan Memorial Park)
Joon Soo.
I heard you were drinking alone when you got drunk that night.
Is something going on?
No, nothing's going on. I'm fine.
I guess you're going through a hard time with your personal business.
Yes, I guess.
That's what business is like.
There's not much I can do,
but call me when you're in need.
I'll help you. You can call me even for small errands.
Thank you for saying that.
I wasn't just saying it. I mean it.
Since we're talking about work, I'm curious to know.
How are things going...
with finding Joon Pyo?
You said whoever lost the executive's badge was going to be...
Joon Pyo's kidnapper, right?
Yes, I did.
The person who took your bag is the suspect.
Who do you think it is?
You must have...
someone in mind.
No.
I don't have any yet.
Then by any chance,
do you think the spam message is...
related to finding the suspect, too?
Sorry?
I was...
just curious.
It was only the executives that received the spam text message.
And the badge is also only for the executives.
I see.
Oh, right.
I guess you didn't get the spam message...
since you're not an executive of our company.
You're right.
Since I'm not an executive,
I didn't get the spam text message.
So I don't really know what it's about.
Well, then I guess that text message has nothing to do with...
finding Joon Pyo.
I guess so.
Oh, my goodness.
Goodness.
- My gosh.
-  I'll clean it.
Don't worry. I'll take care of it.
You should go and wash your hands.
- Sorry.
-  It's okay.
All I need is a genetic testing...
to see whether Dan Tae is Joon Pyo or not.
You can use this towel.
Thank you.
Who wrote this note?
Someone told me to give you this.
"Direct dealing has been cancelled."
"Leave the scene immediately."
Do you think...
the dealer told you to escape because he thought...
the police were on him?
What if your friend from the army is scheming everything...
just to get money from us?
Ahn Soo Yong?
He could've made someone hide at the arboretum to take the video.
He could've purposely got hit by you with everything planned in advance.
Then he why would he tell you to leave without taking the money?
Then who else could possibly write me this note?
My goodness. This is driving me crazy.
Tae Cheol.
I'm so nervous.
Do something. I'll pay as much as I need to fix this.
Just wait a little more.
I'm looking for Soo Yong anyway.
We just need to make sure he keeps his mouth shut.
Ahn Dan Tae is his son.
He doesn't know anything.
He doesn't even see his father.
Do you think he would've stayed quiet if he knew everything?
I don't want to see Ahn Dan Tae around, either.
He makes me nervous.
Soon, I'm going to take care of...
Ahn Dan Tae, too.
You're right.
Since I'm not an executive,
I didn't get the spam text message.
So I don't really know what it's about.
Shim?
Are you going to work?
Yes. What's wrong?
Does it hurt?
I guess it's because of all the painting I did at the sashimi place.
When I woke up, my whole body was aching.
Goodness, I need to go work, too.
Why don't you take a day off?
I get paid hourly.
If I take a day off, I won't get paid as much, so I don't want to.
Have a great day at work.
An economy census?
Yes, we do this once every five years.
It helps the government analyse our country's industry structure.
The information will also be given to the owner.
It'll help him know the business structure of the neighbourhood.
Do I have to do this?
The owner isn't even here today.
It's also business information you're asking for.
According to the Statistics Act, Article 33 and 34,
all the information gathered will remain confidential.
Am I right?
Correct.
You can also give us the information online.
Please tell the owner.
- Okay.
-  All right.
- Bye.
-  Bye.
Goo Nam, Shim will come here soon...
with her neck like this. She'll look for a pain relief patch.
Give this to her.
What's this?
It's a pain relief set that works really well.
According to the Convenient Store Act, Article 33,
it should remain confidential.
Don't ever tell her that I gave this to you.
- Why not?
-  Why do you think?
- Goo Nam.
-  Yes?
- See you.
-  Bye.
(Jean Jacques Sempe Exhibition)
(I told you to come home early, didn't I?)
(I left the meal here since it's too late.)
(Don't forget to take your medication.)
(Should I tell him I like him?)
Should I tell him I like him?
Shim will love this exhibition.
Until when does it open?
This is killing me.
He was right.
What? What's wrong?
What? Nothing.
Goo Nam, do you have pain relief patch?
My arms and neck hurt so bad.
- Here.
-  What's this?
It's good for shoulder discomfort and sore neck muscles.
Take a look.
Really?
What's this? They're all used.
Look. Someone's fingerprints are still here.
What?
But apparently,
they really work well on you.
Go ahead and try.
Is it safe?
Who used this?
I don't know. Someone left it here.
It does feel like a good medicine.
I guess it really works.
Can I really use this?
Of course. Take them.
Great. I just got free medicine.
It's surprising that you're helping me all of a sudden.
- Have a good one.
-  You too.
Bye.
(VIP invitation ticket, Jean Jacques Sempe Exhibition)
(To Mr Seok Joon Soo, From Gong Shim)
I didn't write your company title.
Wow, it looks delicious.
I bought this with the money I made from drawing at the sashimi place,
so I hope you enjoy it.
I'm so happy, Shim.
Try some, Honey.
Mi, now that you finally took a day off,
you get to eat this fancy meal that Shim prepared for all of us.
She's right. You always work too hard.
You should rest once in a while.
You're right. It's more delicious since Shim bought it for us.
I agree with her, Shim.
- Do you want some alcohol?
-  Of course.
Do you want some too, Shim?
No, I have to go to work.
Your phone is ringing.
(Director Seok)
Hello, Director.
Hello, Shim.
Do you have any time available tonight?
No, I don't.
I have to go fill in for a part-time job.
I see.
What's going on?
I have something I want to give to you.
To me?
I'm sorry. I don't have time tonight.
That's fine.
I'll call you again next time.
Okay.
All right.
Do you still keep in touch with Director Seok...
even after leaving the company?
Yes, time to time.
Why?
We kept in touch. That's all.
Why did he call you a while ago?
It was nothing special.
It sounded like you turned him down when he wanted to see you.
It's because I have to go to work today.
I need to go now. See you.
Okay.
Hello, this is the chairman's secretary speaking.
Joon Pyo,
it's me.
Grandmother.
What are you doing?
I'm working, of course.
What about you?
I'm busy thinking about living with you...
in the near future.
Grandmother.
We still need to be careful so that people won't notice.
I know.
Joon Pyo.
Come to my house right now.
To your house?
Yes.
Come home.
It's where you grew up. Everything is still the same.
Look around carefully.
I hope there's something you can remember.
- Who is it?
-  Hi, this is Secretary Ahn.
It took 26 years for me to come back home.
Joon Pyo.
- There you are.
-  Mum.
My lovely boy.
I...
remember.
How does it feel to be back home?
It's exactly the same as it was when you were young.
Grandmother.
I think I remember something.
What?
My goodness. Really?
Go on and tell me.
What do you remember?
I remember that I used to play in the yard.
Yes.
I was holding balloons.
I was in my mother's arms.
She was laughing with me.
She looked like the happiest person in the world.
Yes.
Right.
You're right.
When you were a kid,
you used to play in the yard...
with your mum and dad.
You used to blow balloons, play football,
and you ran around a lot, too.
Yes.
Do you remember anything else?
No. That's all I can remember.
I just slightly remembered as I walked into the yard.
I can't remember anything else...
no matter how hard I try.
I see.
Take your time.
I'm already...
grateful to hear that you remember...
your mother's smile.
Thank you.
Soon, you'll also remember how you got kidnapped.
There's no need to rush.
Okay?
All right?
Yes.
Okay, Grandmother.
Good.
Who are you?
Hello. I'm the chairman's secretary, Ahn Dan Tae.
Oh, I see.
I didn't recognise you since it's my first time seeing you.
It is nice to meet you.
You are so handsome.
I'm President Seok's biological mother.
Does that help you understand?
My goodness.
No wonder President Seok and Director Seok are so perfect.
Now that I meet you, it all makes sense.
My goodness, look at you.
You only just met me, but you know how to flatter someone.
You made my day.
Hey.
Come here and say hello to Secretary Ahn.
My goodness, look how handsome he is.
He seems like he has a great personality, too.
We've already met before.
Really?
Hello, Ma'am.
The chairman normally doesn't call her secretary over to her room.
Why did you come here?
Well, she wanted me to take care of her personal documents.
That's why I stopped by.
She told me to start with documents from 10 years ago.
So I think it'll take me some time.
I'll be here often for a while.
Really?
It's nice to meet you.
Visit us often, okay?
But I'm curious.
Does she choose her secretary based on their looks?
I hope you understand.
My mother-in-law likes to joke.
No, it's okay.
I get that a lot anyway.
(VIP invitation ticket)
(Jean Jacques Sempe Exhibition)
Shim will love to see these tickets.
You're here.
You came early again.
Yes.
- Goo Nam.
-  Yes?
I have a favour to ask.
- What's this?
-  You don't need to know.
Hand this to Shim when she passes by.
She's your neighbour. You can do it yourself.
Why do you keep asking me?
- Goo Nam?
-  Yes, Sir.
These were from you, Dan Tae. Am I right?
No.
I think you're lying.
I think I'm right.
They're not from me.
Okay, fine.
Would you like to come with me then?
Maybe.
I'll take you to the exhibition. You can buy me dinner.
No.
I'm going to buy drinks, too.
You make me shy.
- Goo Nam.
-  Yes?
- Take care.
-  All right.
And stop talking back.
Hi, Shim. Did you go grocery shopping?
Isn't it obvious? What's up?
I have a gift for you.
Take this.
Someone asked me to give you this.
What is it?
(Jean Jacques Sempe Exhibition)
I really wanted to go to this exhibition.
- Who gave you this?
-  What?
Well...
I have something I want to give to you.
I think I know who gave this to me.
- Thank you.
-  Okay.
So this is why Director Seok called me yesterday.
The person who took your bag is the suspect.
Joon Soo, are you taking the company car?
My bag.
(Joon Soo's Great Series)
Wow, Joon Soo.
I thought he was just an obedient rich heir,
but I guess he knows how to start his own business.
How adorable.
All right, Tae Cheol. Let's go.
Yes... Yes, let's go.
Why are you so surprised?
Were you watching something racy or what?
No way.
What brings you here?
I thought we were eating naengmyeon. Do you have dementia?
Right, I forgot.
Wait for me downstairs.
Come on, let's just go. I'm hungry.
Are you?
All right, let's go.
Which one will you have?
The regular one or the spicy one?
I really wish...
we could have both kinds at once.
Both kinds?
That's a great idea! You should develop it.
Should I?
Joon Soo, aren't you going home?
I will. Are you leaving now?
Yes. We're going to get naengmyeon. Do you want to come?
I'm not done with work yet.
You two should go ahead.
That's too bad. Let's get some together next time.
Sure, Uncle Tae Cheol. Bye.
Bye.
Where is my bag?
Did he move it?
Joon Soo.
Dan Tae.
Did you eat?
I can't understand what you're saying.
I asked if you ate.
Not yet.
Joon Soo.
You look so down. What's wrong?
I'm fine. It's nothing.
I'm glad.
Joon soo, even if you're busy,
you should take care of yourself.
I will.
If you need my help, you can always ask me.
Okay. Thank you.
Joon Soo.
Yes?
Why did you follow me here?
What?
You were walking me over, weren't you?
I didn't notice while I was talking to you.
I'll be going.
Bye.
There we go.
You should have checked before bringing that.
- Gosh.
-  Here he is.
What is it?
Why did you call me here so secretively?
Secretary Ahn, we have a favour to ask.
A favour? Go ahead.
Can you put this back in Executive Director Yeom's office?
This bag? Why?
Our ladies here...
emptied his garbage can without looking.
When we were separating the recyclables, we found this.
No matter how much we look at it, it looks so new.
I don't think he meant to throw it out.
I see.
We were going to put it back,
but he'll be in soon, so we can't go in.
So you're asking me to...
take this bag back to Executive Director Yeom's office, right?
- That's it.
-  Yes!
All right.
That's not hard at all.
Joon Soo.
Dan Tae.
Why does he have my bag?
Do you know where this is from?
What?
Doesn't it look nice? It looks expensive.
Yes.
Did he look inside?
Is he joking because he knows it's my bag?
It's not mine.
Who do you think...
it belongs to?
It's Executive Director Yeom's.
My uncle?
Yes.
It doesn't suit him at all.
No.
But...
why do you have this?
The cleaners were cleaning his office...
and took it by mistake since it was in the garbage can.
When they actually saw it, it didn't look like garbage to them.
They asked me to return it, so I'm on my way over there.
I'll take it there.
I have to talk to him about something anyway.
I'll take it to him.
Will you? Thank you.
I'll get going.
Okay.
They must have emptied it.
- This is the information desk.
-  Hello.
It's Executive Director Yeom.
I'd like to know who cleaned my office today.
Are you looking for this?
Joon... Joon Soo.
Secretary Ahn. You have to pay a fine for speeding.
Speeding?
You were speeding with the company car.
It's the driver's responsibility.
You have to pay in the given time.
I will. Thank you.
Hello, Ms Kim.
Do I have any fines to pay?
No.
Have a good...
Hello.
What did the grim reaper bring to you?
The grim reaper?
She's always making the rest of us pay.
So that's her nickname.
Also, she only dresses in black.
I have to pay a fine for speeding.
- Do you?
-  Yes.
What's the rush?
All men...
should be careful about speeding.
Dan Tae, give me a mate tea.
Sir.
The chairman is at home today.
Right.
What's wrong with me?
Dan Tae, forget the mate tea.
I think this was when I went to the arboretum.
What a waste of money.
(Yangpyeong, June 24)
Take a seat.
Joon Soo.
The reason why I took your bag is...
Let me explain.
You'll understand when I explain.
The person...
that sent my mum a note to run away from the arboretum...
was me.
Joon Soo.
Had she been there for three minutes longer,
Lawyer Ahn would have found out.
Dan Tae? He was at the arboretum?
He's been...
looking for Joon Pyo under Grandmother's orders.
If he found out,
you and Mum...
would have been proven as Joon Pyo's kidnappers.
So...
don't bother making an excuse or think about lying to me.
Just answer my questions.
25 years ago,
did you and Mum...
really kidnap...
Joon Pyo?
Answer me.
If you don't,
I'll go to the police.
Joon Soo.
Was it really...
the two of you?
Yes.
It's true.
Tell me.
How did it happen? Tell me from the beginning.
We never intended on kidnapping him from the start.
I was being chased by my debt, so my life was at stake.
Since Joon Pyo's family is rich,
I wanted to make money off of them and then return him.
But it didn't go as planned.
I asked an army friend to keep Joon Pyo for me...
until I got the money,
but he ended up losing him.
This is the truth.
I was going to take the money,
and then return him afterwards.
There were three cases of traffic law violations...
on June 24.
Two of them were parking tickets during lunch hours,
and the other was your speeding ticket.
There are only three from that day.
Thank you, Ms Kim.
Why did you need that for?
Do you know that people are calling you the grim reaper?
Can I come join you in handing out the notices...
if I wear all black?
I think you look cool.
Bye.
No one was speeding on their way to the arboretum.
Do you really have no idea...
where Joon Pyo is?
I don't.
I really don't know.
It's already been 26 years.
How could I know?
What about Mum?
Your mum?
Her only crime is for keeping her mouth shut...
although she saw me take Joon Pyo away.
It was all me from the start.
I'm her only sibling.
She couldn't report me to the police.
I'm going to protect my mum.
I'll become a criminal if I have to.
In order to protect her,
I'll lie and deceive others.
But...
that doesn't mean that I forgive either of you.
Joon Soo.
I'll protect my mum.
Don't tell her...
that I know.
Open it.
Okay.
Did they used to belong to me?
Yes.
Take your time.
See if you remember them.
I'm not sure.
I see.
Why didn't you throw these out?
How can I?
I still have all of your clothes and shoes.
I think we found each other again...
because of your sincerity.
It's all thanks to...
your great parents who raised you.
Is your father still unconscious?
Yes. He's still unconscious.
I wish he'd wake up soon.
I'd like to visit him at the hospital.
Sure, Grandmother.
Eat before you go.
- I don't think I should.
-  It's okay.
You should try and look around the house.
Maybe you'll remember something.
Let's go.
Okay.
- Are you finished?
-  Yes.
You should eat, Mother.
- Ms Jo, Mother's ready to eat.
-  Yes, Ma'am.
Secretary Ahn, you should join us.
Yes, Ma'am.
Come.
I wonder if we'll have eggplants today.
Why did Joon Soo get a speeding ticket?
What's in Yangpyeong anyway?
Yangpyeong?
Hello. You're here again.
Yes. Hello.
Mum, come have dinner.
No, thank you. I snacked on too much at the community centre.
Tell Ms Jo to bring me a cold sikhye to Joon Soo's room.
I'll leave this in his room and take a break.
My goodness, Mum.
All right.
I'll take her the sikhye.
Wait, hold on.
Yes. That's good.
I got it.
One more.
I'll win.
- I brought your sikhye, Ma'am.
-  You scared me.
Why did you scare me like that?
Why are you playing such a fun game in secret?
They hate it when I play this game. They think it's inelegant.
I have to avoid my sister-in-law and my daughter-in-law.
That's why I hide in Joon Soo's room to play it.
Do you want me to play with you?
You have the cards, right?
Gosh, you know how to play it?
Hold on. Stay right here.
- Yes, Ma'am.
-  My goodness.
(Seok Joon Soo)
June 24...
at Yangpyeong, Dokbawi Road.
I was caught at the same spot, too.
This is near the Arboretum.
Why was he there that day?
Mr Ahn.
Mr Ahn, come this way.
All right.
- Here we go.
-  Okay.
- Let me mix it up.
-  Sure.
When I first saw you, I liked you from the start.
- Pick a card.
-  Okay.
Wow.
Gosh, I got you.
- I'm not going to go easy on you.
-  Okay.
All right.
Sorry I'm late.
I missed my bus.
I just got here, too.
Didn't you say you're busy today?
No.
I wanted to get some fresh air while I had you on the phone.
It's already making me feel better.
By the way, thank you for the tickets.
I'm so thankful.
Since you're here, do you want to...
go with me?
Actually...
You must have a lot on your mind.
It'll make you feel better.
Okay.
Let's go together.
(From Paris to New York)
Hold on.
- What's wrong?
-  I'm so nervous.
I think it'll be awesome to see these in person. My gosh.
Do you like them that much?
Yes. I love them.
I'm ready.
Let's go.
You go ahead.
Director Seok.
This is my favourite drawing.
I can't believe I'm looking at it right now.
It's all thanks to you.
Thank you.
No problem.
Director Seok, come here quickly.
Look at this.
These two look like they're going to school.
The one in the back looks like you,
and the one eating at the front looks like Dan Tae.
It's funny.
Don't you think so?
I guess so.
"You can't live your life..."
"without knowing what happiness means."
What does that mean?
You smiled for the first time today.
I think it's true. You really can't live life...
without knowing what happiness means.
He must mean that we should enjoy life.
I guess so.
Can you give us two double meat sandwiches?
Sure.
Here you go.
Thank you.
I lost track of time.
We looked at the exhibition for too long.
You must be hungry.
I put in extra chicken,
so you have to finish it all.
I wanted to buy dinner.
No, I can't let you do that.
You showed me the exhibition already.
Thank you.
I'm so thankful to you for today.
I really wanted to see that exhibition.
I'm glad.
Director Seok. Is there something bothering you?
Can you tell?
What is it?
I'm scared I might not be able to eat all this.
I'm just kidding.
Director Seok.
It's not funny.
I'm serious.
All right, just eat.
It's Dan Tae.
Do you want to come and say hi to him?
Hold on, Shim.
I have something to tell you.
What?
Those exhibition tickets...
weren't actually from me.
What do you mean?
I didn't even get to give you the tickets I got.
I wanted to see it with you,
so I lied.
Then are you saying...
I think they're from Dan Tae.
I'll talk to him...
and apologise.
I'm sorry,
but could you let us talk in private?
Sure.
I'll get going then.
I'm sorry. I only have one beer.
I'm coming back from the exhibition with Shim.
I see.
I'm sorry.
We went to the exhibition...
with the tickets from you.
She thought...
they were from me.
I was mad...
that you beat me to it.
I was also scared of losing her.
That's why I lied.
No matter the reason,
I know it was wrong.
I'm really sorry.
I'm embarrassed about what I've done,
but I don't regret it.
That's how strong my feelings are for Shim.
I'll get going.
Dan Tae.
I...
went to the exhibition with Director Seok...
with the tickets you gave me.
I heard.
You did?
Is that all you have to say to me?
If you gave the tickets to me directly,
there wouldn't have been any misunderstandings.
You're the one who got me the pain relievers too, aren't you?
What's wrong with you?
If you're going to act like this, just leave me alone.
I'll just handle my feelings on my own.
Just because I smile a lot,
it doesn't mean it's not hard for me.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I'm making it hard on you.
I'm sorry I can't say anything...
to help you.
I'm sorry that...
this is all I can do right now.
Dan Tae.
Let me ask you three questions.
Are you...
suffering from a terminal illness? Will your life end shortly?
What?
You're not.
Then...
did your first love come back or something?
Is that why you're not accepting my feelings?
Are you busy comparing me and her?
Pardon?
That's not the case, either. Then...
are you in debt?
Are lone sharks after you or something?
What are you talking about, Shim?
I'm relieved.
It's because of last night.
Although you apologised, you said you couldn't tell me why.
I...
don't know what's going on with you, Dan Tae.
But if it's not any of the three things that I just mentioned,
then I decided that I'll be okay.
So I'll wait until you're done with whatever it is...
that you're going through right now.
But that doesn't mean I'm easy.
What?
I admit that even after getting rejected by you,
I did kind of portray myself as an easy woman...
by...
telling you that I still like you straightforwardly.
But I'm saying that I'm not, so keep that in mind.
All right. I will.
I'll get a job again, soon.
Then new hairs will grow at the bald spot on my head.
I'll become prettier, so don't feel relieved about anything.
Okay, I won't.
Okay. You should go to work now.
See you.
Shim.
Are you all right?
Stand up.
Are you okay?
Father.
Dan Tae, you're here.
Yes.
When will he wake up?
He'll wake up, right?
Yes, he will.
The doctor said there's hope.
Yes, he'll wake up.
By the way, I received a call from the arboretum...
to pick up your father's luggage.
All right. I'll go there.
Okay.
(Blue Sky Arboretum)
Excuse me.
Hello. How can I help you?
I'm here to pick up the luggage which belongs to Mr Ahn Soo Yong.
He worked here until recently.
Please wait a moment. Our staff is on his way here with it.
Is that so? Okay.
Excuse me. By any chance,
have you met this man recently...
at this arboretum?
No, I don't think so.
- Have you seen him before?
-  No, I haven't.
Me neither.
Really?
I see. Thank you.
- There he is.
-  Here you go.
- Thank you.
-  You're welcome.
Excuse me, I have a question.
Sir, have you seen this man...
at the arboretum recently?
Hey, it's that young man.
Do you know him?
Have you seen him before?
Of course. He asked me to deliver...
a small note to a lady standing next to the pond, so I did.
He paid me heavily for such a small favour.
I clearly remember him.
Okay, I see. Thank you.
You're welcome.
Is this yours?
Yes, it is.
Is Ms Nam Soon Cheon registered in your database?
Yes. We have Ms Nam Soon Cheon registered here.
Can you identify the blood relationship with this?
Yes, we can.
Here's the application form.
The name is Shim Young Cheol.
It's you, right?
Yes.
(Pretty Ugly)
(Here come's the second outtake clip.)
(This is how you should sing, okay?)
(He keeps laughing.)
(Applauding)
(Dan Tae finds it really delicious.)
You should eat it later.
(It's really hot.)
(Dan Tae falls down because the soup is too tasty.)
Are you okay?
(I'm glad you didn't get hurt, Dan Tae.)
(Stuttering)
Before he gets too close to...
Okay? No, don't laugh.
(Shim throws him to the bed.)
Wait.
Don't laugh before I say my line.
(It's too funny.)
I didn't do it. I didn't.
(Laughing)
Dinner... Gosh.
I'll buy you dinner.
(She acts cute after making a mistake.)
(Do you want some ssam?)
(Yes, I want to eat this ssam and more ssam.)
Sorry for laughing.
Don't laugh. Don't laugh. Just don't laugh!
(Shim, you should stop laughing first.)
(That ssam is about to fall out.)
(Let's go, Pretty Ugly!)