(Episode 2)
(Law Firm)
Guleum Law Firm.
This is it.
- Thank you, Lawyer.
-  Thank you.
You're welcome.
A lawyer?
He's a lawyer?
Please, this way.
Hey, you guys can go ahead.
- I'll have double portions.
-  Yes, Sir.
Are you my stalker?
You snuck into my room last night...
and you just showed up in front of my office today.
Do you enjoy peeping?
Pervert. I knew he was a pervert.
What brings you here?
Do you happen to be...
a perverter?
A perverter?
I have never in my entire life heard such nonsense.
What does a perverter do?
No, it was just a slip of tongue.
So a perverter...
A perverter...
Oh, I got it.
He must be a pervert with a license.
You go to a private institution...
and pass an exam to become a pervert.
Then you'd say, "I'm a perverter."
It's not even funny.
Right. I thought so, too.
Did you need a lawyer?
I was just passing by.
Are you out of your mind?
It was a bird dropping.
It would have landed on top of your head if it weren't for me.
There are a lot of birds around because there's a mountain nearby.
By the way, do I have to give up my jajangmyeon?
Let's go inside.
Excuse me.
- It's fine.
-  Why?
I thought you needed free counselling.
I'm well aware of your situation.
You don't have money because you paid your rent upfront.
Is it really okay to trust that man?
Okay, that's enough.
Please delete the original copy of the recording until this part.
I get that you are lawyer but to delete the original copy,
I'll need a consent from the victim.
They've already successfully negotiated.
What? Negotiate?
Do you know how angry and upset Shim was?
Shim and I are sisters.
What?
How could you be so different from her?
This is our family relations certificate.
(Family Relations Certificate)
You really are her sister.
Did anyone come to make a copy of the footages?
No one made copies...
except Shim. She stored a copy in her mobile phone.
Gosh, Gong Shim.
I work part-time at a gas station.
Two days ago, I was assaulted by a customer.
Are you sure you didn't fight with her?
From what I've seen up until now,
you look more like an attacker than a victim.
I'm just kidding.
I was just trying to be objective about the case.
Please write your personal information,
the date of the incident and the place over here.
She's our judicial officer.
Hello, my name is Gong Shim.
Hello, I'm Chun Ji Won.
So you want to sue that lady?
Yes.
Do you have a proof of the assault?
We have a surveillance camera at the gas station.
I already made a copy of it.
Did you? Where is it? Let me see.
Goodness.
I don't want to look at it.
(Gong Mi)
You got a call from your sister.
Yes, it's me.
Do you want me to end up dead?
Where are you right now?
Why?
Why did you call?
- Dan Tae,
-  Yes?
- do you know her?
-  Yes.
We live in the same house.
Do... Do you live together?
Don't worry.
I won't get married until you do.
Don't mess with me.
What do you mean you're leaving?
Is this a threat to keep me from suing her?
If you sue President Song's wife,
I have to resign.
I won't be able to open up my own firm in Korea.
I should study for my bar exam if I want to work in the US.
I won't be able to bring home any money.
Okay.
I'll work hard and earn enough...
to support our parents. Happy?
People are staring. What are you doing?
Shim, I'm sorry.
I'll apologise on her behalf.
Can't you forgive her?
Everyone is looking at us. Stop it.
Get up right now.
I know I haven't been good to you.
I know I've hurt you, too.
But...
I worked so hard to become a lawyer.
You know that.
Mum and Dad are torn, too.
I know you want to sue her.
Can't you help me out just this once?
No, do it for Mum and Dad.
Help me out.
Do you think I would have enjoyed...
seeing you get assaulted?
I'm mad and upset, too.
But what can I do?
I'm not strong enough yet.
You can do it to me.
Vent at me if you need to.
Would that be too much to ask?
I'm sorry, Shim.
I'm a pathetic big sister to say such a thing.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
Where did she go?
Maybe she ran away because she couldn't trust you.
Try calling her.
I don't want to.
She hurt my pride.
I even gave up my jajangmyeon for her.
(Your video will be deleted.)
I know it was a hard decision to make. Thank you.
This doesn't mean I forgive her.
I know.
I'm busy, so I have to go.
See you at home.
I'll be going.
President Song, it's finished.
The girl agreed on dropping the charges...
and will forget what happened.
Are you serious?
You're sure, right?
Yes.
Yes, Sir.
I hope I made the right decision.
If I sacrifice myself, it's better for everyone.
I'm used to it anyway.
The bus card is here.
Where is my bell?
I told you to turn around!
You're the one at fault here. Why are you yelling at me?
Oh, no.
You scared me.
I just caught you breaking and entering.
I didn't go inside yet.
Then it's attempted breaking and entering.
I was wondering where you ran off to, and you were here.
Are you trying to break and enter empty houses?
I came to look for my belongings.
Why didn't you change your password?
It's my password to change or not.
That's not the problem. Why are you looking for your stuff at my place?
I dropped it here yesterday.
Listen.
You sneaked in at night and came under the sheets.
During the day, you showed up in front of my office,
then you tried to break and enter. How many crimes will you commit?
Come on. You left midway during the legal advice and didn't call.
I won't sue. I won't do anything.
What?
Did you get a settlement?
Already?
Why would I?
That would mean that I forgave her.
I will never forgive that woman.
The you should sue her and press charges.
You don't make any sense.
Yes, I know. But I'm still not going to sue.
Got it?
I've seen people change their minds a million times.
So just send me the video in your phone.
I'll attach it as evidence.
- I already deleted it.
-  What?
I'm really not going to sue. Let's not talk about it again.
- Goodness.
-  I'm sorry for barging in.
I was going to take my stuff and leave quietly.
Will you grab my stuff for me?
I have to go.
Okay, I'll look for it.
Hello, Sir.
Hello.
You have a female staff with hair...
that looks like this, right?
- Gong Shim?
-  Yes, her.
What about her?
As you know, she recently had someone assault her.
I'm just curious why she would suddenly drop the charges.
Who are you and why are you asking?
I'm a close friend of Shim's.
Here.
Right. You'll believe me if I show you a picture, right?
Her big sister came in and told me that they found an agreement.
Is that so?
Why would I?
That would mean that I forgave her.
I will never forgive that woman.
Could I take a look at the security footage?
Since it was settled, I deleted it when Shim's sister was here.
All right.
Have a good night.
Okay.
- Welcome.
-  Hello.
What are you doing?
There are a lot of security cameras. How fascinating.
Is the new lunchbox in?
Shim.
Why did you drop the charges? I was upset just watching it.
It just turned out that way.
Some guy came earlier...
and asked me why you dropped it.
Some guy?
He told me he's a close friend.
Was he wearing capri pants with flip-flops?
I think so.
He went into that convenience store.
Why is he running around poking at everything?
Goodness.
I'm just curious about where your cameras are.
Where are they located?
Are you looking for a camera that looks towards the gas station?
How did you know?
Some woman came by today and asked me.
But...
we don't have any cameras that look that way.
Why is she angry again?
What are you doing here?
I hear you're asking people why I dropped the charges.
I only asked since I was passing by.
I already told you that I'm not going to sue.
You did.
Then why are you asking around? What do you want me to do?
I was just passing by, that's all. Am I really at wrong here?
Let me repeat myself.
This is already done with,
so don't get into my business.
All right.
Also, please don't mention this incident again. Okay?
Okay.
"Please don't mention this incident again."
"Okay?"
- Lawyer Gong.
-  Yes, Sir.
Have you heard of the television show "Big Match"?
Yes. I've heard of it.
Of course, everyone knows "Big Match".
Why don't you appear on the show as the programme's panel?
You should start showing yourself on media now.
Isn't Lawyer Choi on the show already?
A new face might do well for our law firm.
I already informed the producer.
You'll appear in it starting with the next episode.
All right. Let's raise our glasses...
for the new star, Gong Mi.
- Cheers!
-  Cheers!
I'm so mad.
Stop drinking and go home.
We already had three rounds. You had makgeolli, soju and beer.
My dear elementary friend and best friend, Goo Nam.
I have a favour to ask. Will you do it for me?
Go ahead.
Stop yapping and just sit there...
like an invisible person, will you?
Hey, don't you feel like someone's staring at us?
Who?
Don't look at him.
Who is it?
It's the perverted lawyer you introduced to me!
I see.
I don't feel like drinking any more.
I'm going home.
Good idea. Just forget about it and go to bed.
You always feel better after you sleep.
I hate that even more.
I'm going.
- Bye.
-  Bye.
Hello.
I'm Soo Cheol's friend.
- Bang Soo Cheol.
-  Bang...
Oh, him.
The one that was framed for a motorcycle hit-and-run?
Yes. I recommended you...
to Shim after hearing the story from Soo Cheol.
I see.
Can I ask you something?
Yes, go ahead.
Do you know why...
she suddenly gave up pressing charges?
What happened is...
Shim really wanted to sue her.
But the woman who hit her...
is the president's wife of the law firm her big sister works at.
It's obvious.
She decided to give up because of her sister.
- Have this.
-  That's okay.
It's okay.
It's one plus one.
This one is free.
If she's going to keep this up, she should at least lower my rent.
Hey.
Hey, Shim.
Hello? Get up.
Hey, Shim. Get up.
This girl...
Shim...
My goodness.
Was she going to brush her teeth with this?
She ate the soap.
I can't hold it in any more!
She's a crazy woman!
I didn't change my password because I was lazy, but this is annoying.
I better change it.
They told me it could be up to 20 digits.
7, 8, 0, 3, 1, 2,
9, 8, 7, 2, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
There.
She'll never find this one out.
What... What was it again?
Why would you crawl back in here after what happened last time?
Are you crazy? Are you?
But why isn't he changing the password?
What's wrong with him?
Gosh...
She must have woken up.
It's so cold.
Oh, gosh.
7, 3, 8, 0, 3,
1, 2, 9, 8, 7...
Mum...
(Hyundae Photo Studio)
Mum!
Mum...
(Hyundae Photo Studio)
Who is that kid?
Why does he keep appearing in my dreams?
Forget seaweed soup for his birthday.
But he has to skip breakfast?
I feel sorry for you.
I'm okay. Calm down.
I lost both my daughter-in-law and my eldest grandson today.
So what's there to celebrate? How can I eat a meal today?
Even eating making me feel guilty.
Are you going to the temple in Cheonan?
It's April 22.
My daughter-in-law died...
and Joon Pyo disappeared this day.
I always visited the temple on this day of the year.
I must go down and pray...
for Joon Pyo to come back.
All right. I hope you have a safe trip.
I've heard that you've been preparing and having...
an event to celebrate Joon Soo's birthday since several years ago.
It's not a celebration event. I'm holding a charity bazaar.
I'm holding a charity bazaar to help poor people.
You might be late if you don't leave now. Let's hurry.
Joon Soo, I know you must feel disappointed.
But mourn for your missing brother and hold your laughter for today.
Yes.
It's not Joon Soo's fault. When will she stop talking about Joon Pyo?
You won't be standing in this house if Joon Pyo hadn't gone missing!
How dare you talk like that?
Can you stop mentioning Joon Pyo and make us feel bad?
You don't even know whether he's alive or dead yet.
Mother.
I'm sick of the name, Joon Pyo. I'd like to see if he's alive.
Do you think you can recognise him even if you see him now?
It's been 30 years already. Consider him gone.
He can't be dead!
Stop talking thoughtlessly! You wretch.
- Stop, please. Let's go up.
-  Whatever.
- Let's leave.
-  Goodness!
Let's go.
My goodness.
Everyone in this house makes me feel uncomfortable.
You should relax your mind.
Are you the driver Joon Soo mentioned about?
Yes, it must be me. Nice to meet you.
Granny, you seem uncomfortable. Should I slow down?
Granny?
You're friendly.
I'm not in a hurry.
All right.
My wife wants...
to thank you.
Pardon?
She wants to go with you to a bazaar held by millionaires' wives.
I don't think I'm suitable to attend such an event.
There's no harm in attending it. It's a meeting of high societies.
My wife is on her way here, so get ready.
She will be here in an hour or two.
Okay, Sir.
I'm not dressed well today.
Good morning.
Good evening.
Good night.
- Hello.
-  Hello.
Hello.
- Hello.
-  Move aside.
Hello. Hello.
Please bring these to your sister.
I have to go to the academy.
You can go there right after. Hurry. Your sister needs them.
Tell her I have an upset stomach.
Mum! Mum!
Gosh!
Why aren't you here, Mum? I'm waiting outside.
What? Shim's coming here?
How could you think of sending her?
What were you thinking? What if people in the office see her?
Gosh, I can't believe this.
When did she leave?
Okay. I'd better hang up now.
Seriously.
It's you.
Get in.
Okay, Sir.
My wife arrived early and called me to come down.
Is your wife in front of the building?
Yes.
I must introduce you to each other.
You could go straight to the bazaar together.
Yes, Sir.
(You must pretend...)
You must pretend we don't know each other. Hide.
- What is she saying?
-  Honey.
You're early. Say hello.
This is my beloved wife.
This is Lawyer Gong Mi.
Hello.
My name is Gong Mi. Glad to see you.
Nice to see you, Lawyer Gong.
Thank you for your recent work. Well done.
What?
Who do you think I am to talk back?
My pleasure, Ma'am. Thank you.
The rumours are true. You are very beautiful.
Thank you.
- Honey, we'd better leave now.
-  All right.
Have a good time.
Yes. Thank you.
Let's go.
Gong Mi.
I didn't know that...
you had to fawn over a woman like her.
I pity you.
This bazaar held by the madam of Star Group is a top-class event.
Madams and their children from political...
and financial circles attend.
That apron is the invitation card.
You must wear it before you enter.
Thank you.
- You're here.
-  Hello.
(Charity Bazaar for Those in Need)
- Hello.
-  Come in.
Bye.
Take care.
Welcome, Ma'am.
She's the madam of Gyosin Group.
Yes, I know. How are you, Ma'am?
You're becoming more handsome by the day.
Thank you.
Lawyer Gong. Say hello.
This is my daughter.
Hello.
She kept saying that she's not coming...
but eventually came without telling me.
I didn't know the son of Star Group was coming.
He's really as handsome as the rumours say.
Look at you.
We came here together, but I'm sorry.
No, Ma'am. It's fine.
You must give that back.
Pardon?
That apron is the invitation card, remember?
Yes. I see.
Here you are.
I'm sorry, Lawyer Gong.
I'll call you next time.
- Yes, Ma'am.
-  All right, then.
Hello.
- Welcome.
-  Good to see you.
This is my son.
- Nice to meet you.
-  Please, go in.
Okay. Thank you.
Haven't they heard the rumours about you?
You're handsome, of course.
Of course, you are.
Thank you for your work today.
You're welcome. Stay healthy. I'll be going now.
Hello.
Sorry?
We met at the hospital and here last time.
I see.
Hello.
I recognised you at once.
How can you forget that style?
It's impossible to forget her.
This is Seok Joon Soo. We happened to be friends.
And this is...
Gong Shim who happened to be my neighbour.
Gong Shim,
I like your hair style.
Excuse me?
I don't think that was a compliment. Don't be flattered.
I meant it.
You look cute in that hair style. I really mean it.
I got to go. Please excuse me.
She is walking fast.
She is.
Why am I smiling?
Wake up, Gong Shim.
I thought I should pay for your ride.
I will pass this time.
You worked for me. I want to pay for that.
I don't feel like taking that.
Please take it back. How about buying me some drink next time?
Here.
Wasn't it hard to take care of...
- my grandmother? She can be picky.
-  Not really.
She told me some of her experiences during Korean War.
She has a sense of humour.
Did she really?
Yes.
The story about her eating...
watermelon shells out of starvation when she was evacuating.
It was an interesting story.
Thank you for your work again.
It's dangerous to drive at night.
- How about driving during the day?
-  What?
Why don't you work for our company?
I'm asking you a favour.
Driving for a chauffeur service at night is...
not exactly my job.
It's my part-time job.
I have another job during the day.
I'm a lawyer.
Fine. But I'm still asking you to join my company.
Everything will be better than now.
(Guleum Law Firm Lawyer Ahn Dan Tae)
I apologise for saying that.
I'm truly sorry. I didn't know you have your own firm.
Don't worry about it. It's nothing special to have a firm anyway.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
Then, I wouldn't have made such mistakes.
Working as a chauffeur is...
nothing to brag about. I didn't tell anyone about that.
I can't afford my living expenses only working as a lawyer.
I want to make it up to you.
I think...
this mistake will haunt me every night.
Then let me invite you to my penthouse sometime.
Promise me.
Okay.
Here.
It has been my pleasure working with you.
You have worked hard for us too.
Stop by whenever you want.
- Okay.
-  Keep in touch.
I will.
Hello.
I've never seen a tteokbokki truck in this area.
I didn't see this truck during the day.
I don't work here during the day.
I came here to sell tteokbokki to students who study nearby.
So I wait until their tutoring is over. It's open from 6 to 10.
And from ten to early in the morning,
I take my truck to subway stations.
Are you serious?
I warned you not to come near the gas station.
I'm not going to sue anyone, okay?
Please stop asking around about that assault.
What did I do? Look. I'm just having fish cakes.
Is this the only truck that sells fish cakes?
Try some. This part.
It's another level of fish cake.
I'm warning you.
Stop what you are doing.
"I'm warning you."
"Stop what you are doing."
Hello.
You need to get a document from the Labour Administration.
Yes.
You need a document about the arrear of your valuables.
It is for proving that you haven't been paid.
Get that document.
Then I can help you with your lawsuit.
No worries. You don't have to pay me.
You can pay for the revenue stamps...
and the transmittal fee.
These look like my flower leaves.
What is he doing?
If you get paid your overdue wages,
buy me some soju.
Okay. Good night.
What are you doing to my flowers?
You scared me.
I didn't hear you. What did you say?
My flowers...
Where are the leaves?
Why did you do that?
I'm sorry. When I need to focus on something,
I have a habit of tearing papers.
I'm sorry.
I have a habit of pulling someone's hair when I'm angry.
Oh, goodness. What are you doing?
Watch my hair!
Let me go!
It hurts! You are pulling all of my hair out!
You deserve it.
Why did you do that to my flowers?
Are you out of your mind?
They'll grow back. Water them!
Your hair will grow back too.
Stop it!
My hair won't grow back. Let me go.
Oh, dear. Are you okay?
Pervert.
You're getting on my nerves.
It's you who's getting on my nerves.
Where were you yesterday afternoon?
I couldn't reach you.
Why was the secretary's room empty?
About that...
We are in the process of hiring new employees for the office.
So the office is empty these days.
Secretary room can't be empty.
We are hiring new people today.
Let me interview for female applicants myself.
Why do you need to get involved?
Didn't you know?
He was having an affair with his secretary last time.
Shame on you.
Like father, like son.
It runs in his family.
What did you just say?
I'll take care of the interview for the secretary position today.
I mean it.
This is too boxy.
Do they interview for the cashier position of department stores?
You are not even on the brand floor.
You're applying for a position of a small stand.
It's a temporary position. But after a year, they will...
give me a permanent position.
That's what they say.
They don't even take my specifications seriously.
All they want is my passion about this work.
That's what they all say.
I don't think my clothes fit you.
These are too fancy on you.
Let's choose outfits that are quite practical,
to make you look like a hard worker.
Do you think so?
Yes. Wear your own clothes.
It will grow back once I get a job, right?
I will see you later.
Okay.
You are going to be on TV the day after tomorrow, right?
I'll find out after the meeting at the studio today.
I'll call you after the meeting.
Okay. Let us know as soon as it's confirmed.
I'm going to tell everyone about this.
We're going to be rich too.
Your manager supports you well.
Not really.
It's me who need to work hard.
Look at you, Gong Shim.
You already look like a cashier.
You will get this job. I guarantee.
That outfit is just perfect.
The interviewers will love you.
Do I look like a hard worker?
- Totally.
-  Totally.
Oh, no.
She must be Gong Shim's sister.
I can sell sand on a desert...
and ice on the North Pole. I'm very determined.
Sand and desert.
Ice and the North Pole.
I can sell any products. I will work very passionately.
With all my passion,
I will work with sincere care for my customers.
What are you doing in front of my car?
Hello, ma'am.
You know Gong Shim, right?
The girl you assaulted at a gas station last time.
What do you want?
She deserves an apology.
That's what I want.
Do you have any evidence of my assault?
Can you prove it? I'm willing to see the evidence.
It's in your conscience.
Please make an apology.
Conscience? Is this a joke?
You can't even prove what you are insisting.
Wait. You know the fish cake truck in front of the gas station, right?
Their fish cakes are so good.
Why did I pull my cell phone out of my pocket? I can't remember.
I learned how to play golf when I was in the States.
I'm a 10-handicapper.
You're good.
I might need more handicaps to play with you.
Yes. Sometimes, I score pretty high.
(Highly willing to hire the applicant.)
(Not willing to hire the applicant at all.)
Thank you.
This can't be real.
(Grow with Star Group)
- Hello.
-  Hi, there.
- What brings you here?
-  I'm here for a job interview.
I'm late though.
You have a job interview here? Go to floor 15. Follow me.
Help her to the floor 15.
She's late. Take her to the elevator for the board members.
Good luck with your interview.
Thank you.
(Interview Room)
Hello. It is my passion that led me up here.
My name is Gong Shim. Nice to meet you.
Is Ms Gong Shim here?
Number 132, Ms Gong Shim. Are you here?
Excuse me.
The interview is over.
Please follow me.
Forgive me.
It is truly my fault that I'm late.
But this is an opportunity of my life.
Could you please spare some of your time for me?
I will prove my passion for this job position!
Please follow me.
Hold on.
She managed to apply for this job position.
I will let you introduce yourself.
What are you doing? We're busy people.
I can sell any products with my passion.
I can sell sand on a desert, and...
I can sell ice on the North Pole. That's how determined I am.
For whatever products I might be in charge of,
I will sell them with all my care and love for my customers.
Secretaries don't sell products.
Secretaries sell smiles with pretty faces, okay?
I don't see any smiles on you though.
A secretary?
(Job Interview for Star Group President's Secretary)
I apologise.
I didn't know this room was for secretary position job interview.
I apologise for my mistake.
I thought so. This is not your floor.
If you aimed for the secretary position looking like that,
you must be out of your mind.
I'm sorry, but let me tell you this before I leave.
Is it fun to make fun of other people's looks?
You're not living in Chosun Dynasty. Secretaries are not gisaeng.
Your minds are so out dated.
That's why people make fun of old men like you these days.
Can you even get what I'm saying?
People compare men like you to a dog.
Behave yourself!
Yes, men like you start yelling once they have nothing to say.
Don't do that. You are embarrassing your kids.
If you don't understand what I'm saying, memorise it.
Remember how people call men like you. A dog!
Sorry for making a fuss.
Please forgive me.
Where are you going? She is driving me nuts.
Calm down.
She is crazy. Why did you provoke her?
I shouldn't have planted flower seeds.
What I should have planted were poisonous plant seeds.
Hello, Manager.
What? At the gas station?
She has been waiting for you. Talk to her.
Come on.
What do you want?
I'm here to apologise...
for what I did to you last time.
I'm truly sorry for...
what I did to you.
I made a huge mistake.
I admit my assault.
Please forgive me.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry...
No.
It's fine.
I just apologised to Gong Shim.
You did the right thing.
I'll erase the recording.
(Delete one video file.)
By the way,
where did you get the video file?
This is...
the black box footage of a fish cake truck.
It parks in front of the gas station every day.
The incident was recorded in the black box of that truck.
I already deleted the original copy.
So don't worry too much.
Take care, Ma'am.
Did something good happen today?
You scared me.
You are humming. Is there something to celebrate?
Well, I guess a bit.
Good for you then.
Be careful. This is a poisonous plant.
You'll die if you eat this.
I put a red ribbon on it.
I'm going to use it when I need it.
Why would you ever...
need a poisonous plant?
If you grill samgyeopsal, people will complain about the smoke.
I'll just grill some sausages, so there won't be much smoke.
Do you like sausages?
Not really. I prefer sundae.
I prepared this because Seok Joon Soo said he'd come.
Would this be too much for us two?
Seok Joon Soo?
I forgot to buy vegetables.
Do you happen to have any vegetables?
Of course, I do.
That's great. Bring them here and let's each together.
I have too many sausages anyway.
Why would I join you?
Why not? It's not like we're strangers.
You are going to have dinner anyway.
Maybe, I will.
Gong Shim,
I like your hair.
Pardon?
It's cute, really.
(Seok Joon Soo)
(Seok Joon Soo, Entrepreneur)
(Interview of Seok Joon Soo, an Outstanding Entrepreneur)
How can I get up there?
That way. There are stairs over there.
Right, that way.
Wow.
This penthouse has such a great view.
But if you live in a place like this,
your outlook of life won't be so great.
It's clear and nice.
Have a seat.
Please enjoy as if it's your house.
By the way, is someone joining us?
Hello.
You said you live downstairs.
By the way, we already met at the company earlier.
How was your interview?
Did you interview for his company?
- Yes.
-  Goodness.
I can see that you messed up the interview.
You must have failed.
You're right. I failed.
Are you satisfied?
I'm sure you did fine.
I'm 100 percent sure I failed.
Pigs may fly if I get accepted.
There's no such thing as 100 percent fail.
We all have possibilities.
I'm really confident...
that I failed.
She says she's really confident.
Hold on. Let me find out.
By the way,
- what was your name again?
-  Khong Shim.
Khong Shim
Gong Shim.
It's Gong Shim.
Yes, Gong Shim.
Please, don't. I really did fail.
I'll find out first.
What? What's wrong with you?
Like this, like this...
Whatever.
Did you just do your hair?
What are you talking about?
The ends of your wig are curled up.
Why are you doing this?
Don't you dare talk about my wig.
There's nothing on the grill.
I better grill some sausages.
Congratulations, Gong Shim.
You've been admitted to the president's secretary office.
What? I'm admitted?
To the president's secretary office?
Yes.
They said you passed.
What?
Is she going to be your father's secretary?
"Your father's secretary"?
What? Your father?
Is the president your father?
Oh, you didn't know?
Joon Soo was born with a silver spoon in his mouth.
Stop it.
People say looks aren't everything.
You must be very outstanding.
You've been hired on your first try.
This can't be.
I can't believe this.
This doesn't make any sense.
I just talked to the director of HR department.
It's for sure.
I'm impressed.
Congratulations.
Me, too.
Let's sit down.
Let's make a toast for our outstanding personnel, Gong Shim.
All right.
Cheers!
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Wow, this is cold. It's nice.
Father.
(Pretty Ugly)
I can withstand no matter what.
You are my boss. You can treat me however you'd like.
You can't do that to a friend.
- Tell me if you need any help.
-  You are deeply in love.
Don't you dare say anything to Joon Soo.
It's very obvious.
Gong Shim!
I can't find you, Gong Shim!
Gong Shim.
Gong Shim...