(Episode 09)
So please don't go to Jeju Island.
If you leave,
I don't know how I'll cope.
Don't think too hard.
And tomorrow,
tell me that you won't leave.
Did you finish packing?
What time is your flight again?
I feel sad about letting you go, so I keep forgetting.
I packed everything.
My flight is at 3pm tomorrow.
I made some of your favourite side dishes.
- Take these with you tomorrow. - Okay.
I'm going to bed now.
Dad,
did you really kill Joon Pyo?
Hey, Dan Tae.
What happened yesterday?
Don't just look at me like that. Tell me what happened.
Give me an explanation or an excuse.
Shim.
You should go to Jeju Island.
What?
I think I was being too selfish.
Why are you always like this?
You told me not to go, and now you're telling me the opposite.
Do I look easy to you?
Do you think I'm someone you can fool around with?
Why are you doing this to me?
I guess I was a fool for...
not being able to sleep just by hearing what you said yesterday.
I'm sorry.
My flight is at 3pm today.
Let me ask you again.
Should I go...
or not?
You should go.
Director Seok? What made you come here?
I stopped by on my way somewhere.
Sorry?
I'm kidding. I came here to see you off.
I see.
I apologise for leaving so suddenly last time.
I'm the one who should've been more thoughtful.
I'm sorry.
Please don't be.
I will cheer for you until you become more brave.
Thank you.
Instead, you have to buy me a meal once you get your first pay check.
I will.
I'm going to eat expensive food, so be prepared.
You are greedy.
You should go now.
Okay.
Thank you.
(Jeju Horticulture Trade)
Hello, my name is Gong Shim.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Thank you for coming all the way to Jeju Island.
Welcome.
Nice to meet you.
I need to get going now.
If you have any questions, feel free to ask to our staff here.
Thank you for your work, everyone.
- See you. - Bye, Sir.
Here, June and July are the busiest months of the year.
Your job is to check the orders every morning.
Then check the quantity of the ordered products...
and confirm the placed order.
Okay, I got it.
You said you majored in Horticulture, right?
That's correct.
If you have any questions, don't hesitate to ask anything.
- Your hair. - Hair?
Thank you.
Is Lawyer Ahn Dan Tae here?
Excuse me, Ma'am.
It's time for him to visit me. What's going on?
Please take a look at this.
It is from Ahn Dan Tae.
From him?
Dear Chairman,
Forgive me for writing a letter instead of meeting you in person.
I don't think I can find Seok Joon Pyo any more.
I'm terribly sorry.
And I don't think I can ever meet you again, either.
Please stay healthy.
I apologise for my actions.
I'm so sorry.
From Ahn Dan Tae.
How many times did he say sorry in such a short letter?
(I'm terribly sorry.)
(Missing Child)
Dan Tae.
Did you stay here all night?
Yes, Aunt Ji Won.
By the way, the tree in Yangpyeong...
has been moved successfully to the arboretum.
You don't need to worry about it any more.
I see.
Hold on, Aunt Ji Won.
Has Dad ever contacted you?
Your dad?
No. Why?
I was just curious.
He never called me...
since he left for the Philippines.
That's how your father is like.
You're right.
Hey. Long time no see.
You always call me when you need help.
Sorry. It's urgent.
You're a lawyer, so you know I'm not supposed to tell you this, right?
Sorry.
There aren't any records of your father, Ahn Soo Yong,
leaving the country recently.
Is that so?
That means he's in Korea, right?
That's right.
That's right. Ahn Soo Yong was in the 20th class.
Yes.
I just miss him, that's all.
Please find him for me.
Okay.
I'll be waiting for your call.
Ahn Soo Yong is the man...
who lost Joon Pyo while taking care of him, right?
Yes.
I'm going to take care of this properly, so don't worry.
If things go wrong, we're dead.
I'm telling you. That won't happen.
My goodness.
Lawyer Ahn Dan Tae.
Ma'am.
Why are you so startled to see me?
Your face look so gaunt, too.
Is everything all right?
Yes, don't worry.
I'm really sorry.
Why do you keep saying that? Don't say that.
I don't know what to say.
Don't worry too much.
I knew it was going to be hard to find Joon Pyo.
It's not your fault, Dan Tae.
I came to tell you in person that you don't have to worry so much.
Okay.
Even when you're not looking for my Joon Pyo,
you are always welcome to visit me or call me.
Okay?
Okay.
I'm glad to hear that. I will go now.
Hello, Sir.
Secretary Gong?
I'll make some oolong tea for you.
Are you back?
I guess you're back.
Good.
Hello, Sir.
Wait. You're not her.
Oh, dear.
My goodness. I'm seeing things now.
Secretary Yoon.
Make me some heotgae tea.
Yes, Sir.
Please prepare 50 boxes to be delivered to Seoul.
Okay.
Why is Myung Ok absent today?
We're already busy as it is.
I can help you.
Thank you, Ms Gong.
I heard today's lunch is bibim guksu. I'm looking forward to it.
Do you like bibim guksu?
Bibim guksu?
Here.
I should stop thinking about him.
Do you not like bibim guksu?
I love bibim guksu.
I just have something in my ear.
Ahn Dan Tae?
Why am I hearing things?
What's going on?
Sir, please answer your phone.
I don't want to answer this one.
Don't worry about me, and get back to work.
When can I stop seeing this number?
It was his ring tone.
It startled me.
Ahn Dan Tae?
It's Ahn Dan Tae again.
What's going on?
Ms Gong.
It's lunch time.
Sorry?
When this song goes off, it means it's lunch time.
Why?
Our branch manager loves this song.
Let's go eat bibim guksu.
Andante, andante
- Andante, andante - Andante, andante
Ahn... Ahn Dan Tae.
It's not sweet.
Ahn Dan Tae?
I told you to add two spoons of sugar and cream in my coffee.
- I did. - Oh, it was about coffee.
Taste it.
- It's sweet. - I know, right?
- Yes. - It's not sweet.
Ms Gong Shim, please try this.
Okay.
Is it sweet or not?
Ahn Dan Tae.
- I mean, no, it's not sweet. - It's not, right?
I told you. This coffee is not sweet.
It's not?
- It is. - It is.
It's not sweet.
It's sweet.
It's not.
I planted a seed here.
It'll sprout tomorrow.
What did you plant?
I'm not going to tell you. If you're curious, look after it.
Hey.
You are a sunflower, aren't you?
I can already tell just by looking at you.
But...
when are you going to show me your face?
(Director Seok)
Hello?
Hi, Shim. How are you?
Great. How are you?
I'm good.
I'm at Dan Tae's place right now.
I see.
I haven't heard from him for more than a week. So I came here.
But he is not here.
His mails are still here, too.
I see.
Hearing from your voice,
I guess he didn't call you, either.
No, he hasn't called me.
I see.
I was worried about him.
Do you really not know what's going on with him?
I really don't know anything.
Maybe you'll find him if you go to his office.
A while ago, I dropped by his office,
but I couldn't find him there. His staff was worried, too.
I see.
Are you sure you're doing okay there?
Of course.
All right.
Let's keep in touch.
Okay. Bye.
Stop it.
Don't do that.
(Pervert Lawyer)
They were sunflower seeds.
It took a month for it to fully bloom.
Call me if you think...
the flower looks beautiful.
(Send)
Mum.
(Hyundae Photo Studio)
(Bukseong Theatre)
The boy inside my dreams...
was Joon Pyo?
What's going on?
Where is everyone?
I thought they had to collect all the flowers today.
Gosh, this is crazy.
Is it true? Are you sure?
Shouldn't we sue him or something?
I knew things were fishy when the branch manager didn't show up.
What are we going to do? I haven't got paid for two months.
Let's sue the branch manager. We can't just let him ruin us.
- Yes. - Gosh.
What happened?
Ms Gong, didn't you hear anything from the office?
I just sent out the shipment and came back from the airport.
Our branch manager took all of our sales money and ran off.
What?
How am I going to get paid? What about my money?
- My goodness. - How are we going to make a living?
- We have to catch him. - Yes, let's go.
- Let's catch him. - Let's get him.
This is my computer!
It's our company's property!
Don't take it.
Please don't do this. The manager will be back.
What are you doing? Get out of my way.
Please, just wait for him to come back.
What am I going to do?
You weren't just passing by, were you?
Who would pass by Jeju Island?
I'm on a business trip.
Oh, I see.
How is it working here?
Are you happy?
Happy?
It's what you majored in,
but it might not be what you really want to do.
You have to be apart from your family.
I think it could be tough.
I think it would be a good idea...
for you to take some time...
and think about what you really want to do.
Don't rush yourself.
Do you think that'll be okay?
Of course.
Shim. You're still young.
Thank you.
What are you doing tomorrow?
Do you want to go fishing?
I'm going to Seoul tomorrow. I'm sorry.
I see. I didn't know that.
It's my dad's birthday.
I see.
You really should go then.
Yes.
By the way,
where on earth do you think Dan Tae is?
It makes me nervous as time passes by.
He's been missing for a month already.
Yes. I'm worried about him, too.
Why was Joon Pyo crying in front of the photo studio?
Is the photo studio in my dream...
really in Bukseong-dong?
Mum.
Bukseong-dong is the neighbourhood I lived in when I was his age.
I don't remember.
How can you find someone with a picture from 26 years ago?
You can't.
- You don't recognise him? - No.
(Hyundae Photo Studio)
Then by any chance,
do you happen to remember a place called Hyundae Photo Studio?
I don't need to remember that. It still exists.
- It does? - Yes.
Hold on.
Yes, right here.
Hyundae Photo Studio's address is...
Here. This is the address.
Thank you.
175, Bukseong-dong.
It sounds like my old address.
(Hyundae Photo Studio)
(175, Bukseong-dong)
Are you here for a portrait?
No, I just...
Can I ask you something?
Are you the owner?
- Yes. - Then do you know...
the contact for the person who owned this place...
26 years ago?
That would be my father.
Your father?
Yes. He ran this studio for over 40 years.
I see.
I'm sorry, but is it possible to meet with him? I'd appreciate it.
- Come in. - Yes, thank you.
I noticed a residential space attached to this place.
Yes. We don't live there. We're renting it out.
I see.
- One moment. - Okay.
If this is the place,
does that mean I was born and raised here?
- Dad. - Yes?
I think he has something to ask you.
Is that so?
Hello, nice to meet you.
Yes, welcome.
What is it that you wanted to ask me?
Do you remember this boy by any chance?
Not really.
Then...
do you remember me?
No, I don't think so.
What is this about?
It was so long ago.
I guess I was too young for you to remember.
I used to live in the house attached to this studio.
What? What did you say?
I'm Ahn Soo Yong's son, Ahn Dan Tae.
You remember my name, right?
What?
Who?
Ahn Dan Tae.
What are you talking about?
Who are you?
What?
Dan Tae died. Why are you calling yourself Dan Tae?
Dan Tae died.
He died when he was five.
So who are you?
I'm Ahn Dan Tae.
How dare you? My goodness.
Look here.
Dan Tae died from drowning in that stream up there.
I picked him up out of the water.
What on earth are you talking about?
His father was from the special forces.
Including Dan Tae's aunt, the family of four lived here.
How can I forget about them?
After Dan Tae died, his mother lost her mind.
Just four days after he died,
she ran away in the middle of the night.
What are you trying to do?
Who are you?
Well?
I died?
Ahn Dan Tae died?
Then who am I?
What's that tree in Yangpyeong about?
He called to say that they need to pull it out.
It must be a man who flew from the Philippines...
to Korea between April 18 and 26.
Dad...
arrived...
on April 23.
Dan Tae died. Why are you calling yourself Dan Tae?
Dan Tae died.
He died when he was five.
Does that mean...
I'm Joon Pyo?
Honey, can you give this a taste?
Okay.
Shim, is that you?
Shim!
It's so nice to see you after a month.
It smells like a party.
Happy birthday, Dad.
Is this a flower from your work in Jeju Island?
It smells great. Thank you.
Where's Mi?
At work.
She's working so hard at work.
She started working?
Didn't you tell her?
She works at Star Group's legal department.
Star Group?
What can we do?
I didn't want her to go there since they fired you,
but she wanted to go. How could I stop her?
I see.
She'll be home soon.
Let's have some food. Go get changed.
I'm going to go to the rooftop and check on the plants.
Right. What happened to Dan Tae?
How come he's out of reach for a whole month?
Do you know anyone that knows him?
What on earth is happening?
- Happy birthday to you - Happy birthday to you
- Happy birthday dear Dad - Happy birthday dear Dad
You can't even blow out candles any more.
I don't have enough lung capacity. I must be getting old.
It's okay.
Your face hasn't changed since you were in your 20s.
Mum, come on.
You should be nice to him. It's his birthday.
When I first saw you when I was young,
I thought you were Shim's grandfather.
- You punk. - Goo Nam.
Why are you being mean, too?
I'm just being honest. When I saw him with your mum,
I thought he was her father.
Goo Nam. Go home.
- Sir. - Go home!
Dad, happy birthday. Here.
Cash is still the best, right?
My goodness. Thank you, Mi!
Dad, this honey is the best for heartburns.
Happy birthday.
Thank you, Shim.
It's underwear.
Thank you, Goo Nam.
How many years has it been since you gave me underwear?
I've been giving you the same gift for 10 years, too.
Honey, happy birthday.
I'm so happy.
Keep giving me the same gift for 50 more years.
Don't worry about that.
Hey, let's do a toast.
For Dad's health.
- Cheers! - Cheers!
(Pervert Lawyer)
- Happy birthday. - Here.
- Thank you. - Why are you still here?
- Well? - I...
I'll go in a while.
- When will you leave? - What?
Hello?
We're calling from a hospital. Do you know a man named Ahn Dan Tae?
- What? - He fainted on the street.
He's been transferred to a hospital on an ambulance.
What did you say?
How is he now?
He's still unconscious. We need you to come right away.
Okay. I'll be right there.
What happened? What's wrong with him? Is he okay?
He's getting checked now, so please wait out here.
Doctor, what happened?
Why did he faint?
I think he fainted due to shock.
He seems to be under a lot of stress and exhaustion.
Shock?
If he rests well, he'll be fine.
Okay.
You have to fill out some forms. Please come with me.
Sure.
Happy birthday, Dan Tae!
Dad.
What are you waiting for? Give it a test run.
Gosh, this is a really expensive model.
Dad. Thank you so much.
I'm so happy.
I'm thankful to you, too.
Thank you.
Dad didn't kill Joon Pyo.
He's not a murderer.
That's Shim's bag.
- Here you are. - Thank you.
Dan Tae. Are you awake?
Are you all right?
Can you recognise me?
Doctor.
Shim.
He just visited me a few minutes ago.
I see.
What did he say? Did he say you're okay?
- Yes, he told me I'm all right. - That's good to hear.
Why are you here anyway, Shim?
Aren't you supposed to be in Jeju Island?
That's not what we should be talking about.
What happened? I couldn't reach you for a month.
And suddenly, you're unconscious at a hospital.
Something really bad happened to my father.
But fortunately, it's all fine now.
That's really fortunate.
Shim, how was it in Jeju Island?
In Jeju Island?
Dan Tae, do you know a song called "Andante, Andante"?
It sounds exactly like your name. Don't you know?
I could hear the song everywhere, and I almost went crazy.
Andante, andante
It sounded like this.
By the way, do you remember the seed you gave me on my birthday?
Do you know when I realised that it was a sunflower seed?
As soon as I saw the way it sprouted, I knew it was a sunflower.
The sunflower bloomed completely.
Did you receive the message I sent you?
There is a haenyeo school in Jeju Island.
I thought of becoming a haenyeo, but I gave up.
It's because if I'm a secretary, people call me Secretary Gong.
So people will call me Haenyeo Gong if I become a haenyeo.
But Haenyeo Gong doesn't sound so great, does it?
Gosh, you're loud.
Was I too loud? I'm sorry.
I guess I talked too much in front of a patient.
Your meal is here.
I'll go and pick it up.
Shim, I missed you.
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
Here it is.
Here.
It's meal time. Let's eat.
There.
Wow, it looks delicious.
The kimchi is matured really well.
There's jangjorim, too.
This meal looks quite delicious.
Here. Go ahead and eat.
Shim.
Because I'm unwell, I don't feel like eating anything.
What do you mean? You should eat to recover.
I really don't feel like eating right now.
Have you eaten yet, Shim?
If not, why don't you eat instead?
I'm not a patient. I shouldn't eat a patient's meal.
It doesn't matter. You should eat, Shim.
I didn't come to the hospital for a meal.
I don't understand people who eat the meals for patients.
Are you really not going to eat?
No, I'm not going to. I'm sorry.
I'll return the tray then.
- Gosh, what a waste. - You're really not eating?
I told you already.
Dan Tae. Why did you come out?
I felt stuffy being indoors all day, so I wanted to take a walk outside.
Can you walk? Do you need my help?
Why?
Was it tasty?
- What are you talking about? - You ate my meal.
No, I...
You did eat my meal. My gosh, it smells.
I only ate a little to see what it tastes like.
A little?
You didn't just taste it.
You obviously finished the whole thing.
Tell me. You ate it all, didn't you?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
That's okay. Well done.
Why didn't you eat inside earlier when I told you to?
How can I eat your meal in front of you when you're sick?
You need to take a rest.
I'll push it for you.
Why does it smell so bad though?
- That was amazing. - That was incredible.
- Thank you. - It's the best meal I've ever had.
All right. Let's close the deal in the morning at the office.
- Yes. - Thank you.
Mr Seok, you're a heavyweight. You're incredible.
See you tomorrow.
Thanks. See you tomorrow.
- Good night. - Good night.
Are you really all right, Director?
Didn't you drink too much?
I'm fine.
They offered you so many drinks to make a better deal.
You should go home, Mr Kim.
Thank you.
Go home safely, Sir.
See you.
Gosh, I fell asleep.
Why are you standing up, Dan Tae?
Do you need something? You could've just asked me without standing up.
Shim, you look really tired.
You should go home. It's too late.
No, I'm fine. Ask me if you need anything.
I'm okay.
- Go home, okay? - My gosh.
I'm fine. Really.
I'm just worried, that's why. You should go.
I'm totally fine.
Joon Soo.
Director Seok.
Dan Tae. What happened?
I couldn't reach you, and now you're suddenly at a hospital.
I'm sorry things turned out like this.
Thank you for calling me, Shim.
I couldn't come earlier because I had to dine with my customers.
Take a seat, Director.
Here.
Okay.
- I'll do it. - Put it here.
I'll give you something to drink.
He's a bit drunk.
No, not this. This is more refreshing.
I hate you.
Did you just say you hate me?
Do you know how much I worried about you?
I call you so many times,
but you didn't answer my calls.
I won't let things go if you act like this again.
Okay?
Okay.
Why are you laughing?
Do you get it or not?
I get it. I get it.
I really like you, Dan Tae.
Like this. I'll be keeping an eye on you like this.
It's good to see you, Dan Tae.
Thank you.
Thank you, Shim.
My goodness, Director.
Here, let's take him over there.
- There's a bed for a kid. - Right.
Lie down and rest.
What's going on?
There are two patients in this room.
I hate you more.
He scared me.
I guess Director is really drunk.
I think so, too.
But I thank him for coming all the way here.
Shim, go home now. Will you?
There are two patients in this room. How can I just leave?
I can take care of him. So you can go home now.
It's fine with me.
I'm really okay.
I can take care of myself, so you should go.
Are you sure?
Yes, I am. You should go back home.
Well...
Bye. Sorry I can't see you out.
Call me if anything happens.
Like this. I'm going to be watching you like this.
I hate you more.
Why did I do that?
Did you wake up?
Dan... Dan Tae, how do you feel?
Did you sleep okay last night?
Wasn't the bed uncomfortable?
That's for me to ask. Wasn't the bed uncomfortable?
I got too drunk yesterday.
I didn't make any mistakes, did I?
- You don't remember a thing, right? - I don't.
You didn't make any mistakes.
It's good to know that you're better now.
I have to go to work, so I should get going.
Take good care of yourself.
You came by even during your busy schedule.
I hate you.
Can you please forget about that?
Goodness, you remember everything.
See you later.
Dan Tae, I'll see you later. Take good care of yourself.
- I'll go now. - Okay.
Director Seok.
Are you coming from home?
Yes.
It's very kind of you.
It's nothing.
How is your hangover?
It's fine.
Please excuse me. I got too drunk last night.
- I apologise. - It's fine.
You should go to work now.
Okay.
Has Dan Tae told you about what happened...
to him lately?
Well, I don't know the specific details,
but something must have happened at home.
He said that everything is fine now and that we don't have to worry.
That's a relief.
Well, have a good day at work.
Go on inside.
Here we go. I think we are ready now.
Let's leave the hospital.
Shim.
Yes?
Thank you. Thank you so much.
I'll pay you back one day.
Don't mention it. Let's just go.
You should eat healthy food, and rest well.
Are you going to eat everything like you did the other day?
My goodness.
You're being harsh on me for eating your food just once.
Let's hurry and leave.
Shim.
You should go home first.
Are you not going to go home?
You should rest even if you got discharged.
I'm going to stop by my office.
Don't worry about me and go home.
You haven't perfectly recovered yet, so don't be late.
I'll be watching you. Got it?
Got it.
Go ahead.
Dan Tae.
What happened to you?
Where have you been for a month?
Are you all right?
I'm okay.
You just left me a text saying not to worry about you.
You didn't answer my calls or return my texts.
Do you know how worried I was?
Ahn Dan Tae. Why did you do that?
Aunt Ji Won.
I know...
that I'm not Ahn Dan Tae.
The real Ahn Dan Tae drowned when he was five years old.
I've been to Bukseong-dong.
I went to where Mum, Dad,
you and the dead Dan Tae used to live.
You used to live in a house next to a photo studio.
And Dan Tae is buried...
under that tree in Yangpyeong.
Did Dad...
kidnap me?
No.
He didn't. That's not what happened.
Then what is it?
Why am I living as Dan Tae?
Why?
Why am I living as Dan Tae when I'm not him?
My sister,
Dan Tae's mum,
went insane after witnessing...
Dan Tae drown.
She didn't move. She just sat there staring into the air.
She didn't eat anything.
And she didn't talk.
Here.
Within three days...
after Dan Tae's death,
my sister tried to attempt suicide two times.
She was out of her mind.
But one day,
Soo Yong...
brought home a boy.
Goodness, Dan Tae.
Honey.
My goodness, Dan Tae.
My sister...
believed that the boy who came in with Soo Yong was Dan Tae.
She was so happy...
and took a good care of you.
Goodness, you eat so well.
Just like that, she started raising you.
A day passed,
a month passed,
a year passed and then, 10 years passed by.
You didn't talk when you first came.
But you started to talk and smile.
You started to act normal again.
Aunt Ji Won.
Was it Dad who kidnapped me?
No, Dan Tae.
That can never be.
A person showed up and asked Soo Yong...
to take care of you for a day.
That's why he brought you home.
Soo Yong overheard that...
the person was...
trying to abandon or kill you.
We thought something bad would...
happen to you if you went back to him.
That's why...
we had to leave the house in the middle of the night.
Who is the person that asked Dad to take care of me?
I don't know who that is.
Soo Yong never mentioned anything about it.
This is the truth, Dan Tae.
Dan Tae.
Recently, your father was...
planning to tell you the truth.
But I told him not to.
I was afraid that...
we'll become criminals and lose you.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry, Dan Tae.
Aunt Ji Won.
You'll always be my aunt.
You'll do that for me, right?
Thank you so much...
for raising me well like this.
Aunt Ji Won.
Help me so I can meet Dad.
I want to see him.
Okay, Dan Tae.
Okay.
Let's go back up.
Here are the two boxes.
Thank you. Bye.
You're back safely from Jeju Island.
Don't get sick.
And don't make me worry about you. I hope you grow well.
I told him to come home early, but he's not here yet.
My goodness, he really doesn't listen to what I say.
I'm done.
I told you to come home early, didn't I?
I left the meal here since it's too late.
Don't forget to take your medication.