(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
You're right.
That detective is right.
I'm using you.
What?
Stop it.
Stop fooling around.
- What's wrong with you?
-  Once we con Ho Seok...
and Min A and take Pil Gyu's 50 million...
and burn the money in Choi Chul Woo's paper company...
formed under his relative's name,
Bang Pil Gyu would've been conned...
and Choi Chul Woo would've been the con man.
When that gets out,
the media will dig into the Bang family and all their companies.
Then the one who conned becomes the con man...
and the one who was conned also becomes the con man.
I was going to submit this to the TV station right then.
Mayor Chun Gab Soo...
conned someone who owed a large sum in back taxes...
with Baek Sung Il of the Taxation Office...
and collected the owed taxes. This will have an impact on society.
Do you mean it?
Do you? Do you mean it?
Hey. Jung Do.
Do you mean it?
Seriously.
You've got to be kidding me.
What will I do with you?
Did you actually believe that?
What is this? Shoot.
Oh my gosh, you are so cute.
That's why you get conned.
How are you so naive?
What's wrong with you? Why are you doing that to me?
I just made that up.
But you sounded like you meant it.
You brought up Choi Chul Woo and...
collecting back taxes and stuff.
Don't you remember what you told me before?
What do you call your wife's older brother?
Anyway, at his memorial service...
Remember?
I threw together random facts, relationships and stories.
I just made it all up.
Look at your face.
Don't do that.
I'm timid. I get scared easily.
You really scared me.
I knew you wouldn't betray me.
Stop thinking about such things.
Figure out a way to get to Bang Min A.
Why visit the detective who tried to get us all?
Did you expect him...
to say things like, "Jung Do's a great guy"?
You really get me going sometimes.
Goodness.
Now you told me that, I feel hurt.
Don't be like that. I'm sorry, okay?
Loosen up, will you? Have some squid.
- I don't want any.
-  I'm trying to apologise.
Let's drink.
Sung Il found out.
Let's tighten things up.
Okay.
(Squad 38)
He gave...
the recorder I gave him to Jung Do.
I think that tells us whose side he's on.
What now?
Detective Jang.
Who do you think listens to us the best?
Pardon?
Criminals can't help but do as we say.
They know that if they don't, we can and will ruin their lives.
That's why they become informants,
sell out their friends...
and betray their teams.
Earlier on,
one of them came by.
Someone likely...
to turn against Jung Do.
The person was quite obedient.
It's the guilty conscience.
Who was it?
(Episode 10)
(Commissioner Ahn is following you.)
Chief, you are...
I know.
I know he's following me.
What?
Stop doing this, Sung Hee.
If I go somewhere else now, he'll suspect you.
I said I know what I'm doing.
Talk to you soon.
What does he think he can do?
Go.
911?
Shoot.
- Are you all right?
-  Let me see.
I think I lost my arm.
- Oh no.
-  My arm...
Oh dear.
I'm so sorry. I didn't see you.
Are you all right?
We meet again.
Sorry about that.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry about what happened.
- Are you all right?
-  Yes.
- Here's your coffee.
-  Thanks.
You should've gotten her something for her ankle.
I'm fine. You don't have to.
No, you need a patch for that.
- Go and get some.
-  Okay.
Convenience store coffees taste better than most cafes'.
Have some.
- Thank you.
-  You're welcome.
I should treat you properly after what I did,
but we can't exactly be seen in public.
Why not? Are you up to no good?
What?
I saw you yesterday, too.
Your team members are quite busy.
Oh, I see you got the wrong idea.
You don't have to explain. Do what you can to survive.
You don't get paid much.
Well...
You know what it's like.
Why do we need inheritance tax?
Why should we have to pay tax when a parent wants to leave...
something to a child?
Aren't I right?
The government did nothing when we were born.
Did it send us birthday soup or buy us baby clothes?
My parents were so poor,
I was born at home.
People called me "kid" when I was young.
They weren't sure I'd survive childhood.
Were you helping someone with their inheritance?
With antiques?
It's not exactly a fake donation.
The laws sometimes hurt poor, innocent people.
They could do with some comforting.
That's what I do on the side.
Where do you get the goods from?
What?
Things like this. Where do you get them?
You can't be stealing them from work.
I can't tell you that much.
Then we're done here.
Goodbye.
I should drop by the police station on my way home.
Just a moment.
Sit back down.
You have quite the temper.
Okay, fine. I'll fill you in.
A friend of mine called Chang Hyun...
is an appraiser at Busan Harbour.
When we get something from abroad,
the port appraiser decides whether something is...
genuine or fake.
We're abusing the system.
You have the appraiser lie about the artefact...
and bring it past customs?
When it's real?
Yes.
It's a real bargain.
You get them at a huge discount.
Is that how you got this?
Gosh, no, this is a genuinely rare artefact.
Do you want to see it?
I know you know a thing or two.
Here you go.
You shouldn't touch it, but I'm an expert,
so I don't leave fingerprints even if I touch it.
I'll show you.
There. See?
Look at the colour.
This is...
so beautiful.
Isn't it? You have a good eye.
This is difficult to find.
I will...
just give this to you.
Pardon?
Take it.
I can't take something this precious.
- Is it a fake?
-  Come on, now.
You saw how nice it was.
I don't deal with fakes.
I only wear fake clothes.
Then why are you giving this to me?
Think of it as a token of appreciation.
That way, you'll keep our little secret from today.
Take this and let's just say we're in the same boat.
I'll help you when you need,
and you can help me when I'm in need.
Okay? What do you say?
Would you like to take this or should I take it back?
Should I?
Ms Bang.
Where did you get this?
Why? Is it a fake?
No way.
You can probably get 200,000 dollars for this.
(Bang Min A)
It's her. It's her.
Hello?
It's me.
You said we're on the same side now, right?
Yes, I did. Of course, we're on the same side.
If that's the case,
can you comfort me too?
Of course. I'll treat you.
Don't worry.
To be honest, I've been hurt a lot because of the laws.
Would you please treat my wounds?
Of course, I'll treat you.
Don't worry. Okay.
Okay.
Wow. We got her. We got her.
Yes!
That hurts. You startled me.
I must be a good con man now.
Yes.
You need to eat with me.
- Hello?
-  Are you on your way?
- Jung Do?
-  Yes.
- I'm at...
-  I'm not going. Why should I?
- Hear me out. I'm at...
-  I'm not going. Don't tell me.
- I told you.
-  I told you I wasn't going.
This wasn't my idea.
I refuse. Tell him I'm dead.
- Why do you...
-  I'm at...
your office, is what I was about to say.
- You should've let me finish.
-  Are you insane?
- How could you come...
-  I know.
- Hello.
-  Hurry...
You must still be very angry.
Not at all. We made up last night. She isn't angry.
Right, Honey?
Why aren't you speaking?
Isn't that right, Honey?
Yes. Sure. We made up.
Hello.
Okay, then.
Shall we go eat?
Happy birthday to you
- Happy birthday to you
-  It's my birthday?
- Happy birthday, my wife
-  Happy birthday, Mrs Cho
Happy birthday to you
Let's drink.
- Happy Birthday.
-  Happy Birthday.
Isn't he so cute when he eats?
How are you so cute?
She says she married me because I look cute when I eat.
What did you like about Mr Cho?
Pardon?
I heard you chased him around in college.
Yes, I did.
I chased him around in college.
So why did you chase him around?
I can't remember very well.
You must be embarrassed.
Tell us.
What did you like so much about him?
Tell us. I want to know too.
What did you like so much about me?
I really don't remember.
I mean it.
I don't remember anything.
That's how it is.
When you are hurt badly by someone, you can't remember...
what you liked about them.
Why did I like him?
What emotions did I feel?
What did I do?
I can't remember any of it.
That's how it was for me.
Mr Cho must have cheated on her.
Why do they have so much to talk about?
I know.
When you look at him,
don't you want to punch him?
Pardon?
I really want to step on that stupid pig.
You looked so happy. Why are you...
You mean how I said he's cute when he eats?
- Well...
-  I dated him because he was rich...
and married him because he was rich.
I tried to like him and said he was a good eater,
and he stuffs his face all the time.
I should rip out his jaw...
so he can stop eating.
Honey.
Good night.
Let's go.
That woman is so strange.
What?
Nothing.
Your car's at City Hall, right?
I guess you'll need to get a cab.
I should.
There are no cabs here,
so let's walk a little.
There are cabs right there.
Come on. Let's go.
Thanks.
What did you two talk about?
Just. About investing.
How much should I put in?
However much you want is fine,
but let me be honest.
If you put in chump change, you'll only make chump change.
Do you want to be a man,
a real man, and play big?
What's playing big?
Smuggling?
It's technically smuggling,
but it's not illegal.
That's how it is.
There are cultural artefacts being dug up every day.
Replicas are making a killing.
You'll mix in a few real artefacts with the shipments of replicas,
so invest in that. Is that it?
Yes, that's right.
You got it right away.
Why couldn't Bang Ho Seok get it?
No.
I'm not saying we'll sell replicas claiming they're real.
We'll mix in some real ones with the replicas.
We'll mix them in and import them together. Together.
You don't get it.
Am I speaking Chinese?
I get it now.
You'll throw in some real ones with the replicas.
So what did he say? Will he invest?
No.
He'll refuse initially.
That sounds too tough for me.
So I worked him.
Mr Bang.
If you get...
products for cheap in China and sell them in Korea,
you make at least 10 times the money in profit.
How long...
How long will you play with chump change?
Does that even pay for your baby's formula?
But I don't think I can do it.
It's a world in which money makes money and the rich become rich.
I wouldn't make this offer if you were poor.
How long will you make six figures?
That's not even considered rich...
in China any more.
They give the kids that much for their birthdays.
Mr Bang.
Don't be complacent.
Let's look to be billionaires.
How great does that sound?
Billionaires.
It's so nice.
So...
I can see the goods before we start, right?
Not a problem.
Let's go.
Don't drag me into this any more.
Okay, I won't. Good night.
- Drive safely, please.
-  I will.
(Yang Jung Do)
What is it?
How's the ride?
Just...
I'm sorry...
that only I have the good memories.
Bye.
What I did with you wasn't love.
It was a con.
Jung Do.
Is that her?
Did you really like her?
No, right?
There's no way. Not someone like you.
It's obvious she has no money.
Why did you waste your time on a girl like that?
You know, the first thing...
I ever did after turning 20...
What was real just became fake.
So...
can we just go?
Okay, let's merge the jobs.
Ja Wang, get a montage of the goods from China.
You find me items similar to these.
Okay.
You stay on Commissioner Ahn.
- Are you okay?
-  What is this?
- Oh gosh.
-  Wait.
Look who this is.
I'm glad I ran into you.
Memorise these. There's a lot.
Wow.
Post 20th century, it was...
I'll contact Bang Ho Seok.
Mr Bang. The sample came in.
Would you like to see it?
He will call his sister since she's an expert on antiques.
Hi, Min A. I have a favour to ask.
Then whom will Bang Min A call?
May I ask for a favour?
It's for my brother.
- Have a seat.
-  Thank you.
My gosh.
There she is.
Hello, I'm Cho Hee Joon.
Hello.
Come in.
The only antique expert that Bang Min A trusts.
A public official who is just a bit dirty.
Are you ready?
Let's do it.
This is something I paid a lot of money for.
Is this that expensive?
It looks like clay.
Have a look, please.
Sure.
Who is that gentleman?
Her friend from the Cultural Heritage Administration.
I see.
It must be nice to know someone who works there.
Why didn't you tell me he'd be here?
I could've brought an expert, too.
I hope you aren't upset.
I'm not.
I know it's not easy for one to trust another.
Hey.
Treat it with care, Mr Expert.
Don't you worry about that.
This is wrong.
This is very wrong.
What? Is it a replica?
This is bad.
It's bad.
This shouldn't be here.
What do you mean?
This shouldn't be private property.
This should be in a museum where everyone can see it.
This has immense historic value.
This is a Tang Dynasty sancai.
Something like this was first unearthed...
So...
how much is it?
Listen carefully.
In the 20th century,
when the Chinese built the railroads,
they unearthed a lot of artefacts by bulk.
Okay. So, how much is it?
Hear me out first.
In 1928, when they were building a railroad...
Stop it.
How much is this worth in Korea?
Move your hand, please.
This is worth at least...
500,000 dollars.
100,000 dollars became 500,000 dollars.
What great magic.
Mr Cho.
You can let go. No need to grab my hand.
- See you, Min A.
-  Bye.
- Thank you.
- See you.
-  See you again.
Thanks for coming all this way.
Don't say that. We should help each other.
Are you free later today?
I think so. Why?
Can I take you somewhere?
I'll show you something.
Sure.
I've been thinking and...
I can't stop marvelling at your great skill.
How did you get into this business?
It's the age of globalisation.
China is just across the pond.
Why should we fight for a tiny piece of Korea?
You're right. Globalisation.
Let's get to business.
We'll be getting shipments every other week from China.
I see.
Right. You said that was a sample.
How many will we get this time?
About 300, I think.
300?
15 million dollars.
It's 150 million.
Get your numbers straight.
Right, 150 million.
100,000 dollars times 300 items is 30 million dollars.
If we deduct labour costs, commission,
appraisal and transportation fees, we'll be left with...
half of 150 million dollars?
You mean... 75 million dollars?
You got that one right.
75 million dollars.
Invest 30 million and you get 75 million back.
Would you be interested?
It is a great opportunity, but...
But what?
Do you still have doubts?
Get your sister's friend to appraise the whole lot.
This means...
I need to borrow money.
I see.
A loan...
I think...
you should go for it.
You'll make a 250 percent profit.
Shall I lend you the money?
No, no.
I couldn't borrow your money.
I'm just grateful you let me invest.
Okay, then. Let's do it.
I'll get the money soon.
Do you remember how much you need?
30 million dollars.
You need to give me 30 million, okay, Mr Bang?
Yes. 30 million.
When can I see what's coming into Busan Harbour?
About two weeks.
How much do you need?
I told my friend to focus on ceramic vases.
A Japanese buyer made a big offer.
I think they're negotiating.
How much is it?
After we deduct all the expenses, we'll be left with 20 million.
- And the profit?
-  At least triple that.
As long as we aren't caught.
Can you come with me?
Sure.
Mr Choo.
I don't trust people.
The older you get, the more people hide away.
You hide your emotions and your wrinkles.
These are different, though.
They show you their imperfections.
Chips, discolouration. Everything.
Just as they are.
That's why they're so valuable.
I've been collecting for 20 years.
They say they're the real deal.
Could you appraise these for me?
I'll pay you handsomely.
I trust you, for some strange reason.
Maybe because we're allies.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
That means...
Sung Il's target is Bang Pil Gyu.
His back taxes of 50 million dollars.
You can go.
Get me the mayor.
What do you mean?
Let's be careful. Nothing's sure yet.
Okay?
Yes.
(Chief Baek Sung Il)
Where's your chief?
He's out at the moment.
- On business.
-  That's right.
I see.
All alone? Leaving you here, hard at work?
There's a problem with a taxpayer we couldn't deal with from here.
He went to the borough office to get some files.
Are you sure about that?
- What?
-  Your chief.
Did he go to the borough office?
Yes. He did.
I see.
When he returns,
I'd like to see him.
Give him the message.
I will, Sir.
Is she in the know?
I was going to tell you, but...
Does she know?
Yes, I think so.
Is she helping them?
I don't know that yet.
I apologise.
We have circumstantial evidence that...
Mr Baek is trying to con Mr Bang.
Do you want me to give him a call?
So what?
Mr Bang's son and daughter have fallen for it?
Is it that easy to make 50 million dollars?
Get to work.
See Mr Bang and make a deal.
Unless he wants to lose 50 million,
he should get me out.
What?
Cold feet?
Does the thought of betraying Jung Do...
scare you now?
- It's not that.
-  Call Detective Jang.
- Wait.
-  Call him right now.
He'll drag you by your hair...
and slam you in a cell.
I apologise.
Listen carefully.
With Jung Do gone,
you can get back to your old life.
You can...
go back to taking money from scumbags blinded with lust.
I'll look after you.
But if you...
stick to Jung Do...
like the moronic public official did,
you will rot behind bars...
until the day you die.
I will see to that.
And...
you will never get to put any makeup...
on that pretty face of yours.
I will make that happen.
Do you get that?
Do you?
Who will you side with?
Tell me, you witch.
That is all I can tell you.
The rest is up to you.
Call Dad.
Now.
Where are you right now?
Okay.
Dad, let me explain. I was...
You idiot.
- Dad.
-  You fool.
You moron.
You imbecile!
What did I teach you?
I raised you better than this!
Dad.
I'm really sorry, Dad.
I won't do it again.
Sa Jae Sung wants to be let out?
Commissioner Ahn.
He has a prosecutor friend, doesn't he?
Ask for his help.
I'll give him a call.
Okay.
Tell him I'll meet him for dinner.
Now,
about the conning scumbags.
What should we do with them?
Hello, Ma'am.
Right now?
Okay. I'll come right over.
Bye.
I'm on my way.
Why your sister's home, though?
She's a great cook.
She wants to eat together to thank you for helping me.
Hurry over.
Bye.
He's coming.
Ms Bang. Ms Bang.
I need a favour.
I don't want to be here.
I can't face them again after this.
I can't look into Jung Do's eyes.
Didn't you see this coming?
- Ms Bang, please.
-  Leave her alone.
- Let me leave.
-  Back off.
- I really can't face them.
-  Let go.
Come upstairs.
You didn't have to come here. We can handle it.
I wanted to see their faces.
When will they arrive?
I called them over already.
Dad.
Stop.
I think we're caught.
Shoot.
Hand them over to the police.
Wait. Wait. Hold on. You. Get over here.
You rat. You rat.
You rat. I knew it from the start.
Do you know who my dad is?
You punk. Pay up for the dinner I bought.
- Come out.
-  Pay up, you rat!
500 percent?
Are you insane?
- Hey.
-  Let go.
Why you...
Drag them out of here!
Take them!
You are... You're so...
Shoot.
Hi, Sung Hee.
Something came up,
so I'll have to take two days off. Can you submit the request for me?
What is it?
Is something wrong?
No. Nothing's wrong.
Two days should suffice.
Thanks.
Okay. Bye.
Can't you do something?
They didn't complete the con,
but there was intent.
My friend works at Supreme Prosecutors' Office.
Then go there.
- It's too late!
-  My son is giving his statement,
so make everything fall into place...
and send them to prison for a few years.
They tried to...
con me.
The thing is,
it isn't as easy as it sounds.
I can detain them for 48 hours,
but not beyond then.
He pretended to be a government official and caused our family harm.
I am a government official...
I know your daughter's statement is more reliable,
but there was no exchange of money.
Your daughter received a gift...
that is worth hundreds of thousands of dollars.
Yang Jung Do...
is a VIP client at your son's company.
That was to gain trust before committing the con.
I know that. I do.
But...
there is no proof.
I need proof that at least a dime changed hands...
so that I can lock them up for fraud.
I didn't receive anything from him.
There is nothing...
we can do right now.
They may press charges against your children for fraud.
That's actually easier...
since there was a transfer of goods.
What you're saying is...
you can't help me, is that it?
That's right. I'm sorry, but...
Fine.
I'll take care of it.
Pil Gyu.
Shoot.
Right there.
Should we eat first?
Shall we?
That hit the spot.
Will you go to Bang Ho Seok now?
I should. What about you?
I'll go to Bang Min A...
and...
to Bang Pil Gyu.
- Okay. I'll see you later.
-  Okay.
- I'll call you later.
Thank you.
Bye.
Hi, Ms Bang. It's Choo Seok Hoon.
I mean, Baek Sung Il.
Yes. I'd like to talk to you about something in person.
It's me.
Yes. Can you connect me to him?
Okay. Got it. Good luck.
I think...
Jung Do is about to start for real now.
Is he?
What do you want?
I had something to tell you.
What? Do you want the vase back?
I'm not that low.
Let me ask you just one last thing.
Will you really...
not pay your taxes?
What?
The taxes that your father owes.
45.25 million dollars in national tax...
and 4.52 million in local tax...
for a total of 49.77 million dollars.
Will you not pay that?
Has this moron lost his mind?
Are you crazy?
Don't you understand the situation?
I do.
That's why I'm asking you nicely to pay your taxes.
You rat.
Do you think you're tough just because there was no proof on you?
Do you think my dad will let you get away with it?
You're so rude.
Like father, like child.
Lady. Don't you understand the situation?
Did spending a few days at the precinct throw you off?
She's so dense. How frustrating.
Lady.
Mi Joo didn't betray us.
She went to you because she needed to borrow something.
She wants to eat together to thank you for helping me.
Hurry over.
Now.
- Ms Bang, please.
-  Leave her alone.
- Let me leave.
-  Back off.
That stupid pig is so strong.
Drag them out of here!
Take them!
I have a boss named Commissioner Ahn at City Hall.
He knew we were trying to con your father,
so we beat him to the punch.
We didn't have time to wait.
Aren't you going to the basement?
The house was empty when you took us to the police.
Come upstairs.
They're gone.
Move!
Load them up.
Yes, Ma'am.
Be careful.
I think we're done.
Let's go.
We liquidated everything in two days.
It is nice. It's authentic.
It happened while we were locked up,
so you can't tie it to us.
There's no proof, either.
Now, do you feel like paying your taxes?
Mr Choo.
Mr Baek.
What must I do?
I'm sorry. I...
I was wrong.
I'm sorry.
Let's be rational about this.
What should I do?
If you would...
put everything back to where it was,
I'll give you 3 million. What do you say?
Is that too little?
I'll give you 5 million.
That's good, right? I promise.
I'll tell my dad.
5 million.
My wife runs a pork trotter restaurant.
We do well enough to survive.
We're fine.
Then what should I do?
What must I do?
Mr Baek, what should I do?
- Just say the word.
-  Call your father.
I have nothing else to say to you.
Call your father and give me the phone.
Call him now!
Hi.
Dad.
Hold on.
Bang Pil Gyu.
You thought money would resolve everything.
Who are you?
Me?
I'm Baek Sung Il from Seowon Taxation Office.
You don't remember my name.
You didn't remember my face, either.
I saw you a few days ago and at Insa-dong, too.
You said this six years ago.
I owe nothing to the nation.
The nation owes me.
- You rat.
-  Shut it and listen, you rat.
Why don't you owe the nation?
What nonsense is that?
Fine. Whatever.
Say you owe the nation nothing.
But you...
For the rest of your life, you must compensate...
the people who were hurt...
because of you.
Fine.
I will...
help you fulfil your obligations.
Listen carefully.
Bang Pil Gyu.
The back taxes you owe.
45.25 million dollars in national tax...
and 4.52 million in local tax...
for a total of 49.77 million dollars.
You have paid it in full.
You enjoyed all the luxuries,
thinking you had authority because you had a father like him.
Now,
fulfil your obligations...
and live like a decent human being.
Hi, Jung Do. I'm done.
I'm sorry,
but I can't pay the taxes with this.
Hey. What are you talking about? Stop joking.
No, I mean it. I do.
I need to use it for something else.
I'm going to use it. That's okay, right?
Hey. What are you talking about?
Why would you use that money?
Where... Where are you?
You don't need to know that.
I'll use it, okay?
I did all the work anyway.
Shut your trap!
Jung Do.
Don't do anything funny.
You said you weren't lying to me.
You said the detective was playing me.
How could you...
trust a con artist of all people?
Thanks for the money.
Hello? Hey!
What will you do now?
(Squad 38)
What?
There are too many tails to cut off.
Me or the mayor...
Are you okay?
What do you mean?
Where's Jung Do?
Where is he?
Jung Do doesn't have the money.
Ms Noh has it.
What's going on?
Disband the tax collection team.
Why did you betray us?
Where's Jung Do?
He may know.
I'm on your side.