(THE FOLLOWING CONTENT MAY NOT BE SUITABLE FOR VIEWERS UNDER 15.)
(VIEWER DISCRETION IS ADVISED.)
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Gosh.
I feel so much better now.
Will you go to Bang Ho Seok right away?
I should. What about you?
I should go to Bang Min A.
And...
Bang Pil Gyu, too.
Sounds good.
All right. See you later.
Yes, I'll call you.
Okay.
The food was delicious.
Bye, kid.
Hi, Ms Bang. It's Choo Seok Hoon.
I mean, Baek Sung Il.
Yes. I'd like to talk to you about something in person.
It's me, Jung Do.
Yes. Could you please transfer my call to the common room?
All right, okay. Good luck, Jung Do.
It looks like Jung Do is...
really going to start the job now, Sir.
Is that so?
(SQUAD 38)
(EPISODE 11)
Does Mr Bang know?
Did you tell him?
I didn't, of course.
Then why does he want to see me?
I did him a favour a few days ago.
I think that's why he wants to see you.
What favour?
I took care of something for him through the prosecutor, Mr Han.
Baek Sung Il in Division One and Mr Han...
are university alumni.
Don't worry too much, Sir.
You should just...
think of it as having a casual meal with them.
It's been so long, Sir.
Why did you want to see me?
Let's eat first.
We can talk afterwards.
Thank you.
I'll get going, then.
Mr Bang.
Give us some privacy...
if you've finished your food.
Pardon me?
I should stay here, though.
Sure.
I'm here to meet Mr Bang Pil Gyu.
What is it for?
Well...
Ma'am.
Who are you?
You know Ms Kim Kyung Ae, right?
I'm her son.
Wait.
Did you finish talking already?
No.
I just stepped out.
Have a seat.
I'll call you later.
Did you tell him by any chance?
No, I didn't.
I listened to your advice. It's nothing anyway.
Hello?
What are you talking about now?
I'll see you later.
Sir.
Why didn't you tell me?
What do you mean, Sir?
Is it because of your daughter?
Are you worried that she could be affiliated with it?
Is it because you feel responsible...
for protecting your daughter as a father?
Is that why...
you didn't tell me?
If you go out...
and across the bridge now,
hundreds of people able to replace you...
are waiting for me.
So,
don't ever make the same mistake again.
It's a mistake to do it to anyone else,
but not if you do it to me.
That's betrayal.
Do you get that?
Where's Mr Bang?
Something urgent came up. He had to go home.
Without saying goodbye?
It seemed urgent.
I don't know...
why.
Are you Director Kim's son?
Is that why you approached me?
To avenge your mother?
Not just her.
What about Detective Yang?
My father.
Fine. Let's say that we're partially responsible...
for what happened to Director Kim.
But not Detective Yang.
You shouldn't have done that.
There's no point in talking about the past.
Let's discuss work.
We took and liquidated the antiques your daughter kept locked up.
We liquidated everything in two days.
It happened while we were locked up,
so you can't tie it to us.
There's no proof, either.
Now, do you feel like paying your taxes?
What a wake-up call.
Right?
You lost in a con what you made through a con.
Hello?
Dad.
Hold on.
Bang Pil Gyu.
Who are you?
You thought money would resolve everything.
Check in on Pil Gyu.
See if something happened to him.
Yes, Sir. I will.
Bang Pil Gyu.
The back taxes you owe.
45.25 million dollars in national tax...
and 4.52 million in local tax...
for a total of 49.77 million dollars.
You have paid it in full.
You young people are pretty smart.
You're smarter than your parents.
What you don't know is...
even if you pay my taxes with that, I can get it right back.
I'm close with the mayor.
There are other ways, too.
Ways you don't know.
Are there?
Hi, Jung Do. I'm done.
I'm sorry,
but I can't pay the taxes with this.
Hey. What are you talking about? Stop joking.
No, I mean it. I do.
I need to use it for something else.
I'm going to use it. That's okay, right?
Hey. What are you talking about?
Why would you use that money?
Where... Where are you?
You don't need to know that.
I'll use it, okay?
I did all the work anyway.
Shut your trap!
Jung Do.
Don't do anything funny.
You said you weren't lying to me.
You said the detective was playing me.
How could you...
trust a con artist of all people?
Thanks for the money.
Hello? Hey!
What will you do now?
Your close friend can't get you the refund.
There's no other way.
If you want the money back,
you have to deal with me.
Even if you don't want to.
Apologise.
Apologise for putting the blame on my mother...
sending her to prison when things went bad.
Sir!
Please help me.
Tell them that I did nothing wrong.
Get up now.
Don't act like the ignorant person you are.
If it weren't for this,
why else would I have made someone like you a director?
It's fine.
Take her.
Come with us.
Sir!
Detective Yang investigated her case.
Apologise for sending him to prison over bribery charges.
Jae Sung, you know me.
I wouldn't take a bribe.
You know me better than...
Shut your mouth.
You're a scumbag cop who took dirty money, not a friend.
Lock him up.
Jae Sung, how could you?
Apologise and it'll all be over.
How dare you threaten me.
This is no time to be stubborn.
Your daughter's antiques...
were worth a total of 49.88 million dollars.
Do you want to lose all that?
I'm willing to give it back to you if you will apologise.
Watch it, you jerk.
Did you just curse?
At me?
Hi.
Hak Joo.
Jung Do that idiot just said...
What do you mean?
What does that mean?
I'm impressed.
Where is he right now?
No, hang on.
Jung Do doesn't have the money.
Ms Noh has it.
Oh, my goodness.
What's going on?
It's me, Ms Noh.
He doesn't need the money. Go ahead as planned.
He cursed at me.
Okay. I got it.
It'll take about five minutes.
Five minutes?
Okay then.
What takes five minutes?
You don't need to know, but that's the time you have.
If you don't apologise to me, you'll lose 10 million a minute.
Are you still not up for it?
Let's go.
Okay.
Okay. Point taken.
Gosh.
All it would take is one apology and you just wouldn't do it.
I don't get it.
Hey.
Do you know who I am?
You picked on the wrong person.
Just one phone call and I can end your life!
Wait!
I'm sorry.
What did you say?
Politely.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
What are you doing? Let go.
I'm sorry, Sir.
- Your mum...
- Mr Yang. Ms Kim.
Be polite.
Mr Yang and...
your mother.
Director Kim.
I'm sorry...
for lying and sending her to prison.
for framing Mr Yang...
for bribery he didn't commit...
and sending him to prison.
No. Forget all about it.
That didn't feel sincere.
Sound like you mean it.
We met once before.
You don't remember me.
Do you remember what I said?
Father.
Who's there?
Jung Do.
- Jung Do.
- Father.
- Just a moment.
- Jung Do.
Let us talk, just for a minute. Jung Do.
Jung Do! Will you let go of me?
- Jung Do. Jung Do.
- Give us a moment.
- Just one moment.
- Jung Do!
Wait!
Jung Do!
Don't let what happened get to you.
That is life. We have to bear it.
I'll say it again.
Don't let it get to you.
That is life.
We have to bear it.
I apologise.
I'm very sorry.
Please forgive me.
I made your parents suffer.
I will live with the guilt for the rest of my life.
I'm sorry.
Forgive me this once.
What shall I do?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
It's no fun.
Dump the lot, Ms Noh.
You scumbag!
Dump it.
It's going to where it belongs.
To where it belongs.
Where's Jung Do?
Where's Jung Do? Where is he?
What happened?
- He isn't picking up.
- What?
Mi Joo, do you know where he'd go?
Do you?
No?
Should we try looking for Ms Noh?
What should we do?
Your address is Seowon City...
About 50 million dollars...
is flying around the sky around Seowon City Centre.
It's a sight to behold.
Our reporter...
What's going on?
In this case, seeing is still hard to believe.
Someone threw money into the sky in Seowon City.
It literally is a windfall.
The passers-by stopped...
to stare at the sight for a while...
then picked up what they could.
Estimated to be around 50 million,
the cash in the sky...
Sir, Mr Bang...
Is it a mess?
Yes.
It is.
Thanks for helping.
What a waste.
Thank you.
It wasn't my money. It was Chairman Wang's.
I only did as he instructed me.
Don't thank me.
Still. I should.
Look after yourself.
Thank your assistant for me.
Will he...
be okay?
Who do you mean?
Sung Il.
Will he be okay?
It can't be helped.
What's done was done.
If I say so now,
I helped you for Chairman Wang.
That's what brought me this far.
So...
don't expect my help any more.
Figure your own way on and out.
Okay?
Okay.
I won't call you until I die.
Be well.
Get even richer.
I'm off.
I helped him despite being threatened by a detective.
He stabbed me in the back.
You won't see me again.
The cops will be after me.
I have to run.
Jung Do ruined everything.
Min Sik,
Chang Ho, Noh Seung.
I can never face them again.
It's all his fault.
Don't hate him too much.
He didn't keep it for himself.
It's not about how you take the money.
Isn't it about how you spend it?
Think that it went straight to the people...
without going through you.
Bye.
Everyone has a different theory about where the money came from.
The police and government officials who arrived belatedly...
on the scene said...
Some even got into fights...
trying to take as many bills as they could reach.
Dozens of calls came in from people...
who needed the police to help settle claims over the bills.
The money was thrown...
in just five minutes from multiple rooftops,
but the ripple effect will be greater than imagined.
According to witness statements,
the money was thrown in an area with heavy foot traffic...
from a few of the tall commercial buildings.
Some saw some unidentifiable people throwing the money down from...
Let's go for a walk.
Sir, what brings you all the way here?
I'm a citizen.
Is there a problem?
Sir.
People are watching.
We should meet in a secure location.
Can't people who don't pay taxes come to City Hall?
Is that prohibited?
No, Sir.
Then there's no problem.
I am a citizen...
and I have a right to be here.
Let's go inside.
He's coming in.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
What will you do?
I have people out there trying to collect what they can.
I did not ask...
what you are doing.
I asked what you will do.
Shall I tell you...
what I think we should do?
Cut off our tails.
There are too many.
On both you and me.
Even if you collect the money,
if you dig into where it came from,
it'll lead back to me.
People saw it.
It wasn't just us.
Pil Gyu.
I'll drop him.
- Mr Bang. We're from the police.
- His pyramid scheme...
was illegal and corrupt.
Those charges...
should get him a pretty long stay behind bars.
Are you sure about that?
You are close.
Not at all.
The older we get,
the thicker our skin becomes.
His kids...
can join him, too.
That...
would look even better.
- Wait!
- Come with us.
That's the Woohyang connection gone for good.
Next...
are yours.
You need to let a few people go.
- Where are you from?
- Seowon Police Station.
Baek Sung Il from Division One?
- Yes.
- Do you know Prosecutor Han?
- I don't.
- You need to come with us.
Why are you handcuffing me?
Why...
Be quiet. Talk at the station.
You can talk later.
- What about?
- We'll ask the questions.
- Commissioner.
- What's going on?
Are you Commissioner Ahn Tae Wook?
I am.
Did you ask Prosecutor Han...
to release Detective Sa Jae Sung from prison?
Through Mr Baek here.
I never said that.
- Explain yourself later.
- Let's go.
You're making a mistake!
- Be quiet and come along.
- Let me go!
- Let go of me.
- We'll talk later.
It would hurt...
to lose two smart men.
I understand.
It can't be helped, though.
We can't go down, can we?
Commissioner Ahn.
Let go of me.
Did you do it?
Was it you?
Answer me!
I will tell the cops everything.
What you did until now, got it?
Let's go.
Just wait.
The next one is important.
That punk, Baek Sung Il.
What will you do about him?
It looks to me that he is being used...
by a con artist.
I'll take care of that.
Yes. Please take care of it.
I'll leave it to you.
Also,
this is a bit sensitive, but...
Why don't you disband...
the tax collection team?
Hi, Sung Hee.
Are you okay?
You can't ask to take a day off...
so suddenly like that.
Sorry.
I had something urgent to take care of.
Is everything okay at the office?
Of course. Everything is fine.
(WHO GAVE AWAY 50 MILLION DOLLARS AND WHY?)
Are you okay too?
Yes. Of course, I'm fine.
I'm good.
Really?
Yes. Don't worry.
I'll see you tomorrow. I'll come in early.
Bye.
That will be a bit...
difficult.
The public likes that team the most and is the most interested in them.
- To get rid of them...
- Do you know how much tax I owe?
100 million dollars.
Mayor Chun.
Do you think...
what I did for Seowon City...
and for you...
isn't worth 100 million dollars?
The public...
should not be protected but shoved around.
Pretend to listen. Look afraid.
Act like you respect them.
That's how you shove them around.
Without us, they don't exist either.
We're the ones feeding them...
using a lot of money.
Disband...
the tax collection team...
within the year.
It's getting tougher for me.
Do you...
understand what I mean?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
(JANG HAK JOO)
- Hi.
- Ms Noh is on the move.
She's going into her office. That evil witch.
Okay. I'll be right there.
(JANG HAK JOO)
- Hi.
- Ms Noh is on the move.
She's going into her office. That evil witch.
Okay. I'll be right there.
Get out.
We're here to see Ms Noh. Clear a path.
Go back.
What do you mean? We're here already.
You'll get hurt. Leave while I'm being nice.
Are you threatening me?
- Boys.
- Yes?
She says you'll get hurt. If you're scared, you can go.
See that? My boys don't get scared that easily.
Really?
One is leaving.
Whatever.
He was never a part of the family anyway.
He was...
a mercenary. He's disposable.
I need to talk to Ms Noh, so move.
Hak Joo.
Must you do this?
You started it.
You're the ones who stabbed us in the back!
Weren't you supposed to understand even if we did side jobs?
I understand, but I can't forgive.
I am...
so frustrated, I'm going crazy.
There's no way, right?
What? A way?
If Ms Noh...
brings me Jung Do's head,
then there may be a way.
I guess that's a no.
That's what I think.
Hey.
Do you think you can handle those rats?
Yes, Sir!
Take it easy.
Okay! Let's go!
Sit up! Got it?
You punks.
Are you sleeping?
Who are you?
Hak Joo.
We were outnumbered.
If only that fat pig hadn't run away...
Let them go.
Ms Noh would like to see you.
Let's go.
It's okay. You may go.
Yes, Ma'am.
Where's Jung Do?
I don't know.
Why... Why did you betray us?
I did...
what the chairman that I serve told me to do.
So "betrayal" isn't the right word.
It isn't that simple.
Where's Jung Do?
I told you.
I don't know.
But then again,
that person may know.
Where are you going? What are you saying? Where is Jung Do?
Do you remember when you pulled the job on Ma Jin Seok?
Back then,
a person called me.
You were all caught and Jung Do was in danger, so I had to help.
Mr Baek.
Our chairman is on Jung Do's side,
but I'm on your side.
You've been a good person.
You should be rewarded.
I'm going to step out for a bit.
The air conditioning is giving me a headache.
Things have gotten complicated.
Hello?
Jung Do is in danger.
Sung Il and the others were taken by the police.
Anyway, we don't have time, so go to Jung Do, okay?
Shall we go?
Sorry?
We should finish the job.
Yes, let's go.
What brings you by?
Deok Bae.
Remember the file you showed me long time ago?
When they went after Noh Joong Sik a business owner,
they found a strange file.
Why is he here?
The file that your friend in the RIU found...
while investigating a case.
The file that had Ma Jin Seok and other City Hall people's names.
The one that Jung Do asked for while he was in jail.
What about it?
I was curious,
so I called the Regional Investigation Unit,
and they said there is no one...
by the name of Doo Gil there.
Hey.
What is your relationship...
with Jung Do?
- Sung Il.
- Answer me.
What is your relationship with that rat?
Deok Bae,
you're my friend.
You're not Jung Do's friend. You're my friend.
- Let me explain.
- Answer me, you jerk!
Don't mind him.
Get back to work.
Let's talk outside.
Let go.
Let's talk here.
Let's talk outside. This is a police station.
Tell me right now!
Baek Sung Il!
Deok Bae.
Let me hit you just once.
You rat.
- Get off. Get off of him!
- You jerk! Tell me!
- What are you doing?
- Why can't you answer me?
You jerk! I'm your life-long friend! You jerk!
How could you do this to me?
- Stop it already.
- You jerk!
Let go!
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Jung Do...
is my mentor's son.
- Have some coffee.
- Thank you.
- Coffee sounds good.
- Ji Taek was the captain.
I was the rookie.
What about mine?
Where did you go?
Take this.
- Jae Sung was in the middle.
- I'll go get another one.
The three of us were a team.
We worked well together.
We had the highest arrest rate in the nation.
Anyway,
Ji Taek started to lose focus and was distracted.
His mind wasn't in the game.
So I asked what it was,
and he said...
he thought his wife fell into a pyramid scheme.
So we dug into it.
These are the call records.
Woohyang Group's pyramid scheme con.
It was good.
There were over 10,000 victims...
and the amount was hundreds of millions of dollars.
All the reporters...
latched themselves onto our case...
since they smelled something big.
But...
But those rats...
put all the blame on his wife.
Excuse us.
Are you Kim Kyung Ae?
We're the police.
You are arrested for running a pyramid scheme.
What? What do you mean?
All they had to do was lock up a few executives...
- to close the case.
- Sir.
- They blamed her...
- Sir...
- and sent her to prison.
- Please help me.
Jae Sung...
that scumbag.
Anyway, they bought Jae Sung...
and sent Ji Taek to prison...
for taking bribes.
Jung Do.
(WOOHYANG GROUP COMBINED BALANCE SHEET)
Jung Do started preparing a job...
to get revenge for his parents...
and got caught by Jae Sung who locked him up.
Within a few months,
the entire family went to prison.
Does that make any sense?
Jung Do is impressive.
He knew if they found out that he planned the con...
to get revenge for his parents, he'd rot in prison for years.
He knew Jae Sung wouldn't sit still, so...
Woohyang Group?
What is this?
So he acted like a moron.
Like he didn't know anything.
I did it because I heard they had a lot of money.
No other reason.
Are you sure?
Should I have another reason?
Would that reduce my sentence?
Then I'll make something up.
So he prepared his revenge in prison.
He wanted to make sure he is careful...
and get revenge properly without getting caught.
So that he could move quietly without being noticed...
and so that he could bury it and run if any problems arose.
That's where he decided to bring in people like me...
who had a grudge against Bang Pil Gyu.
He didn't confuse me for another Baek Sung Il, did he?
He was after me from the start.
Right?
Sir.
Do you have a light?
Yes, he's hooked.
Did you tell him...
that you have a moron for a friend...
and that he could get away easily if he dumped it all on me?
How could you say that?
Dump what on you?
Think about it.
You're the one who initially offered to catch Jung Do.
Hey.
Shall I catch him for you?
Do you want to benefit from having a detective friend?
Can you do that?
You said weird things in front of him.
How much is it?
How much does Ma Jin Seok owe in back taxes?
Why do you care?
Didn't you say it's about 6 million dollars?
Hey. Hey.
You said you'd let him go for me.
If the prosecutors get to him, we can't get him out.
Think about it...
and call if you want. Whatever.
You did everything a detective should not do.
Yes.
Sung Il, I'm on my way to pick up Yang Jung Do.
What do you want to do?
It was all for that.
I heard he took a bribe.
Have a nice day.
Must you go this far?
That's the only way he'll work with me.
We need to get him whatever it takes.
What if Sung Il really gets fired?
I'll tell them that it was just a prank call.
That will solve it.
You used me to help Jung Do with his revenge.
Isn't that why you did it?
You've got it all wrong.
Yes, I connected you to Jung Do.
I knew...
you were conning people to collect back taxes.
Shoot.
You have a grudge against Bang Pil Gyu and them too.
You suffered a lot because of those jerks.
Every time you got drunk, you said you'd avenge Min Sik's death.
Still, you shouldn't have done that.
You're my friend.
I'm going to catch that jerk, Jung Do.
I'll catch him, and...
(SQUAD 38)
I don't want to lose any more of my people. Let's stop here.
- I won't see blood.
- Don't do it.
You should clear up any misunderstandings.
You shouldn't con people with their feelings.
If we find the connection between Mayor Chun and Chairman Choi,
our team will survive.
Get Chairman Choi Chul Woo.
You will now be Martin Kim,
the regional head of General Martin.
I'll take care of the contract extension.
This is a con.
Must I do all this just to save you?