(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
Even if you pay my taxes with that, I can get it right back.
Dump the lot, Ms Noh.
You jerk!
(Previous episodes on Squad 38)
Jung Do, you said you never lied to me.
People saw it.
What is going on?
We're not the only ones who saw it.
Let's cut the tail off first.
There are too many tails.
About the Taxation Office...
How about we just get rid of the entire department?
Who's the one who did all that to begin with?
Who's the one that stabbed us in the back? Tell me!
Ms Noh wants to see you.
Where is Jung Do now?
That fellow may know.
What are you and Jung Do up to?
- How could you do that to me?
-  Gosh, stop.
Jung Do is my mentor's son.
Within a few months,
the entire family went to prison.
So his target was me from the get-go.
I got him.
So he prepared his revenge in prison.
Clear up the misunderstanding.
You liked each other a lot.
Go after Choi Chul Woo.
Break the link between him and the mayor.
That way, our department will survive.
He's here.
What's the point in working hard to collect the money...
when the one spending it doesn't change?
Let's really trust each other and do one more job.
Let's get Chairman Choi.
- Deal.
-  You will be...
General Martin's Martin Kim from now on.
Chairman Choi Chul Woo has no children.
He set it all up in order to get you.
Do you get it now?
Do you realise who you were up against?
I heard you sold me out.
Jung Do, that's not it.
(Previous episodes on Squad 38)
Sung Il, go to court and testify.
Go back to being who you used to be.
Work a bit and tiptoe around your boss.
It's your choice.
Please help us so that they don't get rid of the department.
I will testify.
I will announce my decision.
Defendant Yang Jung Do...
is sentenced to 10 years in prison.
I heard you sold me out.
Jung Do, that's not it.
- Hey...
-  Find his real money source.
Not his fake son.
Find where Choi Chul Woo has his money hidden.
Sell me out and stay alive, got it?
Why did you do that to me?
You said let's not betray each other!
Why did you do it? Tell me!
(2 years later)
(Episode 13)
Are you okay?
Of course.
What brings you here?
I have something to tell you.
That's why I'm here.
It's about Chief.
Something happened to him.
- Congratulations.
-  Gosh...
This is...
(Change of Position: Baek Sung Il, Team Manager of Management Support)
Things have gotten very bad since that incident with you.
Anyway,
I know why you're in there now...
and what promise you made to Chief.
He told me everything.
Well, Sung Hee.
What you heard.
In other words, what we're planning on doing.
Your father,
Mr Chun Gab Soo, could be hurt in the process.
I know that he divorced your mother when you were a kid,
but he's still your father.
Are you going to be okay?
My mum still tells me this from time to time.
"Your dad..."
"was the worst husband any woman could have,"
"but he's a very inspiring person."
But...
my observations...
from the last few years tell me that the mayor, Mr Chun Gab Soo,
isn't that kind of person.
It could hurt his career significantly...
to the point that it's not revivable.
When I only think about myself,
I know that it's not something I should be okay with.
But when I think about Mr Kang,
Chang Ho...
and Mr Park Sang Ho,
I know that it is the right thing to do.
Power...
should not be used to hurt people.
It should be used to protect the people who have been wounded.
Are you sure that you won't regret it?
Make me not regret my decision.
Please do it for me.
All right.
I'll do my best.
By the way, what happened to Sung Il?
Why did he tell you all those things?
He...
changed.
He's back to his old self.
(Squad 38)
I asked you to get me the travel ban list. Where is it?
Oh, right. That list.
Goodness. I asked you about it this morning.
You forgot again, didn't you?
Sorry, I forgot. I'll have it ready by this evening.
Forget it! I'll do it myself.
There isn't a single thing you can do properly.
I'm swamped right now. I'm sorry.
Do you think I have nothing to do?
I'm so sick of hearing that excuse of yours.
Mr Baek.
Why are you back here again?
- I said I can't help you.
-  Mr Baek.
There's nothing I can do.
- I can't do anything for you, okay?
-  Please...
Please...
Please help me.
This won't work.
Please leave. Please.
It's of no use. Go home.
Your granddaughter should be home soon.
Go home to her.
Go on home. Bye.
Did you have to be so cold?
What?
He came a long way just to see you.
You were too mean.
He visits so often.
There's nothing I can do.
I'm on the management support team.
- We can't stop redevelopment...
-  That's not what I mean.
That old man, Mr Woo Sang Chul.
Doesn't he remind you of someone?
Mr Park Sang Ho.
Doesn't he come to mind...
when you see that old man?
Give me a discount.
Please.
People like them come to us...
because they have no one else to talk to.
They have a lot to say but no one to talk to.
That's why they come to us.
Can't you hear him out?
It's not that hard to just listen.
To be frank,
if that old man were to end up like Sang Ho,
how would you feel then?
Tell me.
I don't care.
What?
What happens to him is none of my business.
Why should I care...
what happens to him?
We aren't related.
Are we?
What happened to you, Sir?
Nothing's happened.
This is who I am.
Don't call me sir.
I'm on the management support team. I'm no longer your chief.
Am I?
You're the chief now.
Shall we talk outside?
It's a hot day.
So,
that Baek Sung Il guy.
What is he up to these days?
I'm getting regular updates.
You won't have to worry about him.
He's quiet and gets into no trouble.
That's good.
Mr Mayor.
Redeveloping the Maseok-dong plot.
Do you hate the idea that much?
It's the area...
that pays the least amount of taxes.
Maseok-dong.
The poorest area in Seowon City.
That explains why all the landowners dress so poorly.
You can tell right away that it's a run-down neighbourhood.
Isn't that why...
you sold it to me for almost nothing?
All the buildings there.
The landlords and landladies aren't the problem.
It's the tenants.
If we remove them by force, they will become homeless.
I can't give up on my right just for your pity.
I will...
exercise my right.
Did I not compensate them?
Did I not give them time?
I gave them both.
I did what the law requires of me.
Am I wrong?
I'm not talking about the law.
I'm talking about human rights.
Following the law doesn't justify violence.
Can you be responsible...
for what you said?
I can't believe a mayor gunning for a second term just said that.
Did you just reject the law?
- Did you?
-  No.
Forget it.
I followed the law until now,
and I plan to continue to do so.
If you don't like what I'm doing,
take action according to the law.
The few who are still squatting there...
will be dragged out.
The buildings will be demolished.
That's why I wanted to see you.
You can go. I'm done talking.
Mr Cha.
- It's me.
-  Yes, Sir.
Of course, Sir. We'll do that.
Sure. Bye.
I hate this part.
Stop it.
Be quiet.
Old man.
It's like I said. What you're doing is illegal.
You had a deadline.
Didn't you?
Do you know how much we're losing because of you?
Anyway,
now we have to do what the law tells us to.
We're doing this for a living, too.
That was good.
Five dollars, right?
You do pretty well.
You do well enough...
without having to redevelop this area.
We'll die.
We'll starve if we lose what we have here!
Stop whining.
Just die, then.
I hate old people.
Do it.
Go inside.
Bye, old man.
Don't!
Get out! Get out of here!
- Stop it!
-  Get out!
Get lost!
Jung Do's getting released?
So soon?
He got 10 years.
He'll be paroled.
How?
I don't know the details.
He's getting released.
I think he'll be out next week.
I don't get it.
How can a 10-year sentence become 2?
Why did you want to see me?
It can't be so you could tell me that.
No.
I wanted to ask you a favour.
What?
Well...
The people you worked with.
Are you still in touch with them?
You need to do something as soon as Jung Do gets out.
You'll need their help to do it.
Will they do it?
They fell for his sweet talk and played along,
but that was two years ago.
It's different now.
They're frauds.
They won't do anything that's not for profit.
Right.
I'll talk to them. I'll try,
but don't expect too much.
Even I'm not that interested myself.
I'll try talking to them.
Okay.
Thanks.
Why are you doing this?
What's Sung Il up to?
Things happened along the way.
- Here, take a bottle each.
-  Thanks.
- Drink this.
What's this for?
It's a pick-me-up.
- Here.
-  Thanks so much.
Have one yourself, Mr Shim.
You must be tired...
from working away from the office these days.
I'll massage your shoulders. I'm good at that.
- Just a bit.
-  Forget it.
I said forget it. Go and work instead.
Okay, then.
Are these empty?
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
- Give me that.
-  I'll throw them away.
- No, let me.
-  Let's get going.
This is my job.
Mr Kim, you should have one, too.
- No thanks.
-  Come on.
I said no. You drink it.
Mr Baek from the management support team.
Use my title from now on.
Strictly speaking, I am higher up than you are.
Right.
Yes, Sir.
Have a nice day, Sir.
Mr Baek.
Yes, Sir.
Are there any problems?
No, Sir. Not at all.
(Do not develop Maseok-dong!)
Mr Mayor.
Don't worry too much. I'll deal with it.
A citizen should not lose his livelihood...
to an entrepreneur's greed.
I know that.
I'll see to it.
Be strong.
Thank you.
It's me.
Speak.
I will hold a meeting...
with Maseok-dong's residents.
Bye.
I know what he is.
He's a crocodile.
What nonsense is that?
I'm out.
Come on, Hak Joo.
Let's help Jung Do out.
Ja Wang.
I got my draft notice. I'm joining the army.
I'll serve our country.
Please leave. I'm not interested.
Still...
He took the blame for what we did.
He did lie to us, but he did time instead.
Ja Wang.
He sacrificed for us all, didn't he?
He did, but I'm joining the army.
I got my notice.
Do you expect me to believe that?
Don't believe that.
Don't believe Jung Do.
How long will you help...
just because you like him?
You can't go on helping him forever.
Where's your pride?
Just stop it, okay?
Are you out?
Why should I be in?
I can't do it.
I'm joining the army.
If you're done talking, get out.
Get back to work.
Okay, then.
Have a great life, jerk.
No one wants to help.
Really?
It can't be helped.
Thanks anyway.
Mr Baek.
I got what you asked for.
Make multiple copies of it.
Oh, right.
Can I print it on recycled paper?
Don't you see this?
It's for a report.
Do you want our commissioner to use recycled paper?
Why are you so slow?
Sorry. I'll use the new paper that just came in.
Come in.
Yes, Sir.
Is today...
the mayor's meeting?
With the Maseok-dong residents?
Yes, Sir.
They should at least help us.
If they can't make our lives better.
How would you sum up the situation?
They can't just kick us out. We have nowhere to go.
Was there word of compensation?
Who said that? No one did.
There's talk that this area is being redeveloped...
because we pay the least taxes.
- That's nonsense.
-  What logic is that?
No government officials are stepping up.
The city should look after the poor people.
What good is a discussion now?
Where do we have to go?
Sorry, but I have something to say, too.
I lived here for dozens of years,
and I lost the right to my land.
What should we expect from...
Is that the mayor?
- It's the mayor.
-  Mr Mayor!
It's him.
Excuse me!
Mr Mayor.
Mr Mayor. Could you give a short interview?
What's this discussion for?
Is it true that you'll cancel plans for redevelopment?
I'll tell you at the meeting.
The residents said they weren't compensated.
- Make way.
-  Were you aware of that?
-  Any comments, Sir?
What would you say to the residents?
Do you have a plan?
(Seowon's mayor meets with Maseok-dong residents)
Get things going.
Yes, Sir.
It's me. Let's begin.
Say something to the camera.
- I'm sick of it.
-  We have to move.
Please help us.
Say what you want to say.
Mr Mayor.
Crocodiles, you see,
never hunt their own prey.
They make it come to their mouths.
We aren't going anywhere!
My parents are too old to move now.
- Please help us.
-  Do something.
Chun Gab Soo...
is a crocodile.
He hunts,
but doesn't shed blood.
Not on his hands.
We're here because we don't want to fight.
We need your help.
Who did that?
Mr Mayor.
Mr Mayor!
Don't leave us!
Grandpa!
Grandpa.
The crowd suddenly began to yell at the mayor.
Mayor Chun didn't seem to mind being egged...
as he left the scene in silence.
The egg-throwing ignited the fury within the residents...
as they rushed towards the mayor's entourage.
The bodyguards had to fight off the angered citizens.
Ji Yeon.
Isn't he the owner of the diner the boys went to?
Find out what happened.
Okay.
An official within the government said...
The mayor of Seowon City...
was assaulted by the public this afternoon.
He was in Maseok-dong to attend a discussion...
with the residents regarding the redevelopment.
Our reporter has the story.
The residents protesting against the redevelopment...
flocked around the mayor on his arrival.
Mayor Chun was there to attend a discussion with the residents,
and handled the situation calmly.
Just then, someone in the crowd yelled...
and threw an egg at the mayor.
The mayor didn't seem to mind it much,
but he left the scene in a hurry.
The egg was a signal...
Hello?
Was it you?
Yes.
Why?
Why did you do it?
Isn't that what you wanted?
I thought it was.
I wanted to talk it out.
Instead of forcing them out of their homes,
I wanted to talk.
I wanted to solve it with a discussion.
Then why did you tell me?
Why did you tell me...
about the meeting?
You called me.
This is the reason you and I...
get along so well.
Our processes might be different, but we share the same goal.
We do.
No, no.
Our processes are the same, too.
You just...
- keep deceiving yourself.
-  Sir!
Do you think you're good?
If you were really good, you wouldn't have called me.
You wouldn't have tipped me off.
If you want to,
then I'll let you take the high road.
I will do...
all the dirty work.
You need to get re-elected.
You have to win...
the next election.
(Maseok-dong Residents Assault the Mayor)
Guard. Hey.
What?
Sorry, but could I use the phone?
I know I shouldn't,
but I need to.
Thank you.
Ms Noh.
Why should I do that?
I get nothing.
That's not true.
They feared us.
What do you mean?
They looked down on the law and people...
but they feared us.
For the first time in their lives,
they feared the people they mocked.
You people.
You do nothing right.
What's your job?
Am I barking?
Stop eating.
What good is...
Ms Noh. A world where the evil prevails.
That's bad.
A world without common sense is bad.
A world where illegalities trump is bad, too.
So...
Let's do it one more time.
Jerks like us con artists...
Is anyone home?
Mister? Are you in?
We lack common sense...
and we break all the rules in the book.
How angry must we be to do something like this?
How much worse are the people these con artists are fighting?
How evil and how greedy are the people we're fighting...
that made us want to go this far?
Let's show them...
good people winning...
and bad people losing. That should be only natural.
Let's make it a reality.
Mi Joo.
Let's clean this up.
These are Da Mi's.
Let's show...
those jerks.
Mi Joo!
It's so hot. Why is it so hot?
I'm melting.
What?
Did you come empty-handed?
Let alone tofu,
you should've at least brought coffee. You're so clueless.
Give me a smoke. I've been dying for one.
I quit smoking.
Don't lie to me. Give it to me.
It's true.
What?
Good girl.
Hi!
Jung Do!
You're dead.
Come on.
Jung Do! Jung Do!
I'm hot. You're getting your sweat on me. Get off.
- Get off.
-  Get off of him.
You jerk. You rotten scum.
Hi.
You got a new hairdresser.
- What? Yesterday.
-  Yes.
- It looks good.
-  Does it?
- Is it nice?
-  Yes.
Ms Noh,
how have you been?
Same old.
Then let's go...
stomp on them.
You know,
after the IMF crisis,
an insane amount of loans from Japanese loan sharks...
were brought into Korea.
A part of it took over the Pyeong-dong's loan shark market,
and a part of that is Choi Chul Woo's source of funds.
If you check from the bottom...
Put your thumbprint on it.
It would be a loan shark from Pyeong-dong, naturally.
From illegal high-interest loans...
to loans using real estate and cars as collateral...
and recently, even labour,
Choi Chul Woo owns 70 percent of the loan shark market...
in Pyeong-dong.
I'm sure there isn't proof that the loan shark money...
in Pyeong-dong belongs to Choi Chul Woo.
That's right. He doesn't use the money from Pyeong-dong...
to invest in other businesses.
So he won't let dirty money...
mix with clean money.
What other source of funds does he have?
Keep reading.
This is his main source, Kukjin Construction.
After Woohyang Group went under,
they kept changing their name, so it was hard to find...
This was originally Woohyang Construction.
It split from Woohyang Group before its pyramid scheme went burst.
When we found out that Kukjin Construction was originally...
Woohyang Construction, we went after them about a year ago.
Hello. We're here from Seowon City Hall.
May we see Mr Cha Myung Soo?
They've already cut all ties to Choi Chul Woo.
Seeing how he was willing to burn Woohyang Construction and...
Woohyang Tech but he wanted to save Kukjin Construction...
It is clearly important to him.
It was quiet for several years,
but it became active recently.
So Kukjin has the development rights to Maseok-dong, is that it?
Who's the puppet president?
- Cha Myung Soo.
-  Cha Myung Soo...
- Hello.
-  Hi.
If Bang Pil Gyu is Choi Chul Woo's right-hand man,
he's his left-hand man.
He seems to have fudged some numbers...
and embezzled some company funds, but it wasn't that much.
I think that's why Choi Chul Woo is letting it slide.
Only 100,000 a year?
He must be very afraid of Choi Chul Woo.
I'm sorry, Sir.
He's terrified.
I think that's why he gave this man Kukjin Construction.
Scared men don't betray their masters.
He probably has a lot pent up, though.
Everyone has a temper.
Why must I put up with this?
Jung Do, isn't this the man you conned before?
That's right. Cho Sang Jin.
He handles Kukjin's finances.
He went to schools with Cha Myung Soo.
You have such a sense of style.
You're good.
His accounting office must not have done well.
Is this it?
That is pretty much Choi Chul Woo's source of funds.
But there's something you need to know.
Do you remember...
Commissioner Ahn Tae Wook, my boss from two years ago?
He is now a director at Kukjin Construction.
He's very quick,
so you should be very careful when you do your job.
It doesn't hurt to be careful.
Okay. I'll keep that in mind.
I think this...
is all I can do for you.
You can do the rest when you get out.
But... But doesn't it feel...
like something's missing?
Right? It feels like something's missing.
You feel that way too, right?
What? What's missing?
Well, since a person who was always around isn't here...
Do you mean that man, Baek Sung Il?
I think this...
is all I can do for you.
You can do the rest when you get out.
But... But doesn't it feel...
like something's missing?
Right? It feels like something's missing.
You feel that way too, right?
What? What's missing?
Well, since a person who was always around isn't here...
Do you mean that man, Baek Sung Il?
I'm leaving.
- Have a nice day.
-  Don't stay too late.
Okay. Have a nice day.
He's back to being a loser.
He's all watered down.
I hear that's how he's living now...
to fool the City Hall people.
Mr Baek has changed.
He's back to his old self.
No.
The right way to phrase it is...
he'll change. He has to.
What do you mean?
There are many eyes in City Hall.
He needs to fool them.
Forget it. I'll do it myself.
There isn't a single thing you can do properly.
I'm swamped right now. I'm sorry.
That way, when you get out,
he can work with you.
- No, Sir.
-  Okay.
However long it takes for you to get out,
that's how Mr Baek will live.
Your granddaughter should be home soon.
He'll have to ignore injustice.
What happened to you, Sir?
This is who I really am.
He will endure...
people misjudging him...
because he has to.
He has to...
Find where Choi Chul Woo has his money hidden.
Sell me out and stay alive, got it?
Why did you do it? Why?
(Kukjin Construction's Accountant, Friends with Cha Myung Soo)
In order to keep his promise to you.
He's been living in disguise for two years?
Is he capable of doing that?
Da Mi.
Mr Baek!
Are you all right?
My grandpa...
That's how angry...
he was.
The world is too frustrating...
to keep taking it.
I'll get them for you.
I will destroy the people...
who did this to you.
I won't watch my people...
get hurt any more.
I came to tell you that.
I'm sorry for everything.
I had some things going on.
Think of it as a little break...
and stay in there for a short while.
I will...
I will tear...
all those jerks apart.
Take care of yourself.
I told you I'd get out early.
It's good to see you.
We can't go after Choi Chul Woo's money this time.
I'm sure he has barriers up after what happened two years ago,
so that we can't touch him.
I'm sure. He's pretty tough.
What should we do then?
Are you actually asking me? What's gotten into you?
Your intentions are better. Justice.
I want to shake off my personal feelings.
I got had because I followed my emotions.
I don't want to go to the slammer again.
I'm so sick of the sewing machine.
You be the navigation system.
I'll drive.
The elections in the suburbs are a month from now.
If Chun Gab Soo is re-elected,
Seowon won't change.
Even if we con people and collect back taxes,
the same people will use the money.
So?
What do you want to do?
We should look at the person, rather than the tax.
You'll pull down the jerks...
who ignore their duties but force it upon the citizens,
is that it?
How far do you plan to go?
All the way.
Duties aren't one-sided.
Mr Kim.
Mr Kim!
Where's Mr Kim?
I think he went to the restroom.
Does he still smoke?
What brings you here?
Welcome back.
Thanks.
What's wrong?
You look down.
- Did something happen?
-  No.
I went to see Da Mi's Diner earlier. That's why.
It's so good to see you again.
I should buy you something good to eat, instead of coming here.
I was craving soju so badly.
This is better.
Mr Baek.
Don't worry too much about Da Mi's Diner.
I'll pull the plug on the Maseok-dong development...
and save the restaurant...
by destroying Kukjin Construction.
Okay, let's do that.
What will you do about Mayor Chun?
We won't mark him.
He knows us too well.
Then who will?
Chairman Wang.
Chairman Wang?
Welcome back.
Thanks.
It's only natural that you go to prison if you commit a crime.
Don't you agree, Mr Fourth Offence?
Why aren't there any reporters?
We thought the chairman would be uncomfortable.
We told them we'd hold a separate press conference.
Good thinking.
A rich bad man getting released from prison doesn't deserve fanfare.
Even this is too much.
Why did you bring so many of the kids?
You could've just sent a bus ticket.
Stop saying things you don't mean. Where should we take you first?
- Would you like to go home...
-  No.
Not home.
Then where?
Yang Jung Do.
Where is he right now?
(Squad 38)
Mayor Chun wants to meet the chairman.
He gave a lot of money to our city.
Get me an appointment.
I'm Yang Jung Do.
Your 100 million in back taxes...
Is there anything I can do to help?
20 million? Loan scams?
Are you telling me to betray the chairman?
It's nice to meet you.
No one loves the country more than me.
Are you threatening me?
Look at the world with naive eyes, but don't be naive in life.
That's the only way to survive.