(THE FOLLOWING CONTENT MAY NOT BE SUITABLE FOR VIEWERS UNDER 15.)
(VIEWER DISCRETION IS ADVISED.)
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
So, will he do it?
That's good.
Then tell Cho Sang Jin...
to fudge the sales figures for Kukjin Construction in advance.
Okay.
Also,
don't get any funny ideas.
I don't trust you yet.
Okay.
The location is so...
It took me a while to find you.
Are you...
Baek Sung Il?
This is the first time...
we met in person, right?
I'm Choi Chul Woo.
(SQUAD 38)
(EPISODE 15)
Hi, Jung Do.
You need to come here.
We have a guest in our warehouse.
Well...
What brings you here?
I'm asking why you came here.
Oh, there you are.
I thought it'd be rude for me not to do anything...
when you kindly warned me like that.
That's why I'm here.
I'd like to reciprocate.
You didn't have to come all the way to this grungy place for that.
Would you like some tea?
We're out of tea. How about coffee?
Don't worry about it.
I'm okay.
I saw you both...
and said hello,
so I should get going now.
I'll let you get back to work.
I'm sorry that I took up your time.
By the way,
how did you find this place?
How did you know...
that we're here?
That is...
precisely why you guys can't beat us.
You don't know what's important.
Are you all right?
He sneaked in so quietly.
I think he saw that.
Darn it.
What about the other thing?
He didn't see that, did he?
The loan fraud targeting Cha Myung Soo and Cho Sang Jin.
I kept the file inside,
so it's safe.
So there's a reason why they're mobilising money.
(KUKJIN CONSTRUCTION)
They're doing it to distract us...
so that they can cover up the loan fraud.
Many hands are needed to mobilise money,
so they changed their target to loan fraud.
I haven't been informed of it yet.
I apologise.
Don't worry.
I don't think they leaked it intentionally.
They had to get out of the situation.
They'll hurl it at us.
He got all chatty...
all of a sudden.
Then what are you planning on doing now?
Get in touch with Prosecutor Park...
and tell him to get Myung Soo and Sang Jin when they show up...
at the bank to take the loan out.
Then Prosecutor Park will take care of the rest.
And bring the files that show...
that they've manipulated their accounting numbers.
Or how about we get to them...
before Mr Sa and Mr Cho touch the numbers?
If those files that show accounting manipulation...
leak outside of the company,
it could create damage for the company.
Make sure...
that they don't leak.
We need those files in our hands...
as insurance.
Insurance?
That's correct.
There's no guarantee that Mayor Chun will be elected.
If he doesn't get elected,
the Maseok-dong development project will not happen.
What are we in it for?
We should take whatever money we can get and take our hands off it.
Will you really...
go ahead with this?
Are you sure?
Let the useless CEO take out a fraudulent loan...
then sending him to jail...
would actually save me money.
But that could ruin Kukjin Construction...
for good, Sir.
Who cares about a company?
It's money that counts.
I don't need a company that creates empty expenses.
I can kill off a company I created, can't I?
What about me, then?
What...
can you give me?
Do you want money...
or power?
Both.
I want both, Sir.
Then...
stick close to me.
We can discuss this again in four years' time.
If Mayor Chun gets re-elected,
it'll be his third term, so he can't run again.
Even if he isn't re-elected, he still can't run again.
I'll need a new pawn.
Hello, Prosecutor Cho.
Yes.
Are you sure about that?
Prosecutor Cho just called, Sir.
Tell Jung Do to come over.
What do you mean?
Did someone sell him out?
I used all my connections in the Prosecutors' Office.
When you were jailed two years ago.
Prosecutor Park had a file on you.
It had circumstantial evidence of all your cons...
as well as evidence that money changed hands in the first con.
How could he have such information unless someone on the inside...
gave it to him?
Who gave it to him?
I don't know.
How can I know what the prosecutor doesn't?
Even Prosecutor Park doesn't know where it came from?
I'm guessing Chairman Choi helped.
He made sure no one knows where it came from.
If that person from two years ago...
still works for Chairman Choi,
then I'm pretty sure he knows...
what you're planning now.
I think we should pull the plug.
What do you think, Sir?
Shall we pull the plug?
Tell me what you think first.
To be very honest...
I shouldn't doubt my team.
Not after what I did.
I betrayed them first two years ago.
What will you do, then? Will you go on or stop?
I'll go on. Whatever happens.
Okay, then.
You do that.
Remember one thing, though.
I don't bet on a losing game.
Now that you involved me,
do your very best to make it work.
Do you understand?
Yes. I'll remember that.
What will you do about the spy?
Will you keep it?
What do you think?
Will you follow my suggestion?
What is it?
If we're going to do it,
we might as well be open.
That's so typically you.
Call everyone to the warehouse.
That's nonsense.
- Stop it.
- Shall we play?
- Hey.
- Hak Joo.
- How about a game of cards?
- No way.
He always wants to play.
I'm bored.
I called you all here...
- to say something.
- I'm serious.
- Hey.
- See this?
Be quiet, all of you.
Thank you, Ms Noh.
I called you because...
one of you...
betrayed us.
This person gave the prosecutors information about me two years ago.
This is just a guess,
but that person could have told...
Choi Chul Woo all our plans.
If that's true,
we're done for.
Who is the vermin? Who did it?
I don't know.
That's why you're all here.
I don't know who it is,
but remember one thing.
Two years ago, I took the fall.
Not this time.
If this con sinks,
too many will suffer.
That includes us all.
Sung Hee who went out on a limb to help us.
Da Mi and her grandfather who put their hope in us.
In a way,
that includes the people who are fighting for Maseok-dong.
They'll all get hurt...
if this con doesn't work out.
If you did this...
because you hated me and wanted revenge for something,
please hold back this once.
Someone told me I shouldn't play with one's heart.
If you do that...
The other person gets hurt...
and you become lonely.
I can deal with loneliness.
What I can't stand is the thought that...
others might get hurt.
So...
please...
hold back.
Just this once.
Please.
I'm done.
We'll get to work.
We won't stop because there's a leak.
We'll stick to the loan con.
There's no Plan B.
We'll go to the end.
Does anyone have anything to say?
If not,
let's begin.
Why are we here?
There are much nicer cafes.
They know.
- Know what?
- That there's a spy.
They know.
Do they know it's you?
No.
I don't think so.
What will they do?
Change the plans?
They don't want to suspect anyone, so it's still on.
Is that a con, too?
No.
I don't think so.
My gut says so.
What about you?
Me?
Wait.
Are you suspecting me now?
I'm here. Why else would I be here?
It's fine if you're clean.
When will they begin?
Here's what you asked for.
Thanks.
Sir.
Can I ask what you need that for?
Find a nice man and get married.
I have it.
Okay, then.
I'll be right there.
He just left.
Good.
Very well.
The rest is now...
in your hands.
Don't you worry, Sir.
Mr Ma.
I have the papers and I'm headed to the bank.
When will you be there?
Shouldn't you be there?
Of course I should be.
Which bank is first?
That one?
I know where it is.
I'll be right there.
See you soon.
See you.
I'm off.
Call when you're done.
Okay.
Will it work?
Let's make it work.
I'm off.
Call when you're done.
Okay.
Will it work?
Let's make it work.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
It's me.
I'm off to get a loan.
Have you heard from Choi Chul Woo?
Not yet.
If he doesn't call,
take the money and run.
Five million dollars...
is the same wherever it comes from.
Wait.
Weren't we going to get five million each...
and split that?
I'm doing my part.
I don't think you're doing anything.
I'm eating.
Stop bugging me...
and call when you're done.
Hello?
What a jerk.
I really don't like how he talks.
Come in.
Did you ask for me?
I did.
To ask for a favour.
I'm listening, Sir.
Why don't you quit your job and join my campaign?
What?
I need all the help I can get.
Help me...
Ms Chun.
Why?
Don't you want to?
I'm sorry...
to ask something like this.
Do you have to...
run again?
What do you mean?
You were mayor for eight years.
You saw a lot of possibilities,
but also a lot of boundaries and limits.
I think...
you should give it all up...
and make way for the next person.
Those limits.
Are you referring to Chairman Choi?
Sung Hee.
The Seowon I dream of.
A city where the people are happy.
This is the beginning.
Mayor Chun without the backing of Chairman Choi.
No one has seen that before.
I will show you...
what your father can do.
I'm leaving.
Here's your coffee.
Take that ledger and pass it to Chairman Choi.
I have to go through Cho Sang Jin's office.
Okay.
The money's in your account.
Sort things out.
Lie low if you can.
I'd rather never see you again. Okay?
Yes. I get the message.
Here he comes.
There are three.
Seven million each.
Prosecutor Cho, you can move in now.
- Seven?
- Hello.
How are you?
Hello.
It looks really nice.
Mr Cho, you're a real expert.
It's what I've done my whole life.
If you take these to 10 banks,
in just one day, you'll end up with an amount that...
you never dreamed of having.
You'll be richer than most people.
Congratulations.
Don't forget my commission, okay?
Don't you worry.
Be nice to others when you're doing well.
Let's go. We have to go to as many banks before closing time.
Let's go.
Will you emigrate?
I'm not really sure.
They say Canada's nice.
Hello, Sirs.
Isn't it a nice day?
Who are you?
Take them.
What? Let me go.
- Let go of me!
- Let go.
- What's going on?
- Hey.
- Who are you?
- Let go.
Let go of me.
How dare you touch me.
- Not so tight.
- Come along.
How could you do this to me?
Wait.
How could you, Director Ahn?
Wait and see.
Get in there.
Take good care of them for me.
Take this.
Check Mr Cho's office.
Who is Manager Kim?
- That's me.
- Ms Kim?
We're from Kukjin Construction. Do you have something for us?
Does anyone have anything to say?
If not,
let's begin.
It's me.
I did it.
Why did you do it?
Why?
Why did you betray us two years ago?
Da Mi's Diner?
Do you think I'm doing this because of the horrible food?
I'm not.
I'm doing this...
to get back at you.
I re-joined the team to give you a taste of your own medicine.
I gave the money to Commissioner Ahn two years ago.
It was all me.
I conned you.
Do you get it now?
So,
how do you feel?
This is what you get for betraying me.
Okay?
You jerk.
You shouldn't have done that to me, okay?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Did you tell them?
Did you tell them our plan?
How could you do that?
Hak Joo.
You're not a human being.
Why...
Why are you all taking it out on me?
Is it my fault? Is it?
If he didn't...
I'll quit!
Forget about it!
Give up and go home.
Why...
I'm sorry, Hak Joo.
Thanks for telling the truth.
What do you want to do?
I'll do as you say.
I don't get it.
Are you an idiot?
Let's finish this up and have some food.
- Okay.
Let's get something to eat.
Don't just sit there.
Okay. I'll help.
- Hurry up.
- Help out.
I haven't...
I haven't forgiven you yet.
I'll kill you when we're done.
They know our plan.
I told them everything.
We have to change the con.
How?
Forget about the loans. Let's go with accounting fraud.
Do you want to give the faked accounting books to the police?
No, that won't work.
They have a prosecutor working for them.
They'll have spies in every police station.
- Ja Wang.
- What?
Me?
Do you want me to post it all over the internet?
Yes, yes.
Korea is famous for its broadband internet.
Ja Wang. Ja Wang.
Scan these...
Ja Wang...
I had...
a tail put on you.
Idiocy can't be helped.
You let your emotions take control.
You did it with Mr Bang.
You had the girl follow him around.
Why do you stick to the same methods?
It's been two years. Shouldn't you be more creative?
Hand that over. I have to take it to Chairman Choi.
They're on to us!
Let go. Let go.
What? Let go!
What? What?
Hak Joo. Hak Joo!
Hak Joo!
What's wrong? What is it?
What is it?
Hey.
Clean this up and go home.
I'm on my way, Sir.
Good.
Good work.
Come in.
Mayor Chun is here.
Mayor Chun?
Why?
Show him in.
What brings you here?
You didn't even call.
I came to cut my ties with you.
Ja Wang, are you okay?
Hak Joo. Hak Joo.
Hak Joo. Darn it.
Hak Joo, wake up.
Hak Joo!
- What... What happened?
- What happened?
Call 911. Hurry.
Hey. Hey.
911?
What do you mean?
Cut ties with me?
Are you feeling sick?
Did you get heat exhaustion or something?
You always thought I was beneath you, right?
To you, Sir,
I'm just another fool.
I'll call you later.
Okay.
You acted like you listened to me, feared me and respected me.
That's how you've handled me all this time.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Two years ago,
when he found out you cut him loose, Mr Ahn was very bitter, too.
How could you do this?
Be quiet and move!
I thought Mr Baek had done this to me.
But I was wrong.
Choi Chul Woo did it...
to cover his tracks.
This is what happens...
if you abandon your people.
Don't tell me...
you intentionally planted...
Mr Ahn...
against me.
I'm sorry, Sir.
If this gets out, the prosecutors will dig into Kukjin Construction...
and...
you'll lose your source of income.
Is that what you want?
What do you want?
Disappear from my life.
Hello?
Pardon?
I understand.
I'll bring her right over.
Okay.
Why? What is it?
There was an accident.
I'll be a mayor who is not obsessed with money.
I'll be a mayor who does not work with dirty money.
I'll be a mayor who looks at and stands with the people.
That's the type of mayor I'll be,
so...
disappear from my life...
and from Seowon City.
I understand what you mean.
I do,
but if you were such a person,
you never should've come to me.
Money...
doesn't entice...
clean people.
Why don't you know yourself?
What could I say when you have your hand around my throat?
I'll do that.
I will disappear...
from your life...
and Seowon City.
But remember this one thing.
You and I are the same.
Even with the Maseok-dong development matter.
I couldn't do it alone,
but once you and I joined forces...
Soon enough,
you'll realise what kind of a person you are.
The Maseok-dong development is my final consideration toward you.
We will never have to meet again.
Did you get a new sponsor?
The election is just around the corner,
but you are too confident.
It suddenly made me wonder...
if you had a new deep pocket.
Are you done?
What did they say?
Pardon?
Will they live or die? What will happen to them?
You're confused.
They're sleeping after eating all of this.
Their lives aren't in jeopardy.
Where are Mr Baek and Jung Do?
What will you do now?
We'll start over.
How?
Do you know why the chairman has been supporting you?
Because you were as skilled as you were arrogant.
But Jung Do,
all I see right now is arrogance.
That's not it.
You're being arrogant again.
Don't make excuses.
Just tell me the conclusion. What will you do?
How will you take Chairman Choi down?
I don't know if it's okay for me to chime in,
but there's something I told myself for two years...
as I waited for Jung Do to get out.
Don't get tired.
Hang in there,
and once Jung Do gets out, let's fight.
Don't fight to win, but fight until we win.
We barely threw one jab.
We need to hit them more until they collapse.
It may have always been...
an impossible foe to go up against.
Choi Chul Woo is no easy foe.
What will you do now, Sir?
Tell Detective Sa Jae Sung...
that I want to see him.
Next.
According to the public survey,
Mayor Chun Gab Soo...
and Woo Soo Myeong are...
leading the polls.
The two of them are throwing everything in...
and battling.
Mayor Chun Gab Soo has 21.5 percent,
and Woo Soo Myeong has 21.1 percent.
There is a difference of only 0.4 percent...
I hope I'm not disturbing you when you're busy.
No, it's okay. What is it?
I've left...
Kukjin Construction.
Why?
I went in to help you cut ties with the chairman.
There was no reason to remain. I finished my job, too.
I need to find my own life now.
I'd like to be vice-mayor of Seowon, Sir.
I will devote myself to you.
I will give my life to you and Seowon.
The current vice-mayor...
is soft and doesn't do anything anyway.
You are a smart man.
Why are you trying to do something so foolish?
I'm not smart.
I'm not smart and I'm foolish.
That's why I've been doing your dirty work all these years.
That's a bit harsh.
No one knows as well as I, what you've done...
with what types of people...
and what you did to become free of them.
You need to have someone who knows everything about you...
by your side in order to win this election.
The margin is razor-thin.
Between you and Woo Soo Myeong.
Are you threatening me?
I'm begging you.
I'm asking you to save me.
What would happen if I can't bear it and I go to Chairman Choi Chul Woo?
You can't want that.
Chairman Choi...
doesn't know the details of what happened eight years ago.
Should I go and tell him...
what you and Mr Bang did eight years ago?
Ahn Tae Wook!
Have some respect.
The margin is narrow.
This will come down to money anyway.
Now that you've lost Chairman Choi, what can you do?
And why did you give...
the Maseok-dong development right to Choi Chul Woo?
A beautiful parting.
Do you think there is such thing in this country?
You seem to have bet on Chairman Kim Chang Soo...
of Sangjin Group, which is why you decided...
to cut free from Chairman Choi.
But that is friendship, not politics.
You should hold onto the Maseok-dong development right...
and do another type of politics.
To put it bluntly,
you don't really know what Kim Chang Soo is like.
What do you mean?
I mean Chairman Kim Chang Soo of Sangjin Group.
Right?
That is why you need me.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Let me hear it.
What is worth 5 million dollars?
Hello, Sir.
Did you know Chairman Kim Chang Soo was looking after those con artists?
Forget it.
Whether or not you knew isn't important.
Ahn Tae Wook...
is meeting him right now.
You're a businessman.
Don't waste your time with those con artists and work with us.
How did you find out?
I looked into how Noh Bang Sil...
was able to get involved,
and I followed up the line...
and it led me to you.
Are you telling me...
to betray Jung Do?
Yes, I am.
It is beneath you to work with a con artist like him...
just because of your friendship...
from when you were in prison. You have a status to uphold.
- What if I refuse...
- The Maseok-dong development...
right will go to someone else.
We are doing politics right now.
You are a businessman, are you not?
You should do business.
Baek Sung Il. Yang Jung Do.
Cut them loose and work with us.
Then we will give you the Maseok-dong...
development rights.
With this much politics and this much business,
it's a great synergy.
I will...
work with Chairman Kim Chang Soo.
But...
it won't be the way you guys want.
Look at the world with naive eyes,
but don't be naive in life.
That's the only way to survive.
Goodbye.
Mr Mayor. Mr Mayor?
Hi, Sung Hee, what's up?
Mr Baek.
The mayor found out about Chairman Wang...
and Jung Do's relationship.
Okay.
Please make your decision.
There isn't that much time.
Mr Kim!
Yes, Sir.
Tell Jung Do...
to put this job...
on the back burner for now.
Pardon?
Yes, Sir.
(CHAIRMAN CHOI CHUL WOO)
It's me, Choi Chul Woo.
What is it?
I'm sure we don't have...
I have a question for you.
That's why I called.
You'll be shocked as well, once you hear it.
(CHAIRMAN WANG)
Yes, Sir.
I've cut ties with Jung Do.
So Bang Sil, you should also...
cut ties with Jung Do.
Let's live as proper businessmen.
Do you understand?
Eight years ago.
Kim Min Sik.
That man.
I heard he didn't commit suicide.
(SQUAD 38)
I'll tell you who made me do this.
Bang Pil Gyu killed him...
and I covered it up.
So this is how it ends.
Let's put an end...
to our relationship.
Sir!
Find your own way.
You worked hard getting here.
Where should I meet you?
We need to split the money.
Thanks.
Where is it?
I can't keep my promise.
Stay on Choi Chul Woo...
and collect his back taxes.