BioskopKeren,org
That's what we'll do,
Is it Chairman Wang's order?
No, It's my decision,
Okay, then,
Let's do it,
Thank you,
Mi Joo, help Ms Noh,
Okay,
Let's do as he asked,
If,,,
for some reason it doesn't work out,
find your own way out,
Ms Choi and Mi Joo, you, too,
Will you not tell them?
I can't tell them all that,
They'll feel hurt,
Especially Mi Joo,
Who cares?
I'm a con artist, remember?
(Squad 38)
(Final episode)
How will you get out?
Pardon?
This con,,,
will most likely fail,
We might have no time,
You need to fend for yourself,
What will you do?
What do you think?
I think,,,
we should do as Chairman Wang said,
Yes,
We should,
That's the right thing to do,
Hi, Sung Hee, what's up?
Mr Baek,
The mayor found out about Chairman Wang,,,
and Jung Do's relationship,
Okay,
(Mr Kim)
Hello?
I have to go,
Let me hear it,
What is worth five million dollars?
Do you remember Kim Min Sik,,,
who worked at Seowon City Hall eight years ago?
The man who killed himself,,,
trying to use Pil Gyu,,,
to get to me?
Who told you that,,,
it was suicide?
Bang Pil Gyu killed him,
and made it look like suicide,
Mayor Chun,,,
covered it up,
Is that true?
What do you think?
Isn't it well worth,,,
five million dollars?
There are times,,,
when money is earmarked for someone,
Those bills,,,
were meant for you,
Take them,
(Jang Hak Joo)
How will you get out?
You need to fend for yourself,
(Jang Hak Joo)
You cannot reach,,,
Shoot,
Why isn't Mi Joo picking up?
What a brat,
Hak Joo, Hak Joo,
Can you feed me?
I'm starving,
Please?
I can't bend my arm,
The seaweed,,,
I can't eat myself,
You idiot,
I'll feed you,
You made the seaweed look so tasty,
Did I?
- Wrap some rice in it first, - This first, rice later,
Eat this and this,
- Slow down, - Just eat,
Is it good?
Yes,
- Down this, - It's hot,
It'll cool in your stomach,
Hello, Mr Hwang,
Hello, Ms Choi,
Why does Ms Noh want to see me?
Come upstairs,
She wants to give you a special tip,
It has to be kept a secret,
What story is this?
You'll find out,
(Chairman Wang)
Yes, Sir,
I've,,,
cut ties with Jung Do,
So,
Bang Sil, you should also,,,
cut ties with Jung Do,
Let's live as proper businessmen,
Do you understand?
I'll do that, Sir,
Reporter Hwang is here,
Thanks for coming over,
Have a seat,
Wait until he comes,
Will that do?
Yes,
Then let's discuss money,
Sure, Sir,
What is the information you have for me?
I'll give you a tip about a con artist,
Mr Yoon,
Is the chairman in?
Go away, Jung Do,
After I see the chairman,
Let go, Let go,
I said let go,
Mr Kim, it's me, Jung Do,
You can't do this to me,
Chairman, Chairman, I,,,
Hear me out!
- You can't do this to me, - Shouldn't you go out?
I already cut ties with him,
Why should I see his face?
Sir!
Hear me out!
Don't do this to me!
Sir!
Sir,
There's one way to get rid of,,,
Yang Jung Do for good,
Shall I tell you?
You might as well,,,
spend a bit more on me,
I'll get the whole team of them,,,
off your back,
You're really determined,
There's so much I can do now that I'm not a policeman,
Give me,,,
five million more,
Then I'll get rid of Jung Do,,,
and the public official,
I can do that,,,
- without your,,, - Ma Jin Seok,
He didn't,,,
name those two,
Who's the broker?
Will you really not say?
You wanted Ma Jin Seok,,,
to name Jung Do and Baek Sung Il,,,
and lock them up for brokering the fraudulent loans,
but Jin Seok is keeping his mouth shut,
One call from me,,,
and he'll spill all,
Give me five million more,
Five more million,,,
and you can control Chun Gab Soo forever,
Not only that, you can get rid of the little insects,,,
who just won't leave you alone,
10 million dollars is nothing to you,
Okay, then,
Give me,,,
- a few days to,,, - No,
I can't wait,
I want it now,
In cash,
Then,,,
make 100 fake accounts and I'll wire,,,
No,
I want it in cash,
How am I supposed to trust you?
Cash is the only thing I trust,
It's hard to trace,
Mr Jang,
Yes, Sir,
Call our loan offices in Pyeong-dong,
and have them send over five million in cash,
Pardon?
Pardon? Five large?
Hello? Yes, how much?
Here you go,
I have three,
We need two more,
They're on the way,
Yes, Sir,
The man called Ma Jin Seok,
Is he still,,,
keeping his mouth shut?
Yes,
I offered to cut him loose,
but he won't budge,
Put him on,
- It's me, - Do you have it?
You bet,
I got 10, in fact,
Oh, that sounds lovely,
What shall I do?
What do you think?
Tell all,
Okay,
I'll tell you,,,
who put me up to this,
This is heavy,
Does five million weigh this much?
I'd never touched this much before,
Can you help?
Give him a hand,
8563,
Take a bill as a tip,
Look after yourself,
Spend all you have before you die,
I'm off,
Detective Sa,
That money,
It's just a loan,
It will come back to me,
Watch your back,
What a joke,
Mayor Chun,
It's Choi Chul Woo,
What do you want?
I'm sure we don't have any more to discuss,
I have a question for you,
That's why I called,
You'll be shocked as well, once you hear it,
Eight years ago, Kim Min Sik, That man,
I heard he didn't commit suicide,
Where are you?
The basement of Majang-dong 154-4, Block all exits,,,
and meet at the entrance,
Yes, Sir,
I'm on my way, Bye,
It's me,
Where shall we meet?
To split the cash,
Yes,
I'll be right there,
Get a suite,
Goodbye, then,
Wait,
Thanks,
You two stay here, You three, come with me,
- Yes, Sir, - Yes, Sir,
We meet again, Mr Baek,
I'm a prosecutor,
Why are you here?
Did you tell,,,
Ma Jin Seok to apply for fake loans?
He told us everything,
Where is Yang Jung Do?
We can talk in my office,
- Take him, - Yes, Sir,
How much do you know?
Pil Gyu had him killed,,,
and you covered it up,
Is there more to it than that?
Tell me what you want,
I want back in,
Keep me in the loop,
Keep me in your life,
Ja Wang, where is it?
In the lower part of the locker,
Why do you need it?
Mr Baek,
Do you know where Jung Do is?
Don't stall,
Tell me where he is and I'll cut you a deal,
Will you not cooperate?
Sir,
Why are you,,,
so loyal,,,
to Chairman Choi?
What?
I think this is all going really wrong,
Shouldn't public officials like us,,,
work for the public and not for a few rich individuals?
Isn't that why the people pay taxes to pay our salaries?
You need help,
I think this is all going really wrong,
Shouldn't public officials like us,,,
work for the public and not for a few rich individuals?
Isn't that why the people pay taxes to pay our salaries?
You need help,
How shall we make the transaction?
We can host a book publication party or wire it to multiple accounts,
There are many ways,
No, Such methods,,,
are tedious and easy to trace if we get caught,
Instead of beating around the bush,
let's do it directly,
Mr Kim, are you there?
- Sir? - How much cash,,,
can we put together right now?
Let me find out, Sir,
Yes,
Don't embarrass me,
Bring as much as you can,
Yes, Sir,
I don't understand,,,
what is going on,
Isn't it obvious?
You taught me about politics,
I'll teach you a bit about business,
This is how I do business,
Can you really not,,,
let go of me, Sir?
Please,
I want to be a great mayor,
Please, Sir,
You are,,,
already a great mayor,
There couldn't be a better mayor,,,
for me,
You may go,
If you're done,
Hello,
But why didn't you bring the money?
Money?
What money?
Why would I give you any money, you punk?
You didn't do anything right,
This isn't right,
You said to split it evenly regardless of who succeeds first,
Hey, Ma Jin Seok,
- Do you want to go back to prison? - What?
If I pay some of the guys who used to work under me,
I can get you,,,
locked up right now,
Should I do that?
Why are you doing this to me, Detective Sa?
I quit being a detective long ago,
Take care,
That nasty old fogy,
It's me,
Why don't we go out for dinner?
Let's get some wagyu beef,
And Honey, I'm going to be a company president now,
Forget that, That sounds weird,
Chairman sounds better, Call me "Chairman Sa",
Look,
You must not understand what's going on,
You are here for brokering fraudulent loans,
You're in no position to lecture others,
Yes, I know that,
but will you hear me out?
How will you give me the right to Maseok-dong?
I'll take care of it,
Chairman Choi Chul Woo has no choice but to listen to us,
given the current situation,
Come in,
The money has been prepared, Sir,
Has it?
Would you lend him your car keys?
Sure,
The trunk is very small,
Is it?
Then we should expand your trunk first,
You're doing such good work,
I'll be in touch,
Sure, Good day,
I'll be back,
Okay, bye,
- Let's go, - Okay,
Hello?
What kind of a mayor am I?
I thought I had to do it just once,
I thought if I'd accept their help just once,,,
and become mayor,
I could do the things I had dreamed of,
But you know,
in this world,
convenience becomes a privilege, consideration becomes a bribe,,,
and friendships become a crime,
Eventually, those things will hold me back,
Let me ask you one more time,
What kind of a mayor,,,
do you think your dad,
Mayor Chun Gab Soo is?
Okay,
I shouldn't have asked,
If I were a decent mayor,
you wouldn't have helped that con artist,
Okay,
I'm sure,
Mayor, I,,,
I'm sorry,
Get back to work,
Bye,
Is that true?
Yes,
What do you want me to do about it?
Your job,
Your duty,
That's what you should do,
You're a prosecutor,
I am giving you,,,
a chance,
I've convinced Chairman Kim Chang Soo,
Chairman Choi found out,
- Pardon? - About eight years ago,
Choi Chul Woo found out,
Don't worry too much,
There's no evidence,
And I'm sure Bang Pil Gyu is upset with Chairman Choi,
so if I go talk to him,,,
How far must we go?
What do you mean?
How far must we go for all of this to end?
It isn't easy for me to hear you say that,
We must go all the way,
Sure,
We must,
That way,
you'll become the vice-mayor,
Right?
I've received campaign funds from Chairman Kim,
I'll take care of Chairman Choi,
so you should focus on Chairman Kim from now on,
Okay,
Please take care of it,
Sir,
Hang in there,
I haven't shown you,,,
the Seowon that I dream of yet,
Thank you,
For what?
All I did was eat at a restaurant,
When is he being let go?
Now,
Now?
No, Not there, That tickles,
Would you turn on the news, please?
Sure,
Thank you,
- Turn on the TV, - Yes, Ma'am,
Breaking news,
Mayor Chun Gab Soo,,,
reportedly received 10 million dollars in illegal campaign funds,,,
and will likely be disqualified,
This morning, around 10am,
Kim, who runs a loan shark business in Pyeong-dong,
went to various illegal money lending companies,,,
and gathered five million dollars,
Kim thereafter went to the house and office,,,
of the past owner of Woohyang Group,
who now owes 100 million dollars in back taxes,
Chairman Choi Chul Woo,
What is the information you have for me?
I'll give you a tip about a con artist,
What kind of a con artist?
A true con artist who deceives the people of this country,
May I help you?
I came to report a crime,
This money,,,
was given to his broker Sa,
Sa, who used to be a detective,
brought the 10 million dollars,,,
to a coffee shop in Cheongsam-dong,
where he left his car and disappeared,
The second broker appeared here,
- What will you do to make a living? - The second broker,,,
Whatever,
The first broker, Sa,,,
Maybe I'll get a job at a detective's office,
He moved the money into another car and disappeared,
Thank you, You should go,
I should as well,
Okay,
Bye,
Don't bother people any more,
I'm a changed man,
Move the money around?
Yes,
How?
I asked Jin Seok,,,
to mark Sa Jae Sung,
According to him, Sa Jae Sung,,,
was called in by Choi Chul Woo,
Let me hear it,
What is worth five million dollars?
He'll get several million in exchange for some Intel,
I'll get the whole team of them,,,
off your back,
Give me,,,
five million more,
Then Choi Chul Woo will naturally gather that money,,,
from his loan sharks in Pyeong-dong Market,
Call our loan offices in Pyeong-dong,
and have them send over five million in cash,
While Sa Jae Sung moves with the money,
we'll dig a trap,
Where shall we meet?
To split the cash,
I'm saying let's swipe the money,
Ja Wang, where is it?
In the lower part of the locker,
Hello,
But why didn't you bring the money?
Money? What money?
Why would I give you any money, you punk?
You didn't do anything right,
Then we'll take that money and give it to Chairman Wang,
The money has been prepared, Sir,
Has it?
Chairman Wang will pretend it's his and give it to Ahn Tae Wook,
The trunk,,,
is very small,
Is it?
Then we should expand your trunk first,
Is Chairman Wang with him now?
Yes, Ahn Tae Wook just figured out that Chairman Wang,,,
is working with us,
So we asked Chairman Wang to act like he's switching sides,
I've,,,
cut ties with Jung Do,
If we move the money like that,
Pyeong-dong loan sharks' money,,,
will go to Choi Chul Woo,
and through a broker,,,
It will be handed over to a second broker,,,
Who will give that money,,,
To Chun Gab Soo's campaign,,,
as an illegal contribution,
Then Choi Chul Woo, Chun Gab Soo, Ahn Tae Wook,
Sa Jae Sung and the second broker,,,
will all go down,
Who will be the second broker?
I bought someone who will go to prison for us,
You bought someone? You don't have the money,
Why wouldn't I have the money? I have a lot of money,
I'll take care of it, so don't worry too much,
Ms Noh, call the reporter and have him follow with his camera,
Mi Joo, report it to the police, Okay?
Okay,
That's all,
Is it Chairman Wang's order?
No, It's my decision,
The money transferred to the second broker, Yang,
was transferred to Ahn, who is known to be,,,
Mayor Chun Gab Soo's aide,
Even if that happens,
unless someone on the inside testifies,
there's no way,
The case will be dragged out and eventually dropped,
What if we have someone who will testify?
And who would that be?
You know Yang Jung Do, don't you?
You locked him up two years ago,
Sir, Jung Do and I,,,
must do this,
If Jung Do,,,
didn't do this,
we couldn't even touch,,,
those rats that we should be fighting,
If he didn't fight like this,,,
The shocking fact about Mayor Chun's illegal funds,,,
We could never beat them,
It is because the first broker, Sa,
was a detective,
- Isn't that Jung Do? - And that the second broker, Yang,
- It is, - Is an ex-convict,
And more people around us would have been hurt,
He was preparing to escape,,,
and was arrested,,,
All those people who worked with me,
At least for all those people,
I need to fight like this,
So,,,
please do this for us,
To whom must government workers like us look to?
For whom and with whom must we fight?
Please think about that,
Please show the people whose side the law is on,
Let Baek Sung Il go,
Did you convince him?
That's why I'm out,
It was worth getting arrested,
I'm sorry,
For what?
It's only natural that I should go,
You're a public official and I'm a con artist,
I'm sorry, I can't keep the promise I made you,
Even if I can't,
you have to,
Don't get fired,
Okay, I won't,
Okay, then,
We should each go our way,
Okay, let's get those rats,
You in your way, and I in mine,
That's right,
My dad gets out in a year, but there's no one,,,
to pick him up,
Would you go for me?
Of course,
Don't worry,
Thank you, Sung Il,
(Broker Yang confesses about the origin of the "black money",)
What happened?
How will you fix this?
- How will you,,, - Sir,
There are only three things,,,
that we can do,
I can make Mr Ahn take the fall and save myself,
You can go public about what happened eight years ago,,,
and destroy me and save yourself,
And finally,
we can both die,
Which would you prefer?
Which route would you like me to take?
I would prefer it not be,,,
the 1st or 3rd,
We apparently disagree,
Goodbye,
Call Prosecutor Park,
I can't get in touch with him,
Why not?
Why not, all of a sudden?
I'm sorry, Sir,
Long time no see,
We don't have time, so I'll get right to it,
I delivered the money,
Whose money did you deliver to whom?
I delivered Choi Chul Woo's money to Mayor Chun Gab Soo,
I got the money from Sa Jae Sung,
So this is how it ends,
Why do you think that?
There's no proof that Mr Ahn gave me the money,
Jung Do is being interrogated as we speak,
Once he's done,
there will be a public announcement that Chairman Choi Chul Woo,,,
gave you illegal campaign funds,
It's over,
I'll go now,
Sung Il,
I need to tell you something,
Min Sik,,,
didn't commit suicide,
Bang Pil Gyu killed him,,,
and I covered it up,
I knew that already,
I found out while investigating,,,
Choi Chul Woo,
You knew, but you didn't do anything about it?
To be honest, I wanted,,,
to grab you by the collar and beat you to a pulp,
- But I couldn't do it, - Why not?
Why didn't you do it?
Because there was something I had to do,
What Min Sik tried to do back then,
What you wanted to do,
I had to do it,
Gab Soo,
You know,
I wish you'd go back to the person you used to be,
Back then,
you were really cool,
I'll go now,
(Sung Hee)
Hi,
I wanted to answer,,,
your question from earlier,
You were,,,
a mayor consistent with,,,
the husband Mum said you were,
You tried to be,,,
a good husband and a good dad,
but Mum had a tough time because you were never there,
She said that's why she had no choice but to leave,
From now on,
don't make Seowon,,,
and the people of Seowon,,,
end up like Mum,
Please,
Sung Hee,
I have one request,
Collect all of the back taxes,,,
that Chairman Choi Chul Woo owes,
Okay,
I will,
The accusation of illegal campaign funds raised yesterday,,,
are all true,
For the past eight years,
I had been receiving illegal political funds,,,
from Chairman Choi Chul Woo,
During the last elections,
I received funds far exceeding,,,
the campaign funding limits,
and violated,,,
election laws,
(Wife)
I knew,,,
about Chairman Choi Chul Woo's loan shark business,,,
in Pyeong-dong Market,
Kukjin Construction's illegal acts and Chairman's Choi's taxes owed,,,
I'll be home late,
I catered to people like Choi Chul Woo,
I,,,
convinced myself that it was necessary in order,,,
to run the city,
I realised,,,
I can't create a city in which the people can be happy,,,
by breaking laws and sacrificing my conscience,
That is why I came here today,,,
to tell the truth,
I was wrong,
Accordingly,
I will,,,
withdraw from my candidacy,,,
for mayor of Seowon City,
I also promise to cooperate with the prosecutor,
That is all,
Mr Choi Chul Woo,
We've confirmed that the 60 loan shark businesses in,,,
Pyeong-dong and Kukjin Construction are wholly owned by you,
We will proceed simultaneously with the prosecutor's investigation,
We will proceed with the search and seizure,,,
right now,
- Proceed, - Yes, Sir,
Hello,
It must be eating you up inside,
You must not have friends, playing alone like this,
I heard you got your old position as chief back,
Congratulations,
There's no need,
I was a chief to begin with,
I came to tell you something,
I paid all of my taxes, What could you possibly have to say?
My gosh, You paid 100 million dollars in taxes,
You should at least hear this,
What is it? Let me hear it,
Local tax of 9,27 million dollars,,,
and national tax of 91,72 million dollars,
for a total of 100,98 million dollars,
Your total tax owed of 100,98 million dollars,,,
has been paid in full,
It took you a while,
Continue with your game,
(Chase until the end and collect it all,)
It's nice to meet you,
- Thanks, - Thank you,
K University, which had been in the news lately,,,
because of the director's corruption has been found,,,
to have received 20 million dollars anonymously,
We do not know who gave them the money,
but there is a rumour that the director,,,
had been a victim of real estate fraud recently,
People are wondering,,,
who was generous enough to give the university 20 million dollars,
Some of the students feel this incident,,,
is similar to when someone threw 50 million dollars,,,
into the streets of Seowon City,,,
several years ago,
The 50 million dollars in Seowon City,
The 20 million dollars at K University,
We don't know who gave away,,,
tens of millions of dollars and why,
but many people are cautiously saying,,,
they think they are both,,,
the work of the same people,
(A pile of money given to a university hurt by corruption)
(Squad 38)
Sung Il, you punk,,,
What, you rat?
I'm Park Woong Chul, you punk,
Sung Il,
Who? Sung Il?
Do you know me?
What are you doing?
Darn it, I'm getting out soon,
(Thank you for watching Squad 38,)
(We will be back,)