I need you to come with me to give a statement.
Will you come? Will you come along?
Is this the police?
I want to report something.
Fraud.
(Episode 4)
Here. I got the money.
I withdrew everything from my account.
Here you go.
Why are you giving it to me?
Right.
Goodness. I'm so out of it today.
I need to explain a few things to you. Should we sit down?
Sure. Have a seat.
I need you to come with me.
Read and sign below.
All right.
Because of smart phones, personal information leaks.
It causes this kind of incidents a lot these days.
There is a page on the back.
If you follow our instruction, you won't have any problem.
But the world is so chaotic now.
Mr Noh.
Hello?
Someone is at the door.
Who are you?
Yes. Are you Mr Noh?
Yes. I'm Noh Deok Gi.
We've got a report on you. I'm the police.
The police?
Yes.
What brings you here?
I'm Kim Doo Man from Gangnam Police Station Serious Crimes Squad.
I'm a detective.
A public official.
You called to report voice phishing, right?
I need you to come with me to give a statement.
What? I never reported to the police.
- What?
-  I didn't report to the police.
- You didn't notify us?
-  No, I didn't.
Why not?
Why didn't you report? You should report the police.
Then who made the report?
Why are you asking me?
Then who should I ask? No, it's...
I was sent here because you made a police report.
But you're telling me you didn't notify us.
Whose report was it then?
Why do you keep asking me?
Well...
Maybe your co-worker called the police.
You got a call from a real estate agency, right?
I did get a call from a real estate agency.
It was from a real estate agency.
Gosh, I'm sorry.
I'm so busy that I'm so forgetful these days.
Did this man from the Financial Supervisory Service take care of it?
Yes, he did.
Hold on.
How did you know that he's from the Financial Supervisory Service?
Detectives know everything.
I know because I'm a detective.
He's wearing a name tag.
Anyway, I need you...
to come with me to the police station.
Why should I?
Don't ask why. I just need you to come with me right now.
It's very urgent.
I'm asking why I should go with you.
- It's...
-  Gosh. You can't drag me there.
What kind of a detective does this?
Are you really a detective?
Do you think I'm lying to you?
I'm a cop, of course.
Do you think we are a bunch of fools?
You should listen to what I say and come along.
Let's go. We must hurry.
- You can't do this. You don't...
-  My gosh.
- even have a warrant.
-  I said we must hurry.
- My goodness.
-  We're running out of time.
- Hold on.
-  Let's go.
- Gosh.
-  Hold on.
Mr Noh.
I think you'd better go to the police office with him.
All you have to do is give a statement.
It's just a formality. It won't take long.
Yes. It won't take long.
You should've said it sooner.
- I'll head back to office and...
-  You should listen to...
what the police says.
What are you doing here?
Sung Hee. What are you doing here?
Chief. What on earth are you doing?
Hang on.
I called the police. You should go if you don't want to get caught.
The police will be here. This man is a swindler.
What?
Were you just trying to con me?
You two are swindlers!
- Sir, listen to me.
-  Chief!
The police are coming.
Sung Hee, wait a minute.
Sir, I will explain the whole thing.
Let me explain.
Just a moment.
Sung Hee.
I can't leave here like this.
This all started because of me.
What have you got yourself into?
We've got a report.
Who called the police to report fraud?
(Squad 38)
We need you to come with us to make a statement.
How did you find out about this?
I just happened to...
By the way, the man in the car is another victim.
He is my co-worker.
The investigation will determine who is a victim.
Please come with me. You are the reporter.
I have a lot of cash at home.
It won't take long. Get in the car.
I can't leave it there.
I can't believe this.
I'm telling you that I got swindled.
What are you talking about?
You should ask if I'm okay first.
How can you ask about money?
You are ridiculous.
Where are you now?
What?
Are you gambling again?
Don't you dare lie to me.
Stop gambling, you idiot.
I will break your wrist so that you can't play cards.
You are not at a sauna.
I can even hear you shuffling cards.
(Nambu Police Station)
Ms Chun Sung Hee. Mr Noh Deok Gi.
Please wait here for a few minutes.
You will be sent home after writing a statement.
Are you scared?
You should have run away earlier. Why didn't you?
I would've made a fool of myself.
You sound like a decent man.
It's me.
Is everything okay in the office?
I will be there soon.
I will see you soon.
Hello?
It's me. Noh Deok Gi.
That's right.
- I'm at the police station.
-  How did they know my name?
I almost got swindled.
I can't believe this.
Ms Chun Sung Hee. Mr Noh Deok Gi.
Please wait here for a few minutes.
You will be sent home after writing a statement.
I never told them my name.
This is ridiculous.
- Some crazy man...
-  Police.
- Hello.
-  Hi.
We received a report on fraud.
- A fraud?
-  Yes.
I don't know about that.
Oh no.
I guess you got a prank call.
Pardon?
Okay. Thank you.
I will buy you a drink later.
That's okay. Give me a call later.
Let's go.
I will see you later.
Thank you.
The car is here.
What?
Let's go.
Get in the car. We don't have much time.
Okay.
What?
Ma'am.
I got it.
What is going on now?
Well, it was a success.
- Gosh.
-  Give me your hands.
I was startled. You should have told me sooner.
Wasn't it fun?
This is what fraud is.
Oh my goodness.
It was the perfect timing.
- Let's go.
-  Okay.
Are you saying that...
I need to stay quiet to get my money back?
You can't sue us as we don't leave any evidence behind.
And a civil litigation...
can't be an option as it will take forever.
Let's take it easy.
You should always put people before money.
Don't you think?
Hello?
I need to talk to you.
Chief!
I will be back soon.
Why do we have so many meddlers for this business?
It's very distracting.
Why are you not saying anything?
I explained the whole thing.
It's your turn to say something.
Don't do it.
Just stop what you are doing.
I understand...
it doesn't make sense to swindle tax out of a delinquent taxpayer.
I knew you'd react so.
It is not what public officials are supposed to do.
- Sung Hee.
-  I'm not talking about...
the law or your duty as a public official.
I'm just worried that you'd get hurt.
Don't do it.
Ma Jin Seok is not worth risking your whole career.
Chief.
What if...
I manage to get all 5.77 million...
that Ma Jin Seok owes the government?
Can you stop?
Sung Hee.
Commissioner Ahn is covering for him.
You can't make him pay up.
Stop talking such nonsense.
I'll do it.
I'll make him...
pay the 5.77 million.
Sung Hee.
You can drink.
I can now.
I see.
When did you become a public official?
You studied art.
After what you did to me,
I learned to hate abstract ideas.
Public officials stick to the law.
You seem close to your chief.
He's an honest man.
He's very different from you.
That's why I like him.
I'm lost for words.
If...
we meet again, even by chance,
don't even say hi.
You disgust me.
Sir.
What?
Can you help me?
Listen up.
Ma Jin Seok.
He owes the government a total of 5.77 million dollars,
including 520,000 in local tax.
We're going to get him.
He's both tough and mean,
so brace yourselves.
He abuses his rights,
and ignores his duties,
and it's time we taught him a lesson.
- Yes, Sir.
-  Let's go.
Real estate fraud.
We get the target to buy land...
and we take the profit.
Clamp all his cars.
- I'll go inside.
-  Yes, Sir.
Get clamping.
I need help over here.
Here's our plan.
It's simple.
It's fraud. Why make it hard?
We're here to see Mr Ma.
Who is this Mr Ma?
23-1 Hwado-ri, Bongpyeong-eup in Hwaseong.
That's the plot we'll sell to Jin Seok.
I know that Mr Ma...
This is obstruction of justice.
Open the door!
- We can't get in.
-  Hey!
- How's your shoulder?
-  Bad.
16 acres worth 240,000 dollars.
Say, for example, that I have a son who has a son.
Call the police.
- Call them!
-  Ma'am.
We won't leave.
We will take what your son owes.
My son and I...
If he has a son who has a son,
that would be 500 to 600 years down the line.
Anyway,
even after all that time,
these 16 acres will never be redeveloped.
We will sell this to our dear Mr Ma.
That's our plan.
- He's in the family portrait.
-  Right?
- Come on.
-  How dare you.
I think two large bills will cover...
all the expenses needed to pull this off.
Six million is the price.
If this is to work,
we need you to do well.
Jin Cheol.
Let us in.
One whisper from you and men in bed...
with a stroke jump up to buy land.
Is that true?
Ms Noh, buy the land...
and give him the bait.
Mr Ma Jin Cheol?
We know that your older brother transferred...
some of his assets to you in 2009.
Who did what?
Did you see it happen? Did you?
Spread rumours that this plot...
is near an area that will be redeveloped soon,
and that the profit will last him three generations.
Then Jin Seok will come looking for you,
and we will get to work.
What do you say?
- Go.
-  Leave.
Get out of here! Will you just get the hint?
Let's go, Sung Hee.
Wait.
Mr Ma Jin Seok?
I'm from Taxation Office Division...
Never mind.
Listen carefully.
I will...
report you to the prosecutors.
If you don't want to rot in jail for the rest of your life, pay up!
What do you want?
I heard you planned something.
With Jung Do.
What are you scheming?
What do you want?
I heard you planned something.
With Jung Do.
What are you scheming?
Please help me, Sir.
If we report him to the authorities,
we can make him pay...
There is a process to everything.
If we were to ignore it like you do, nothing would work.
You know me.
I'll follow the protocol.
But you ignored everything already.
You went to see people who have nothing to do with this,
clamped their cars, disrupted their businesses and caused a fuss.
What protocol is there to keep now?
Sir, I...
I really need to make him pay up.
I need your help. Please, Sir.
Sung Hee.
What you should be saying to me now...
is not "I need your help" or "please".
It's "I apologise."
"It will never happen again."
Do you get that?
Good job.
Split it up into eight separate plots.
I'll wire you the fee right now. Bye.
We purchased all 16 acres.
You're good at what you do.
Thank you.
I want out.
What?
A detective came by.
He seemed to know all about what you did to Noh Deok Gi.
But still,
if you quit on us now, we can't reel Jin Seok in.
You're the only one who can bring him in.
Use Noh Deok Gi.
He taught your target all about real estate.
He can't act to save his own life.
We can't use an outsider. He can jump ship at any time.
Then close up shop.
This one stinks.
I can't.
I have to go on.
It's not on you.
What's the real reason you're doing this?
Why would a man like Chairman Wang...
care for the likes of you?
I have too many doubts.
What is it?
Why are you doing this?
My ex-husband told me to date...
a widower or a divorced man, but not a single man.
Single men can't be trusted.
You're like that.
I can't see through you.
The land is yours.
Call it my farewell gift, corny as that is.
Who is it?
- Hi, Sir.
-  You're at home.
Wow, what a great view.
If you found a place to stay,
the least you could do is have me for a meal.
Where are your manners?
How do you pay rent?
Did you buy the place?
Why are you so quiet?
I heard...
you got your fangs...
into an old land-crazy man.
Is that how you could afford this place?
What do you mean?
Don't look so scared.
How many large ones did you get?
What on earth do you mean?
Did I tell you not to do anything...
to rouse my suspicions or not?
Hey.
Do you want to be like your father?
Do you want to prove an apple doesn't fall far from the tree?
I know.
Your dad was a corrupt cop,
and you got into fraud as soon as you got out of jail.
What kind of a mess is that?
No family should be like that.
I just...
If you're going to con someone, do it properly.
Even if I were to lock you up, I wouldn't get much of a fanfare.
You stole too little.
You're a waste of space.
Next time, do something big.
Okay?
I'll see to it that you stay in until you're 60.
Like your dad did.
I live in a rotten little apartment,
and you have a nice flat.
How much does a place like this cost?
I have too many doubts.
What is it? Why are you doing this?
Ms Noh quit on us.
We need a change of plan.
Yes.
We still need to reel Jin Seok in.
Let's try something else.
He likes to bet on golf, right?
Hak Joo, did you check...
the indoor golf place he goes to?
Mecca Golf in Cheongsam-dong. Three times a week.
Cheongsam-dong?
Mi Joo, get a job there.
(Part-timer wanted)
When will you start?
Thank you. I can start tomorrow.
Ja Wang.
The thing I asked for.
These? We used those before.
What are those?
Remote controls.
Remote controls?
I'll explain it to you later.
Goodbye.
I'm here to check the system.
Is that PC number seven?
Yes.
Look carefully.
Press once for over par.
Press twice for under par.
Press thrice for a hole-in-one.
Don't you forget it.
Take it.
What's wrong with my swing?
It went in. Oh, my gosh.
- How did you do that?
-  I don't know.
I was terrible until now.
We have a caddie and remote control in place.
Now,
we need a golfer.
A golfer.
What?
Have fun.
Swing properly. You have to at least hit the ball.
It's so small.
It's tiny.
Are you new here?
We move into action as soon as the target appears.
Wait until he speaks to you first.
A conman isn't a lion. Be a crocodile. Wait for them.
Look at this.
I got Albatross.
- I didn't know it's possible.
-  It's amazing.
- You did an amazing job.
-  Thank you.
You must be thrilled.
What are you doing here?
Oh, it's you.
I wasn't expecting to see you here. How strange!
I have bad eye sight. What a surprise!
You look very awkward.
Do you play golf?
I thought you looked more like a pool person.
Golf is a great hobby for every middle-aged man.
A hobby? What a joke.
Forget it. Just carry on.
Just play with your own skills.
You have to make him think you're a pushover.
How is your daughter doing?
The world has become so equal.
Everyone plays golf these days.
Kids with rich parents and kids with poor parents...
study in the same classroom.
Equality is not a good thing.
Those stupid jerks...
don't know their place.
I'm not sure I can do this. I might make a mistake again.
I'm not good at golf.
I heard your nickname was Holiday Mother...
because you're so ferocious.
That's not...
Imagine your daughter-in-law insults your son.
People should know their place.
All those poor jerks...
who try to look rich.
Once a beggar, always a beggar.
That's how we feel about Ma Jin Seok.
His money is not his. It's taxes.
Wouldn't we be angry?
I guess.
He's not even paying taxes. He shouldn't show off his money.
That's why you're angry.
Will this do?
Get your uniform dry-cleaned.
Just follow your heart.
That's enough.
You seem to be struggling.
I guess both you...
and your daughter are good for nothing.
People should know their place.
Hey.
Ma Jin Seok.
- Me?
-  Yes, you.
You're a man. Why do you talk so much?
What?
Why don't you compete with me?
Why would I?
Do you have any money to bet?
You don't even have any money. Don't act up.
I don't have much money,
but I need a car.
As I work for the government, I can't take bribes.
I'd like to buy a car with your money.
Are you in or not?
What are you going to bet?
Me?
Fine. If I lose,
I'll give you up.
I'll let you go. What do you say?
Are you sure?
I'm a public official. I don't lie.
1,000 dollars per hole, deal?
Deal.
Good.
It's 1,000 per hole. Keep your words.
Let's get to it.
Nice shot.
Oh my.
That's too bad.
Shoot.
What were you trying to do?
Okay.
Nice shot.
Oh my.
- It was too short.
-  Gosh.
- That was close.
You didn't get anything in.
Look at that.
There you go.
Gosh.
You look tired. Should we stop here?
- Go on.
-  One more round? Okay.
All right.
Let's see.
Oh my.
Nice shot.
That was nice.
Stop.
Sorry?
Stay still.
Are you looking for something?
My goodness.
Weren't you holding something?
- No, I wasn't.
-  You weren't?
No.
Gosh.
Are you coming back?
Let's call it a day.
Hey. Be careful.
Are you feeling bitter?
I'll think of it as giving money to charity. It wasn't a lot anyway.
That's good. Think of it as donating money to the government.
Do you have any plans for tonight?
It's none of your business.
Let me treat you to some drinks now that I won some money.
I'm not much of a drinker.
I can treat you to a meal, then.
I'll give you the money back.
What?
I'm a public official.
I don't feel good about taking your money.
Let's have some nice dinner. We're like friends now.
I'll buy you dinner and give you the money back.
Let's go.
What a silly jerk.
The difference in Seowon City's tax increase rates between...
individuals and corporations, which are 122 percent...
and 50 percent respectively, has evoked strong opposition.
Seowon City is...
Here's the report on the merger, Ma'am.
I told you to talk in a casual way when we're alone.
How can you not change for 10 years?
Since it's a huge project, we should report directly to Chairman Wang.
Should I schedule a visit?
It reflects the increase in prices...
and the change in the tax environment.
Ji Yeon.
Yes.
Why do you think taxes go up every year?
Would it be because the government is running out of money?
They why did corporate and real estate tax go down?
It's because the lawmakers are rich.
Although I'm rich myself, this is not right.
It's not fair.
I promise that,
with this enlarged city budget,
I will carry out more realistic and active policies...
for the citizens.
The meat tastes great.
You can eat it as soon as it browns.
Why aren't you eating? It tastes great.
I don't really like the person in front of me and the smell.
You can't avoid the smell when you eat meat.
I'm afraid I can't do anything about the person, though. Try some.
Enjoy it yourself.
(Kim Sang Pil at Hwaseong City)
- Didn't you have something to say?
-  Please excuse me.
I have to answer this call.
That fatty.
Hello, Mr Kim. Go ahead.
I failed to get that money.
Of course, I'm interested...
in the Hwaseong New Town thing.
But I have no money saved up, and it's hard to get such big money.
The money I can get is not enough.
Yes, I'm talking about the Hwaseong New Town thing.
I understand that it's a great opportunity.
If you invest now,
you'll earn money that is worth dozens of cars, right?
Cut out the nonsense!
Why are you talking about cars all of a sudden?
What?
Anyway, do let me know when something comes up.
Who knows if I'll win the lottery?
Say only what's necessary. Don't ramble.
Okay. Thank you.
Let's drink together soon.
Okay. I'll talk to you later.
Gosh.
I'm sorry. It was an important call.
Weren't you saying something?
Let me fill your glass.
Thank you.
I'm afraid I overheard your conversation.
It sounded like you got some useful information.
Never mind.
Share it with me.
I'm just curious.
The thing is...
I know someone at Hwaseong City.
I'm not supposed to tell anyone.
Look at you.
You were going to say something. What about Hwaseong City?
This is a sensitive matter.
My friend might get in trouble if it leaks.
I want to be careful.
- I shouldn't...
-  Mr Baek. I'm a businessman.
I understand the importance of secrecy.
What about Hwaseong City?
There's this man...
who used to work with me and transferred to Hwaseong City.
He works in the urban development now.
Okay.
And they're planning a major development.
He's been persuading me to buy some land there...
before the plan becomes official. He says the land price will leap.
That's about it.
Is that so?
What's the expected earnings rate?
Five times.
- Five times?
-  Yes.
You're kidding me.
What kind of investment gives you five times earnings?
Oh my.
Take it or leave it. This is why I didn't want to tell you.
He's my close friend. He works for the city. He knows this stuff.
My goodness.
I have to go to the bathroom.
(He went to make a call.)
Are you ready?
Hi, Jin Seok.
I was about to call you.
Have you heard anything about Hwaseong New Town?
The expected earnings rate is five times, and I don't believe it.
How do you know that?
I had to pay a fortune...
for that information.
It's supposed to be a bonanza.
It'll be a golden goose.
Invest all you have.
Once you do that,
we'll sleep and live...
all covered in money.
Buy land there.
If this works out,
it'll change our lives.
- Did you eat a lot?
-  Yes.
Mr Baek.
Should I...
invest in that?
What?
- You didn't believe it.
-  Gosh.
I'll give you some money.
Let's invest in it.
I'll give you five percent...
of the profits.
Five percent?
Let me meet your friend at Hwaseong City.
Well...
We'll go down to Hwaseong the day after tomorrow.
Meet us there. I'll call you again.
Mr Baek.
Your case will go through the disciplinary committee next month.
It'll be in two weeks. Why don't you take some time off?
You haven't taken a vacation in a long time.
What are you talking about?
Once the informant testifies regarding the bribery,
I don't think it'll end with suspension.
It's highly likely that you'll be dismissed.
I know Ma Jin Seok told on me. What are you talking about?
Who said Ma Jin Seok told on you? I didn't say that.
When we were searching his house,
was it you that tipped him off?
It's been a while. How have you been?
- They're searching your house.
-  Sorry?
You better hurry home.
You seemed very close to each other at the golf club.
I'm pretty sure it was you.
You're very imaginative.
Don't you feel ashamed in front of your kids...
of the way you live your life?
No, I don't.
My son loves me.
I let him do whatever he wants.
He can't hate me.
Tae Wook.
What happened to you?
Worry about yourself.
I'm going to dig into your bribery case...
so that you won't be able to step into the city hall again.
Just go home and take some rest.
What do you say?
Think of what to do when you're fired, too.
I think you'd make a great writer.
I see you. I'll come down.
I mean...
You're not supposed to come here. I might get in trouble.
I was feeling impatient.
Your friend at Hwaseong City.
Can't we meet him today?
Today?
What are you talking about?
I'm working right now.
I gave it some thought last night.
Isn't it strange that things are working out so smoothly?
Everything seems to be falling into place.
It feels strange, doesn't it?
What? Are you suspecting me?
No. I'm not suspecting you.
I've seen a lot of guys who approach me for my money.
Some of them want to con me.
Some of them hope to get some crumbs off of my table.
Anyway, I've seen many of them.
Do you know how I filter them out?
I rearrange the appointment.
Why? If it's real, it won't be a problem.
If it's not, they will fail to keep their words.
Another reason is that swindlers...
prepare everything for the day of appointment.
That jerks.
They set up a trap and wait for me.
They want to eat me alive.
Maybe they do. But I'm not lying.
That friend of yours.
He works there every day, right? He should be there...
whenever I visit, right?
Gosh. Of course. What are you talking about?
Why won't you believe me? He works there. Gosh.
Let's go down there right now.
Then I'll believe you.
I'll believe every word you say.
Of course we can go now.
But I'm working now. I can't leave office.
Come on. I know you're often on outside duty.
You can go out.
Let's just go now.
We can take a drive and have nice dinner on our way back.
How does it sound? Let's go, Mr Baek.
Gosh. You're being suspicious again.
Come on.
My goodness.
Well...
We can go if you want.
But there is heavy traffic today.
- Let's just go.
-  I have to finish up my work.
You're the chief. It'll be okay.
- Hello?
-  Hello, Mr Kim. This is Sung Il.
I'm on my way to Hwaseong City Hall.
I mean we are on our way.
Do you have a minute to see us?
What are you talking about? You said it's the day after tomorrow.
Don't mess around.
You do?
All right. We'll see you there.
See me where? It's the day after tomorrow.
I'm going down there with Mr Ma.
To Hwaseong City Hall?
Hello? Can you hear me?
Hwaseong City Hall is where you work, right?
I'm going there now with Mr Ma.
- Did he change the plan?
-  That's right.
Mr Ma wants to see you today.
He thinks it's better to talk to you today.
Anyway, we are on our way now.
We'll probably get there in an hour and a half.
I'll look forward to it.
All right. Bye.
Hello?
Did he say he can see us?
Of course. That's where he works.
Darn it.
Can you turn on the air conditioner? It's hot.
- Hi.
-  Hello, Sir.
- Let's have lunch together.
-  Yes, Sir.
- Have a great day.
-  All right.
- Hello?
-  Is this Detective Sa Jae Sung?
I'm calling to report a fraud.
His name is Yang Jung Do.
Do you know him?
Who?
Darn it.
Gosh.
Ja Wang.
Ma Jin Seok changed the plan, so hack into the website in an hour.
Do as I say.
Stop saying we don't have time!
Ja Wang.
We'll be dead if we fail.
Ma Jin Seok may be on to us.
If we fail...
If we don't succeed, we'll be all dead.
So...
(Squad 38)
Bang Pil Gyu invests his money to Ma Jin Seok and...
Ma Jin Seok doubles that money and gives it back to him.
If we get Bang Pil Gyu,
maybe we can help Sung Il keep his job.
Listen to me carefully.
Ja Wang is working on a phishing website.
Stall him while we install the website on his computers.
How can I stall him again?
It's not the land we showed him.
Jung Do. I heard you're trying to con Ma Jin Seok for six million.
Go to him yourself with that contract.
The second you sign it,
- I'll arrest you.
-  Give it your best shot.
I'll be hard to catch.