(THE FOLLOWING CONTENT MAY NOT BE SUITABLE FOR VIEWERS UNDER 15.)
(VIEWER DISCRETION IS ADVISED.)
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Hak Joo. Mi Joo.
The pig.
Even the idiot from City Hall.
I arrested every one of them.
Too bad.
You gave me a reason to come after you.
Money didn't change hands. It doesn't constitute as...
No.
I will let the others out after 48 hours.
You and Jin Seok will sign those papers tomorrow.
Take the contracts and do it yourself.
The second you sign the papers,
I'll bring you in.
I got you good,
didn't I?
So stop while you still can.
I'm lecturing you for your own sake.
I wouldn't be bothered to do this for my own son.
Okay. I'll go myself.
I'll get Ma Jin Seok to sign the papers.
You jerk.
Come after me.
I'll keep running.
You just can't stop it.
Cuff yourself tomorrow when you see me.
I'm too old for this.
I'm too exhausted to even cuff you.
Darn it!
Mr Ma, it's me from Hwaseong City Hall.
Mr Park has an urgent issue to tend to.
I think I'll have to meet you in person.
Okay. Do you have time today?
(SQUAD 38)
- Let me see. You are bleeding.
- Excuse me.
Can I please talk to the person in charge?
There seems to be some misunderstanding.
Sung Il.
They're not after us.
They arrested us to catch Jung Do.
Jung Do will have to meet him himself because we're here.
This is a trap.
Gosh.
What if I tell you the truth?
It is true...
that Jung Do saved Chairman Wang's life...
twice.
I heard they were arrested.
- When?
- It's been about an hour.
So where is Jung Do now?
He's here.
He's really doing it today.
He can run, but he can't hide.
He is on the move. Make sure to put a tail on him.
The second they sign the papers,
cuff him in before the ink dries.
Do you understand?
I see Yang Jung Do passing by.
Hello? Okay.
He's got the papers.
Where is he going?
Stop.
Go.
Gosh.
Stop there!
Yang Jung Do!
Stop!
Stop right there.
Chase him.
Yes, Sir.
Stop!
You jerk.
- Corner him.
- Yes, Sir.
Shoot.
Ma'am.
What is that?
Why are there two cars?
What are you talking about?
Chase the car.
There are two same cars.
Whatever, just chase the car.
Shoot.
Chase the car.
There are three of them now.
What should we do?
Go catch any one of them.
Where are you now?
Go to them.
Darn it!
What's your problem?
How could you miss him like that?
You fools.
Ma Jin Seok.
Where is he now?
If you chase Ma Jin Seok, you can catch Yang Jung Do.
- Find him immediately.
- Sir.
Forget about Yang Jung Do. We should worry about what we did.
We just made a big mess outside of our jurisdiction.
What did you just say?
He didn't even commit a fraud yet.
If they find out that we did it out of speculation,
we'll get suspended.
Jerks.
Shoot.
(WANTED: DETECTIVE SA JAE SUNG)
What?
What is it?
Sorry, Sir.
Wait.
What are you doing?
Let go.
Come quietly.
Let go!
Let go of me.
Take him.
Guess why it's good to be rich.
You can buy many of these cars.
How did you find out?
Someone called my office.
He said the others were arrested...
but that you were being chased.
Who do you think called?
I don't know.
Are you sure?
How would I know?
I see.
I thought you knew.
If you find out later, do tell.
Hello?
Yes.
What?
Okay.
Are you Detective Kim Hong Gil?
Yes. I am.
Hello.
Shall we go?
Pardon?
You must finish what you started.
- Right.
- Yes.
We should go.
Hi.
Hello.
Did I make you wait?
No.
Let's finish the deal.
- Here.
- Okay.
- Take your time.
- Sure.
Should I affix my seal?
Did you read it all?
Yes.
That's it, then.
Do you have the eight account numbers I gave you?
Wire the six million to those accounts.
Sure.
Just a moment.
It's me.
Transfer the money.
It's on.
I'm here.
I'll call in a bit.
It shouldn't be a minute.
Okay.
So, Mr Kim.
Can I make you an offer?
Sure.
I promised Mr Baek...
a five percent commission.
But I just realised that he didn't do anything.
You did all the work, didn't you?
What are you trying to say?
If I give Mr Baek five percent,
you and he must share it.
2.5 percent each, right?
How about I just...
give you three percent instead?
Let's do that...
and cut Mr Baek out of the deal.
Wouldn't that be nice?
Now we know each other, I can contact you directly.
- Gosh...
- You're scum to the last minute.
It's not like that.
- He said...
- Jin Seok.
What?
You just got conned.
What do you mean?
You got conned, you moron.
The land you just paid over six million for.
Guess how much it really is.
It's 10 dollars per Pyeong.
It's not good for anything because it's part of the greenbelt.
You aren't making any sense.
Jung Do, he won't believe me.
You love checking cadastral maps.
Go online and check the appraised value.
Hwaseong, Bongpyeong-eup Hwado-ri 23-1.
- Look it up.
- What?
Mr Kim.
I'm not Mr Kim.
I'm Mr Yang.
Over there.
Look it up.
You crazy...
- It's mine.
- Sit back.
(CADASTRAL MAP SEARCH)
(HWADO-RI 23-1)
(APPRAISED VALUE: 10 DOLLARS 20 CENTS)
- You look like you're doing fine.
- Do I?
Sorry.
Jin Seok.
Don't wire the money.
- What?
- Don't transfer the money!
Don't do it! Don't do it!
Freeze!
Where's the money?
Where is it?
Gone. I wired it.
What?
- Cancel it.
- Let go of me.
Cancel the transfer!
I've never seen you make that face.
Six million must be a huge amount.
The lady you told to drink water.
She made the exact same face.
Do you see how she felt?
You should never use money to toy with others.
- Okay?
- Mr Baek.
Help me out here.
Mr Kim.
I'm really sorry.
You can't do this.
You know...
I worked hard to save up.
How dare you!
Help me out here. This will kill me.
Mr Baek.
I worked so hard for that money.
You scumbag!
You good for nothing jerk!
Oh, hello, Mr Ma.
You look very angry.
Is he the one who didn't pay up?
You're all frauds.
You picked on the wrong person.
I'll put you all behind bars.
Calling the police won't help.
- Sit and listen.
- What?
Sit down, you jerk!
Listen to me very carefully.
520,000 in local tax.
5.25 million in national tax.
You owed a total of 5.77 million in back taxes.
That's now paid in full.
Jin Seok.
From now on,
try to be decent.
We shouldn't be an embarrassment to our own children.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Those jerks.
Hello, this is Seowon City...
Pardon?
Okay, thanks.
(PAID)
Sir, Ma Jin Seok just paid his back taxes.
What?
(MA JIN SEOK, CURRENT AMOUNT IN ARREARS: 0)
Hello?
What?
Mr Ahn.
Mr Ma Jin Seok just paid his taxes.
How much?
All of it.
I called the National Tax Service...
and he paid the 5.25 million off.
That's great.
So,
why do you look so upset?
It's nothing, Sir.
Thank you. You can leave.
Ma Jin Seok...
is one of Bang Pil Gyu's collaborators.
I was shielding him so as not to upset Mr Bang.
Whose case was it?
Mr Baek's of Taxation Office Division Three.
He's a big man with almost no guts,
so I didn't think he'd do much damage.
I don't know why,
but he's been really trying to get his claws into Mr Ma.
Ma Jin Seok, Bang Pil Gyu, Choi Chul Woo.
If these three go down, we will suffer as well.
Do you think...
they'll get to Mr Bang as well?
Bang Pil Gyu is 58 years old.
I'm sure you heard of Woohyang Group, a company that guaranteed...
a 250-percent profit...
that turned out to be a pyramid scheme.
Woohyang Construction is a subsidiary.
Bang Pil Gyu is the CEO.
Do you call this a proposal?
- Do you?
- He's Choi Chul Woo's friend...
and worked as his right hand man...
since the company's expansion in 2002.
Since Woohyang's bankruptcy, Bang Pil Gyu owes...
45.25 million dollars in national tax...
and 4.52 million dollars in local tax.
That's a total of 49.77 million dollars.
Why are you going after him?
We can't get him to pay up this much money.
This is a long term project...
It's to save Mr Baek.
Why are you going after him?
We can't get him to pay up this much money.
This is a long term project...
It's to save Mr Baek.
Once Pil Gyu is caught,
Sung Il won't have to be suspended.
- How?
- TV cameras.
If we were to visit him with cameras rolling,
what would the media report?
We'll use public sentiment.
The rich fear that more than our seizure stickers.
We'll take down Bang Pil Gyu who has direct ties to Ma Jin Seok.
Tens of thousands of people lost their jobs because of him.
- Can you explain?
- Say something.
Do you admit it's true?
He transferred his assets to his kids,
didn't pay millions in tax,
and yet he still lives in a huge mansion and eats good food.
Let the media catch wind of that.
The National Tax Service will be forced to take action,
and Ma Jin Seok, along with Bang Pil Gyu...
will take a hit.
We'll use Bang Pil Gyu to cause a media frenzy.
When Ma Jin Seok gets cold feet,
we'll get him for bribery and assaulting Mr Baek...
and take him down, is that it?
That's it.
It was my idea. I still have it, don't I?
To be honest,
this isn't like any other job we did before.
Our goal is to use their weaknesses and offer a deal.
Ma Jin Seok will never pay his taxes,
so we'll turn the media against him.
Let's help Mr Baek.
Mr Kang, how many cameras will there be?
We're going to visit Bang Pil Gyu, the CEO of Woohyang Construction.
Yes, see you there.
Three national TV channels, the cable news channels,
and some local channels.
Hello, Mr Lee.
They can't refuse a story like this one.
They're all waiting for us there.
Shall we get going, then?
Let's go.
- Are you wearing makeup?
- What?
My wife did it for me in case I appear on TV.
How do I look?
You look fine.
- You look 10 years younger.
- Do I?
Let's go.
Mr Park.
Yes?
Go and work instead of wasting your time here.
It's not that easy.
I think Sung Hee should take the lead on this one.
Be nice, Division Two.
Is this in case it backfires?
Don't worry about the cameras.
Just do what you always do.
- Good point.
- Okay.
- Let's study his house.
There are two floors.
It's in his son, Ho Seok's name.
Division 2 will take the 1st floor, Division 3 will take the 2nd floor.
- Will that do?
- Yes.
There's a brick wall on either side of the gate.
I think it's about 5m high.
The trees in the garden obstruct the view into the house.
It's your typical rich man's house.
If you enter through the main door, you'll see three rooms.
The first room is Bang Pil Gyu's study.
Leave the books alone...
and target the antiques and ceramic vases.
You do that, Sang Hee.
If you don't find anything,
leave the room and help out in one of the others.
Don't waste time in there.
Okay.
The second room.
It's the housekeeper's room, so let's skip it.
I'd like the rest of Division 2 to focus on the 3rd room.
What is it?
The dressing room.
Designer brand bags, clothes and watches.
Mark everything you can find.
If possible, make a scene in this room.
What kind of scene?
A fight.
Not that.
Fight over a bag from a brand that everyone will recognise.
If you were to do that,
and that were to air on TV,
we should get the media on our side.
We can drop some hints and give them a show.
That should work for us.
The reporters will get everything,
so don't push too hard. Consider it a gentle massage.
- You're good at that.
- Don't you worry.
Now for the second floor.
There's a hallway and two rooms.
Room four, the master bedroom.
Inside the closet should be important papers,
jewellery and precious metals.
Mark everything down and hold them up for the cameras.
Okay.
Open that up.
Here you go.
Room five is the most important one.
Bang Pil Gyu owns this one.
It's always locked,
and you can't get in without a key.
Even his wife has never been inside.
I bet it's in this room.
- Right.
- The safe.
What's inside that safe...
and how we get it out...
will determine the result of this raid.
Mr Kim and I will take this room.
Dong Soo, you help out wherever help is needed.
Mr Kang, can you brief the photographers?
I will.
We're going up against Woohyang Group's CEO.
Let's do this.
Good luck.
- Good luck.
- Go.
The Prosecutors' Office...
vowed to make this incident a turning point.
Now the weather.
Typhoon Bolaba is moving north fast.
At 3am on the 21st, it was located at sea,
560km to the northeast...
of Manila, the capital of the Philippines.
It's expected to change direction as it passes Taiwan,
and will head toward Korea and Japan.
If this typhoon makes landfall on Korea,
experts say it could cause more damage than...
the disaster caused by typhoon Bompass...
just six years ago.
Let's do this.
Thank you for coming all this way.
We're from Seowon City's Taxation Office,
and we're here to urge Bang Pil Gyu...
to pay his back taxes.
Please film what you see and report the truth.
Thank you.
Get the ladder.
Hey.
What if we go in and no one's there?
I'm sure someone's inside.
What if you're wrong?
We'll be embarrassed in public.
Don't worry, someone's in.
Get the ladder.
- Get it.
- Okay.
This looks dangerous.
This is just part of how we do things.
All this is legal, so don't worry.
Be careful.
Hold on tight.
We got you.
Are you okay?
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
We're from Seowon City Hall. Open the door.
Is the house empty?
The ladder.
The ladder?
What if the house really is empty?
It's not. I'm positive.
It'll be so embarrassing if you're wrong.
- All these cameras...
- Don't worry. He's in there.
Excuse me.
Sung Hee, there are people inside.
Let's get the door.
Okay.
- Hurry.
- This is also...
a part of the process.
Go on, then.
Be careful.
We can go in now.
Mr Park, Chang Ho, go upstairs.
Okay.
Hello? We're from Seowon City Hall.
- I...
- Hang on.
What did you say your name was?
It's been a while, hasn't it?
Sung Hee.
Seowon City Hall's Taxation Office. Are you Mr Bang Pil Gyu?
I was expecting your visit.
Have you eaten?
You shouldn't skip meals. You do a tough job.
We're here today because you owe...
45.25 million dollars in national tax,
- and local tax...
- 4.52 million dollars.
The grand total is 49.77 million dollars.
Today, you want to collect the 4.52 million dollars.
To seize my belongings.
Yes. I'm glad you're up to speed.
- According to...
- I believe it's Article 131.
House search and personal distress.
Go ahead.
But before you do,
let me say one thing.
This is the reason I didn't pay my taxes.
I wanted to meet with the press.
When else would I get...
a chance to explain myself to the public?
I lost my company because people said I was a fraud.
Now I'm penniless and can't afford to pay any tax.
Aren't I?
Woohyang Group...
was sacrificed...
in a witch hunt carried out by the previous president,
police and prosecution.
Our business model...
was about sharing purchasing experiences.
It was a legal pyramid business...
and we broke no law whatsoever.
Just because a company with sales of over two billion a year...
refused to pay a single penny in bribes to any official,
we became a target.
The government tagged us an illegal pyramid conning scheme,
and tore us apart.
I think this is about to turn political.
I tried...
to protect the company...
to the very end.
We supported 200,000 employees and their families.
I tried to protect them as best I could.
I'm so sorry.
I owe those 200,000 people a debt I cannot repay.
I will carry the guilt...
for the rest of my life.
I am very sorry.
You can begin.
Look around.
Let's do it.
Well... Go ahead.
Yes, Sir.
All right.
Please inspect the second floor.
- Chang Ho.
- Yes.
Search the dressing room.
- Sir. I found it.
- Yes.
- There it is.
- Seize it.
- Yes, Sir.
Excuse me. Please cut us some slack.
I'm sorry. We have to execute it as we're told.
This is a gift from our daughter-in-law.
- Well... Sir.
- Please forgive us.
We're following the procedure. Please cooperate.
I'm so sorry.
Please cooperate.
Just give it to them.
This is something we should do for our country.
We should expiate our guilt.
My daughter-in-law gave me this as a birthday gift last year.
Because of my incompetence,
we're living in my son's house.
I feel bad for my wife.
Let's go.
Was the watch really a gift?
Tell us how you feel.
It's okay.
Is it not here?
This room is almost empty.
I think they moved it to somewhere else already.
Chief. There is nothing here.
Officer Kim.
You didn't find anything, did you?
No.
We're in trouble, aren't we?
We are.
I don't think he even cares about what we're doing.
We should shake things up a little.
That was a gift.
Could you open the door of the room on the second floor?
That room is empty.
That's something we have to check.
Open it, please.
All right.
It's a safe.
Open it, please.
I only have a personal item in there.
I can't wait to see what it is.
Open it, please.
Must you do this?
Yes. It's our job to do this.
Do you want me to call a technician and get it open?
It may damage your safe.
It must cost a few hundred thousands dollars.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
What is your name, Inspector?
I'm from Taxation Office Division Three of Seowon City Hall.
My name is Chun Sung Hee.
I'll remember that name.
What is it?
What is your name, Inspector?
I'm from Taxation Office Division Three of Seowon City Hall.
My name is Chun Sung Hee.
I'll remember that name.
What is it?
They say you never understand your parents until you become one.
As I get old, I miss my father.
That picture is all I have.
That's the only thing I can look at when I miss my late father.
Ms Chun.
Why did you come...
to my house today?
Are you here to collect taxes,
or to put on a show?
If you went through all this...
just to put on a show,
I'll be generous and let this one go.
But...
if you really came to collect taxes,
you're about to be in big trouble, Ms Chun.
I'll ask you again.
Did you come here to collect taxes,
or to put on a show?
I came here to work.
I got it. You can go now.
- Hello?
- Dad, I'm in trouble.
Ma Jin Seok, that jerk...
Where is he now?
What did you just say?
I said Ma Jin Seok has paid off his tax arrears.
What's happening, Sung Hee?
Why would he...
pay his tax arrears all of a sudden?
Gosh, you startled me.
I came to see Sung Il.
You and Chief did it, right?
- Did what?
- Ma Jin Seok's back taxes.
You and Chief conned him and made him pay.
You and I are always at odds.
Because Ma Jin Seok paid his taxes,
there's no way we can save Chief.
He would have to admit charges of assault and bribery.
- What are you talking about?
- We were going to make a deal.
For clearing Jin Seok's back taxes,
we were going to ask Chief's job in return.
We wanted to clear his assault charge and...
erase the record of the report that says he took bribes.
But we can't do that anymore.
Jin Seok wouldn't help someone who conned him and made him pay taxes.
I don't understand.
What you said is news to me.
I'm saying Disciplinary Committee is going to dismiss him.
You're not going to jail because you made him pay his taxes, right?
I heard that's what he promised you.
Congratulations.
But we can't save our chief now.
Now, let's move on to the next story.
Seowon City has declared that they will increase...
the reward for reporting concealment of assets...
from 30,000 dollars to 100,000 dollars.
Moreover, they will designate an inspector...
to every upper-class family and celebrity with high tax arrears...
and closely manage their tax payment.
Ji Eun, bring me canned coffee.
- Okay.
- Seowon City renewed...
the Act on Tax Arrears...
- with the changes.
- Dad, should I bow as well?
- Tax arrears have increased...
- No, it's fine. Turn down the TV.
- since 2016.
- Stop giving him coffee.
His teeth turned yellow and he didn't feel good because of coffee.
- He used to like it. It's okay.
- A police officer...
who aided, abetted and took bribes...
from fraudsters got arrested.
He's not my brother. He's my enemy.
Because of him,
I married someone so dumb.
Mother might hear you. Keep it down.
She's asleep.
Also, she agreed that...
you're foolish like a bear.
You said you like big guys.
You said I'm your ideal type.
Ji Eun, your mum is a strange woman.
Who is it at this hour?
I didn't know there was...
someone so handsome among his subordinates.
Are you married?
Not yet.
How about a girlfriend?
- I don't have one yet.
- I see.
How about someone you flirt with?
I don't have that one, either.
Then, would you like to go on a blind date?
- There are so many...
- My goodness.
let him have his meal in peace.
Why did you invite him for dinner? You should've just let him go.
Why are you getting upset?
You often get cranky these days.
I'm not being cranky. I'm just saying you should let him eat.
Eat.
It's okay.
I already had dinner, so I'm not that hungry.
Eat up.
How old are you?
I'm in the first grade in high school.
How old does it make you?
Count it yourself.
You're right. I can count it myself.
You're smart.
By the way, you're so pretty. You must be very popular at school.
You're a con man, aren't you?
What?
I'm not pretty. I'm just ordinary.
I'm not popular either.
Just eat your dinner.
Don't try to compliment just because I'm your boss' daughter.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
The man that you held a memorial ceremony for.
Who is he?
He's my wife's older brother.
It looked like he died young.
Why did he pass away?
He killed himself six years ago.
Why?
He was my co-worker.
We got a report that said he took bribes.
Anyway,
it gave him a hard time. That's what happened.
If only...
If I had believed him that once,
maybe he wouldn't have done it.
Do you know what the last thing I said to him was?
I told him to stay low.
I told him I wanted my pension.
He was thinking about ending his life,
and I said things like pension.
But...
did he really take bribes?
Maybe he disturbed someone he shouldn't have.
Woohyang.
He went up against Woohyang Group.
Choi Chul Woo, the president of Woohyang Group had...
the highest amount in arrears in Seowon City. He wanted to get him.
He started it because he was young and fearless.
We couldn't even get near Choi Chul Woo.
Because of Bang Pil Gyu, his right-hand man.
He had made so many allies inside City Hall.
We wanted to get Bang Pil Gyu and Choi Chul Woo together.
A phone call was made and we were done.
- Please.
- I'm sorry.
The next day, Commissioner Ahn wanted out.
I'm sorry, Min Sik. I'll help you out next time.
Baek Sung Il from Division One...
- left us as well.
- Sung Il.
A few days later, Noh Seung left.
Eventually, I...
Let's stay low.
I need to get my pension.
That led to his death.
That's how he passed away.
Then, who was the person...
that Bang Pil Gyu called?
He must've been someone in a high position.
That one phone call destroyed your division.
Just someone.
Come on. Who is it?
It's just someone.
Forget it. He's not your concern.
By the way, why did you visit me at this hour?
I didn't come here to see you.
It's not that.
Well...
Why didn't you tell me?
Tell you what?
About Disciplinary Committee. I heard you might get fired.
I'll have to wait and see.
Maybe I'll just get suspended.
With Ma Jin Seok's six million dollars in arrears,
didn't you think to make a deal with him?
You could've asked him to forget about...
the assault and bribes and you'll give him the money back.
What is that? That'd make me look bad.
I also made a promise to you.
Somehow,
I used violence,
but I never took bribes. So, I don't think I'll get fired.
I'll try to make it moderate as suspension.
I'll be great if you can make that happen.
But I don't think you can.
I'm just saying.
I have something to give you.
I'm not giving it to you now.
Sir, it's...
I got conned...
by swindlers.
- Then they used...
- Your money to pay taxes?
Yes, Sir.
All of that 5.7 million dollars?
Yes.
You think we're fools? You jerk.
Hey.
You.
Hit.
Hit yourself.
Harder.
Harder, I said.
Gosh.
Look at this jerk.
Hey.
Come on.
Raise your chin.
Let go. I said let go.
Ho Seok.
That's enough.
Gosh.
Jin Seok.
Yes, Sir.
Our calculation's done now.
- Pardon?
- Go back to where you belong.
Wait, Sir.
Please forgive me.
I'm sorry, Sir.
Please forgive me. My family will go completely broke.
You know it. Please don't do this.
You know how loyal I've been.
Please, just this once.
I'll do anything you ask. Anything, I promise.
- Jin Seok.
- Yes, Sir.
You thought you swam into the golden pond.
You thought you would never have to worry about money.
Jin Seok.
You know,
all the ponds in Korea have dried up.
No more golden ponds.
People like you...
should be grateful that you live near the golden ponds.
Go back to your league, the filthy brook.
Spend your days worrying about petty bills to pay.
Right.
Wrap up things here and his business.
- When should I do it?
- Now.
More people are out about in the afternoon.
Don't let the driver drive the car.
I'm sorry, Dad.
I'm still a terrible driver.
This jerk's a great one. He knows all the short-cuts.
- Did you just give me the look?
- No, Sir.
Focus on driving, you fool.
You would've lost your job long ago if you didn't drive well.
Driving is the only thing you're good at.
You're pathetic.
That's why your life is pathetic.
The only thing you're ever good at is driving, you fool.
Stop blabbering.
How did the thing go?
I've taken care of it and planned it out.
It will work out soon.
Those taxation office people must have pushed it hard this time,
seeing how you make me do such stuff.
They tried.
Those obnoxious jerks.
I have something to give you.
What brings you here?
I'm just here to say hello.
Where are you going?
Why? You don't like it?
Not exactly.
Must we do this?
It's not a must.
Don't you feel sorry for Mr Baek?
- Somehow, he ended up with us, - Hello.
but he's a person of justice.
Hi.
People like us.
We never cared about the law.
But this time, we worked towards abiding by the law.
This is...
the first time I had this feeling after our work was done.
Wasn't it fun?
Was it not, Ma'am?
So...
Why don't we help Mr Baek...
who made us realise we could do meaningful stuff?
What was it?
Article 38, Constitution of the Republic of Korea.
"All citizens shall have"...
"the duty to pay taxes"...
"under the conditions as prescribed by Act."
Just to abide by that, he joined hands with swindlers like us.
We can go back to where we belong,
but people like him should stay as just.
People like him are needed...
for justice to prevail.
This is all I had to say.
So,
who is in?
I'm here.
What... What is all this?
You caught us.
That's...
the list of tax in arrears your division is in charge of.
What are you going to do with that?
We'll stop your dismissal.
Will...
300 people's back taxes do?
(SQUAD 38)
This is Taxation Office.
The tax paid in the last few days adds up to 10 million dollars.
Set up a meeting with Bang Pil Gyu as soon as possible.
The one who doesn't know his place.
If you carry out one task for me,
I will cover up Mr Baek's case.
Is money everything?
Of course. It is in this country.
What's wrong with you?
You'll get released soon. I trust you.
You said this to my dad too, right?
You scum...
Don't give me a reason to go after you.