Jung Do.
I need to crush them all.
Let's do one more job.
- 50 million dollars?
-  Who is this person...
who has that much back tax to pay?
Bang Pil Gyu. He's the right-hand man of Choi Chul Woo at Woohyang.
We can't find his whereabouts.
There's a company called UN Communications.
His son Bang Ho Seok is the CEO.
His daughter Bang Min A is the advisor.
So what do you have planned for the 50-million-dollar con?
- Rich!
-  Rich!
Why don't we have dinner together one night?
I thought you're having dinner with your wife tomorrow.
What does Ms Bang Min A do?
She doesn't care about anything because she's so into antiques.
Antiques?
Ceramics?
Did you really come up with this?
Hello?
Do you have some decent ceramics?
Why was there a price tag attached on this...
with scotch tape?
Why are we going through all that trouble?
- Networking.
-  This is the Ministry of Culture.
Don't touch me. Tell me first.
It's been a while.
(Squad 38)
(Episode 9)
Tell me honestly. Have you bought anything from Ms Koo?
I really haven't bought anything from her. I already told you.
You can't lie to me and sell what you've bought from her.
You know what happens when you sell knock-offs, right?
I visited that store for the first time today,
and I was aware of the fact that they aren't authentic.
All right, I'll trust you.
If that's the case...
Mr Choo!
How can you do this to me?
You wouldn't have been able to make a living if it weren't for me.
I'll tell them everything.
I remember all those things you siphoned off for money!
- Goodness. Just get her in the car.
-  Brace yourself!
That woman is so chatty.
What a nuisance.
What was she going on about?
She's lying.
She's saying all those things because she's guilty.
Here. Feel free to get in touch with me if you need anything.
Don't hesitate to call me.
- Well, then.
-  Bye.
(Cultural Heritage Administration, Choo Seok Hoon)
That was pretty good for a first try.
(Commissioner Ahn)
Yes, Sir.
Now?
Sure, okay.
It looks like I need to go to City Hall now.
Go ahead without me. I'll meet you there later.
All right.
There you are, Mr Baek.
- Have you eaten yet?
-  Yes.
Oh, why are you here?
Mr Shim from the Tax Collection Division here...
will be appointed as chief of the Taxation Office Division Two.
We need to fill Mr Kang's position.
Right, I see.
I look forward to working with you. I have a lot to learn.
All right.
Congratulations on your promotion. You're already a chief.
Good.
Having a university alumnus pays off.
Do you have plans for this evening?
Have drinks with me and my...
Sorry, I meant Mr Shim.
I am a little swamped today.
Let's go for drinks another time.
Why? What's going on?
Well, I'm just a bit busy.
Let's go for drinks next time.
Sung Il, come with us.
Are you that busy?
Yes, I'm quite busy.
Why are you the only one so busy?
I don't think Division Three has any out-of-office tasks today.
I have some out-of-office work to do.
Well, then.
Too bad.
Mr Shim.
- Yes.
-  Public officials...
shouldn't con people, right?
Of course not.
Only scoundrels would do such a thing, right?
Yes.
Get back to work now.
Where are you going?
Yes.
I'm almost there. I'll be there shortly.
All right.
Yes, Detective Kim. This is Commissioner Ahn.
I have information that can be useful for you.
It's about a con job.
I got wind of a con artist trying to scam me.
I'll call you again later.
Hello?
Yes, Ji Eun. Whose number is this?
Dad is working.
Oh, your phone broke?
(Chief Baek Sung Il)
Gosh, how did you drop your phone in water?
Wouldn't it work if you dry it out?
The number you dialled is busy at the moment.
The number you dialled is busy at the moment. Please leave...
(Commissioner Ahn)
- Hello?
-  Sir.
I need your authorisation on something urgently.
- Where are you now...
-  I'm busy. Let's talk later.
It's very urgent, though.
Hello?
Sir?
Hey, how many boxes do we have in total?
About 1,300.
Gosh, I'm so sick and tired of them.
It's a phone usage record. Organise and summarise it for me.
- Hello?
-  Mi Joo.
Is this Mi Joo?
- Hello?
-  It's me, Sung Hee.
Is my chief on his way there?
Your meeting place, the warehouse.
Is my chief headed over there?
Jung Do.
Is the tax man on his way here?
I think so.
Don't drink-dial me.
They said yes. Why?
I'm not sure, but...
I'm pretty sure.
I don't know how he found out,
but my commissioner is following...
It's so muddy.
Jung Do. That was Sung Hee.
Sung Il's being followed.
I know it was old.
I don't have a lot of money right now.
I'm really sorry.
Yes, Detective, we just left.
I said I'm sure. Don't you believe me?
Mi Joo, the boxes.
Hak Joo, where's the thinner?
Paint thinner? In the bathroom.
- Where?
-  Bathroom!
Listen carefully.
The conman is a public official.
It's not a bad plot.
Put your mum on.
Honey, I think that...
Ji Eun...
She needs a new phone.
Is he not answering?
Is this the paint thinner?
You idiot.
Whatever. Let's get back to work. Keep packing!
What's not important to us could be important to kids.
Kids get teased if they have an old phone.
Right now?
I'm near Majang-dong.
Where are you?
Wangsimni? You're close by.
See you soon.
Throw the stuff away.
Why would I do that?
It took ages to collect.
Jung Do.
Okay, I'll deal with it.
Don't ask how. Leave it to me.
He got out.
I think it's time you head over here.
Hang up. I'll be home late.
(Yang Jung Do)
I'm almost there.
Don't come here.
Why not?
You're being tailed.
Your commissioner followed you.
He's bringing the cops.
Are you listening?
Sung Il. Shoot.
Who's following you?
He followed you all the way from City Hall.
Who are you?
I'm a police officer.
You know Detective Sa Jae Sung, don't you?
He wants to see you.
He locked me up once before.
He had nothing on me, so I was let off.
It won't take long. Don't worry. Come with me.
Could you tell me why I should come with you?
Shall I go after Hak Joo instead?
Okay, then. Let's go.
Excuse me.
What?
Get in and drive home in peace.
Don't follow people around.
Who are you?
What's going on here?
Did something happen?
This is... Right.
Still no answer?
Did someone nab him?
Sorry.
Why are things getting so complicated?
I just don't understand.
Why did you bring me here?
If you have something to say, I'm listening.
How much do you know about Yang Jung Do?
Stop letting him toy with you.
You'll end up like me.
Did you bring me here to say that?
Thanks for the advice.
I have to go.
Sit down, you moron.
Baek Sung Il.
Don't make me get to your team.
Sit down and hear me out.
Go on, then.
Listen carefully.
Yang Jung Do...
acted like a fool for years just so he could...
put me behind bars.
Just to put me here.
He put money in a fake account in the name of my brother...
I haven't seen in 20 years.
Then he set me up...
for taking a bribe.
Did you do it properly?
Don't make a mistake.
Don't make a mistake on what?
What?
Nothing, really.
It's just Ma Jin Seok.
How did you two first meet?
If you think back now, didn't anything seem strange?
Can you make them pay by using the law?
Leave it to me and I'll get you the six million.
You wouldn't have approached him and asked him...
to con people into paying their taxes.
I have a great idea.
Are you interested?
Do you think you met Jung Do by chance?
Nothing happens by chance.
Look at me.
Look where he put me.
I know...
you're going after Bang Pil Gyu.
Him and his 50 million dollars in back taxes.
You want it.
What will happen to you once the con's over?
Let's be brutally honest.
A con artist helping a public official gather taxes?
It makes no sense.
If Jung Do runs off with...
Mr Bang's 50 million dollars, you'll have to take the blame.
You are not working on a con...
with Jung Do.
You are...
being conned by him.
He'll ditch you once he's done with you.
It's time to switch sides.
Isn't it?
How did you two first meet?
If you think back now, didn't anything seem strange?
Can you make them pay by using the law?
Leave it to me and I'll get you...
the six million.
You wouldn't have approached him...
and asked him to con people...
into paying their taxes.
I have a great idea.
So...
are you interested?
Do you think you met Jung Do by chance?
Nothing happens by chance.
Look at me.
Look where he put me.
I know...
you're going after Bang Pil Gyu.
Him and his 50 million dollars in back taxes.
You want it.
What will happen to you once the con's over?
Let's be brutally honest.
A con artist helping a public official gather taxes?
It makes no sense.
If Jung Do runs off with Mr Bang's 50 million dollars,
you'll have to take the blame.
You are not working on a con...
with Jung Do.
You are...
being conned by him.
He'll ditch you once he's done with you.
It's time to switch sides, isn't it?
Why didn't you pick up?
I should be able to reach you.
I was so worried.
Sorry. Something came up.
What?
Did the police take you somewhere?
No... It wasn't that.
Good, then.
What about your commissioner? He's onto us.
I'll make sure no harm comes to you.
I'm worried about you, not us.
Be careful.
We promised that I wouldn't get caught...
and you wouldn't get fired, so let's keep that promise.
Okay?
Okay.
I only want proof that Jung Do framed me.
Find that...
and give it to him.
I'll take that...
and make an appeal.
Then I can get out.
Once I'm out,
I'll get Jung Do for you.
He'll go to prison...
and I'll be reinstated.
You can...
go back to your ordinary life...
as if nothing had happened.
Do you expect me to take you for your word...
and betray Jung Do?
Why should I do that?
Will you...
believe Jung Do instead?
He's a fraud.
Sung Il.
Forget about what I said.
We're in this together.
I...
owe you a lot.
You helped me out and I'm grateful.
We're doing this for us, so don't worry.
Jung Do.
I'll do better.
Let's do this.
We're doing fine.
You're doing fine.
Good morning.
- Hello.
-  Good morning.
Hi.
Chief.
What?
Can we talk?
Talk here.
It's not something we can discuss here.
I know what you're going to say.
Don't worry. I'll deal with it.
Chief.
Get to work.
I have to be somewhere.
- See you later, Sir.
-  Okay.
Hello?
Yes, Sir.
Sit.
Have some coffee if you want.
I'm fine. Do you want some?
Strong and black, no creamer.
How much do you know?
- Pardon?
-  I'm asking if you know...
what your chief is up to.
I don't know what you mean.
- You knew.
-  Pardon?
About what?
Why are you shaking?
- I don't know...
-  Are you part of it?
Tell me the truth.
Only then can I help you.
The police are onto him. It'll be game over soon.
Sung Hee.
If you helped him con taxpayers into paying their taxes,
then get out of it right now.
You can't save Sung Il, but you can at least save yourself.
- I don't understand...
-  You did understand.
You got it very clearly.
Or maybe not.
I'm done talking. You can go.
She's with him, too.
What should I tell the mayor this time?
This is what the Taxation Office looks like.
I recognise a lot of you.
I'm here for the public hearing.
Get back to work. Don't mind me.
Ms Chun.
How are you?
I hope you're fine. You have an important job.
Is the commissioner in?
- Hello.
-  Welcome, Mr Bang.
How are you?
(Chun Sung Hee)
(Ignore)
(Chief Baek Sung Il)
(Chun Sung Hee)
Hello?
Hi, it's me.
What do you want?
Just a moment.
It's for you.
Who is it?
You'll see who.
(Chun Sung Hee)
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
Hello?
Hi.
What is it?
Now?
Yes. Now.
Okay. Where should we meet?
Going somewhere?
For a walk.
What for?
She wants to meet up.
Why are you so obedient?
What?
You never come to see me when I ask you to.
The situation is totally different.
How is the situation totally different?
The person is.
You must feel rotten.
You feel like you're losing out,
and you wonder why the guy doesn't know how you feel.
But...
what you're doing now...
It's always like that.
You give too much and get too little.
What comes and goes is never equal.
That's the problem.
Stop being a know-it-all.
I do know it all.
Liking someone?
That's your right.
You should enjoy those rights.
But don't think that the man...
should be obliged to accept your feelings.
That will only make you feel even worse.
And the list.
That's all good.
However, I think you should change to Hwajung Law Firm instead.
Sure. I'll do as you say.
Mr Bang.
This is something I haven't even told the mayor yet.
The police are onto us,
and your commissioner met with Bang Pil Gyu?
Yes.
Our commissioner knows...
what you and my chief are up to.
So, what you want to say is that...
your commissioner could have tipped Bang Pil Gyu off?
If that's the case,
you really have to stop. That's what I'm here to say.
Okay.
I'll ask Bang Pil Gyu myself.
I'll test him.
See if he knows.
You can't be so flippant about this.
I'm not being flippant.
There could be a problem. We're not yet sure if there is.
Don't overreact.
What if there is a problem and my chief gets hurt?
Will you pay for it?
That won't happen. Don't worry.
It's easy for you to say.
Don't you have any sense of responsibility?
That day...
and today, too.
You say things so easily.
That's why you hurt the people around you.
I never said things so easily.
To you, at least.
Let me ask you something.
Why did you do it?
Why did you tell me you're a conman?
We could've broken up without you telling me.
I know that nothing would have changed...
if you left without telling me,
but you didn't have to tell me.
Hey.
Get a caramel macchiato.
Yes, Sir.
With extra toppings.
Do you even know what that is?
- Topping!
-  Yes, Sir. Got it, Sir.
That moron.
If you...
If you didn't tell me...
- Still.
-  That was...
Shoot.
Hello, Mr Bang.
I thought it was you, Mr Cho.
I came in to get coffee.
Seoul is so small, isn't it?
Where are you going, Madam?
I'm not a madam.
Isn't she your wife?
You said...
you had a meeting with someone named Xun Ji Ha...
and dinner with your wife.
Pretend to be mad and leave.
Come on.
What?
You're going to leave angry like this?
Let it go.
If you leave like this, you'll lock the bedroom door...
and stay angry at me all day again.
Like last time.
You wouldn't eat and packed your bags...
saying you were going to your parents' place...
and made a big mess.
Why did you...
cancel your appointment with Xun Ji Ha?
What?
I told you already.
He...
wanted to reschedule to tomorrow.
How could he reschedule on the day of?
What's the big deal?
Xun Ji Ha wanted to invest.
So? Who cares about a measly 100 million?
To me, your word is more important.
There are truckloads of people willing to invest as much.
Was it...
because of our appointment...
Are you Mr Bang from UN Communications?
Yes, I am.
Because of you,
my husband lost 100 million dollars.
What will you do about it?
How... would... I...
I mean...
Forget it.
I don't know how great you are,
but just know this.
My husband...
made plans with you tomorrow and lost a 100-million-dollar contract.
So...
So tomorrow night, make sure...
to buy him a nice meal.
- Pardon?
-  Yes?
Buy him something expensive and good.
So that he'll forget all about the 100-million-dollar contract.
Take him to one of those hot spots where you have to wait in line.
I think that's what you should do.
I'll see you at home.
Why did you tell him to buy him a nice meal?
Are you saying Jin Seok...
was telling the truth?
One of your men...
is conning people...
to get them to pay their taxes?
I'm tailing him, so I'll be able to put an end to it soon.
But I don't know who their target is after Ma Jin Seok.
You never know,
so you should be careful.
Hi, it's Dad.
Have you recently had...
There's no one like that.
Who gets conned in this day and age?
Don't worry. Your son is smart.
Anyway, I have to go.
I'm busy.
I'll see you this weekend.
I love you, Dad.
What did your father say?
Oh, well.
He said to be careful of cons.
Nothing much.
Anyway,
I can't believe you lost 100 million dollars because of me.
I feel terrible just thinking about it.
I told you not to think about it.
It's fine.
Mr Bang,
money...
all look the same.
I may lose 100 million here,
but I can make 100 million there.
But no two people...
look the same.
There's only one in the world.
That's what people are.
Thank you so much for saying that,
but I feel so bad. I'd like to compensate you somehow.
It's okay. There's no need.
You know what,
what if I invested a little in your company?
Invest?
No, there's no need.
There are plenty of people who want to invest...
No, no.
I'm doing it for myself, not to help you.
You said investors make 500 percent of their investments.
That's true.
No, it's okay.
I'd like to keep our relationship...
nice and friendly like it is now.
No, no.
I won't put in that much money, so don't feel bad.
Let's talk about it tomorrow.
My wife is waiting.
I'll call you.
I'm sorry. I'll see you.
That's not good.
We should remain friends.
Mr Cho.
Why don't we make it...
a double date tomorrow?
Stop letting him toy with you.
You'll end up like me.
The neighbourhood hasn't changed.
I needed to talk to you,
but I didn't have your number.
I couldn't reach Mi Joo...
and I felt weird asking Mr Baek.
Don't tell Mr Baek what happened earlier.
I won't. That's why I came here instead of calling.
Why are you laughing?
It's funny.
Why did you tell him to buy me a nice meal?
Do you think that's funny?
You would've been in trouble if it weren't for me.
I told you to get angry and leave. Why did you keep talking?
How could I just get angry?
What? Curse at you and leave? That's ridiculous.
Whatever.
I'm too tired to talk.
If you have something to say, say it and go.
You need to eat with me.
You should've refused.
I did. I kept refusing,
but he kept begging, saying he wanted to apologise to you.
Why did you have to say all that and create this mess?
Why should I go there? I won't go.
You take care of it.
I'd like to take care of it.
Whatever.
Tell him I died.
Don't get me involved.
I don't want to make you feel uncomfortable either.
You should've flat out refused. That's what you should've done.
I did. I flat out refused. I did.
Anyway, I told you, so bye.
Where are you going?
I'm not going. I gave you my answer.
Darn it.
Hello?
I heard the daughter is on the move. We should get moving too.
Yes, Ma'am.
Okay.
We laid the foundation well.
I think we can finish the job relatively simply,
so please keep it up.
Ms Noh, please go back to the antique shop...
Hello.
Give me the most expensive celadon you have.
Sure.
Get us a really nice celadon.
As for the two of you, please get a bunch of items...
that look like antiques. They can be cheap.
We'll take them all.
Pardon?
Okay.
And then what? What will you do?
She's only heard of what kind of people we are.
Now, we'll show her.
(Cultural Heritage Administration)
She collects antiques to avoid paying taxes,
so we should show her that we are just as dirty,
and that we will do anything...
and everything...
to make money.
People need to see it to believe it.
Excuse me.
Don't mind me.
Go about your business.
You'll show her...
and then what?
We'll become friends.
If Jung Do runs off with...
Mr Bang's 50 million dollars, you'll have to take the blame.
He'll ditch you once he's done with you.
It's time to switch sides.
Dad.
What brings you here?
You should be smarter about whom to take on.
Okay?
Don't confuse pity with authority.
I was just passing by.
Let's go.
Hey, you.
You should apologise for bumping into an elder.
Let's go.
Did you want to say something?
Next time.
No, not really.
Has there been any suspicious people around you lately?
Like who?
Never mind. As long as there aren't any.
Let's go.
So, you didn't do it?
No.
Mr Kim called earlier.
We should start preparing a contingency plan.
What do you mean?
We should be true to who we are.
We're con artists.
I'm glad you came.
I'm more trustworthy...
than Jung Do, aren't I?
I work for the government,
after all.
How much do you know...
about Yang Jung Do?
What will happen to you once the con's over?
Let's be brutally honest.
A con artist helping a public official gather taxes?
It makes no sense.
Be careful.
We promised that I wouldn't get caught...
and you wouldn't get fired, so let's keep that promise.
Okay?
Who is it?
You're dropping in late often now.
Well, I was just passing by.
May I come in?
If I say no, will you just leave? Come in.
I heard you had to bail because you ran into Bang Pil Gyu.
Are you sure he didn't recognise you?
No, I don't think he remembered me.
Thankfully.
Thanks.
Well...
Well, Jung Do...
Do you remember the detective that we got locked up...
when we ran the con on Ma Jin Seok?
Yes.
Did you know he's in prison...
for taking bribes?
He...
gave me this.
He says...
that...
you're using me,
and that you'll ditch me once you're done with me,
so if I'd bring a recording of you saying you framed him,
he'd take care of it.
So he gave me that.
Why are you telling me that?
It's not like I believe him,
but I thought I should tell you...
and confirm for myself.
Shoot.
You're right.
That detective is right.
I'm using you.
What?
(Squad 38)
This is it.
The antique appraiser, the only person Bang Min A trusts.
You can get at least 500,000 dollars for this.
I have evidence that Baek Sung Il is conning Bang Pil Gyu.
Does Sung Hee know too?
I think so.
- Let's do it.
-  Three times?
Minimum three times.
Get started.
Those con artist punks.
How should we deal with it?
I think we fell into a trap.
Hand them over to the police.
Are you afraid of betraying Jung Do?