Episode 34
Look here. Look here. Are you okay?
Hello. Please wake up.
Oppa!
Chae Ri.
Oppa, who is she?
I don't know. She collapsed while passing by.
While passing by? It is strange.
Did you get back to your senses?
I am sorry because I have anemia.
Do you live in this neighborhood? Where do you live?
Excuse me. Get on me. I will take you home.
Chae Ri, you have baby lamb...
Huh?
I can go alone. Thank you.
Hmm are you really going to be okay?
What's wrong, Chae Ri?
I got dizzy suddenly.
Oh yeah?
Is it a pregnancy symptom?
Huh? Is there something like that?
Yeah, I read it when I was studying.
If you are carrying a baby, you can become anemic.
This won't do. Get on my back.
Can I?
Of course. When you have a husband, why not use him?
Hey, how could you just jump on like that? You might scare baby lamb.
This is great! Let's go! Move, move!
You like it that much?
But you got heavy, really.
Is our baby lamb making you heavier?
- Oppa.  - Hm? What's wrong?
You have something you feel sorry toward me, right?
Huh? Why?
When you call me "Oppa", the intonation is different.
Just like now, if you call "Oppa", I feel like you feel sorry about something.
No.
Such a quick sense.
What is there for you to be sorry toward me? I am always sorry toward you.
By the way,
my wallet.
Huh? Why?
Oh, nothing.
Where did that pick pocket go?
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by Mom Knows Best Team @ Viki
Go! Go!
-Giddy up and go!-Wow, you really are heavy.
Let's go. One...two...
Lee Hyeong Soon?
Lee Hyeong Soon.
Are you uncomfortable somewhere?
Your mom went somewhere for a moment. Do you need something?
Because I am thirsty.
Oh okay. Wait a minute.
I will do it for you. Here.
It is okay. Drink.
You said you have something to say to me?
Yes.
I gave much thought to it.
I won't go study in America.
In the end...
For saying I would go and canceling, I'm sorry.
Why not? Because of my Hoon Jae?
Yes.
Due to this incident, just with me being by Hoon Jae's side,
with the fact that Hoon Jae is breathing in this world,
I realized how grateful I am...
and how happy I am.
So I will no longer be greedy.
You really love my Hoon Jae, huh?
If you are against our marriage, we won't do it.
If you tell me not to see him, I will be patient.
If you tell me to go down to Seondam factory, I will.
Regardless of what it is,
it is better than Hoon Jae not being in this world.
You dreamed often that I came to save you?
I heard it from Assistant Manager Lee.
It happened when I was young.
Now I don't have that kind of dream anymore.
You still haven't left, huh?
Yeah. Now I am going to leave.
Jin Ae.
My Hoon Jae's smile is beautiful like that, huh?
The smile that he never shows to me.
To the kids who love each other that much, doing like that...
What? Someone robbed you?
Did you report it to the police?
Yes. I did, but it is the money that Chae Ri's grandma gave in order to buy Chae Ri something delicious.
How could you...you should have taken better care of it.
How could you not know someone stole from your left pocket?
That is what I want to say.
You, really. How are you going to take care of your household in the future when you are so reckless?
Don't say anything. If you were in my situation, you would have been victimized without even knowing.
Why would I be your situation? Am I such a irresponsible guy like you?
Am I the kind of person to jeopardize someone else?
What? Are you done talking?
Hyung, you still see me as an immature guy, right?
Then, an immature guy lives like this?
- Hyung, seriously.  - Hey.
Instead of this, you should go to sleep. Aren't you going to work tomorrow?
You go and sleep.
Sleep.
Oppa must be upset.
Jang Chae Ri, you are immature. If you didn't say you wanted to eat the expensive food,
Oppa wouldn't have accepted the money from Grandma.
Isn't Hyeong Soon Oppa's Hyung-nim too much?
I hate you, Hyeong Soon Oppa's Hyungnim.
I will go home and come back 2 hours later.
Please take care of Hoon Jae during that time.
Yes.
You didn't leave?
No. To take you home.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by Mom Knows Best Team @ Viki
- CEO Jang.  - Mother.
Miss Hwang.
Hello.
Mother, what brought you here?
Because Chairman Seo's mother got admitted to the hospital.
Then why are you two together?
Yes, we came here to take care of something and we're leaving.
Excuse me. I will leave first.
Yeong Seon. CEO Hwang...
Mother, you came with Chauffeur Park, right?
Yes.
Then please go back safely. I have something to say to CEO Hwang.
CEO Jang.
How suspicious.
Over there. Over there. It's clothes I've seen often a long time ago.
Take your mother home.
I won't do that anymore.
Please go.
I will take you home.
Oh yeah? I guess my mother gave us some space so we can be together?
Was it the case? No way.
Here?
Okay. Just 5 minutes.
This is great. It feels like all the pain is gone.
So you really aren't going abroad to study?
Really.
If you kept saying you will go, I was going to follow you.
There is a reason for my injury.
My head.
How could you say that? You know how shocked I was because you got hurt?
For me, it was torture.
I am sorry. I said it wrong.
You are crying again.
I got it. Now I won't ever get hurt. I will always be careful.
This is all yours so I will make sure you don't have to worry.
Now you are thinking this, right?
"How could he be so good looking even with the bandages?"
You seem to be better if you're joking like this.
It seems so, right?
Jin Ae, I love you. I love you. I love you.
Saying "I love you" so easily like this is great.
Thank you Hoon Jae for coming back so I can hug you like this.
This tofu isn't meant to just be put in the stew and be finished.
You have to cut it like this so the water can come out.
Stop eating.
It is delicious even if you eat it like this.
You should eat like this then. Why make rice?
Why don't you live in a cave? Why?
Nobody should eat things raw all the time.
Then what will become of our side dish shop?
That's right. People need this so our shop will do well, right?
That's right.
So cut it.
Did you sleep well?
Jin Ae, how is Manager Kang?
He is a lot better now. He will get discharged soon.
Aigoo, that's a relief. I guessed he must have been scared out of his life.
Get discharged from the hospital? Is Oppa Hoon Jae sick somewhere?
Yes. I didn't tell you because I thought you will get shocked. Hoon Jae...
got hurt a bit. Now he is better.
Got hurt?
You scared me.
But why didn't you tell me? You guys went to the hospital, just leaving me behind, right?
Not just you. We also left Hyeong Soon.
Also, so what if everyone went? We just stood there and came back.
Mom, Hoon Jae's condition wasn't good at that time.
Oh I see. I didn't know that.
If people see this, they will think you are Mr. Fixit's biological sister. Just go slice that.
Where did my other pair go?
Are you going to work?
Yeah. Hey, did you see my dress shoes?
I didn't see it.
Where did it go?
Did you come back from opening the store?
Yes. Work hard.
Hyeong Soon.
Come here.
Use it where needed. Eat something delicious with Sister-in-law.
It is okay. I have money.
Just use it. You can't refuse.
I told you it is okay.
Hey, let me be a Hyung.
What's the point of giving it to someone like me?
Since you mess up all the time, I should be taking care of you.  Who else would if your own Hyung doesn't?
And keep your spirit up, punk.
- Hello.  - Hello.
Where did you leave Chae Ri and always have you two alone?
Our Daughter-In-Law Che Ri is so precious that we kept her in the lower hall. Why?
Your hair pin is pretty.
Your daughter made it for me.
That Hye Joo has no sense!
President.
Oh, you came again, Miss.
I told you you can't.
- Ok.  - What again?
Oppa Chool?
Right? Ok?
- Oppa!  - Aigo.
Hey Ok.
How long has it been?
So, you were the young miss who used to work in finance from the factory that Chool used to work.
Oppa Chool was very nice to me at that time.
Oppa Chool?
You are also Ok, Miss? She is Ok as well.
My name is Han Eun Ok.
I guess she is Ok. San Ok and Eun Ok. It is funny.
It's "Ok" festival time!
So my children's father called you "Ok" "Ok" at that time?
Yes.
Ok, during that time, Ok was a child.
So I called "Ok" "Ok"...
Is the heater too high? It's hot.
I told Daughter-in-law to come to the shop.  Where is she?
Ok! Drink coffee before you leave.
Ok! Ok!
Don't be like that, Noona.
The the person who graduated the vocational school was that shorty?
Oh, now I remember. When Lee Dong Chool used to grease up his hair
and used tons of perfume on his hair, it was about that time.
When he used to work at the factory.
Since we are in this situation, you still are not going to hire me?
What?
I mean, you rejected me because I come off as a cold person.
But since you know I know Chool Oppa,
can't you reconsider?
The term "extenuating circumstance" shouldn't be used in this situation.
I think I already got hired.
Huh?
Yeah Noona, do Ok a favor.
Because Eun Ok graduated from the vocational school, she's fast with calculation.
Noona.
Seriously.
Should I let that cunning In San Ok get burned with jealousy?
But Ok, you got married, right?
Excuse me?
Hello.
Hi Oppa.
You came early.
Working here is a bit difficult.
Huh?
The thing that I like is...
Look here, look here.
Yesterday, that..?
- Can you do it? - Yes.
You have to work hard.
- You're hired.  - I will work hard.
Let's work well.
Hello? Oh yes, CEO! Yes, yes.
Yesterday, you're the anemic girl?
Yes.
Thank you for helping me yesterday Oppa.
It wasn't much. But you got a part-time job here?
Yes, starting today. Please take care of me.
Right, my name is Eng Du (Cherry). Go Eng Du.
Eng Du.
Around me, why Cherry and Eng Du?
- What's your name?  - Oh, my name is
-  Lee Hyeong Soon   - It's Lee Hyeong Soon .
Hyeong Soon.
Since you took off the patient gown, you look much better. Now, you seem like my nephew.
Isn't that so? This is better.
Excuse me.
Chae Ri.
Cheol Woong Oppa's daughter?
I heard you got heard. I just found out this morning.
Is that so?
Did it hurt a lot?
Well, when I got injured, it hurt a little but I'm okay now.
Did you come here because of me?
Yes. I was worried about you.
Oh, my look at her. I guess blood relatives do attract each other.
You shouldn't have come since you are with a baby.
Are you okay?
She's pregnant?
I'm okay.
Even still, it's a relief that I got to see you before you left.
Yes, that's a relief.
Chae Ri.
Are you doing well?
Did you come because Hoon Jae Oppa is your employee?
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
Yeah. That's right.
I heard from Lee Jin Ae that you're doing well.
Yes, everyone is good to me.
It isn't uncomfortable?
I'm not uncomfortable.
Mother-in-law cooks well so everything I eat is delicious. I eat so much
I gained some weight.
Your face looks well. That's good.
Right, Hyeong Soon Oppa got a job.
Where?
He's working at a BBQ restaurant as a part timer.
If his working ability get's recognized, he says he can become a full time employee.
Dad, don't worry. We will do well.
Dad.
Should I tell Chauffeur Oh to drive you?
No. You said you won't help with anything anymore.
You said I'm a stranger.
Why would you offer a ride to someone you don't know?
I will be going now. Stay healthy.
Are you leaving now?
Yes.  Aunt, please go to the car first.
Okay.
What about Chae Ri?
I haven't said anything yet.
Yes. Chae Ri is pregnant so it wouldn't be good to shock her with such news.
For coming to the hospital and watching over me, thank you.
But you can just end it here.
I got hurt due to work.
I think of this as you being concerned due to that.
Thank you.
Hoon Jae.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by Mom Knows Best Team @ Viki
Where did you go during lunch?
Since it was lunch time, I took personal time.
What did you do?
I got my hair done at the salon.
Since you're going on a blind date today?
My hair turned out well, right?
- No.  - What?
Somehow it doesn't suit you too well. Shall I say it's like a country bumpkin?
This is the newest style.
Since not anyone can handle the newest style.
Choi Suh Hyeon.
Who is this?
Yes Choi Suh Hyeon.
Did you have my number saved?
Of course. Isn't it a right manner to show to a person who met on a blind date?
You don't look like someone with manners.
It's a joke. Look here.
You know how we both decided to reject each other. Let's forget about that.
The meaning of forgetting it is...
Let's meet again. I feel like it was a waste if I just saw you once.
What do you think?
Sure, let's do that. Shall we meet today?
Sounds good. Where shall we meet?
I will let you know. Then see you later.
I should get a haircut.
Lunch time is over.
What?
Shouldn't it apply to you that when lunch time is over, you can't use personal time?
As the boss, you should set an example.
Your hair doesn't suit you. You should get it redone.
Did you discharge well?
Yes. Right now, I'm comfortably sitting on my bed.
Did Hoon Jae get discharged?
That's good news.
I miss you.
Shall we see each other at night?  No, I'm not hurting anymore.
Mother.
- Jin Ae, I'll talk to you later. - Okay.
Mother, at this time..?
My son has been discharged so I wanted to stop by.
Mother.
Son, thank you for getting well so quickly.
You worried a lot, huh? I'm sorry.
Your face isn't well, Mother.
Really?
Yeah. I'm serious.
I'll approve of your marriage with Assistant Manager Lee.
Mother.
Mother, thank you.
Last time, I told you, right?
The reason I can't forgive CEO Jang,
is because he couldn't change his mother's mind and gave up on me.
But I couldn't do that to you.
Mother, I'm really
really thankful. I will be better to you.
Jin Ae will do well too.
Mother, thank you.
You like it that much?
Okay. Since you like it, I like it too.
Put the meat at the end.
The vegetables in the middle.  That's what you have to do.
How do you use this Oppa?
For this, you rotate this to turn it on.
To clean it, you move it to the left.
Something must have went in my eye Oppa.
Can you blow in it please?
Where?
I haven't blown yet. Come here.
Oppa!
Chae Ri.
How could you point my eye Oppa?
Sorry, are you hurt?
Oppa, what are you doing right now?
- Eng Du said something went in her eye.- Eng Du?
You! You're the fake girl from yesterday.
- F-Fake?  - I see.
You came here to meet my oppa, huh?
What are you saying Unni?
Chae Ri, what are you doing? You're embarrassing.
She's here again.
Aishee.
What? You want to work here too?
I have to stay right next to you. This won't do.
Who? Do I just meet the CEO?
Hey, hey, hey. You have to be careful because of baby lamb. What can you do here?
- I'm okay.  - How are you okay when you're pregnant?
- I'm not pregnant.  - What?
What are you saying?
Huh?
You, you you.
You're just saying you're not pregnant, right?
You think I'm going to stay still?
Then what do I do?
Girls keep chasing after you.
Chasing what? I was trying to help her.
But why did she have to get a job here?
- It was a coincidence.  - I have a feeling it wasn't a coincidence!
How can you?
- How can you what? - How can you be just like my mom?
You're the same when Mom catches Dad.
Me?
Oppa.
- The CEO is calling you.  - Okay, I'll be there.
Chae Ri, let's go home.
Should I call a taxi?
Chae Ri, I have to work.
Okay. I'll go.
But why did you come here?
-You came to spy on me?-No, I just got sad.
I ran into Dad a while ago.
Is that so?
Chae Ri, I don't have a dinner shift,
so I will go home early and make you something delicious.
Also, don't be so upset with me.
In here, there's no one but Chae Ri.
Chae Ri, Chae Ri, Chae Ri, there's no one but Chae Ri.
Aigo.
I'm not pregnant?
Even though it didn't show on the test, I was hoping I was.
I heard it can happen if you're not pregnant for that long.
But why did it not show a sign?
Also, why I felt like I was pregnant?
It may be that you
had a high desire to be pregnant.
Do you want a baby very badly right now?
I did want a baby so much.
If I have a child,
I thought Dad would approve.
Since I knew everyone would accept (me).
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by Mom Knows Best Team @ Viki
Mother-in-law.
Aigo, why is a child's mom sitting on the cold cement?
- Use this to sit.  - It's okay.
Sit here.
I heard you went to see Mr. Fix It.
I got a call asking if you got home safely.
Aigo, why did you go there?
But why are you sitting here?
Are you frustrated?
- No - Maybe your morning sickness is going to start.
You don't feel nauseous or anything yet, right?
Yes.
- Mother... - Look at that fake girl.
Who is she?
Someone.
A sly fox that's dripping with fake shyness.
I have someone like that too.
It's time to leave.
Where is your blind date?
- Why?  - Just because.
If it's a secret then it's fine.
What's this? You just lost interest?
I don't want to go on a blind date.
Wow, I'm lonely.
I'm so lonely.
Christmas is sparkling.
There's no one to keep me
warm.
Wait a minute. She should be here.
Here.
No, no.
This isn't it.
Nice to meet you.
♬ She may be the face I can't forgetThe trace of pleasure or regret ♬
Wow! That beauty. ♬ May be my treasure or the price I have to pay ♬
♬ She may be the song the summer sings ♬
♬ May be the chill the autumn bringsMay be a hundred different things ♬
Hello. I'm Seon Hye Joo.♬ Within the measure of a day ♬
Ah, ah yes.
He..he..hello.
I'm Kim..Kim..
I'm Kim Sa... Kim Sa...Kim Sa Jang (president)
Ah.. your name is Kim Sa Jang, too?
Yes, my name is Kim Sa— No, it's not.
No, no, my name is...
Kim Jun Yeon.
Just please comfortably call me "Jun Yeon Oppa".
Yes, Jun Yeon..
Ah, ah.
Wait a moment. Wait a moment.
Yes.
You think I wouldn't know if you didn't tell me?
Of course he would want to meet in his own store.
So he can show off.
Would you like some tea? Tea? What kind?
Yes, then...
I'll have some Earl Grey.
- Earl Grey.- Earl Grey.
That's good.
Excuse me.
Earl Grey.
We're going to eat all of this?
Yes, our cake is very delicious.
I wanted you to sample them.
Eat.
We're going to eat dinner later.
Of course we should eat.
So this is
the appetizer.
Eat.
♬ She may be the face I can't forgetThe trace of pleasure or regret ♬
♬ May be my treasure or the price I have to pay ♬
♬ She may be the song the summer sings ♬
That human, really?
Lawyer Lee.
Lawyer?
How could you be here when we were supposed to meet at the other store?
What happened was, I stopped by here and was going to go.
But how did you know I was here?
I was sitting over there and saw you here.
I was confused so I came here.
What? Wait,
you can see from there?  - Of course.
I have really good eye sight.
Ah, who's causing a commotion. They have no manners.
Oh! Hyeong Gyu.
Hyeong Gyu, it's been a while.
Yes.
Oh! San's mother!
We see each other again. We're destined to meet.
You two know each other?
Come here for a bit.
Seeing
like this again, we should shake.
Again?
Ah yes. Is Jin Ae doing well?
Yes. She's going to get married.
I think I'm going to get married too.
What?
Introduce yourself to my future wife.
- What?  - What?! Mr. Kim.
Well,
Hye Joo,
I liked you from first sight.
We should just start a relationship.
San's mother has a family.
Ah, Hye Joo is single with a kid.
I am single with a kid too. We're both single with kids.
- Ah, you two suit each other well.  - Isn't that right?
We're well suited.
But what's your relationship?
We're having blind dates but we're considering a relationship.
Ah, if that's so
you must have a profession.-What?
See, Hyeong Gyu is famous for only meeting women with a profession.
Or you have some land or something.
Hyeong gyu, you achieved your dream after all.
A woman with a profession!
Hyung, I did what?
Since meeting like this way is fate, let's share the same table.
Let's have dinner together.
- I'll pay.  - That would be great.  - No.
- Then let's go.  - Yes.
- Excuse me.  - Excuse me.
Aigoo, here...
Over here please!
Yes?
Instead of this, please bring more.
A big bucket full.
If the table isn't full, I don't have an appetite.
You won't be able to eat it all.
Believe me.
I am limitless!
Yes.
Omo, you came again?
Eat deliciously.
Mom!
Oh.
Mother-In-law, hello.
In-law?
Aigo.
Are there inconvenient issues with my building?
Yes, well..
That's your mother.
That's Hyeong Gyu.
San Ok, is that dentist Hyeong gyu met on the blind date?
Yeah, he said he wouldn't see her but I guess they're meeting again.
Omo, hello Madam.
Mother.
It's been a while.
It's been a while Mr. Kim.
How...?
Are you on your date with Hye Joo?
Yes, yes. I heard you hooked us up.
Thank you.
For the next 3 years, I will not increase the rent to Madam Im.
I just spoke about it.
Hello, are you Hyeong Gyu's mother?
Hyeong Gyu looks just like you. I'm Choi So Yeon.
Yes. It's nice to meet you.
How did you come here?
I wanted to see Hyeong Gyu again so I told me we should meet.
Is that so?
So what do you think after meeting him again?
I'm alright with him.
With Hyeong Gyu, I'm not sure.
- I'm...  - Anyways, please take care of me, Mother.
- I will stop by to say hi often.  - Okay, come visit.
Wait a moment. Today
Today, it's how I feel!
I will ring this golden bell.
All the customers who came in today, I will pay for your meals.
Mother-in-law, please give me all the chicken from today.
Everything? Omo.
Your chicken is really delicious.
What the heck. Fry up everything. Everything!
President Kim, don't you think you are overdoing it?
No.
If it's for Hye Joo, I can do anything.
President Kim sure does things with a gusto.
It must be nice.
Eat as much as you want. As much as you want.
He must have a lot of money.
Yeah, fry up everything. Everything.
Hoon Jae should be cold right now.
- Jin Ae.  - Oh!
Hoon Jae. How did you come here?
Am I kid? How could I not get here?
You were just discharged. How could you be walking around like this?
It's okay. I didn't drive and I took the taxi.
I have good news to share.
Good news?
Mother approved of our marriage.
Really? Really?!
Really.
Hoon Jae.
We can get married now.
Jin Ae.
We should get married quickly.
Let's get married quickly.
Mr. Fix It!
Engineer Kang.
Mother, Father, hello.
Aigo, I heard you got discharged.
Even if you're discharged, you should be taking care of your body.
I'm okay now.
I heard you stopped by the hospital.
Even though you miss Jin Ae, how could you come here at night?
I wanted to see Mother and Father.  Also, I have something to tell you.
Huh? What do you need to say?
Marriage?
So now you two can get married?
Yes, Father-in-law.
Wow, finally. Finally.
Our CEO has changed her mind.
Aigo, Jin Ae, you like it, huh?
Yes, Dad.
- Mom.  - Mother-in-law.
So? Your CEO allowed the marriage,
so I should applause and dance?
I am sorry but now I can't give permission.
Honey, why are you changing your mind?
I also told you, right?
Until your mother apologize for what she said to Jin Ae, I can't approve of this marriage.
I can never.
Mom!
Why are you like this? It hurts.
Aren't you really too much?
You were waiting for CEO's approval to change your mind, huh?
After she approved, you were going to disapprove, right?
Aigoo, I was thinking about overturning the dinner table as soon as it was set.
Since I'm not a parent who wants to see you do well, right?
Yeah.
Aigo, where is your pride? Did you pluck it out and move all the way over there?
After saying "I don't like you!"
Even after hearing that? Even after trying to send you far away like New York,
do you have feelings that you like?
Then what should I do? Hoon Jae and I came this far with so much difficulty.
So do I give up and say I'm not going to get married?
Hey, that CEO lady wanted her son to get married to someone else.
When Mr. Fix It was laying in bed at the hospital and we went to visit
some girl went in saying "Mother-in-law, Mother-in-law".
After seeing that, do you have happy feelings?
Then what do you want me to do?
Accept an apology. Get a promise.
We have to get a solid promise before we move forward. Do you know what kind of daughter you are?
You know what kind of daughter you are to me?
If somebody saw us now, they must think that we have an exceptional mother daughter relationship.
They may think that among our siblings, you must have loved me the most.
Why can't you answer?
I really don't understand why you are doing this now.
Why are you being like this and starting to care?
Anyways, I won't accept unless that happens.
You're my kid and I can do that but I can't see someone else mistreat you.
Hey, before you get married,
aigoo, even if she thinks there's no one better than her daughter-in-law,
once you get married, mother-in-laws are known to flip on you.
To someone who told you "I dislike you!" To that woman, how can I trust that woman?
Mother-in-law, I'm sorry. I was short minded.
I will make it so you two meet.
Mother-in-law.
Aigoo, there are no parents who can win against their child.
You had no choice.
I know, huh?
You should have accepted Assistant Manager Lee from the beginning.
I wanted to do that but my feelings weren't that way.
I know why you did that.
Why did I do that?
Hoon Jae likes Assistant Manager Lee more than you.
So you couldn't accept it.
That's why a long time ago, Cheol Woong Oppa's mother pushed you away too.
Because someone stole her precious son away from her.
Hey! I'm different from that Grandma.
Well, anyways,
even so, you didn't lose the game yet.
What are you saying?
Unni, now you are her mother-in-law.
You can do whatever you want with Assistant Manager Lee.
Hey. I'm not that type of Mother-in-law.
I don't think so.
Be quiet. Just drink this.
Doing this, you're to die for.
Killer?
You say such nonsense.
Mom, to that CEO, don't give in.
The way I see it, forestallment is important with that ahjumma.
Hey, but how could you speak less to me?
What? Mom?
Saying Mother-in-law, it seems like I'm not close to you.
And I don't have a mother.
So my Mother-in-law is my mom.
Mom, fighting.
Aigo. Aigo.
- Are you all ready?  - Yes.
I should clean Mom's heels.
Wow, our Ok, dressed like this, my mood is great.
Aigo, CEO doesn't compare.
I will be back.
Ok, that is... I know that you're upset and offended,
but still, try to be more positive.
Once you see her, you will have many thoughts.
While she was here, how she glared at our Jin Ae like this.
Those kind of things.
Also, when you speak, think of Jin Ae.
After she met Engineer Kang, she's been out of her mind and excited.
So you are telling me to keep my temper in check?
Okay, I won't turn the table over.
Ok, smile.
Smile.
- Mom.  - What?
You know...don't do too much.
Why? You think I'll jeopardize the marriage?
Yes.
Leave. Leave.
At the end, it happens like this.
Hwang Yeong Seon, you lost.
Have you come?
You came early.
I just got here.
Hoon Jae has some work at the company so I think he is still at the company.
Yes, I heard.
Leave.
Assistant Manager Lee, why don't you stay as well? Hoon Jae will come one hour later.
No. As for today, I just want to talk to you alone.
Mom.
Yes, Assistant Manager Lee. Please leave.
Yes.
Please sit down.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by Mom Knows Best Team @ Viki
♬ Love is good even if my heart aches ♬
♬ No matter what anyone says to me you are the best ♬
♬ Even if life is difficult even if life deceives me ♬
♬ For me there is no one except you ♬
♬  Even if life makes me cry ♬
♬ Because you will make me smile again ♬
In front of you, even these flowers don't have a chance to shine!
Who are you, Ajusshi?
Your mom's boyfriend.
What are those? Then how about you, Mom?
I really wanted to change how I lived.
Hoon Jae, you have to tell your Mom that you want to live with her. that's the main point.
What? Chae Ri Daughter-in-law...
turns out to be our In-Law's young lady.
How in the world...