All characters, party names, and incidents appearing in this drama are fictitious creations.
Assemblywoman Hong Chan Mi was pissed.
How are other members reacting to Assemblyman Jo Woong Gyu's enrollment?
The response was not good.
They will like it when they see the things happening in the future.
What?
We've transferred in the new student.
Now we have to take care of the troublemaker.
Jin Sang Pil... I will expel him from the party.
For sure.
Episode 15
Gisong Island is our country's iconic migratory bird sanctuary.
Every year, tens of thousands of birds flock to the wintering grounds
and more than 30 of the world's rarest species can be observed there.
What do you mean you want to build a massive resort there?
Not there but next to it...
- Vice Minister of Ministry of Environment.- Yes.
This is an issue that is directly related to the raison d'être of the Ministry of Environment.
You can never endorse the Environmental Impact Assessment.
Man cannot be the only species populating the earth.
Animals have to live too and plants too. We all have to co-exist.
That way, we can achieve that sustainable development or whatever.
As Assemblywomen Cheon said, the Ministry of Environment should
firmly intervene.
Yes, after a careful review...
Point of order.
"Don't endorse the Environmental Impact Assessment."
"Intervene."
These are obviously and explicitly pejorative words.
At this rate, how can the Ministry of Environment work in a principled way
and conduct an unbiased review?
I request your retraction of the statements.
Assemblyman Jo, since when did you belong to the ruling party to side with it?
Be ashamed of yourself.
Please also retract your ad hominem statement toward a fellow assemblyman.
I too raise a point of order.
Vice Minister, please come to our Gookmin Party to do an environmental assessment.
- Excuse me?- Our party is supposedly a newly rising migratory bird habitat.
And supposedly we have a strange bird, too, which thinks of itself as an assemblyman.
You know ornithologists? Please bring them on your visit.
Please come without fail. Please I beg you.
How can you spit out whatever comes to your mind like that?
Did you see the meeting?
Assemblyman Jo is holding it in because he has a twinge of conscience.
What do you think would have happened with another assemblyman?
They would have raised a ruckus about taking you to a disciplinary action or suing you for slander.
Would I have said such a thing to another fellah?
It was because Jo Woong Bird spoke too brashly like that.
Don't even mouth the words of Gookmin Party being a migratory bird habitat.
You must refrain from all statements provoking the party for the time being.
- Why?- With Assemblyman Jo's enrollment, the ratio of the ruling and opposition party seats changed to 152:148.
The swing vote, the Indifferent-to-BH faction's sole weapon, is gone!
So you are saying even if I'm kicked out of the party, the majority government by the ruling party will be maintained.
That is right.
Even though we look very serene on the outside, the Indifferent-to-BH faction is facing a very serious crisis.
- Aide Choi, it seems like you don't know much now.- What?
Why is the swing vote the Indifferent-to-BH faction's sole weapon?
When we have secret weapons?
Flame Man, JSP.
And Aide Choi and Kids.
The only solution is to recruit a new assemblyman into the Indifferent-to-BH faction.
Unless that person is out of his mind, who would want to join the Indifferent-to-BH faction?
That is right, though. If they come, it's not like some special benefit will be waiting... was what you were going to say, right?
But lately, there is a person in the Gookmin Party who has lost her grasp on reality.
- Who?- Who do you think it is?
Madam Hong?
Stop shoddy construction, waste of budget, and environmental destruction!
Stop it! Stop it!
- Stop shoddy construction!- Stop it! Stop it!
Stop shoddy construction, waste of budget, and environmental destruction!
Stop it! Stop it!
Stop shoddy construction, waste of budget and environmental destruction! Stop it!
Madam Hong?
Party Leader Yoon Jeong Soo is said to have taken umbrage at Assemblyman Jin's migratory bird habitat comment.
But we can't sanction him for that alone. We may get a media whiplash that way.
Secretary General, how about using the method I proposed...
No, that is too risky.
I'd like to hear your explanation about the election of the party chapter head in Seogyeong City Gap Voting District.
Secretary Lim, you may leave.
Please have a seat.
- Answer me first.- Assemblywoman Hong.
If only you had given me some support,
I would not have lost so shamefully.
What is the reason you didn't help me?
Tell Assemblywoman Hong Chan Mi to schedule meetings with Assembly news desk chairs.
But... I can't get in touch with Assemblywoman Hong.
I think an order has been handed down from the Blue House.
The secretary general is a position that cannot and must not interfere with any election within the party.
Secretary General Baek!
Humbly accept the outcome.
The reason for your defeat was not lack of my help.
But would it not be because you failed to capture the party members' hearts?
I will cut to the chase. The possibility of my getting next year's nomination for the Seogyeong City Gap Voting District,
is there any remaining?
No, I will revise my question.
Inside you, is there any intent to give me a nomination?
That is enough for today.
I have done my best for you for the last four years.
Is this how you repay me?
Assemblywoman Hong.
When you were getting pressured by the Blue House to resign,
who appeared in this room first and shielded you...
Have you already forgotten about it?
You came to visit me in this room that day in order to shield me?
Yes.
Assemblywoman Hong, you merely got in my line.
- What?- Rather than from Jin Sang Pil,
it would be far easier to get a nomination from the Baek Do Hyeon Secretariat. Such a thoroughly political calculation.
The subject toward whom you did your best for the last four years
was not Baek Do Hyeon, but a nomination. Can you deny that?
For whatever term that remains, have some faith in the voting district
and faithfully carry out your duties as a proportional representative.
Just do it while I'm telling you nicely.
- I don't want to.- Let's do it.
- I said I don't want to.- Why don't we listen and be obedient?
You'll have to talk sense before I will listen.
Why is this nonsense?
Go outside and ask the secretaries...
whether seducing Assemblywoman Hong Chan Mi to join the Indifferent-to-BH faction makes any sense.
But the only recruitable person right now is Assemblywoman Hong Chan Mi.
Still, you have to look before you leap.
Just leap anywhere, when a viper is there? You'll get snapped at, bitten!
Even though Assemblywoman Hong has become too puffed up after sudden success at a young age,
originally she was a rather sensible woman.
Don't just say no but rise to the challenge.
Challenge what? I hate the idea.
Seriously!
- Let's do it already.- If you are so desperate, you can just go and do it!
Go and do it! Valiantly!
I can't do it because I'm scared. Of getting bitten. I will never do it!
If you keep doing this, I will disregard our ranks again.
You just try disregarding ranks, really.
The last time, I overlooked it because you were drunk, not because you were a girl.
And do you even know how heavy you are...
Where are you going in the middle of the conversation!
I have to go self-wash the car. It's really dirty.
So why did you send Secretary Byeon on a vacation, when we are dying from overwork!
Civil Service Exam Prep School Signs
Aish, really...
How can there be so many civil servant schools?
At this rate, everyone will become a civil servant...
Work hard.
Hyung, why does it takes days for you to find one person?
Hyung, are you perhaps screwing around somewhere?
Are you going to keep saying those things that get to me?
Hey. Do you really think Secretary Kim is around here?
To me, I don't think he's here.
He told Aide Choi by email that
he was with his buddies who studied together for the police exam.
So, hurry up and find him. Don't contact me until you find him. Jeez.
Hey, Sang Pil. Hey. Hey.
Why is it so hard to find one person?
Hong Chan MiAssemblywoman
The only person we can recruit now is Assemblywoman Hong.
Why are you loitering around another assemblyman's office?
I wasn't loitering. Since you are just across from me, I was wondering how you were doing and such.
Step aside.
Assemblywoman Hong.
I... about the committee chairperson election,
I know about it.
So? You came to congratulate someone when they're mourning?
No. That's nonsense.
If you are inclined,
in Indifferent-to-BH faction, there is this one good position.
Maybe you can come into our faction...
-What did you say?-It's not that I am trying to belittle you.
As for me, with sincerity...
If I go in, what are you going to do for me?
What?
Are you able to give me a nomination?
Come on, that would be hard for me.
What about political funds?
What about an executive party position or an organization?
All of that I can't...
Then, shut that mouth of yours.
But honestly, if you come into the Indifferent-to-BH faction,
guaranteed monthly income, room and board, things like that are impossible, but...
-You will suffer like a dog but...-Stop!
But since both of us are in the same situation...
Stop. Stop and shut your mouth! Shut it!
If you ever start talking about frivolous things again,
then, you'll end up dying and I'll end up dying.
Did you see that just now?
Did you see the venomous snake ripping me to shreds?
You knew you couldn't get her to join, so you made me do it.
I was so scared, my smile muscles atrophied.
Welcome, Assemblyman Kang.
So, what brings you here?
A while ago, during the Secretary General upheaval,
I heard that there was something promised between you and our Assemblyman Park.
Are you talking about increasing the Anti-BH share to 40% in next year's general election?
Yes, as it's an important matter,
either a memorandum or written promise
would put him at ease, he said.
His personality is not by nature that meticulous.
But Secretary General Baek, you've been doing a lot of backstabbing.
That's why he's being this way. So you'll understand and write one, right?
Assemblyman Park, Baek Do Hyeon asks for a little more time.
I guess he's afraid that he might fall into our trap.
Don't worry.
I will punch in at his office every day to badger him.
And if things don't work out, I will just punch him.
Hello.
To what do I owe this honor, Assemblywoman Hong?
I have something important to tell you face to face.
Oh, yes, I understand. Then I will see you there.
By Assemblywoman Hong, do you mean Hong Chan Mi?
She says she has something important to say.
Important my butt.
She got used and ditched by Baek Do Hyeon.
It's obvious that she will ask us take her in.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Viki
Secretary General.
Why are you here?
Assemblyman Park Choon Seop asked me to relay this message to you.
He is having a hard time as it is to take care of current family members.
He's not in a position to accept a new family member.
I will overlook this for old times' sake.
But you'd better be more judicious in the future.
Since you brought up old times,
let me just ask you one question.
During the last 4 years, what was I to you, Secretary General?
A butler or a trainbearer?
If neither, a dog that barks on command?
If I have to put it into words, probably a partner.
Who can always be contractually terminated if she fails to meet the profit goals.
So it was like that, after all. When I considered you a comrade.
Assemblywoman Hong, a comrade refers to a person
who will gladly accompany you any time through thick and thin.
If it's Choi In Kyung, then maybe.
So till the end, you are talking about Choi In Kyung.
That word "comrade" does not fit you, Assemblywoman Hong.
Secretary Baek! No, you! You underestimated me.  (The form of "you" rather than his name is an insult.)
You will end up regretting this.
So it is a word that describes the relationship between an act and the law.
Commonly, legality means...
Maybe it's because I know now. He's a spitting image of his father when he was young.
They say becoming a civil servant is like plucking a star out of the sky.
Will he do well?
Let's go now.
And not see Secretary Kim?
It's enough that I've seen him doing well.
How can you make me work like a dog for several days just so that you can see his face, huh?
I am sorry, Hyung.
Could you give me some time? Hong Chan Mi.
Why, is Aide Choi giving you a hard time again?
I was rude to you earlier. I am sorry.
Aigo, well, I didn't do anything commendable either. Just ended up rubbing it in...
I am sorry, too.
The reason I asked to see you
is to add to the Indifferent-to-BH faction's track record.
Track record? What track record?
Just promise me one thing.
The information I am about to give you now,
not to tell anyone that you got it from me.
But at least to our Aide Choi --
I have to say it.
Then consider this never happened.
You can turn back.
What is it, so you're like this?
Promise me first.
But I'll get into big trouble.
Okay, I will promise.
You mean it?
Have you been tricked all your life? Yes, I will promise.
What is it?
An allegation about cutting up the nomination pie along the faction lines in Gookmin Party...
You should not have done as you wished. You should have consulted with me first!
- I can no longer do it.- Aide Choi!
I can't do it!No way!
Good morning!
Did you have a good vacation?
What vacation? I've come back from studying to death.
- Study?- You must have studied oriental paintings (Go-stop game).
Right, right.
The Assemblyman didn't come up with you?
Assemblyman Jin is holding a press conference in the Media Hall now.
- What press conference?- How would I know what even you don't know?
Pro-BH faction's Assemblyman Baek Do Hyeon and Anti-BH faction's Assemblyman Park Choon Seop
had a closed-door meeting during the Secretary General's resignation scandal
and, in return for their support of Assemblyman Baek Do Hyeon keeping the secretary general position,
agreed to cut up the nomination pie along faction lines for the next general election.
The gist was
to enlarge the Anti-BH's share, which currently makes up
35% of the incumbent party assemblymen, to 40%.
Has Assemblyman Jin scored another one again?
That is not just one score, but it's a mega-ton nuclear bomb.
At this juncture when a special committee to reform the party nomination system is actively working,
the leaders of these two factions were meeting behind closed doors and colluding this way.
In a nutshell, this was a textbook case of the old-school, anti-democratic,
backward-looking politics that undermines democracy.
Wake up. The people are watching.
Secretary General Baek Do Hyeon and Assemblyman Park Choon Seop,
explain yourselves before the people right away.
That is all.
Yes?
By this, what are you trying to pull now?
I am in the middle of investigating the circumstances under which this came to pass myself.
The circumstances or whatever, I am telling you in no uncertain terms.
If this agreement was all for naught, you won't be safe yourself.
Assemblyman Park, don't you think Baek Do Hyeon passed on the information
to Jin Sang Pil so as not to give us a written promise?
Do Hyeon, was Jin Sang Pil's disclosure true?
Whether it's true or not, put out urgent fires first.
Don't give reporters time to exercise their powers of imagination.
Make an immediate announcement that it is baseless.
How come it's quiet... Is it a situation where she's praising him for a good job?
Don't you know Aide Choi's personality? Wait. For an explosion in no time.
- You should have consulted with me first!- See?
So I am apologizing to you right now because of that.
Would an apology solve this problem?
Don't you know what a huge mess you created just now?
I know. Wouldn't I know it?
If I don't know that, then I am a real psycho, a real jerk.
I know, but my situation was...
Here, Aide Choi. When you're angry, chocolate...
But who ate all of this?!
Really people, without telling me, seriously...
Please stop being angry now.
Okay.
I will stop being angry and ask you a different question.
This... comes from an informant, right?
- Yes.- Who is it?
It has quieted down quickly.
Today's ending is boring. What a pity.
Why don't we all go back to work?
- You can't tell me? Does that make any sense?- They are going at it again!
But I told you I promised that informant not to divulge the identity.
Not to other people, but you must at least tell me.
- Don't you trust me?- I do!
I trust you so much. If not you, whom would I trust, huh?
But that is really... A promise is a promise.
Hurry and tell me. I have to know who the informant is
so that I can figure out if that is reliable information,
and if it's reliable, the reason behind the tip-off.
I'm really sorry.
Assemblyman!
I am really truly sorry, but a promise...
Why don't you just hit me instead? I'm okay, just hit me!
Slap me, I'm fine with it!
Do you want to give me an ass whooping? Do it, whoop me!
Assemblyman Park, Baek Do Hyeon held a press conference.
- The contents?- Jin Sang Pil's statement was a total fabrication
and an epitome of mudslinging politics that abuses his parliamentary privilege. (i.e. cannot be sued for slander)
Assemblyman Park, if it plays out like this,
our share of 40% is completely out of the question now.
Is it Secretary General Baek?
Ah, Baek—
Assemblyman Park, is Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil's disclosure true?
Have you agreed to a faction share with Secretary General Baek Do Hyeon?
But reporters, Assemblyman Park is not running away or anything.
So calm down and sit down to drink some tea
and share some cookies as well...
Secretary General Baek officially denied it. What is the Anti-BH position?
Assemblyman Park, please answer.
This should be, in a calm manner...
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil's claim is made up.
Without fail, I will ask him to bear responsibility for this fabrication.
Joint Announcement of Baek Do Hyeon and Park Choon Seop: "Agreement about Gookmin Party Nominee Shares Is Fabrication!"
- Yes.- How does it feel to get beaten up by a partner who had been contractually terminated?
I should rather thank you for stopping the Anti-BH's share from getting bigger.
Is Assemblyman Park Choon Seop the kind of person who'd tolerate a loss?
Even though not much time remains in my term,
I will be able to watch you losing the election, while exchanging blows with the Anti-BH faction.
Good luck.
Secretary General Baek, what on earth happened here!
Explain yourself!
Are you stabbing us in the back so as to not to give us the written promise, or what!
- It was Assemblywoman Hong Chan Mi.- What?
- Hong Chan Mi?- She holds a grudge because of yesterday's event and she tipped off Assemblyman Jin.
We don't have any interest in that sort of thing.
What I want is
Secretary General Baek's promise to carry out the agreement.
Yes, a written promise!
Before you write us that promise, I won't take even one step from here ever!
Aren't you two somehow mistaken about the priorities?
- What?- Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil who has dishonored the party by spreading a false rumor
and Assemblywoman Hong Chan Mi who fed him that false rumor!
I think taking appropriate measures against those two comes first.
Do you intend to drag this out again?
I'm just saying we should get rid of weeds first to harvest better fruit.
What do you think?
Exposé politics, obnoxious politics.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
Out, Jin Sang Pil!
I, Park Choon Seop, during the last 30 years
of my political career, acted with rationality,
and I'm proud to say that I've always kept my dignity and stayed only on the right path.
However, because of Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil's irresponsible exposé,
the pride and honor that I have built through all these years
collapsed completely.
All this time, our party
has done its part with patience and efforts at persuasion
in dealing with Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil's perpetuation of exposé politics.
But we can't approve it anymore.
We have decided to file a complaint against Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil to our party's ethics committee.
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil shall, before the Ethics Committee hearing,
prove to the party and citizens that what he exposed today was not false information.
If he ignores our demand,
the Ethics Committee shall remove his name and expel him from the party.
Exposé politics, obnoxious politics. Out, Jin Sang Pil!
Out, Jin Sang Pil! Out, Jin Sang Pil!
To avoid being removed from the party,
you have to prove the credibility of your claim.
You'll have to tell us who the informant was in the end.
That's right. Stop being stubborn.
You'll get kicked out at this rate.
If they want to kick me out, let them.
Assemblyman.
The Ethics Committee disciplinary hearing has been scheduled.
What discipline?
Notice of the Party's Ethics Committee Hearing.Expulsion of Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil
Wow. These people
Wow. These people are surely moving fast.
Are you still not going to tell us who the informant is?
I can't help it.
Do you know what it means
to be expelled from the party?
It means the Indifferent-to-BH faction that has been gaining much support from the citizens will cease to exist.
I still can't help it.
The informant definitely belongs to Gookmin Party.
From this point on, log onto the websites of every single assemblyman as well as the party,
and find out if anyone used the same format as this one
- for a press conference statement.- Yes.
Even if the format's different, if the statements have similar text or expressions, print them out
and bring them to me.
- Understood?- Yes.
To stop Assemblyman from being expelled from the party, we must find the informant.
Yes.
Assemblyman Jin, you must keep your promise.
Why aren't you answering?
You promised you would never tell people that I was the one who gave you the tip.
It's just that you asked about the obvious.
Don't worry. Bye.
Assemblyman Jin. Assemblyman!
Who was that?
It's nothing.
What is it?
A notice from the Ethics Committee was transmitted.
Ethics Committee?
What is it?
List of Members of the Committee: Hong Chan Mi, Kang Sang Ho...
Whose idea was it to put me on the disciplinary committee
to judge Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil?
I'm not sure. Why don't you ask the Ethics Committee?
I asked who!
It's Park Choon Seop.
Why did you include me in the disciplinary committee?
Obviously, because what you did was despicable.
Aren't you being too hasty to decide it was me?
If it ever turns out
that you were Assemblyman Jin's informant,
Secretary General and I will issue a joint statement
I'm listening.
Assemblywoman Hong Chan Mi, who lost the election for the chairman of the member council,
became upset at Secretary General for not helping her,
and was denied after attempting to join the Anti-BH faction.
She then began to bear a grudge, and in order to create conflict between the two factions,
on the condition that he wouldn't reveal the informant,
she supplied Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil with false information.
Do you think I'll just let you do that and do nothing?
I'm an attorney.
Look, Assemblywoman Hong.
The place we live in is not a law court but Yeouido.
Turning a Spokeswoman who gained popularity with her looks alone into an idiot
is a piece of cake here.
Hello.
Assemblyman Park's green tea's quite aromatic.
It truly is.
Attend the disciplinary hearing and demand Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil's expulsion from the party.
Why do I have to do that?
If Jin Sang Pil says your name aloud, isn't it better for you to deny it right then?
It would be extremely troublesome for you if things get out of hand and you're not there.
Assemblyman Jin will never disclose the informant.
Don't forget. Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil must be expelled.
Look, Assemblywoman Hong.
Will Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil
disclose the informant or not?
He won't.
Although he's incompetent, he's a man of principle.
It might seem people are different,
but if you look inside, they're all the same.
If you like something, others like it too, and if you hate something, others hate it too.
If you think you might tell on someone, others will do the same.
Aide Choi.
We looked everywhere but can't find anything similar to this.
- Secretary Sim.- Yes.
Did you check everything from the Spokeswoman's office and Assemblywoman Hong Chan Mi's office?
Yes, I compared them all.
Why Assemblywoman Hong Chan Mi all of a sudden?
No matter how much I think about it, Assemblywoman Hong Chan Mi is the informant.
To have access to such classified information, the person must be one of the assemblymen.
Because Assemblywoman Hong had a falling out with Secretary General Baek, that gives her motivation too.
What's up with him?
Aide.
- About Assemblywoman Hong.- Yes.
I just received an electronic notice.
She's one of the disciplinary committee members for our Assemblyman.
Disciplinary committee member?
Then it's not her.
Unless she's gone crazy, would she strike him with disciplinary action when she was the one feeding him information?
Attend the disciplinary hearing and demand Assemblyman Jin's removal.
What are you doing?
I'm here because I have something to say.
If it's Choi In Kyung, then maybe.
That word "comrade" does not fit you, Assemblywoman Hong.
I have nothing to hear from you.
Would you vote
against expelling my Assemblyman?
What did you say?
Disciplinary committee member.
You probably became one by Secretary General Baek's order.
But instead of Secretary General Baek who has hit rock bottom,
I'm asking you to choose my Assemblyman.
You seem to be relapsing into the symptom of not knowing your place again.
Do I look like a person who will work with someone like Assemblyman Jin?
About 6 years ago,
at a gathering of attorneys who loved the environment,
when you were demonstrating for amending the environmental acts,
I accompanied Secretary General Baek there.
What?
At the place where the demonstration took place,
there was a young lawyer who wrote something on the big poster.
Even though she had magic marker pen marks all over her hands and face,
she asked to shake our hands without hesitation.
She was brave and passionate.
What are you talking about right now?
I am telling you that you were like that in the old times.
So?
You want to tell me I have changed, huh?
"After a promising person got the gold badge,
she became trash." That's what you want to ridicule me about.
Assemblywoman, you have not changed nor became trash. But...
What about But?
Like many of the proportional assemblymen,
I think you are weighed down by the badge worn suddenly
without much preparation.
Ally yourself with our Assemblyman.
Our Assemblyman is the person who can bear the weight with you.
Get out.
- Assemblywoman. - Didn't you hear? Get out!
Still, I...
did my best. Do you know that?
If anybody among the proportional assemblymen worked harder than I did on Assembly activities, ask him to step forward.
I admit that you worked hard on Assembly activities.
But as a proportional assemblywoman,
whom you represented, indeed --
- can you say that with confidence?  - What?
Please check with whom you ate lunch and dinner for the last four years.
It shows there whom you represented.
This bravado...
In Kyung, what are you going to do if you started a fire?
Aide Choi.
What?
I found...
The informer.
The informer has to be this person.
Your reasoning?
There was a fact that went unnoticed.
Madam Hong is the incarnate fiend of ad lib.
-Ad lib? - Yes.
Hence, from the statements on the home page
we couldn't figure out who was the informer.
Because those statements were written by the aides.
Right? Look at this.
The people watch us.
Here.
The Assemblyman's statement written by the informer herself.
Wake up! The people are watching!
The people are watching.
She is properly caught. M.a.d.a.m. Hong.
Did I do well?
Yeah.
Praise me.
That was praise, wasn't it?
Do you understand the meaning of getting expelled?
It means Indifferent-to-BH, who received a lot of support from the public, will disappear.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Viki
Aide Choi.
Assemblywoman Hong, who gave the information to you,
became a member of the very disciplinary committee that will discipline you.
Tell the press now. Even though Hong Chan Mi will deny it.
First, break the news.
- It's okay.- Pardon?
In order not to get expelled from the party,
revealing the informer seems so low.
Assemblyman.
Assemblywoman is going to expel you from the party right now.
Is it a big deal that you don't look low in this situation?
Go home now.
If you are not able to do it, I will.
Aide Choi. Wait for a moment. Wait.
It is no use even if you stop me.
I can't watch Indifferent-to-BH to disappear like this. If Indifferent-to-BH disappears,
my goal, that I will get you re-elected, will vanish.
Aide Choi.
I, too, do this to save Indifferent-to-BH.
What are you saying?
You said I can't act by myself for Indifferent-to-BH.
Then, you are doing this because of recruiting Assemblywoman Hong?
Assemblywoman Hong asked me what I can do for her if she joins Indifferent-to-BH.
Nomination? I can't offer it to her.
Political funds, a party position, or an Assembly position...
I can't get her any of them. But, when I thought about it,
there is one thing I can do for her.
What is that?
Keeping the promise. Not betraying her.
I can be trustworthy to the person who always deceives or is deceived.
Assemblywoman Hong
almost lost her reason.
Do you think she would know your intention?
Whether she knows or not, if I am a leader of Indifferent-to-BH, I have to act this way.
-Assemblyman.  -That's why you just pretend not to know it.
I beg of you.
Gookmin Party
2015 3rd Ethics Committee
Agenda: Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil's Disciplinary Punishment of Expulsion from the Assembly and the Party
Ahh, really crazy.
Because Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil circulated the fabricated false information,
the image of the party has fallen to the ground, right now.
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil, do you admit your conduct is subject to discipline?
No, I don't admit it.
I told the truth. How is it that conduct subject to discipline?
Playing pat-a-cake with the shares of nominees between the Pro-BH and Anti-BH factions
is the conduct for which discipline should be applied.
Are you saying pat-a-cake? Give proof we played pat-a-cake!
Huh? From whom on earth did you receive this information?
-What are you doing without answering?- Confess quickly who that person was.
I can't answer.
What does it matter who the informer was?
I made a promise to the source to keep it secret.
Do you know you will be expelled from the party? Do you still want not to tell?
No. I will not.
Assemblyman Jin, don't make it too complicated.
How about resigning on your own?
You don't love our Gookmin Party much, do you?
Yes. I love it very much.
Sometimes, it looks like Balsam Institute; I feel right at home.  (A school in comedy show Gag Concert ).
Its environment is so pleasant that even a migratory bird flies in.
Assemblyman, your speaking is subject to discipline.
Assemblyman Jin, what is your true color?
What do you mean what? He is a leftist.
I am an onion (Yang Pa) that belongs to leftist (Joi Pa) and to rightist (Wu Pa). The more you peel it, newer ones show up.
Stop playing on words. Where is that kind of ideology in the world?
Yes.
If you want to hear my ideology, I am...
only a human. A human.
Assemblyman Kang!
A human, like truly being a human:
to believe one another;
to get along well;
not to stab someone else's back, please;
not to fight each other; not to make someone cry;
to join hands,
and to walk together...
that's my political idea.
Humanism
Aide Choi who had worked in BH sent a text to me just now.
That it is called  Humanism.
Will this be the answer to your question?
Excuse us during the meeting.
I came to watch here as a representative of the assemblymen who filed a complaint.
This Committee thinks that we have to take the action of
Assemblyman Jin's expulsion from the party right away.
-I agree.- I agree.
Assemblyman Jin has to be expelled from the party.
Assemblywoman Hong Chan Mi Schedule
Please check with whom you ate lunch and dinner for the last four years.
It shows there whom you represented.
Assemblywoman Hong, what have you been looking at continuously?
State your opinion of the disciplinary punishment quickly.
If I have to put it into words, probably a partner.
Who can always be contractually terminated if she fails to meet the profit goals.
The place we live in is not a law court but Yeouido.
Turning a spokeswoman who gained popularity with her looks alone into an idiot
is a piece of cake here.
Assemblywoman Hong?
I will tell my opinion of the disciplinary punishment.
I want to take the action of expulsion.
But the target of the action is not Assemblyman Jin.
It must be to me, Assemblywoman Hong, who told the truth to him.
Assemblywoman Hong? Assemblywoman Hong!
Assemblyman Jin only trusted the informer.
He had no intention to drive the party into a difficult position by circulating false information.
Therefore, there is no cause for discipline in Assemblyman Jin's action.
If you want to bring disciplinary action against me,
please form a Disciplinary Committee at your convenience.
Whether the information I supplied is true or not,
let's call that into question there, again, Secretary General Baek.
Assemblyman Park,
well... shall we proceed properly?
Avatar of Anti-BH, will you announce the result of today's meeting?
From this moment
I resign from the position of Spokesperson of the Gookmin Party.
Oh, No... Assemblywoman Hong...
Assemblywoman Hong!
Please. Assemblywoman Hong.
Assemblywoman Hong.
You are...
a fool.
Hello.
Assemblyman Jin!
I know. I know. So creepy!
It's okay. Okay.
Well done, Assemblyman.
I am sorry. I always make you edgy.
I will consider it as my fate from now on.
Meet Assemblywoman Hong soon.
Ah...Really. Where is Assemblywoman Hong?
How...
on earth...
Why on earth...
Long time no see. Have you been well?
You are studying well?
Yes. Aide Choi, you've been well, right?
Don't even mention it. You don't know how hard I have to work to raise a kid who is not supposed to be my fate.
I saw the news. He was almost expelled from the party.
He had a close call.
Assemblyman might have saved the country in his previous life.
It's because you are by his side.
When you two team up, no one can match you.
By the way, how is the bill you were making going?
I stopped making it. It looks like I don't yet have the ability to make it.
Try to send it to me although it's not finished. I will check it for you.
That's okay. If you read it, it will only hurt your eyes.
Next time, just call me with your cellphone.
I won't tell Assemblyman. What is this, like a criminal?
Yes.
Anyhow, Aide Choi, cheer up.
Okay. Thank you.
Aide Choi.
What are you doing?
It seems Assemblywoman Hong hasn't come to work today either.
Did you think she would come to work in the middle of a rumor about her resignation from the Assembly?
She doesn't answer the phone.
Will she really resign?
-Hello?-Kim Gyu Hwan?
Yes. Who is calling?
I am Section Chief Kim Sang Jin from Central Branch Prosecutor's Office.
Central Branch Prosecutor's Office?
What is the question you want to ask?
Yes.
There is a case that we are investigating secretly.
Secret investigation?
Do you know Hanmin Bank?
Hanmin Bank?
You received a shopping bag where there was money from the secretary of the bank president.
And you delivered it to Assemblyman Jin, didn't you?
If...I mean if...
If you have not received the money back from Assemblyman Jin,
there seems no chance to hand over to the prosecutor your loan irregularities we discovered.
6th day of the Parliamentary Inspection
Of course, Bank President, you will get a punishment, but
compared to the punishment for the illegal loan of $140 million, it will be a mere smidgen.
Bank President.
Have you received the money back from Assemblyman Jin?
Tell me.
Did you deliver the money to Assemblyman Jin or not?
Of course not.
I have not received it back.
Yes. You haven't so.
I understand well.
Secretary General.
Assemblyman Jin, he is in no exit situation now.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Viki
This inspection is the first and last parliamentary inspection for you.
I will beat you even because of Hyung Dal Soo.
Did you deliver the money to Assemblyman Jin or not?
I want to see you now.
What did you do with the designer watch you received from President Lee Taek Jo?
Kim Gyu Hwan said he delivered the money to Assemblyman Jin.
In this case, Secretary General Baek must be behind it.
People don't believe me.
We can have the motion for the arrest rejected.
I will appear in the prosecutor's office.