All characters, party names, and incidents appearing in this drama are fictitious creations.
What do you want to ask me?
Oh, there is a matter we are internally investigating.
Internal investigation?
You know Hanmin Bank?
Hanmin Bank...
You received a shopping bag with money in it from the bank president's secretary
and delivered it to Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil, right?
Tell me, did you deliver it to Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil or not?
6th Day of the Parliamentary Inspection
Topic...
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Viki
Episode 16
- Dong Cheon.- Yes.
You didn't leak this questionnaire to the Ministry of the Environment, right?
Absolutely not.
Oh, wait...
I guess even a busy person like you participates in the parliamentary inspection?
- Because I'm an assemblyman before being a secretary general.- Yeah...
How do you find your first parliamentary inspection? Doable?
Haven't you seen the mid-term announcement from that Parliamentary Inspection Monitor or something?
I made the candidate list for being the best assemblyman during the parliamentary inspection.
That deserves congratulations.
Shall I tell you one more thing I should be congratulated on?
Our party conduced a public opinion poll in Gyeongje City yesterday.
Secretary General, you got 35% and I, 58%.
Public opinion is like a lover just before jilting you. Don't count on it too much.
Didn't I tell you before
that I would never lose to you, if only for Hyung Dal Soo's sake?
I... will trample you.
There is a fact that you must be aware of, too.
That this inspection is the first and last parliamentary inspection for you.
Ah... just one look and I can tell
you are brewing some stinking sh*t. I better be careful.
Then.
2015 Parliamentary Inspection by Environment and Labor Committee
See this, okay? See this right now.
These are the numbers showing marine pollution
due to the industrial wastewater in Gyeongje City.
Look, in BOD from 5
to 16.4, 4.5 to 18.95 in COD. Take a look!
How many times is this!
Are you going to kill them all?
Are you crazy?!
What are you doing not managing these things!
Are you going to kill everyone in Gyeongje City?
Don't touch the glasses!
I'll give this to you, so take it home and study it.
Take a very careful look.
Frame it, put it up on the wall and study it everyday.
Play it, Secretary Park.
A group of experts, my staff and I
personally went down to Gyeongje River and tested the water quality.
Our Director of Korea Water Quality Management Company, take a look.
Take a good look. Is that a river now?
Huh?
Does that look like a river? What do you see?
Does it seem like sewage water?
Do you think that was pumped from a septic tank?
That is none other than the Gyeongje River. The current Gyeongje River where all fishes have died out!
Huh?! What are you going to do about it?
What are you going to do about all those fishes? You hurry and revive them now!
Moving on to the next one.
Do you see that, huh?
Are you tending a green tea field in the river, now?
Green tea field, green tea field? What are you going to do?
What kind of management work are you doing, seriously!
Stop fidgeting with your glasses. Why do you, why...
I even personally brought a sample.
Do you see this? I thought you might not believe it. I didn't put anything in it, I just ladled this out, personally.
Taste it.
Here, this too. You are getting plenty today.
Why are we not prepared?
Are you sticking it to me?
From tomorrow until the end of the parliamentary inspection, prepare all questionnaires like that. Go back to your seat.
Only my aides can do it. Not everyone is capable of that.
And do you admit this levee construction in Gyeongje City was done shoddily?
It wasn't shoddy work.
Not shoddy work? Are you sure?
You can get punished for perjury during a parliamentary inspection. Don't you know?
Seeing how you're touching your glasses, it is a lie. Fine.
I will read you all of the materials I prepared.
First... Ah, ah, ah. Chairwoman, please give me more time.
Enough already. Other assemblymen have to question too.
But I have to do everything I prepared. When I came with this much preparation...
If you do everything at the beginning, what does that make us?
Are you the only one doing the parliamentary inspection? When we've prepared as much as you?
Wow, between fellow party members, you're so petty.
Assemblyman Jin, I will give you my five minutes of additional question time. Use that.
Aigo, thank you, Assemblywoman Cheon! Aigo, thank you.
Did you see that? When even an opposition party assemblywoman is like that?
But please give it to me quickly, the 5 minutes?
Oh, it's working well.
Witness, from now on, to the questions I ask
answer in no uncertain terms. Understand?
Aren't you really going to submit the materials?
Don't you know this is against the Board of Audit and Inspection Act?
What? A meal?
That place's taste has changed, unlike the good old times. But I know...
Now, did I ask for a meal or materials? It's not like I'm going around hungry.
Send them to me by midnight. Hang up.
But what do they take an aide for?
Rain, rain. Eat the rain man.
Which one do I eat? Which one?
Of course you have to eat ssangpi. That's right!
Rain ssangpi.
That's right.
What are you doing?
I'm just taking a breather from making press materials.
I'm going to go to Aide Choi and tell on you.
It's fun, right? Right?
So much fun. You can't lose the money I've won.
I got it, I got it.
Just because they don't have to work on questionnaires, they are being too much.
Yes, why?
Environment and Labor CommitteeMeeting Room
Aide Seo, you did write a questionnaire to support companies with innovative environmental technologies, right?
Yes, but why?
But the Assemblyman does not have it.
What did you say?
When I worked so hard to make this questionnaire,
how can you take this out?
It does not fit the tone of the Assemblyman's legislative activities.
But that the government should give some support to companies that come up with cutting-edge new technologies...
Why does that not fit the Assemblyman's tone?
It does not fit.
Look here, Aide Choi. Even though you're the senior aide, this is exceeding your authority.
I'm in charge of questionnaires.
I was not going to bring this up, but
that questionnaire. Didn't a new technology company solicit you to write it?
What? What do you take me for...
Special interest legislation after getting lobbied for it, that is not the only evil thing.
Making special interest questionnaires like this one after getting solicitations, that practice also has to disappear!
Since the Assemblyman does not know about this, be careful not to repeat this sort of thing in the future.
What do you mean the Assemblyman doesn't know? Do you even know who that company owner is?
- Who?- President Lee Taek Jo of SOI.
Lee Taek Jo?
I mean that $5000 designer watch that almost cost Secretary Kim his job...
The person who gave that.
The Assemblyman returned that watch.
Who returned what now?
When the giver says he didn't get it back.
- What?- How could I stick it out without writing him that questionnaire?
Give it to me. I will return it to President Lee.
It's okay. The punk who received it must return it.
Parliamentary inspection is no small job.
Really...
Aide Choi, get me Assemblywoman Hong Chan Mi's address.
So I can try to see her.
Give me an honest answer to the question I'm about to ask.
Why are you like this again all of a sudden? What is it?
What did you do with that designer watch you had received from President Lee Taek Jo?
I got cash for it and bought bread for homeless people.
Don't joke around!
I'm not joking.
You are not joking?
If you don't believe me, ask Gyu Hwan.
He worked like a dog for several days because of that.
Didn't you say you exchange emails everyday?
Why don't you just confess?
From a trustworthy source,
we got very detailed information about your involvement in the delivery of the bribe before summoning you.
Because I was not convinced by Chief Secretary Lim's transcript alone,
I put temptation in the Assemblyman's way.
Pleading the fifth, may get you left holding the bag.
Fine. Why don't you just leave for today?
Take out money from the Assemblyman's salary
tomorrow and buy the exact same watch as the one President Lee gave.
Okay.
Forget it, why do that?
You stay quiet, Assemblyman.
Clearly you have violated the Political Funds Act.
But, just...
It's just, it's okay.
If I had that kind of money, I'd rather buy my Joo Hee some clothes.
Would it have been any better to do that?
Are you some sort of a benevolent thief who robs from the rich to give to the poor?
Why did you buy homeless people bread, why?
Then, should I have bought those people in poor health alcohol? Of course I should have bought them bread.
Assemblyman!
I am sorry. At that time, I did not know
that things would get this serious.
You just try this one more time. Then, I'm really going to cane you.
Me too.
7769? Call.
Who is it?
Oh, hello. I am Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil, the People's Spoilsport who always tries his best.
Is Assemblywoman Hong home, by any chance?
No, she is not.
Oh, really? Then, do you by any chance know where...
Hello?
Hello!
What the...
Does this run in her family? Why hang up so suddenly?
Seriously...
Yes, this is Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil, the People's Spoilsport who always tries his best.
Assemblyman.
Oh,
it's you, Gyu Hwan.
Yes.
Okay,
have you been well?
Where are you right now?
Hey, punk, while an elder is
greeting you, how can you abruptly ask for the whereabouts?
Punk, do you really want to get some beating?
I said where are you!
I am out to meet someone, happy, punk?
I would like to see you now.
Now?
- Gyu Hwan, let's meet at home.- Assemblyman!
I'll get home soon, so let's meet at home in a little bit. I've got to go.
Assemblywoman Hong!
How can an assemblywoman not come to the Assembly?
Because you are not even showing your face in the inspection hearings,
reporters and NGOs are up in arms about that, do you know that?
I am prepared to be reviled.
During my press conference to announce my resignation, I will return my salary
and apologize to the people.
Are you really going to resign?
Yes.
No, don't do that. Just join Indifferent-to-BH faction.
I will be good to you.
I guess you're mistaken because I opposed your expulsion.
But at that time, just out of embarrassment...
I did that because I didn't want to be embarrassed.
It's okay if you do not join Indifferent-to-BH faction.
But isn't quitting the Assembly too much?
When the people put you there.
The people
put me there?
Of course.
No.
I was just the newest model...
the brand-new latest product.
What, newest? A new model?
During the general election 4 years ago,
displayed in a window of the shop called the Gookmin Party,
the latest item with a glitzy design but of unproven quality!
That was Hong Chan Mi.
Why do you torment yourself like that?
What's wrong with you, when you are pretty and smart?
You talk well. You're diligent.
It's just your personality that is a bit...
When I was selected as a proportional representative and entered the Assembly with high expectations
I heard the words the staff and reporters were whispering behind my back.
What did they say?
Hong Chan Mi, a pretty face put on the general election.
Hong Chan Mi who picked up a windfall gold badge.
Sooner or later, she will fall out of fashion
and after 4 years, Hong Chan Mi will be flung into a pile of drastically discounted sale goods.
Yes, so that maybe why
I was so hung up on getting a nomination.
Because I didn't want to acknowledge what was said,
But...
But, truthfully, I,
Hong Chan Mi, I was really
the worst.
You still have a lot of time. The game is not over yet.
Muster up courage
and let's walk together.
Okay?
But, Assemblywoman Hong...
Frankly, I...
do not dislike you, Assemblyman Jin.
But when I see you, I feel very uncomfortable.
Am I that shabby?
Our Aide Choi didn't speak harshly, to that extent at least.
I want to quickly forget how cheap I was.
But when I see you, I cannot.
What?
Let us never see each other again.
Assemblywoman Hong!
Kim Gyu Hwan.
What are you going to do when you see Assemblyman Jin?
Whatever I do, what business of yours is it?
Just now,
I got a statement from the Hanmin Bank employee who delivered the bribe to you.
That is a lie. I do not know anything about this.
Mr. Kim Gyu Hwan, you are under arrest.
Secretary General, Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil is now like a cornered rat.
Secretary General?
Do Hyeon, is something bothering you?
Eh, punk.
How did I end up like this?
What are you talking about?
No, it's just... that thought came to me.
I understand that your pride is hurt because of Jin Sang Pil.
But don't worry about that rascal. I will cut him out.
No need for that.
Because it's coming to an end now.
You, do you want to be jailed?
That will be a huge obstacle if you want to be a civil servant.
Everything is bound to come out when cross-examination is conducted and the CCTV footage is analyzed.
Answer me. You received it, right?
Yes, I received it.
You delivered it to Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil, right?
Yes.
Yes, Prosecutor. Kim Gyu Hwan says he delivered the money to Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil.
But the Assemblyman must have returned the money. You're doing all this for nothing!
But the giver says he never got it back.
What?
Sang Pil, can't we just eat first?
But we have to eat together with Gyu Hwan when he comes.
The stew and all this will get cold.
Then we can re-heat them.
Your call is not answered and will be connected to the voicemail box...
Why isn't he answering?
Do you think maybe he got into a car accident on his way here?
Don't say such an unlucky thing. Three spits (and what you said will never come true).
Besides this questionnaire, is there any other favor you did for President Lee Taek Jo?
No.
Delete the questionnaire file right away.
Okay, I understand.
Who are you people?
What are you doing right now?
We are from the Central District Prosecutors' Office.
Search and Seizure Warrant
Please cooperate with our search and seizure.
You didn't even take off your shoes.
No...
It's okay if you do not join Indifferent-to-BH faction.
But isn't quitting the Assembly too much?
When the people put you there.
Last evening, the Seoul Central District Prosecutors' Office carried out a search and seizure
of Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil's residence and Assembly office.
- Bribe?- During the past Babel Tower City bankruptcy scandal, Assemblyman Jin
met Hanmin Bank President Kim Doo Shik who had sold his wife, a Mrs. Kim, a share of the related fund,
and by threatening him with service of a subpoena
to a parliamentary investigation, allegedly extorted $20,000 of illegal money from him.
Yes, it is true that I... met with Bank President Kim.
And
it is also true that I told him I would subpoena him to a parliamentary investigation.
However, it is nonsense that I acted with the intent to extort money.
The prosecution immediately arrested Assemblyman Jin's former secretary, a Mr. Kim, and questioned him on related facts.
That Mr. Kim allegedly stated that he had delivered the money
he got from Bank President Kim's side to Assemblyman Jin in the bank's underground garage.
It is true that the money was delivered to me.
But that very day, I met Bank President Kim and returned it right away.
Directly. Frankly, because my wife and daughter were on my mind
it is true that I wavered a bit.
If you want to punish me for that, I will gladly pay for it.
From Bank President Kim's Associate:It's true that the Assemblyman returned in a few hours
but Bank President said he demanded more money because it was less than the amount his wife lost.
When he refused, he left in a huff
and when he called for a special prosecution out of the blue, the president was shocked.
The prosecution plans to summon and question Assemblyman Jin after completing analysis of the seized evidence.
This is KBC News...
Wow, what a ridiculous bastard...
After having done that, in that press conference
"Honey... I'm sorry.
I... am not a person who can only look after my family, right?"
Didn't he say that?
The case feels somehow... a bit... strange.
Ehhh, really.
The prosecution opened up the case to the public too because they feel sure about it.
The only thing remaining for Jin Sang Pil now is to stand
in the mugshot line and get his ID photo taken.
You just watch. No doubt about it.
Secretary General, congratulations.
You can leave now.
Assemblyman Jin, are you going to respond to the prosecution's call?
This is the parliamentary inspection season. I don't have time to go there.
Are you saying you will be unresponsive? Please tell us!
Tell us.
Assemblyman.
I... cannot cooperate with the prosecutors who only believe
Bank President Kim's lies and paint me as a shameless criminal.
If they want to see my face, they will have to drag me there by force.
Just one more word.
Let us go in now. Enough already.
- I am sorry.- Assemblyman!
We will distribute additional press materials soon.
- By when...- We are sorry, sorry.
Assemblyman!
Ahew, but if a wife does not tell her husband, who does she talk to?
Isn't that so?
Don't worry and just take good care of Joo Hee.
You... are really okay, right?
Yes, that is what I said. Our Aide Choi said, with regard to assemblymen,
unless they are caught in the middle of committing a crime, the prosecution can do nothing.
Right, that is the kind of person I am right now.
So there is nothing to worry about. Right.
Okay, okay, bye.
This matter...
Secretary General Baek is behind this, no doubt.
Gyu Hwan... What is happening to him?
It seems he's still in the prosecutors' office.
Don't worry.
Since they have to release him within 48 hours of arrest, he will be out in no time.
Since I have given all my statements, I can leave now, right?
Let me just confirm one more thing.
- What is this?- We found this while recovering data from your laptop computer.
Tell me what that is.
Okay then.
Did somebody die?
Why are you all so crestfallen?
You can't possibly be thinking that I pocketed that money, can you?
subtitles ripped andsynced by riri13
There is no one here who thinks that..
Da Jeong, why are you crying?
It's just that... I'm so mad at these absurd things taking place.
I am sorry.
Don't cry. Why cry?
Your assemblyman won't even bat an eye at this.
Secretary Song, how are the netizens' responses?
Half on the Assemblyman's side, half on the prosecution's side.
Good, that is plenty.
- Aide Seo.- Yes.
Please work with Secretary Sim and Da Jeong to wrap up the parliamentary inspection that is soon coming to an end.
I got it.
Everyone else will work with me to wage a nationwide campaign asserting the Assemblyman's innocence.
But will it work with just us?
Just now, Jin Ji Mo leaders all over the nation called saying they would help out
together with the fan club members.
- Really?- Uh huh.
See? Even if the sky caves in on you, there will be a way out of it for us.
There are people who believe in JSP till the end!
So let us cheer up and fight for it. Aja!
Aja.
Eh, why are you guys like this, really? Louder! Aja aja!
- Aja, aja, aja!- Scorchhh...
What is scorchhh?
Assemblyman, the designer watch President Lee Taek Jo gave you ..;
just came up in an article.
Huh?
Jin Sang Pil Received a Designer Watch from a Businessman, Too!
Revealed that he liquidated it and used the cash...Prosecution will prove it was a kickback.
How did they find out about this?
- It's Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil!- I heard that bastard is a total thief?
I had thought we finally got ourselves a pretty decent assemblyman, but...
- This is why the have-nots should not get involved in politics.- Aish!
Hyung, just come.
Hurry and come.
We urge that Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil be detained and investigated!
Even though Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil is claiming
that he bought bread for homeless people with the designer watch he received,
he's lying through his teeth!
In a seized parliamentary inspection questionnaire, the prosecution
found a proposal to provide financial support to the company
run by the person who gave the designer watch!
A person like Jin Sang Pil...
Let's go quickly.
...should no longer waste the people's blood-like taxes!
Everyone! Please sign the petition for his arrest and interrogation!
A motion to approve Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil's arrest is before the Assembly that just concluded inspections of the affairs of state.
Today, the government submitted to the Assembly a motion to allow Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil's arrest so he can be
interrogated in custody over bribery charges.
The Assembly plans to open a plenary session soon to address the arrest motion.
Under current law, the Assembly in receipt of an arrest motion must propose an opening of a plenary session
and vote on the motion in that plenary session 24 hours after and within 72 hours from the report of the motion.
An arrest motion can be passed only if a majority of the assemblymen are present
and if a majority of that quorum agree.
It is not clear yet whether this motion will be passed.
In fact, there have been many incidents where an arrest motion failed to pass the Assembly.
You will only get more depressed if you keep watching this kind of news.
Go home early today.
People do not believe what I say.
It's not that they don't believe you,
but as much as they liked you, they've received a huge shock.
With time, they will change.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Viki
What will happen if the legislature passes his arrest motion?
Eight or nine out of ten, he will be taken into custody.
Custody?
If things go wrong, he may not even be able to leave jail until the end of his term.
No matter what, we have to block the arrest motion from being passed.
What do you think about writing to all Assembly members, pleading with them not to vote for his arrest?
No. If the Assemblyman makes such a move,
he may get criticized for using parliamentary immunity against being arrested during the session as a shield.
He was framed anyway, so what's wrong with using it as a shield?
Insist on the injustice of passing the arrest motion...
I know it is a huge favor to ask.
However, the only person who would help our Assemblyman right now is you, Assemblywoman Cheon.
I am sorry, but that will be difficult.
Assemblywoman...
As you know, my party's position is that we should curtail
or repeal parliamentary immunity.
Even though I feel sorry for Assemblyman Jin, I am afraid I can't.
I am here to ask your learned opinion about the motion to allow Jin Sang Pil's arrest.
The prosecution is too insolent.
They should not scoff at the legislature like this.
Consider the citizens' sentiment nowadays.
If it fails to pass, the whole of the legislature will be reviled.
Okay, I will send a message to Assemblyman Kang.
- Thank you.- But...
- isn't this the sort of matter handled by the floor leader?- Excuse me?
Secretary General Baek... Lately,
you seem to violate too often the lane change and speed regulations.
In the past, while observing the traffic rules,
you drove very cleanly too.
I guess lately I feel a bit pressed.
I will be more careful.
At any event, I guess this is the end of Jin Sang Pil too.
Dad!
Startled me... Hey, how did you get here?
Is it true that you will get nabbed?
Who told you? Who said that I would get nabbed?
Then, what is that that allowing arrest thing?
Where did you pick that up?
Hey, if you are a ninth grader, then you should ask a ninth-grader question.
Tell me quickly! What is that?
Your daddy is an assemblyman.
A person who does a very important job.
But when Daddy is working hard on an important job, the police ahjussi's cannot catch Dad, willy nilly.
They have to get all the other assemblymen's agreement.
Then, other assemblymen must oppose it for you.
That's right.
But, your Daddy is the most popular one among the assemblymen.
So in terms of celebs, I am on the same level as Ahjussi Song Hae.
So everyone is on your Daddy's side.
You're telling me the truth, right?
Truthfully. Daddy will never get nabbed.
Yes.
Aide-nim.
Kim Gyu Hwan?
You've had a really hard time, haven't you?
I am sorry.
Isn't there a way for me to help the Assemblyman?
For now, laying low is helping him.
Staying near the Assemblyman may
only raise the prosecution's suspicion needlessly.
It's all my fault.
Don't blame yourself too much.
Even though you may have been responsible for the luxury watch,
being momentarily tempted by the money
received from the Hanmin Bank president was the Assemblyman's fault.
At the time...
I forced the Assemblyman to accept the money against his will
when he told me to return it immediately.
What?
So if the Assemblyman actually accepted it,
I was intending to give a tip to
Chief Secretary Im Gyu Tae.
What do you mean Im Gyu Tae?
Secretary General Baek's Chief Secretary?
Yes.
What are you saying?
What brings you here?
Is it true that
you incited Secretary Kim Gyu Hwan to feed you information about Assemblyman Jin's corruption?
If it's true, is that a problem?
Leave.
You piece of trash!
What?
What is happening?
Secretary General Baek.
So you've met Gyu Hwan, together with Secretary Lim?
I only met him because he said he had information to give.
The fact is he changed his mind and just left.
Like hell!
The real fact is
you have become a scumbag politician
who goes around digging up other people's dirt.
Yes.
That's what has happened to me now.
And I
am willing to sink a lot lower than this toward the bottom
if it is expedient.
Understand?
Get ready to provide food and supplies to your Assemblyman when he is behind bars.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Viki
What do you mean it's difficult?
Why are you saying it's difficult to consent to the arrest motion?
We're not the government's minions.
We don't have to process it without hesitation
just because they send us a motion.
But we're talking about Jin Sang Pil here.
Yes. Even though Jin Sang Pil has been behaving inappropriately all this time,
he is a fellow assemblyman, eating at the same table.
Strangling him with our own hands... that's a bit... you know.
Just be honest. Something's bothering you, right?
It's not me. It's Assemblymen Choi and Nam.
It seems President Lee Taek Jo fed them with something.
Stupid fools...
They say Lee Taek Jo's wife imports watches.
Wow... if it seems for their own benefit,
no questions asked, they just drop off these watches to those assemblymen.
I'm guessing it might be dozens who got them.
Did you get one too?
Jeez. What the heck do you see me as? Gracious!
I...!
I returned it the day before yesterday.
With the vote coming up, it's developed into a headache.
Why suffer a headache over it?
Just let the assemblymen who approve it vote to approve it, and the ones who oppose it vote to oppose it.
Just let them vote however they want.
The Anti-BH faction decided to vote autonomously and not in a bloc today?
Yes. I positively heard Assemblyman Kang Sang Ho's aide say that.
But why this... don't you feel it's a bit odd?
Sorry, I'm late.
Assemblyman.
Yes?
Why?
Whom am I secretly meeting?
Oh Sae Chang. The Korean Democratic Party Chair.
Am I going to join that party now?
Then I won't be Jin Sang Pil but will become Jin Sang Bird.
When it comes to birds, let us raise just one bird, Jo Woong Bird.
Oh Sae Chang is a reasonable person.
If you explain all the circumstances leading up to this and ask for his cooperation,
there is a possibility that the Korean Democratic Party also will decide to vote autonomously like the Anti-BH faction.
Autonomously?
If that happens, there's a good chance the motion will be voted down.
Voted down?
You're saying it can be defeated.
Yes. I'm going to contact him right now.
I have a friend among Party Chair Oh Sae Chang's aides.
Wait a moment, Aide Choi.
Yes?
I will just do it.
I will appear before the prosecutor.
Assemblyman, are you in your right mind?
My mind is clear, of course.
After agonizing over it all night, that's the decision which emerged.
You understand that way.
I will go see Joo Hee and Joo Hee's mom and come back.
Meanwhile, get ready for my appearance at the prosecutor's office.
Why on earth are you doing this? I'm saying that the motion to allow you to be arrested can be defeated.
Defeating it does not mean I won't ever be arrested..
It's only until the end of the legislative session that I have immunity.
Until then, somehow, conditions favorable to you can be created.
Don't you know the regular session will end when the first snow falls?
Until the first snowfall, you want me to hear people saying "son-of-bi*ch"?
What?
-I can't do that, seriously. So---Assemblyman.
This time, please let's do what I decide. Without "but"...
No!
Are you out of your mind? Don't you know what'll happen if you appear at the prosecutor's office now?
The prosecutor already applied to a judge for an arrest warrant.
The court still has to review it and sign off on it.
But, as of now, chances of your arrest warrant getting denied
are extremely slim.
See? You are to eat bean rice, bean rice (euphemism for going to jail)!
If that happens, then it can't be helped.
What, you punk?
Secretary-nim.
Why are you like this, Hyung?
Then it can't be helped?
How can you say such a thing to Ae Ri and me?
Are you saying we should just watch
you wearing prison uniform and chowing down bean rice, punk?!
Assemblyman,for Kyung Ah and Joo Hee's sakes, too, you shouldn't be doing this.
I have already made up my mind.
Just because you're doing this, which citizen
would understand how you feel?
Only you will just end up being a fool.
All the difficulties you've gone through so far...
They were all for nothing and it will be the end for you!
Why is that the end? It is not the end.
What did you say?
The real end for me is that I hide behind
that parliamentary immunity or whatever. So the people
believing that this People's Spoilsport Jing Sang Pil is a real son-of-a-bi*ch.
So they will believe that the Indifferent-to-BH thing
we did was all just putting on a show.
That would be the real end.
Let's just say that I somehow got arrested. That I am all locked up.
Then, Aide Choi, and you, Hyung, and Secretary Oh, and our secretaries...
will you just play around? Of course not.
You will work even harder. To get me out.
To prove my innocence.
So how can that be the end? When I have you people.
Hey...
Aide Choi.
Yes?
You said you didn't want to make me
into an assemblyman who shines just for a moment and then disappears.
Yes.
Then let me go.
I'm sorry.
Assemblywoman, what brings you into the office today?
I wanted to do something before I resigned.
What's that?
The motion to arrest Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil.
Pro-BH and Anti-BH must be playing pat-a-cake together.
At least I should vote against it, as a neighbor.
How can you change your position just before the vote?
You scared me.
Who's changing his position?
The arrest motion. I heard you were going to vote yes.
So what do you mean, an autonomous vote?
I never said such a thing.
And the autonomous vote,
isn't that a good thing?
Let's not tire ourselves out like this. Please unify Anti-BH faction's votes.
Assemblyman Jo.
Democracy itself is exhausting.
Are you not going to do democracy just because it's exhausting?!
Ha!
Where...
Yes.
Voluntarily go to the prosecutor?
Who? Jin Sang Pil?
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil decides to voluntarily go to the prosecutor.
Jin's side insists on his innocence and emphasizes that he will be openly interrogated by the prosecutor regardless of the Assembly's decision on his arrest motion...
Voluntarily go to the prosecutor.
What is this?
Please take good care of them.
I have great faith in you. Please help Aide Choi out a lot.
Assemblyman, please don't worry about this office.
Yes.
Secretary Sim, spend less time drinking, singing, and dancing.
Yes, I will.
You've lost a lot of weight.
For Miss Song, I have a special gift.
What is this?
Gyu Hwan's phone number.
Assemblyman, don't go.
Do well.
Da Jeong, do well too.
Don't be too disappointed with the National Assembly. Understand?
Yes.
Secretary Oh, what's with you?
Huh?
That’s what I’m saying.
Why am I like this?
Why is everyone's mood like this, really?
Is Assemblyman Jin going somewhere to die?
Assemblyman Jin is obnoxious, so even the jail won't accept him.
So he'll come back in one piece.
Isn't that so?
I don't think so.
Assemblywoman Hong.
From the looks of everyone's moods, you're really voluntarily going to the prosecutor.
Yes, well, there's that.
Now that you're entering a lion's den, who's your guard?
Is it So-and-So Choi who's the star of the tabloid rumor?
We're a combo, you know.
What can an aide do with the prosecutor outside the Assembly?
I'll introduce a good lawyer to you.
Lawyer?
Who?
Me, Hong Chan Mi.
What?
Why are you suddenly becoming my lawyer?
I can't give you any money. I don't have any.
Gosh.
I got so frustrated watching you two fools that I couldn't help it.
Fools?
The two of us?
Assemblyman Jin.
Now I am a discontinued item with only a few months left of her term.
But if it's okay with you, Assemblyman, I will work with you for my remaining months.
With me?
I will join the Indifferent-to-BH faction.
Assemblywoman Hong.
Please take care of me.
But!
Choi In Kyung is barred within my 2-meter radius.
Also prohibited from eating together or seeing me alone.
No...
Aide Choi, what do I do now? This is trouble.
I'll make one for you.
I'll make you a really great wrap.
Kimchi, kimchi.
Garlic too.
And... I should put the soybean paste.
Of course.
- Looks delicious.- I don't do this for Mom.
Jealous, aren't you?
Cheers!
Ah.
Ah, seriously.
Delicious!
Delicious.
You get a glass.
Yeah?
You, too. Joo Hee. Have a drink.
It's really been a long time.
Cheers. Say something.
Our family will stay together forever!
Okay. Forever!
This is good. Why aren't you eating? Have a sip.
We trust Assemblyman Jin!
Cheer up, Assemblyman!
He's coming!
He's here!
Jin Sang Pil! Jin Sang Pil!
From this point on, don't answer the reporters' questions.
Just a word about how you feel.
- Okay.- Jin Sang Pil! Jin Sang Pil!
Jin Sang Pil! Jin Sang Pil!
Let's go.
- Okay.- Jin Sang Pil! Jin Sang Pil!
Jin Sang Pil! Jin Sang Pil!
What made you decide to come voluntarily?
Tell us how you feel about getting investigated.
Are you still denying all charges?
Yes. I'm innocent.
What made you make a voluntary appearance?
What do you mean, by innocence?
Are you prepared to be detained?
- Tell us. - Say something.
Assemblyman Jin, please tell us what made you make an appearance.
Assemblyman!
- Please give us another word.- Assemblyman!
Please tell us why you're voluntarily going to the prosecutor.
Please give us another word.
Assemblyman!
You're the best.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Viki