All characters, party names, and incidents appearing in this drama are fictitious creations.
Episode 18
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Viki
Sang Pil.
Assemblyman.
You suffered a lot.
I congratulate you on your release.
Thank you.
All of you really, really suffered a lot.
Congratulations.
National Assembly
Thank you. Now, let's go get them.
What?
Secretary General Baek.
Let's go.
Delete what's in here.
Hurry.
Hey, won't you get rid of it quickly?
- Hey, USB!- Okay.
Up there. That's right. Hurry up and put the hard disk.
-Quickly get it wiped clean. Hurry.-Yes, I understand.
Hurry! Hurry!
Hello?
What did you say?
Secretary General, they say that the investigators have arrived.
Please block it. If I get arrested, I'll go to jail immediately.
You made the situation like this and...
what is it that you want me to do?
Secretary General.
I have no way to do that immediately.
- Secretary General.- Secretary General, we'll be entering.
Since you can think on your feet, you'll know how to handle it.
Secretary General...
What are you guys doing right now?
I'm sorry, Secretary General. We are from the Prosecutors' Office and we ask for your cooperation.
-Im Gyu Tae.-Yes?
Your arrest warrant. We are arresting you on charges of defamation and destruction of evidence.
Let's go.
Secretary General.
Why do you want to go in there? I told you that the police will take care of it.
Since Secretary General Baek sent me to prison, I ought to thank him.
What is this? Where did everybody go? They are not even outside.
What did I tell you. There is no way they'll be here.
They ran because they got scared.
-What is the motive for your crime?-Were you ordered by Secretary General Baek?
Secretary Im, did all this happen because of Secretary General Baek's order?
The Secretary General has nothing to do with this matter.
With a sincere thought that a demagogue like Assemblyman Jin must be eliminated,
I did everything on my own.
All of you move. Move.
Is it really true that you did everything on your own?
The Secretary General has nothing to do with this matter.
With a sincere thought that a demagogue like Assemblyman Jin must be eliminated,
I did everything on my own. ( Baek Do Hyeon's Chief Secretary insists he committed crime alone)
Yeah, right. Sincere thought, my ass.
Looks like they'll be looking into who is behind the matter.
This is KBC news.
Assemblyman Park, he is doing that hoping that the Secretary General will save him.
It's because the only person he can trust is Secretary General Baek.
But... if the feather won't budge like that,
what's going to happen to the main part of the body?
Since the feathers have been plucked, there'd be countless people who would cook it up and eat it.
What?
We can just wait with a spoon ready.
Reporters, take a look at the haetae statue.
Haetae is an imaginary creature who's supposed to crush evil and create good.
What would be the reason they have this statue in front of the Assembly?
Political schemes such as the one that happened recently must be eradicated.
Are you saying you also think there's someone behind this incident?
Every citizen knows already,
who the mastermind is.
If the investigating authority feigns ignorance,
they'll have to face huge resistance from the citizens.
I demand an investigation against Gookmin Party's Secretary General Baek Do Hyeon.
Im Gyu Tae is just a mere minion.
At least this time we mustn't make the mistake in which
we just pluck a feather and let the body survive.
The investigating authorities must summon Secretary General Baek Do Hyeon immediately...
and reveal the truth behind the scheme with absolute clarity.
How can something like this happen?
I have nothing to do with it.
You can't just say you have nothing to do with it. You have to take responsibility!
What do you mean, responsibility?
Our party is about to take a hit because of you.
Assemblywoman Park.
We have no more to say.
Make a statement regarding this incident ASAP,
and decide what you're going to do.
What do you mean, decide? What are you talking about?!
How dare you? Do not interrupt when the party leader's speaking!
Let me be clear. I can't leave you with the task of choosing nominations in this circumstance.
Party Leader.
Please leave.
Yoon Jeong Soo, that person is leader of the party in name only but now, he acts like a real leader.
I made a puppet into the party leader and...
He thinks you have no more strings to pull.
So meet up with VIP and get Chief Secretary out of jail ASAP.
You have to save yourself too.
Because you are an astute politician, you'd better get your act together somehow.
I trust you know what to do.
What's the matter?
Do Hyeon.
Here comes the stew.
Wow, it looks good!
Let me know if you need more. I can make it fast.
How come there's just tofu? How many tofu dishes are there?
They taste good. You're being fussy for nothing.
- You eat 'em all, then.- Yeah.
Aigoo, really.
Now that we're all gathered together, shall we make a toast?
Indifferent-to-BH, fighting!
Fighting!
But Assemblywoman Hong, are you really going to keep sitting there?
Did you forget the conditions for me joining Indifferent-to-BH faction?
Eating at the same table with Choi 00 is prohibited.
Just come over here. Conditions, my butt. What are you doing?
- Sit here.- What are you doing?
It's weird, you sitting here alone.
- Assemblyman Jin.- Just come. Come!
Sit next to Aide Choi. Hurry!
Seriously.
From what I heard,
you were a perfect couple.
Don't even bring it up. Remember the old movie we watched?
Starsky and Hutch. They were even better.
Nah. They were men.
Thelma and Louise.
Are we Chinese restaurant ad stickers? Stop sticking it everywhere.
I don't want to be considered at the same level as her.
Ah, bad temper.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Viki
What are you trying to do?
I'm giving you my heart.
See. She says it's her heart.
Miss So Min, have you tried to get in touch with Gyu Hwan?
Pardon? That's...
You know his number?
Yeah.
I want to call him.
She called him several times, but he doesn't answer, she says.
Look here, everyone.
We can't not sing on a great day like this, right?
That's enough. Whose clamorous noise do we have to hear again?
Stop acting like a fool and sit down already.
I changed my repertory. You're too much.
Seriously.
What doesn't someone else sing? Miss So Min.
Huh? Me?
Or Da Jeong?
Get out there, together.
Yeah, do it!
Me, me, too.
♫  Touch my body Body ♫
♫  Touch my body♫
♫  I know you want it. Come up to me.♫
♫  I have wine and sweet chocolate chocolate ready
♫  A bit tender and just for you a little warmed up  ♫
♫  My face is turning crimson in the reflection in your eyes ♫
♫  Take the wheel. Right, two hands up toward the sky ♫
♫ Yeh baby dancing with me you're my star♫
♫ Touch my body let's do it a little faster♫
♫ Oh everybody higher than the blue sky. ♫
♫ Now the rhythm is great. You and I under the hot sun. ♫
♫  My body body Touch me body ♫
♫ Baby so good now I feel it's paradise. ♫
♫  Baby so nice just by ourselves summer night
♫ Bit by bit, one step, two step. You and I in the moonlight. ♫
♫  My body body Touch my body♫
♫  Touch my body Body ♫
♫ Touch my body Body ♫
I have to see VIP and tell him I have nothing to do with this incident.
Secretary General Baek, let's not become any more disgraced.
What did you say?
If you really are VIP's close aide, act like one,
don't be a burden and deal with it yourself.
Because you are an astute politician, you'd better get your act together somehow. I trust you know what to do.
-Have you heard the Supreme Council will be held?-Yes.
They're trying to push through Secretary General Baek's dismissal.
Seeing the timid Party Leader Yoon Jeong Soo's attempt at a quick procedure and conclusion, there must be mediation between BH and him.
Secretary General Baek is now in the Nakdong River...
A duck egg. ( A saying which means someone has been totally isolated.)
What is this? Why are you suddenly well paired again?
What are you doing by standing over there? Sit here.
Are you serious?
You are getting muscles on your ugly legs. Sit quickly.
Thank you.
By the way, Secretary General Baek seems to be doing some tricks like political engineering.
He won't docilely resign.
Before, when you were about to become Secretary General, he demanded secession of the President from the party.
There is one thing that bothers me about him.
What is it?
As one of those closest to VIP and having the most actual influence in the ruling party,
the intelligence that Secretary General Baek has!
The intelligence?
The statement that urges Baek Do Hyeon's resignation?
You have to funnel the wind before the Supreme Council meeting is held.
That's how that worthless person, Yoon Jeong Soo, will get his strength.
I got it.
The eel-like punk!
Let me see...
Yes.
What's the occasion for this visit to my office, Secretary General?
I came to deliver something to Assemblyman Kang.
To me? What is it?
Oh... What...
What is it?
Assemblyman Kang Sang Ho.
My name is listed here?
Do you remember President Lee Taek Jo who gave a luxury watch
to Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil and raised a scandal?
Lee... Lee Taek Jo?
This is a list of the Anti-BH assemblymen who received those luxury watches.
Oh, yes.
Deliver this to Assemblyman Park.
Until the Supreme Council meeting ends, do not take any action but stay still.
Gookmin Party
So, did you decide?
-Yes.-You thought well.
Then, before the Supreme Council meeting opens, have the press conference to announce your resignation.
My decision is not to do that.
Party Leader, I am aware that you have a rather intimate relationship with Chairman Kim of Yoongwang Company.
What is the meaning of your saying that?
Earlier, I know that you and Chairman Kim went together to Central America for economic issues.
At that time, the amount of travel expenses you received was...
Secretary General Baek.
This is but one of the many pieces of information that I have.
If you are interested in other information that I have, then dismiss me.
Today, the Supreme Council should adopt an official position
that I had nothing to do with Im Gyu Tae's case.
Then...
Yes, Chairman?
Connect to the BH quickly.
Are you saying you won't dismiss Secretary General Baek?
Chairman, why are you doing this all of sudden?
For now, I understand. I'll call you back.
Assemblyman's prediction was correct.
Party Leader Yoon changed his position.
I just said that. This prediction came from Aide Choi's brain.
I see. The VIP praised her from time to time but
I see that you were worthy of the praise.
Anyway, because of this one loach (bottom-dwelling scavenger fish), whether it's the party or the BH,
face isn't the only thing lost.
Secretary.
Please, relay this to the VIP.
What is this?
It's a loach recipe that the Indifferent-to-BH faction made.
Recipe.
Gookmin Party
2015 Gookmin Party's 57th Supreme Council Meeting
On the Agenda: Secretary General Baek Do Hyun's dismissal
Party Leader Yoon's not here yet.
He must have a lot to think about.
Do you really think you can hold out?
Punk, I guess he has something he can count on.
Hello, Assemblyman Jo Woong Gyu.
It's been a long time.
You're suffering a lot, Secretary General Baek.
Not at all.
What's the occasion? The main body and Avatar rarely come together.
Are you here to watch?
I came to warn you.
This is a fight between you and the leadership.
Don't threaten us or try to get us involved. You're not the only one with classified info.
I'll keep that in mind.
I wish you luck.
Thank you.
Do as Assemblyman Jin says. That's the right thing to do for the party.
Party Leader, they're just jumping to conclusions by themselves.
Don't let them deceive you.
Jumping to conclusions?
We're aware of both of your involvement in Party Leader Yoon's corruption.
- What?- Did the Blue House really give such information to you?
Yes.
That's a lie. There's no way the Blue House could've done such a thing.
Then shall we head straight to the press conference and expose the truth?
I have nothing to hide. Do whatever you need to do.
I understand.
Choi In Kyung, let's go.
You two ladies. What's so urgent? Wait there for a bit.
Party Leader.
Don't you understand why
I brought this here instead of making this public right away?
Reason? Are you saying you did this for me or what?
Why would I do that for you? I don't even like you that much.
I did it because I don't want to.
You don't want to do what?
I want to be a politician,
not someone who exposes things.
What... expose?
Yes. What I've seen the most ever since I came to the Assembly...
subtitles ripped by riri13
What I saw happening so often that I'm sick and tired... were exposés.
Someone did something to someone, someone swallowed up how much from someone...
Exposing everything and taking everything off and just...
Stabbing someone's back... and most of them turn out to be rumors...
and fabrications and... They're all like that.
So?
I've done that a few times myself,
but it's not very good for mental health, and it seems quite addictive, too.
But the bigger problem is that the citizens are really sick and tired of it.
They're really disgusted.
Party Leader. Please do as I say this time.
Let's not commit fraud against the citizens anymore, please?
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Viki
What a nice sight.
I'm not feeling good about this. Do you think the Indifferent-to-BH is cooking up something?
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
From now on, I will open 2015
Gookmin Party's 57th Supreme Council Meeting.
From three members of the supreme committee, a petition for
Secretary General Baek Do Hyeon's dismissal was submitted.
I'll listen to what Secretary General Baek has to say first.
First,
for worrying the party and the citizens due to my chief secretary's offense,
I feel deeply sorry.
But since I have nothing to do with Chief Secretary Im Gyu Tae's crime,
I believe I have no reason to be dismissed.
He sure has a thick face.
If I turn out to have committed even the slightest wrongdoing,
I'm willing to accept any kind of appropriate legal consequences.
But until then, I would like diligently to fulfill my duty as the Secretary General.
I request that the Honorable Party Leader Yoon Jeong Soo
as well as the supreme councilmen make a wise decision. Thank you.
We'll make the final decision.
We will not accept the petition for Secretary General Baek's dismissal.
How despicable.
We will present an urgent matter.
Urgent matter?
Since I became the chairman of the ruling party,
it has been more than 1 year.
During that time, I don't think I fulfilled my promise made to the people and party members
to carry out public office innovation and reform.
Besides that, events up to the case of Secretary General's Chief Secretary damaging an assemblyman, etc.
have mired the party in confusion and chaos.
Since I fully realize the heavy responsibility borne by a party leader,
I will resign
the position of party leader.
What? Resignation?
I, also, will do the same as the Chairwoman of the Party.
I will resign too.
What on earth are you doing now? Resignation?
Gookmin Party Regulations Article 172:
If more than a half of the supreme committee resign,
the organization of the party leaders shall be dissolved automatically. Don't you know that?
Wow, he doesn't know it yet, because he landed in the Gookmin party only a few days ago.
Then, what is Secretary General Baek going to do?
The leadership of the party is dissolved so there will be no Secretary General.
It will be an auto-resignation.
Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil.
Yes. President.
I watched how one cooks the loach.
By the way, isn't it too extreme?
Yes. It is extreme but...
I will read what my aide wrote for a moment.
If we are to regain the citizen's confidence in government and the party and
if there is to be stable leadership during the latter half of my term
it would be best for incompetent party leaders and Baek Do Hyeon to resign. That is my opinion.
What are your thoughts?
My thought? Yes. My thought is important too.
My thought is that catching only one loach will be not enough.
After taking out all the water and catching the rest, then we have to refill the water.
Assemblyman! Manners, be polite.
Yes. I think we have to fill the water again.
Yes. I understand. If you rely on us,
we will try to do it.
Yes. Goodbye, President.
Aide Choi.
You, too.
Citizens.
We are sorry.
Following the resignation of the Gookmin Party leadership,
the party will temporarily be run by an Ad-Hoc Committee.
Floor Leader Choe Joon Goo, who is acting head of the Gookmin Party,
revealed at a press briefing
that a convention to elect the party's leadership will be held
either at the end of the regular legislative session in December
or in January next year.
... is something especially different. Our Indifferent-to-BH's position is firm.
Meanwhile, Assemblyman Baek Do Hyeon, who is suspected of suborning perjury by the President of Hanmin International Bank,
appeared behind closed doors to be examined by the prosecutor
and then returned home today.
It is known that Assemblyman Baek flatly denies the allegations against him, but
the prosecution intends to carry out an intensive investigation
by summoning him again to confront Mr. Im.
Once called the Seo Dae Han Administration's Crown Prince
and classified as a next-term candidate for President,
Assemblyman Baek is on the brink of becoming a political pariah.
Assemblyman.
You didn't go to bed?
Yes. I have something to do.
Oh.
You really are trying to make something?
Yes.
But what kind of bill?
Just... I want to make a law
for the ordinary dads of this world.
Huh?
But since I don't know what to do, it is possible I might not make it.
I think I still won't be able to draft it.
Assemblyman Jin.
Gyu Hwan didn't show up now.
But why?
I don't know what.
He didn't enroll this month.
Actually when you were in jail, Aide Choi met with him.
-Aide Choie did?  - Yes.
She asked him to come back to your office,
but he refused.
But why?
Even when he hears the "po" in "politics"
he told her it makes him sick.
What she said is it seems he feels remorse because you were arrested.
He has become more cynical.
Honestly, I'm concerned.
Okay. I understand.
Thank you for telling me.
But... Aide Choi said you would worry
so I was absolutely never to tell you.
If you were to say I told you,
But why is everyone more afraid of her than me?
Just the sound of her bawling you out terrifies you.
You're a hopeless wuss. A wuss! What is so scary...
Oh.
Aide Choi.
Assemblyman, is is true the money you received while in prison was given to the prisoneers?
Ah, that money?
Yes, I... that...
I bought and shared tasty side dishes too with those around me...
That money would have paid the car rent expense for a month.
Did you think we were in a position to be helping others?
That's true. I know, but I felt sorry that I was being released from prison first...
I'm sorry. I forgot that.
Secretary Song, what are you doing here?
What? Ah I was... asking for advice about life.
Assemblyman. Thank you for the wise advice.
Yeah. Okay.
Ask anytime. About living life.
Yes.
What are you saying?
Aigo. Life...
She's still an adolescent.  What now?
While checking the documents seized by the prosecutor
I found a file.
What is this?
It's the bill which Secretary Kim drafted.
A Proposed Bill re: A Second Chance
Is this everything?
Yes.
A Second Chance?
So random. What the heck does "Second Chance" mean?
I doo have never heard of this before.
Hey Song. Did you do an internet search?
Yes. I tired, but there isn't anything much.
It's just some scribbling.
Because Secretary Kim drafted it
could if have something to do with his father?
I knew it! I knew it!
That's surprising.
When Hyung Dal Soo got divorced he lived life like a widower.
So isn't the bill made for people who live alone and those who remarry?
What does the law have to do with that?
You hook up with someone and live together.
What are you up to?
Speaking of which, we also should have a comeback together.
Have I even had a first?
Jeez. Stop making a fool of yourself in front of the staff.
This feeling is a first for me too.
There's something I figured out.
Is there?
I knew you are a computer, really.
Secretary Kim. He wasnted to make a law about a consolation prize for losers.
Consolation prize?
Just... I want to draft a bill for the ordinary dads of this world.
But then, how did you know what it is by looking at the title?
A long time ago there was someone similar who drafted a bill like this.
A long time ago?
Yes.
Chief Secretary Im... Has it been really hard?
It's unfortunate you are in detention.
I will do my best to prevent somehow your serving a prison sentence.
Will you go so far as a suspended sentence?
Do it as quickly as possible.
It would be great if it was a minimum sentence.
I will claim substantial compensation after I get out.
- Chief Secretary Im.  - Don't forget
your political life
depends on this.
Let's make a consolation prize law.
Consolation prize law?
Think about it. You have multiple competitions in this world and
competition by necessity has winners and losers.
When there is only a reward for the winner without any consideration for the loser,
how far can the world go?
How do you intend to show consideration for the losers?
By giving a belief that life is not over after you have lost once.
How will that be done?
By giving an opportunity to try again.
A Second Chance.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Viki
Eight years ago. Do you remember the Second Chance Bill,
which was not submitted to the Assembly because the party's policy panel opposed it?
That was your original resolution.
I am looking forward to seeing you admit your past mistakes and making a fresh start.
Secretary Lee.
Please make a U-turn at the next light.
Yes, Assemblyman.
Yes.
Hankook University Professor Park Young Sam and Attorney Yoon Sun Hae seem to be strong candidates to chair the Emergency Response Commission (ERC).
Really?
They would be okay.
How did they decide to make up the Emergency Response Commission (ERC)?
One from each faction and the rest will be filled by public figures from outside.
One per faction, does that include the Indifferent-to-BH faction?
Just get ready to print new business cards for Assemblyman Jin.
Assemblyman.
Aren't you happy? An Emergency Response Commission member is at the same level as a supreme councilman.
Can't you just do it, Assemblywoman Hong?
But I am in the National Election Commission's clutches over a political contribution issue.
People will cuss me out, saying I haven't come to my senses yet.
I guess you're like this because you feel uncomfortable about factions divvying up the positions.
But this is an emergency. You have to be there to counterbalance the Pro- and Anti-BH
and to help out the chairperson coming from outside.
I really don't feel like it. The very sound of it is unattractive, Bidet... (Korean pronunciation sounds like toilet seat or obese)
If you won't do this either, I will really quit this office.
Why do you bring up this unnecessary topic again.
I really mean it.
Why are you like this again, scaring me...
If you're scared, be an ERC member!
Ah, I got it. I will do it.
Really?
Ah, yeah...
You should have done this earlier.
Assemblyman Jin.
Yes?
As the old saying goes, never hang on to a daughter-in-law or an aide who wants to leave.
Should I introduce you to a very capable aide?
Oh, well, can you do that for me? Even better
if the person doesn't engage in drunk drivel and is amiable.
That kind of person is a dime a dozen in the Assembly Hall. The age group?
The younger, the better... I guess.
If you are going to buy a skirt anyway, go for the vermillion one (prettier, better one). Trends cannot be ignored in politics.
A guy would be better. I can go to the bathhouse with him and we can scrub each other's backs.
Guy? Bathhouse...
Do it.
What? You want me to step down from the Strategy and Finance Committee chair position?
But, why are you saying this out of the blue?
Just quit if I tell you to quit.
But, this old man, has he gone senile?
Assemblyman Park, do you know how meaty that position is?
Do you know how much I wined and dined assemblymen to occupy that seat?
Assemblyman Kang.
You will have to take our seat on the ERC.
Ah, well, ERC...
Emergency Response Commission member? Me?!
It's about time that you take a party position.
Do well.
Oh...
Assemblyman Park, thank you very much! I will work hard!
Yes, work hard.
Yes, yes, yes.
A glory to my family.
Assemblyman Park.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Viki
Go to the investigating authorities and promptly admit the charges.
Hiding behind an aide is not something an old hand should do.
I intend to get Mr. Im Gyu Tae out as soon as possible.
Do you have that kind of power still remaining in your hands?
I will have to regain it.
Because one defeat does not mean no second chance.
It is getting late.
Why don't you go back now?
Actually, I
have a very dangerous item in my hands.
But it is also an item
you would covet a lot if you saw it.
What is that?
Presidential election funds that were not reported to the National Election Commission.
If you help me with my comeback, I will gladly give it to you.
Oppa, it's me, Joo Hee. Have you been well?
Yes, go on.
Aigo, really, so gruff. When you answered only after one million calls.
Sorry. I've been a bit busy. What's up?
Oppa, what are you doing tomorrow? If you have nothing to do, would you like to go to a PC room with me?
Oppa, I am dying of boredom nowadays.
But I have so much to do lately. I don't have time to play with you.
Ah, really. I wouldn't ask you for this kind of favor if only my dad lived with me.
- Joo Hee- Huh?
I'm sorry but don't call me in the future.
Don't text me either.
Um, I got it.
Good-bye.
Oppa!
Really just one game, okay?
Okay. Just one game. Let's go!
You could be a pro gamer. How can you move your hands so fast?
It's because I did martial arts, why?
Ah... I want to play with you like this everyday.
- Joo Hee.- Yes?
I have an exam coming up soon. So don't call me for a while, okay?
I understand.
I will leave first.
Uh huh. Good-bye.
Yes, Aide Choi.
Assemblyman, where are you right now? Hurry and come back.
Why? Did something happen?
The atmosphere is ominous.
Assemblyman.
What's the matter?
The deputy party leader had an emergency meeting with the floor leaders.
A rumor is circulating that they are going to announce the members of the Emergency Response Commission.
Without consulting us, just among themselves? Where is Assemblywoman Hong?
She went to the meeting place but was refused entrance because they said it was private.
These people, really.
Assemblyman.
Assemblywoman, what happened?
We got shafted.
I am Assemblyman Kang Sang Ho who has been
selected as a member of Gookmin Party's Emergency Response Commission.
I will tell you the names of the five people
who were finalized as the ERC members today.
As members from outside the Party,
former Supreme Court Justice Park Joo Young, Professor Jo Jeong Hwa,
these two people were appointed.
And as inside members, I, Kang Sang Ho,
and Assemblyman Baek Do Hyeon were chosen.
What the heck is this?
Assemblyman! But isn't Assemblyman Baek Do Hyeon currently being investigated by prosecutors?
Oh,
but he is neither indicted nor
are his charges proven, right?
I will continue and announce the chairperson
of the ERC that everyone is curious about.
Until the next party convention, the chairperson
who will lead our Gookmin Party's
Emergency Response Commission is...
Assemblyman Park Choon Seop.
Emergency Response Commission Chairman Park Choon Seop
Assemblyman Park.
You seized the party leadership. Congratulations.
Congratulations on your comeback.
Let us work well together in the future.
Please take care of me.
There definitely was a certain deal among Baek Do Hyeon, Park Choon Seop and the BH.
Cornered Baek Do Hyeon must have offered something
while pushing Park Choon Seop as the chairman of the Emergency Response Commission.
What is that?
Assemblyman Baek Do Hyeon oversaw the affairs of the past presidential election.
- For sure...- The election-related funds?
Yes, that must be it.
I will further analyze the situation and come up with a counter-strategy as soon as possible.
Just let it be.
What?
No matter what foolery the Pro- and Anti-BH factions engage in,
let us just do the work that we have do.
Assemblyman, I understand that you are disheartened.
But because of Assemblyman Baek's power hunger,
the leadership of the ruling party fell into the hands of the tired old power.
Are you saying we should ignore it?
I'm not saying this because I'm disheartened.
Nor am I ignoring it.
I just want to stop exchanging blows and fighting.
I want to start doing real politics.
What is the real politics you have in mind?
Lawmaking.
Assemblymen are not fighters.
They are lawmakers.
They are elected so that they can make good laws that would better the people's lives even by a slight degree.
But look. How much remains of the regular session now?
Not much.
Aide Choi.
Assemblywoman Hong.
No matter what foolery other people engage in,
let us just go our way, okay?
Yes, let's.
Yes.
I was short-sighted.
I am sorry.
Gyu Hwan.
Assemblyman.
What are you doing here right now?
When you should be studying, what are you doing here?
I am doing this so I can study.
What?
Leave. The business will be open soon.
Hey, did Hyung Dal Soo also know about what a troublemaker you are?
Don't bring up father.
I still
cannot laugh and talk about him with you.
Leave. The owner will be here soon.
Leave what, punk?
Call him and tell him you're quitting.
And register as an intern again.
I won't make you work overtime, so you can attend a night school, got it?
Let's go.
I have no thought of that. Just leave.
Let's go, punk.
Didn't I tell you I don't want to?
Listen to me, please, punk!
Why on earth are you doing this to me?
Because I'm Bae Gyu Hwan?
Because you think you can erase your guilt towards my father this way?
I don't need all this almsgiving.
So just go.
Yes, punk, it's because you're Bae Gyu Hwan.
So I want to show you, that's why.
You, punk, said just the sound of "po" in "politics" makes you retch.
So let's go. I will show you what real politics is.
Stick by my side and watch.
Got it?
Chairman, Jin Sang Pil is giving a news conference right now.
This fellah... did he catch on somehow?
Yes, I am People's Spoilsport Assemblyman Jin Sang Pil, the big boss of Gookmin Party's Indifferent-to-BH faction.
The reason I am here today...
is not to expose something.
Nor am I here to criticize the Pro- and Anti-BH factions suddenly being very buddy-buddy lately.
My purpose for being here today is to introduce
a bill that I must absolutely, undoubtedly
pass during this regular session of the Assembly.
What the...
Yes, I know.
That this kind of story is not newsworthy, I do know.
But you have to publicize these kinds of stories too
so that we assemblymen would try to make even better laws.
It won't take much of your time, so listen carefully
and I hope you report a lot about it.
Ms. Choi In Kyung, over there...
Yes, the bill I will primarily sponsor this time
is one that allows our country and society to support,
and to extend a helping hand to those among our countrymen
who could not help but fall down, despite having done their utmost to live diligently.
Namely, a bill to support giving a second chance to those who have lost.
But what kind of bill name is like that?
Just by hearing it, I can tell it's about populism.
All the while I was making this bill,
there was a person who did not leave my thoughts even for one moment.
That person worked harder than anybody else.
He was more conscientious than anybody else.
And more than anybody else,
he was a really great father.
But because of just one defeat,
because of that defeat,
he was a person
who broke down so helplessly, so painfully.
If to that person, just one more chance had been given,
no, even if he could have had a belief that one more chance would be given to him,
in my opinion, I absolutely believe
that he would not have climbed that tall crane.
That person is...
Even though some of you might remember, probably
almost everyone must have forgotten him, probably so.
The late Mr. Bae Dal Soo,
the laid-off worker from Korea Shipbuilding &amp; Repairs Co.
Assemblyman...
has bet even his life on this bill.
If something goes wrong, that will be your responsibility.
Yes, so for me, the real name of this bill is
Bae Dal Soo,
yes, it's Bae Dal Soo's Law.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The Assembly Team @ Viki