Oh, my.
Is she trying to stand out
by herself?
She didn't have to direct traffic.
Why is she doing that by herself?
You're right.
She also made the party awkward
yesterday.
She must like the attention.
I'll send you a signal
Tingling
Dad, I'm so excited today.
You're taking me to school,
and Mom's already there.
- I wish it was like this every day.
- Really?
- Are you happy?
- Yes.
That's Mom.
Mom rocks! She looks so cool.
My goodness.
Oh, my. Can you that too, Mom?
- Mom, can you do that for us too?
- Please?
Let's go.
- I said, let's go!
- Yes, ma'am.
Are you just...
going to watch her?
(Borg Mom)
(A malware virus has been detected.
Code Name: Outcast)
Yool, hurry inside.
- Mom. Dad. Bye!
- Bye.
Borg Mom, go and get changed.
Let's go home together.
- That's not possible now.
- Why is that?
I have a meeting with the Elegance
Mother Committee.
- Today...
- Today's meeting...
has been canceled.
Is it canceled because of the rain?
You might feel better if you think
it's because of the rain.
What is she talking about?
Whatever it is, it's canceled.
So let's go now.
Go get changed.
Yes, I will see you
after three minutes.
(1 hour ago)
The location of the outfit
has been changed.
An item that was not seen earlier
has been spotted.
Acquisition of the outfit's
new location is completed.
Oh, my. It smells so bad.
Your clothes are all ruined.
What will you do?
Are you sure that I became
an Elegance Mother this time?
- Just...
- Just finish it well.
- You...
- You should hurry up.
Finish it, and come out.
Okay.
I'm going to do this to become
an Elegance Mother.
What are you doing?
I'm greeting you gladly
out of surprise.
Why are you still wearing that?
What are these?
What is this smell?
These are my clothes.
What happened to your clothes?
I haven't found out the exact cause.
You're a mess. I'm sure...
that I clearly set the data for
personal belonging organization...
and cleanliness.
That's strange.
Anyway, let's go before
someone sees us.
According to my analysis,
you're embarrassed by me.
It might not seem like it, but it's
the trendy color of 2017, greenery.
Anyway, keep yourself 1m away
from me. Let's go.
The weather is so nice.
(Maintaining a distance of 1m)
I'm maintaining a distance of 1m.
That doesn't matter anymore.
What happened to your memory chip?
Yes, I will protect
my important parts.
(May 2, 2005,
The first day of class at college)
Thank you.
You're that guy
from the orientation.
That guy?
You'll have to hurry if you
don't want to be late for class.
It's the first class today,
but the professor is famous...
for being a psycho, and
he's really stern.
He's going to be really mad
if I'm late.
You should really hurry before
the psycho and really stern...
professor scolds you.
Yes, let's go.
I won't forget this, and I'll repay
this kindness later.
Okay.
Hurry.
Thank goodness.
The professor isn't here yet, right?
Did the teaching assistant check
attendance?
Yes, a minute ago.
I answered in place of you with
my naturally talented voice.
So treat me to lunch later.
Okay, thank you.
I thought I'd give a bad impression
of being late on the first day.
In my opinion,
you left a bad impression
in another way.
What? Why would I?
There's no reason for me to
leave a bad impression...
to a professor
I've never seen before.
Don't you know who the professor is
for this class?
I know.
I heard the rumor of him being
a psycho and really stern.
Why? Is there something else?
- Is there?
- She must not really know.
Why?
- Mi So.
- Yes?
My condolences to your future.
What are you talking about?
I saw that guy from the orientation
who couldn't drink alcohol well.
I met him.
- What?
- He's there.
That's him.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Professor Choi Go Bong, who
will teach the required subject...
"The Emotional Interaction
Between Cyborgs and Humans".
(Choi Go Bong)
Why is he there?
Professor?
I will look forward
to this semester.
Since I became a professor
at a young age,
I wish I will be able
to communicate and spend...
time with you closely. But,
please don't mix drinks
and ask me to drink them for you.
Please verify the rumors
of me being...
a psycho from now on.
I will announce first...
that I'll be very strict in grading.
Hey.
"If you drink this,"
"you'll go out with me."
- Oh, my.
- Gosh.
- Lee Mi So.
- Wasn't I like Son Ye Jin?
Aren't I pretty?
What?
Aren't I really pretty?
- Oh, my.
Do you know now?
You threw up in his arms
during the orientation.
Mi So, I recommend you spending
this semester as quiet as possible.
Let's start our first class.
Wasn't it so funny?
Isn't Borg's mom scary?
She should know by now.
How could she look so calm?
She feels different from
all of the other moms.
You're right.
Her poker face gives me goosebumps.
- Stop.
- She wants us to stop for today.
Are we done already?
I had a hard time.
My neck became stiff.
Wait.
Do Hye has to change alone.
Why?
She never shows us her naked body.
She's too mystic.
Fields have eyes,
and woods have ears.
What?
Fields have eyes,
and woods have ears.
Be careful what you talk about.
Come here.
Oh, my. Fencing.
This is it.
Did you hire a special coach?
Why fencing suddenly?
What do you mean?
Our kids will enter
elementary school next year.
To endure the hardships
of examinations,
it's a must to train their physical
and mental strength.
Didn't you know?
Kids learn horse riding
and fencing...
before they enter elementary school.
That's right.
But we don't have time for it.
I can't cancel her Chinese class.
Should I cancel her coding class?
Some mothers say that coding classes
aren't essential these days.
Coding? What is that?
Anyhow,
William can join your group, right?
Under a condition.
What is that?
I heard his class went home
two hours later than the schedule.
I mean Borg's class.
I heard you loud and clear.
Then you're going to let William
join your fencing class, right?
I see.
- Hello?
- Ma'am.
You didn't come to pick up
Borg over two hours.
I was wondering
if something happened to you.
I heard his class would be dismissed
two hours later...
as it's an extended school day.
Wait, no. That's not true.
Where are you now?
I'm in front of your classroom.
He just fell asleep
while waiting for you.
- Are you Mr. Kwon Hyun Bin?
- Yes.
- Please sign here.
- Thank you.
My mom sent this.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
Hold on a second.
Borg just fell asleep. I don't think
waking him up now is a good idea.
By any chance, are you free now?
Gosh, I don't usually
celebrate my birthdays.
I just had my own birthday party.
Don't people spend their birthdays
with their family or loved ones?
That's right.
That's what people usually do.
But actually,
ever since when I was young,
my mom has been working
hard overseas.
So living separately has
become the norm for our family.
But she never forgets
my birthdays...
and makes sure she sends me
a gift every year from afar.
Thank you, Mom.
This year, my mom is giving
me some love as always
(Happiness: 50 percent, Longing:
20 percent, Excitement 30 percent)
This is too much for me
to finish by myself.
But it'd be a shame
if I throw this out,
and you have to wait for Borg
to wake up anyway.
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday, dear Mr. Kwon
You must not.
You must make a wish first
and blow out the candles.
Okay.
Happy birthday to you, Mr. Kwon.
Now this feels like
a real birthday party.
To be honest, it's my first time
celebrating my birthday...
after my seventh birthday.
Anyway,
thanks to you, Borg's mom,
this years' birthday will
be unforgettable
It would've been nicer
if I prepared a gift for you.
What a bummer.
Right on.
That's quite disappointing.
I really want a birthday gift
from you.
Is there anything you want?
Can I keep that birthday gift
for now?
If I happen to think of a gift
I want,
I'll make sure I tell you about it.
Okay. You can do that.
All right. Shall we eat?
Which dish would you like?
This is...
Bulgogi made with Korean beef
from Hoengseong, Gangwon Province.
Sushi with the best sea urchin roe
from Hokkaido.
Caviar salad with the caviar
from Russia.
And you have an octopus dish
from Muan which gives life...
into a dying cow.
Here's my respect.
You have great eyes.
Dig in, ma'am.
You must eat sushi with your hands
to avoid messing up the form...
and dip the raw fish
into the soy sauce, not the rice...
in order to enjoy the real taste
of the ingredient.
And this.
- Ma'am, please have some.
- Okay.
Mom.
Borg, you're up.
Join us. This is really good.
Yool, which one would you like?
You're a man.
I can't believe this.
(Happy birthday, Mr. Kwon, the
sunshine of Buckingham Preschool)
Unbelievable.
How can she reject me?
Ah Reum.
Wasn't I good enough
for your hot fling?
Why did I buy this?
Give me a bottle of soju.
- Oh, no. We're packed now.
- Darn it.
Hold on. Excuse me.
Please share your table with him.
- Take a seat right there.
- Okay.
Excuse me. Please share the table.
How dare you sit
at the same table, you trash?
Me?
You're from Cola Girls.
It is you.
Are you the weasel from upstairs?
Let me be upfront with you.
We've met a long time ago,
haven't we?
Goodness, seriously? Are you going
to bring that up again, weasel?
Goodness, I'm so sick of you.
Wait. You know each other?
What a destiny. This is good.
Share the table. I'll throw in...
a bottle of soju
and stir-fried eels for free.
Goodness, you're quick-witted.
I know. I'm so nice.
You...
I waited for him so long.
Me too. I waited for her so long.
It happened to you too?
I even...
prepared a gift for her.
So did I.
Aren't these pretty?
They're great.
Aren't these awesome?
They are awesome.
I can't even wear them because
they're for men. I'll throw them...
Don't do it!
Give me that.
In exchange, I'll give you these.
Put it on.
- This looks nice.
- You look great in it.
All right. We should drink to this.
Here you go.
Here.
- Bottoms up!
Why are those two here?
Do you know them?
Yes.
One of them is my neighbor, and
the other one is almost like family.
Then please take them with you.
They got drunk
and were making a scene.
Because of them, the other
customers are about to leave.
In that case,
can I borrow this for one more day?
I'm sorry.
Come back to me.
How can someone be this drunk?
It's a similar disgraceful behavior
as yours yesterday.
That's enough. What about Yool?
He's in REM sleep...
after I read
"Red Riding Hood" to him.
Go Bong?
I really need to do it tonight.
What?
Do what?
I can't...
stand it anymore.
I'm about to burst.
I can't stand it anymore...
seeing your condition.
I'm sorry.
I was too urgent.
Don't close your eyes.
Look at me.
I'll open it up for you now.
Yes, please be careful.
Go Bong.
(Fingerprint recognition complete)
(Pupil recognition complete)
The food waste disposal is open.
Oh, my.
You ate a lot.
It's completely filled.
Oh, my.
Okay.
The disposal of the food waste
inside the body is complete.
The residue is 0 percent.