Subtitles by DramaFever
To tell you the truth...
I can see ghosts.
Stop spouting nonsense and review the
interview article from last month.
Really? You know, my shoulder's
really been hurting lately.
Do you read palms, too?
What a load of bullshit.
This is it.
Oh, there's one over there, too.
Since when has it been here?
Did you decide on a date
for your interview with the dean?
Is it a boy?
Is it good-looking?
Ask it for some lottery numbers.
It's supposed to be like this.
So what's with those girls?
Do spirits have colors, too?
You weren't just asking that for fun?
What about brain-dead people?
Where are the souls of
brain-dead people?
It makes it super awkward if you
take a joke that seriously, you guys!
Oh... then I guess
I did kill her that time.
What the... do all of you have a
ghost or two that you think it may be?
It could be a soul of a person
that will be murdered in the future.
Not you too, Madame Jung!
So why did you have to lie?
It was some nonsense
I said while we were all drinking.
It was a simple joke!
A white...
lie.
I told you to fix that nasty
habit of yours, didn't I?
It was just a silly joke to bring some
tension to our boring everyday lives!
Was that really so wrong of me to do?
Did I commit a huge sin?
Yep.
Fine. If that's a sin, all right.
I'll acknowledge it.
It's all my fault.
Cast stones at me!
Spit on me!
Only those who've never lied
can spit at me.
- What do I do?
- What are you worried about?
I thought you said it was just some
nonsense you said while drinking.
A white lie.
Stop acting cutesy.
It became like that.
[A Small Lie That
Became a Big One]
[Episode 10: We Believe
Because We Want To - Lie]
Should I come clean now?
That'd be best, right?
I'm sorry! It was all a lie!
I deserve to die for what I've done!
Wait. Honestly, this whole situation
doesn't warrant that kind of apology.
Ghosts? You guys really
believe in that kind of stuff?
You believed that?
Wait, no. That approach
may be a bit dangerous.
Should I settle for what's in between
those two options, then?
Hey, sorry. I was just messing around.
Why are you acting like that?
You're pissing me off.
Why are you smiling,
and then frowning?
You know... I have something to confess.
Oh, it's nothing serious, really.
No need to focus on me. Just listen
while you're doing what you're doing.
Just a moment.
But before I tell you,
promise me something.
Promise me that you won't hit me.
What is it, already?
About what I said before...
You'll have to be more
specific than that.
About the thing
I said was over there...
- Is it a thief?
- What is it?
What? What is it?
- What's the matter?
- What?
Over... there.
Senior Yoon!
When did you get back, Senior Yoon?
Huh?
Are you not feeling well?
What time is it now?
It's past 10:40 p.m.
- See you later!
- Okay.
- Bye!
- Be careful!
Okay.
I guess she slept all day.
She even missed her classes.
I guess Senior Yoon
was quite taken aback.
Well, she had high hopes, so...
No! I'm going to congratulate
you while I can! Congrats! Congrats!
I should've congratulated her less.
It's a public enterprise! If you're hired
you'll be set for life. I'm so jealous!
How much will your annual salary be?
I overreacted.
Really, congratulations!
It's okay. She's Senior Yoon, after all.
I'm sure she'll rise from
the ashes soon enough.
Yeah! It's Senior Yoon, after all!
Yes! It's Senior Yoon, after all!
- What happened? Wow!
- Since when?
- I can't believe it!
- Wow!
Hello.
Congratulations.
Thank you, Senior.
Seriously, that's amazing!
[Latter-Half of Year Recruitment
For New Employees]
[Looking for Talented Individuals
to Work Abroad for Us]
Eun Jae!
Aunt!
We're not even that far by subway,
so why didn't you visit even once?
I told you to drop by and pick up
some kimchi, and eat with us.
Yes.
What, your mom won't let you come?
No.
Eat up.
You have some too, Aunt.
You really do take after your father.
If your father saw you now,
he would've been so proud.
You do remember your dad, don't you?
Of course you do.
You're his daughter, after all.
Hurry and eat up!
Eat, eat.
Those insurance people
came to see you too, right?
I did think it was quite strange
how your father died.
I mean, it's not like he
was a beginner at driving.
And it's not like he was
a heavy drinker, either.
Wasn't there anything
that seemed off to you?
I mean, a lot happened before your
dad's accident. There was a fire, too.
Only my mom got hurt that time.
That's true, but it's not like there
was ever a proper investigation.
Who knows what really happened?
Eun Jae.
Let's re-investigate your father's case.
Your mom is ignoring this whole thing,
so you're the only option I have left!
Why are you putting your spoon down?
Hurry up and eat!
Hurry and eat.
Eat up.
Oh no, it's all cold now.
Oh, whatever.
I don't need to tell them the truth.
I just said that there was a ghost.
I never said whose ghost it was.
They just believed it because they
wanted to, so it's not my fault. Right?
Do whatever you want.
I never said anything.
I mean, in books,
all lies get exposed and such.
But it's not like that in real life!
And there's no need for such honesty!
There are lies that just flow on
and disappear eventually, too!
What?
Is that book fun?
What happens because of that small lie?
Someone dies.
- Song! Do you have any eye patches?
- No.
Senior Kang!
Do you have any eye patches?
Can you lend me one,
if you have one?
What is this?
What are you doing?
Oh, I'm planning to sell them.
Really? Why? Why are you selling them?
Are you selling this one, too?
Do you like it?
Buy it, then.
I'll give you a discount on one of them.
How much of a discount?
10 percent off the retail price?
Senior Kang.
Are you doing this because of the
ghost over there, by any chance?
What I'm saying is...
is this sudden change of heart related
to the ghost in the shoe closet?
Oh, never mind.
It's nothing.
Continue on with what you were doing.
I'm here to sell some bags.
I think you've misunderstood.
Our store doesn't buy just any bag--
So, are you going to buy it or not?
We'll buy it.
Just a moment.
Dong Joo!
Do you buy shoes, too?
Wait, not these.
I'll just be taking these back, okay?
11,690,000 won! Wow!
Are you checking the serial
numbers on the bills?
Yeah, just in case.
Want to get smacked by a wad of cash?
Are you that happy?
Yeah. What do you want to eat?
I'll buy you something yummy.
- It's fine.
- Why?
Do one of your girlfriends
want to meet up?
Yeah.
Oh well, then. You have
to make a living, too.
Drop me off at that intersection.
Call me.
What?
Is it really okay for me to call you?
You crazy... what, were you
planning to cut ties with me?
Are you by yourself?
Yeah.
Senior Yoon.
The microwave.
Oh.
Wear these to your next interview.
To tell you the truth,
your old shoes really don't cut it.
You probably failed the interview
portion because of your shoes.
I know it might be funny
hearing this from me
but there are tons of other
jobs left to apply to.
I'm sure it'll work out great next time.
Do you think that I failed
because of my shoes?
I told you, yes! Don't you know
how important those things are?
There's a girl in my major
who got into that company.
Her financial situation
is the same as mine.
No. If anything, she's worse off.
She helps pay for her family's living
expenses with her part-time jobs, too.
I don't remember, but I don't think
her shoes were better than mine.
So in the end...
It was all my fault.
It wasn't due to her
parents' financial power
or her qualifications.
Or her connections.
All I need to do is be a bit better.
But the problem is... I don't know
how I can improve myself.
But still, take these. I'm giving these
to you because I'm thankful to you.
Why would you be thankful toward me?
There's reasons.
I have my reasons, so take them.
I'm sorry.
I didn't do it on purpose.
Hell?
You only do nice things things
for Senior Yoon.
Those shoes aren't even your size!
I can make them fit, if I tried!
I had a bad dream.
In my dream, I was sent to hell.
How is it that even your
dreams are so you?
When I get stressed, I always dream
about taking the College Exams.
In my dream, I always say,
"that's weird, I'm already in college!"
But I still keep taking the exam anyway.
Is that the kind of dream
that college students have?
Guys say that they usually dream
about going back to the army.
Do you have dreams of taking
the College Exams, too?
I have dreams of being chased by a dog.
Dad!
Shoo!
Were you scared?
It's okay. It's okay.
You said that your dad rescues you.
So why is that a nightmare?
That's a happy ending, then, isn't it?
That's true, but...
Attention!
Everyone, your attention please.
As you all may be aware,
I'm a reporter for the school newspaper.
Also, my motto is, "Keeping silent
is the worst type of lying!"
I could just blow past it
as if nothing happened
but for the sake of righteousness,
as well as my peace of mind--
- Give us the short version.
- What is it?
Um, about that.
About how I--
Who the hell is it,
at this time of night?
Mom?
Eun Jae!
Mom, what's going on?
What do I do now?
What do I do, when we live together?
Sheesh!
How could they do this to me?
They didn't lay a hand on me,
but this was definitely assault!
Assault and battery!
So? What did Mister say?
"Ms. Jung Hui. Is there anything
that you haven't told me?"
How could he say that to me?
Was that all?
You should've seen the look
on his face when he said that!
He said that as if I had a huge secret,
and his eyes were full of doubt!
He thinks that I'm someone
who killed her husband!
How could anyone think that of me?
Huh? How could they?
I'm sure that he didn't
mean it like that.
He just asked you a question, is all.
Why would he ask me that? Why?
How could I live with him while
being doubted like that? I can't!
I can't live with him
for one more second!
She seems more like a child
than Eun Jae, right?
Maybe because she's young at heart?
I mean, she had amazing skin.
Is that the only thing you noticed?
Is your mom okay?
Something unpleasant happened
between her and my stepdad, I think.
Your mom was just like a young girl.
Oh yeah. I knew that Eun Jae's mom
reminded me of someone.
Me? How?
- She's not like me at all!
- Why are you saying that?
Are you looking down on
Eun Jae's mom, right now?
Um...
I think my mom will have
to stay the night here.
Yes, so?
- But Senior Yoon...
- What about her?
You want to use my room?
How could the two of you
sleep in one bed?
What do you mean?
All close and cozy, of course!
I don't really want to sleep
with Senior Yoon, though.
Even though you like her
enough to give her shoes?
I'm sorry.
My mom dropped by all of a sudden,
so I think she'll spend the night here.
I'm sorry, but could you sleep in
Senior Kang's room tonight?
Kay.
Should I move to the other side for her?
She'll probably feel cramped.
Good mor--
- What about your mom?
- She went out.
She went out?
Okay.
Oh, you're all awake already?
The flower shop was open already!
Isn't it pretty?
What?
Hello.
- Mom, go in.
- Why?
Why?
Sheesh!
Why'd you sleep on the couch?
I just sat here, and before I knew it...
Get some more sleep, Senior Yoon.
Okay.
Go sleep in my room, if you want.
Who is it?
It's certified mail!
Sorry about this morning.
It's all right.
I heard that you work at your part-time
job until early in the morning.
You must be so tired.
Do you want some coffee?
No, it's fine.
Oh yeah, who's Yoon Soon Myung?
A piece of certified mail came,
and I left it right there.
What's the matter?
Is it not for you?
No, it is mine.
[Resume]
Were you sick for a long time?
Excuse me?
I mean, you didn't do anything
after graduating high school, so...
Yes, I was.
Where, exactly?
Here, there, and all over.
You're fine now, right?
Yes. I'm healthy now.
Our store opens at 11 a.m.,
and closes at 9 p.m.
Including the time it'll take you to
clean up, you'll be here until 10 p.m.
And on the days we need extra
people, you'll be here from 4 to 10.
The hourly wage is 6,500 won, and
you'll have to be here five days a week.
You have to work on the floor, but
you'll also have to organize inventory
and send packages, too.
There's a lot of extra work to do.
But still, it'll be a good
learning experience.
Do you have any questions?
No.
Then you can come to work
starting next week.
Thank you.
[Looking for a part-timer]
Mister!
I lost two hours worth of pay,
just like that.
Shall I help you?
How come this doesn't work?
- Oh, can I see your card--
- Oh, my card? A credit card?
Do you have a transportation
card, by any chance?
A transportation card?
- He's cute.
- Yeah, he's okay.
I don't know. I'm not feeling it.
Oh, a med-school student?
What? He's in a band, too?
He's a drummer?
I don't mesh that well with musicians.
What's with her? Wait,
let me download this app, too.
Wow, look at how tall he is!
I don't know. 187 centimeters
is a bit too tall.
Why are there no good guys?
What?
It's not that there's no guys.
It's just that you're not into this.
What are you talking about? I totally am!
I'm definitely going to meet a guy!
Fine. Tell me the kind
of guy you want, then.
Your ideal type!
Hmm, my idea type?
I don't want a guy who's too tall.
Someone who's the perfect size to hug.
So maybe 15 centimeters taller than me?
As for his hairstyle, I like someone who
keeps it neat and short rather than long.
I like guys who have pretty,
double eye-lidded eyes.
And for his nose... I want
his nose bridge to be a bit high.
Let's see. Oh!
I like guys whose eyes turn
into half-moons when they smile!
As for his body... I like a guy
who looks like he works out.
That way, anything he
wears will look good
and the feeling you get
when you look at them is...
He sounds like a guy
we've seen a lot before.
No, no!
You should've forgotten
about him by now.
I told you, I have!
You know what they would've called you
if you were born in the Joseon Era?
Stop it!
Let's eat spaghetti tomorrow. It's better
to eat oily things in the day, right?
Oh, hey.
- Yeah.
- It's been a while.
What brings you here?
Well, I was just passing by, so...
- Did you have lunch--
- Go about your business, then.
How about seafood
cream sauce spaghetti?
Did you see that show last night? I saw
that there, and I really want it now!
- Ah, the weather today is so nice!
- Yeah.
- Oh man.
- Good job, friend!
Really, good job.
Really?
I was so nervous that
I thought that I'd die!
Yes, Mister?
You're... not going to class?
No. Something came up, so...
Sure.
Man, it's hot.
Do you know why people have two kidneys?
One's for purifying your body,
and one's a backup.
So you only need one.
What brings you here?
I got this in the mail.
[Military Draft Notice
for Yoon Soo Myung]
You didn't apply for disability benefits?
No, I didn't.
Why not?
Because I thought he'd wake up
tomorrow, or the day after that.
It's because I thought he'd wake up.
I'm sure he'll wake up next
month, at the very latest.
It's been six years.
I understand how you must feel.
I'm sure that you wanted to believe.
It's not because you had
legitimate reasons to believe.
You believed because you wanted to.
And you couldn't bear it, if you
didn't have that belief to hold on to.
But, did you know...
that hope brings misfortune?
Jin Myung!
There!
Pass! Pass it!
He's back to normal.
- Hello.
- Oh! Ms. Jin Myung!
Today's Thursday, though.
Where's the manager?
He's in the storage closet.
Oh yeah. About that wine...
he said that he made a mistake.
It was a mistake on his part.
You didn't hear about that, right?
I knew it.
Evil bastard.
Ms. Jin Myung.
We were talking... and if you
call him out, we'll help you.
This isn't the first time.
He's way out of line.
He always touches us more than he
needs when he's checking out uniforms!
Isn't all of that sexual harassment?
And he keeps extending the
time we have to work, slowly.
And last time, he called
Sae Hee out on her day off
and asked her to come to a
new restaurant with him.
We've all been holding it in until now,
but if you decide to call him out now
all of us will--
I have something to speak to you about.
Oh, about what happened last time--
I'm quitting.
What?
Please give me the money
that's due to me for working.
I mean, if you quit so suddenly, we...
Well, if you really need to,
I guess it can't be helped. Yeah.
Sure.
Why are you quitting?
You told me not too long
ago to quit, didn't you?
Back then, I...
I thought you said that this place
was like the ends of the earth for you.
I thought that this place
was your cut-off line.
That's right.
This place is my cut-off line.
That's why I'm quitting.
And if you do quit?
Can you get some time off
tomorrow afternoon?
I do have some common sense, you know.
You can't sleep properly, and it has
you on edge to have me here, right?
I'm sorry.
But in exchange, I'll make you
tons of delicious things, so eat up!
Are you done peeling the onions?
If you are, cut them here.
Yes, ma'am.
Wow, you're way too slow, Student!
You have to work on the squid after that.
You're doing well, though, Student!
- Eun Jae!
- Why are you back so late?
You're back?
- Hurry up, and--
- Please come in.
Ms. Jung Hui!
Let's go home, already.
Why are you even here?
I'm sorry. I was wrong.
What did you do wrong, exactly?
Everything.
I hate you.
I hate you!
Here. Let me see your face.
Did you cry a lot?
I'm sorry.
Yeah. I bet you really are.
Man, I thought something
crazier would happen.
Wow, I'm so jealous!
The entire house is a mess!
It's all your fault.
No, it's not my fault
that you got all fussy.
Idiot! Idiot!
Stupid idiot!
Did you send your parents off well?
I'm sorry.
What? It was romantic.
Do you really mean that?
Wow, this is good.
Oh, Senior Yoon!
You're back?
You don't have your part-time job today?
I took the day off.
What's all this?
It's a long story, but here.
Come and sit.
What's all that?
I bought some fish cakes
and ddukbokki.
I bought some so we
could eat it together, but...
No way.
- Who are you?
- Did something happen?
No, it's just that I feel like I've
been kind of a downer lately.
I guess I bought this for nothing.
Whoa, whoa, no!
What are you doing?
This ddukbokki isn't just
regular ddukbokki!
And these fish cakes aren't
just regular fish cakes, either!
These are ones that Senior Yoon bought!
Yes, that's right! Senior Yoon did!
Wow! Move that crap aside!
Forget about that garbage food!
Wow! This is insane.
What a relief. I was worried because
you seemed down lately, Senior Yoon.
Yeah. I felt so bad,
that I thought I'd die!
Why would you?
We helped get your hopes
so high for nothing!
Yes. I'm sure you must've had
even higher hopes than we did, too.
It's not your fault.
I just believed that I'd get hired,
because I wanted to.
Because I wouldn't be
able to bear it otherwise.
All right, let's all have a drink!
We have beer that we bought, right?
Yep!
All right. For Senior Yoon,
who's now reborn! Yeah!
- Yeah!
Wow, I can't believe that I'm eating
food that Senior Yoon bought me!
Wow, my life is pretty
much complete now!
Hurry over here!
Come here!
Hurry! Let's go!
What is this?
Sorry.
Oh my gosh,
I thought you were a ghost!
What are you doing?
You should be sleeping!
I was just thinking about
a couple of things.
Oh man. You scared the crap out of me.
You know, about the ghost
that you said was here...
It's my little brother.
He hasn't been able to live
or die for six years now.
He can't even move.
I'm sure that must really be terrible.
Right?
Oh my... geez.
- What is it now?
- Tell me that it's my fault.
It's your fault. I don't know
what it is, but it's all your fault.
The fact that it's hot today
is all your fault, too.
No, no, no. I'm sure they all just
have a ghost that they want to see.
There's a ghost that they've
all had in their hearts, is all!
Hey!
Senior Yoon is acting weird.
About the ghost that
you said was here...
It's my younger brother.
- She was up in the middle of the night.
- Let go before you continue talking!
He hasn't been able to
live or die for six years now.
And he can't even move.
Okay, so he was like that for six years.
Whatever. Why bring that up now?
Your account is expiring in a month.
But you want to close it down now?
Yes.
Thanks. See, I told you.
If there's a will, there's a way.
- We're all done here, right?
- All right.
8,900,000 won.
It's all here.
What happened? Did you
win the lottery, or something?
- Sir, he didn't give us the IOU.
- What?
The IOU.
Hey, I have hemorrhoids!
It you make them worse, I swear--
- What was with that look in her eyes?
- What look?
I'm sure that must be terrible.
Right?
Hey. If you don't let go by the time
I count to three, I'll kill you!
One, two, three--
It's nothing.
Of course it's nothing.
It'd be bad if it weren't.
Should I just kill her?
It's nothing.
I wanted to meet up with you and have
coffee, and spend time talking to you.
Just like everyone else does.
That's okay, right?
I want ice cream.
What about you?
I'll have ice cream, too.
Excuse me.
We'd like to order.
Ms. Jin Myung.
How does this look?
I don't think it suits you.
- Really?
- Yes.
You pick one out too, Ms. Jin Myung.
No, it's okay.
Let's go.
What should we do next?
- Let's go see a movie.
- A movie?
Yeah, Mom? What now?
"What now?"
What kind of greeting is that?
- Everything's okay, right?
- Pretty much.
I just felt bad that I couldn't
properly say goodbye to everyone.
Tell your seniors that
I'm sorry about that!
- All right.
- Especially to that scary one.
The one who got a letter
for Yoon Soo Myung.
Yoon Soo Myung?
Make sure you get along with everyone
and bring them over to our
place sometime, okay?
Hey, Eun Jae!
Are you listening?
Huh? Yeah.
Okay. Bye.
- Senior Yoon!
- Senior Yoon...
[Song Ji Won]
I guess we walked too much.
I wanted to try this once.
Walking places without having a
clear destination in mind, I mean.
Come with sneakers on next time.
Next... time.
The day's almost over. There were
tons of things I wanted to try, too.
We can do them next time.
And we can take our time.
Next time?
I don't think I'd be able
to do this next time.
Yeah. She told me that she
had to leave, all of a sudden.
She said that her mom would
come and get her deposit later.
She didn't mention
why she was moving out?
No.
[Senior Yoon]
The party you are trying to
reach is currently unavailable.
Please leave a message
after the tone.
- What'd she say?
- She's moving out.
The shoes I gave her... are gone.
She's supposed to be a smart cookie,
but she went and forgot this.
It's only because it's me
that I brought this for her.
Nobody else would've been as kind as me.
At any rate, we upheld our
end of the deal, okay?
Do you know where that is?
The hospital where Senior Yoon --
I mean, Yoon Jin Myung's brother is.
There's the bus.
No. It's not my fault.
How is that my fault?
Humans are not such simple creatures.
She wouldn't have made a decision
like that just because of one reason.
Right? I mean, even if one
final straw breaks the camel's back
that's just one piece of
straw we're talking about.
The reason is because of the crushing
weight, not just that one piece of straw.
The same weight and responsibility
as one piece of straw...
Please... please, please!
- Oh my!
- Oh no.
Excuse me! Move!
Senior Yoon!
Senior Yoon.
[Police]
Lord, I know that you're trying to
strengthen me through heartbreak.
I know that you'll only give me
obstacles that I can handle, too.
I'll try my best to become a
better person every day.
Please protect my family today, too.
And the girls. Song Ji Won,
Kang Yi Na, Yoo Eun Jae...
And I'd especially like
to pray for Senior Yoon.
Senior Yoon needs help right now.
Please let me know how I can
be of help to Senior Yoon.
And if I can't be the one to help
her, please help her, God.
Amen.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Why did you tell that kind of lie?]
It just... kind of happened.
[Let's say that we can let this slide.]
To tell you the truth,
I can see ghosts.
- The ghost is really angry right now.
- [But wasn't this going too far?]
It's the soul of someone
who was murdered.
Yes, I know.
[Isn't there always a reason
why people tell certain lies?]
[You noticed that Senior
Yoon was off, so you're perceptive.]
[So maybe you did it because you felt
your housemates were keeping secrets?]
No.
[Did you really just
do it for fun, then?]
Rather than saying
that it was for fun...
Oh, I don't know, either.
Those were just the words that
popped into my head at that moment
and I felt like I had to say
that no matter what, so...
[Do you have a secret of
your own, by any chance?]
Me? No.
No, I don't.
- Huh? What's with the audio?
- We're checking it right now!
Hyo Jin?
[What did you just say?]
What? No.
I didn't say anything.