Subtitles by DramaFever
She said that it was all a lie
when she said that you saw ghosts,
that the ghost was mad
and that the ghost was the spirit
of someone who was murdered!
I was so shocked!
Why would she tell a lie like that?
I mean, people always have a
reason for the lies they tell, right?
She said that it was just a prank,
but it's been months since she started!
Can you really just call that a
simple prank? No, that's fraud!
I mean, I didn't think about it too
much, since I believe in God
but other people are at a loss,
now that her lie has been exposed
because they always believed
every word that she said.
Everyone thought that the ghost
was someone they knew.
Goodness. Why do you
think she did such a thing?
I just don't get it!
[Final Episode: And Yet,
Life Still Goes On - Aftermath]
Senior!
Yeah. Are you by yourself?
Yes.
Should I apologize to
her one more time?
And tell her that I didn't
mean to do that
and that I kept losing my
chances to tell the truth?
And that she doesn't need to worry,
because I won't tell anyone her secret?
She probably thinks that
I'm cocky and disgusting.
No. If I say something like that,
it might just make matters worse.
She's probably thinking, "look at
that murderer, eating apples."
They'll all find out when the
results of the autopsy come out.
What will everyone say?
Oh... I don't know.
Do you want an apple?
No thanks.
They say that eating apples
in the morning is like medicine
but eating apples
at night is like poison!
That's how the saying goes.
It's just a saying.
What would you do if someone told you
you didn't have many days left to live?
What do you mean by that?
Just asking.
I was just curious.
I was just wondering what
others would do in that situation.
Things I must do.
Things that I want to do.
Speaking of which, she's weird, too.
It seriously made me wonder if
she had mental issues, at first.
She won't clearly state her
opinion about anything.
The only thing she ever says is, "that's
not true, Senior?" in her mumbly voice.
It kind of seems like she's a
misanthrope, and... oh yeah!
She reminds me of a dog
that was abused as a puppy.
She's always flinching,
and is always so hesitant!
I don't know why she has
such little self-esteem!
I mean, she's not ugly.
And if she got into our school,
that means that she's smart, too.
Isn't it strange?
You eat parsley?
I don't really like it.
It tastes so soapy.
It's actually my first time trying it.
I just wanted to try it once.
- It tastes weird.
- Right?
You can't bear to eat any more of that?
Senior.
Want to go and drink some alcohol?
Alcohol?
Yes.
I want to get a bit drunk.
Is there something you're worried about?
Yes.
Tell me.
I'll tell you a bit later.
All right. Drink up, okay?
Drink as much as you want!
I'll take responsibility for you,
and take you home.
Cheers!
Senior.
Yeah?
You know... later on...
When you find out
the truth about me...
Keep going. I'm listening.
Don't... hate me too much, okay?
Okay.
The lines need to be uniform from
beginning to end, when you're shading.
And take some of that
pressure out of your wrist!
Just focus on your own.
We're supposed to help each other.
What's so great about her?
She thinks she's all that!
She thinks that she can
just do whatever she wants!
She's been living however
she wanted all this time
and she's saying she wants
to become a designer now!
Geez. Does that even make any sense?
Does she think that all designers
have to do is wear nice clothes?
She's trying to re-invent herself now,
when she's 24 years old!
Geez. I feel like I wouldn't be
able to get any sleep at night
because of anxiety, if I were her.
She has delusions of grandeur!
She's the one who should be here,
not me!
What if I'm in huge trouble?
I've set an unstable objective
for myself, at my unstable age.
Maybe I should just quit.
What's the matter?
Is it not going well?
No, I'm getting better bit by bit.
Really?
That's great.
Are you going to your part-time
job at the convenience store?
- Yeah.
- You're heading out early.
The person working before me
asked me to cover for them a little.
- See you later.
- Okay.
This is so embarrassing. I'm so
embarrassed that I can't even quit.
If I give up after putting this little
effort into it, they'll all laugh at me.
How could she manage to study
in that kind of situation?
She's the same as always, even though
her mom is in jail and her brother still
hasn't even had his funeral yet.
How could she manage to keep attending
school, and going to her part-time jobs
and studying, in that kind of situation?
It's like she has no emotions.
She's like a robot!
And also, I found out not too long ago
that her brother was in a coma.
It's been two years since
we've known each other
so how could she not have said
anything about that to me, for that long?
I was a bit disappointed, honestly.
At any rate, none of them are normal.
What the...
What is it?
I need the fridge.
Oh... sure.
When are the results
for the autopsy coming out?
Next Wednesday.
If, by any chance, you...
Aren't you hot?
In this? It's thinner than you'd think.
It's pretty nice and cool.
Let's go.
You're going to wear that?
This is the only black thing I have.
Hurry.
Let's go.
How could she wear that?
She might as well just wear red!
Thank you.
How did you get here?
We took the village bus and
got off in front of the center
and then took the number 760 bus,
which brought us straight here.
Of course we should be here.
Come on in.
You can get up now.
Okay.
- Oh man, I'm tearing up!
- That was so funny.
- We're sorry for laughing.
- I laughed too, so it's okay.
Look at what happened, because of you!
What? What'd I do?
Hey, you're sweating.
It's because I laughed too much.
They'll probably think that we're crazy.
It's strange. Despite the situation,
I couldn't help but laugh.
Yeah.
What about your mom?
She's on her way here.
You all should be going now.
Already?
There's not much to do here, anyway.
And you have classes, right?
Oh... but still...
I'm really okay.
Go on now.
Go. It's okay.
- Bye, then!
- Okay.
- We'll be going.
- Bye.
Senior.
On that day... um, so, on the day
that happened to your brother...
if your mother hadn't
done what she did...
You want to know if I
would've done it instead?
Probably.
Why? Why did you think to
do that, all of a sudden?
You didn't do anything up until now.
I was wondering if that, by any
chance... was because of me.
Because I lied about seeing a ghost.
Yeah, it might have been.
I never once thought about it before
you started talking about a ghost.
I only thought about whether
my brother was alive or dead.
I never thought of anything beyond that.
Before you talked about the ghost
I never thought about his soul,
how he felt, or what he wanted me to do.
Or what I'd want, if I were in
Soo Myung's situation.
So...
Thanks for lying to me.
How old was Senior Yoon's
younger brother, again?
22 years old.
I wonder how old he was
when that photo was taken.
He looked really young.
He looked like he was
way too young to die.
Maybe we should've stayed a bit longer.
Yeah. We should have
stayed a bit longer.
She told us to go, though.
She might actually just
want to be alone right now.
You think so?
I wouldn't want to be alone
if I were her, though.
What do you think will happen
to Senior Yoon's mom?
They said she'll probably
just be on probation
due to the nature of the situation.
Are you hot?
No. I just feel itchy.
Have you been to a lot of
these types of things before?
You knew exactly what to do.
I saw what they did during
my dad's funeral, so...
Oh yeah.
That's right.
I was actually really
nervous back there.
Right? Me too.
I was really nervous, too.
Even though I never knew him.
Yeah. This is the first
funeral I've ever attended.
Me too.
I'm sure one can even get used
to places like this, after a while.
Yeah, I'm sure.
I'm sure that a lot of people I know
will end up dying in my lifetime.
- And we'll die one day, too--
- Stop it. This is depressing.
- Sheesh, this--
- I told you, I'm not hot!
I was going to talk about
this damn bus not coming!
Oh.
Ms. Jin Myung.
Your mother is here.
What time do you have to head back?
Five.
This is a great photo.
Yes.
It must've been hard for you,
preparing all this on your own.
Why won't you meet with the attorney?
I want to be punished
properly for my sins.
You didn't do anything wrong.
Why did you even do it, if you were
going to be so remorseful?
Why did you even do it?
Mom, did you do this for me,
by any chance?
Because you were afraid
that I'd do it, if you didn't?
I feel like there's a weight
off my shoulders now.
My sin is that I feel too
lighthearted after what I've done.
I know I shouldn't be acting this way
after I've killed my own child, but...
[Demian]
Why didn't you tell me?
Well...
it wasn't a proper funeral,
and it's not exactly good news.
I wasn't exactly excited
to tell you about it.
But still, it would've
been nice if you did.
Don't worry about it.
I didn't tell anyone about it.
Am I just "anyone" to you?
- What I meant is--
- I thought...
that I was a bit more
special to you than that.
Sometimes, you make me quite sad.
I'm sorry. To tell you the truth,
I've been a bit weird lately.
I have no idea what I should do.
I feel like I've lost my way...
but I don't even know
where I took a wrong turn.
So things with Senior Yoon
got resolved, for the most part.
And as for the rest...
ah, whatever.
But the issue is her.
It's no good to confess things
out of the blue, though.
My heart isn't ready for this yet!
And I can't just act as if nothing
happened, since she heard it all.
The day after tomorrow.
So there's two days left.
Should I just confess?
What do I tell Mom?
Man, I'm so tired.
Living life diligently
sure is a lot of work.
Should I just quit?
What if I just keep trying my best,
but this isn't the right path for me?
Shouldn't I try to find a different goal
to work toward, as soon as possible?
Man, this is driving me crazy!
It's not like I'm going through puberty!
Why am I worrying about what I want
to be when I grow up, at this age
when other people have been done
thinking about this a long time ago?
Get it together, Yoon Jin Myung.
Only average people feel lost, and such.
Stop giving yourself excuses,
saying you've lost your way, and such.
And the issue with Mom will be
resolved better than I'd expected.
The situation now is a
lot better than before.
There's only a little bit left to do now.
There's only a little
bit left to do now, but...
What the heck? Thinking about it,
everyone here is weird in their own way.
Someone here almost died, while
another person had a comatose sibling
and had something like
that happen to their mom.
And this girl is a mythomaniac.
What about her? Is there
nothing weird about her?
No. That insurance claims investigator
guy has been here a lot lately.
She looks like a really plain
person on the surface, but...
am I the only normal person here?
I heard about your dating violence
experience. Are you all right?
How could something like that happen?
I'm totally in shock!
She heard that,
instead of my confession!
I only have two days left.
Mom! Senior Jong Yeol!
I've lost my way.
Why am I worrying about something
I should've worried about in my teens?
I'm not normal, either.
You're not going to school?
I'm going to go later.
Senior.
Yeah?
Remember the nightmare
I told you that I have?
What? Oh... the one where a dog is
coming at you, but your dad saves you?
Why do you think my dad
saved me, back then?
Maybe because my dreams
and reality are totally different?
I thought about it, and...
all you did is switch your mom's
and dad's tumblers. Right?
Whatever was in those
tumblers is not your problem.
It doesn't matter if there was poison
or sleeping medication in there.
It has nothing to do with you,
since your dad did it. Right?
You're innocent, even
in the worst case scenario.
You just did that in order to protect
your mom and yourself.
What else were you supposed
to do, in that situation?
When I first heard your story,
I was a bit scared.
But this is the conclusion I came to,
after thinking about it.
So don't feel too guilty.
I'm sure everything will be okay.
How will everything be okay?
I'm sure they'll just look
into a couple of things.
And if they do,
they might find out the truth.
I'm sure that all my fearful
suspicions will be confirmed.
About the car accident,
and our house burning down...
and the reason why my brother died.
My dad used to be really
nice to us until that fire.
He was such a good dad.
That's why I have to tell them
that I was so scared.
I have to tell them that I haven't been
able to sleep properly since then.
I have to tell them that the first thing
my dad did on the day my brother died
was to wash the cup that my
brother last drank from.
In order to expose the
fact that I'm not a murderer
I have to say that my
dad was a murderer.
Is that a good thing?
My situation right now...
feels kind of like Russian roulette,
with a fully loaded gun.
This incident definitely
won't end well.
I don't know why she's being so serious.
Why were you hiding there?
I wasn't hiding.
I'm just trying to water my plants!
If she's playing Russian
roulette with a fully loaded gun
she just doesn't have
to pull the trigger at all.
You were eavesdropping!
- Sung Min.
- Geez!
No.
- Let me ask you a favor.
- Don't.
You're close with
Senior Sung Yeol, right?
No, I'm not.
Who's Sung Yeol?
You know, the Senior who
works at the Gookgwasoo (NISI)?
What's the Gookgwasoo?
Oh, is that an acronym for
Korean, Science, and Math?
They're performing an autopsy
on a body from six years ago.
How much can you find out about it?
An autopsy?
No, no. You take care of that.
He won't pick up my calls
since last April!
Figures. If he picked up your calls
after all your verbal abuse toward him
he wouldn't be a mere mortal.
He'd be Buddha himself.
I know, right? So please, Sung Min!
We're club buddies, right?
- Please?
- What's with you?
Why are you acting like
a girl, all of a sudden?
- Please, just once!
- Okay! Okay, so stop it.
Find out by 6 p.m. today.
Hey, why are you giving me a deadline?
Him and I are both busy!
I'll do it, okay? I'll do it.
So please, stop.
Punk.
Okay, I'll be back!
Eun Jae!
What brings you here, all of a sudden?
I just wanted to see you.
Oh, good! I really didn't want to work.
I'm going to use you as an excuse not to!
Why? I'll feel bad toward Mister, then!
There's just no end to this!
I don't want to work.
Let's do it together.
- Mom.
- What?
You have to be strong,
no matter what happens.
What do you mean?
Mom. You know...
It's a snake! A snake!
- Where? Where?
- Snake! Oh my gosh!
- It's a snake! Right there!
- It's not a snake, Mom.
It's not a snake, Mom.
It's not a snake!
It's not?
See? It's just a tree branch.
Oh, I was so scared!
I was so scared!
I saw a snake last time.
Ugh, I hate snakes so much!
I'm scared of them the most!
They're so, so scary!
Ugh. Ugh!
I'm scared of snakes, too.
I hate snakes, and I'm
scared of them, too!
You think you're the
only one who's scared?
What's wrong with you?
Why do you always hide behind me?
Why do I have to protect you
all the time?
You're supposed to be the one
looking out for me, and protecting me!
You're the mom!
Eun... Eun Jae.
Nothing is going through
that head of yours, is it?
You're not worried about
anything, are you?
You get to do all the good, nice things!
Why? Why should I be the only
one worried, and full of doubt?
Why do I...
Eun... Eun Jae.
You're the worst.
You are.
You're the worst person
on the face of this planet!
Eun Jae!
[Mom]
[Power Off]
Welcome!
Oh wow, I'm so shocked!
- I was so surprised before!
- Me too!
- Hi there.
- Hi.
She's that girl.
The one that got kidnapped.
Really?
Want to go get some coffee, Ye Eun?
- Yeah. Let's go!
- Yeah!
[Casebook from the Autopsy Department]
You asked me to look into it.
You know, at the NISI.
Hey, why did you give me a whole pile?
You should've weeded out the
unnecessary information!
Am I your damn slave?
Hey!
I guess humans really can
adapt to just about anything.
This is tolerable.
It's all right.
Jerk.
Is Yoon Jae home?
- No.
- Aw, where did she go?
- Try calling her.
- Her phone's off.
Where are you?
Why can't I get in touch with you?
As soon as you get my text...
What was that for?
Sheesh!
Are you home, Eun Jae?
What, are you sad that it's me?
What's your problem?
Be good to me, all right?
Things have been terrible for me lately.
It even feels like people
are looking down on me
when people laugh among themselves
across the street from me.
I feel like I'm going to end up
with a wretched fate, at this rate!
What's the matter?
- Huh?
- Did something happen to Eun Jae?
No, not exactly a
problem... well, um...
well, there is a problem, but...
I'm not at liberty to say.
What are you saying?
- Is Eun Jae here?
- What?
Um, no. Why?
Her family called. They say they
can't get in touch with her.
They said that she came home all of
a sudden, and then left in a hurry.
She went home?
She didn't go to school?
Gosh. That young lady
has so much on her mind.
Tell Eun Jae to call her family
when she gets home, okay?
Yes, I will.
Maybe something really is the matter?
Eun Jae has looked
a bit depressed lately.
And she doesn't talk much.
She's always been like that.
That's true, but...
What's going on?
What's wrong? I'm getting really
worried because you're so serious.
Remember how the insurance
claims investigator came by last time?
So when are the results of the
autopsy coming out, again?
Tomorrow.
Wow.
I mean, um, what I mean is...
I'm so in shock right now.
This is quite a serious
situation, right?
What do we do?
Hey, you idiot! Where are you?
What are you thinking, right now?
Come home, right now.
Come home, already!
What should we do?
Should we report her missing?
The cops won't do anything for us
even if we report her missing now.
What do we do, then?
You all are smart, aren't you?
Think of something!
I'm going to go and look
around the neighborhood.
- I can't just sit here idly.
- I'll come with you.
I'll go to school
and look for her there.
You're not going anywhere?
At least one of us should stay at home.
- Welcome!
- Hello.
- I'm coming in!
- What?
You're still a baby, aren't you?
Do you have something you want to say?
Um, hello.
- Would you like a tangerine...
- Hey!
Is the stuff in the washer yours?
Hurry up and hang up your clothes!
I need to use it!
Um, that is...
- You said I could eat it.
- That was one time...
Oh, I'm sorry.
To tell you the truth, I was a bit
of an outcast in high school.
Well, no. More like, I had no friends.
I wanted to make friends and go to
fun places no matter what, in college.
It's so hard for me,
that I feel like I'll die!
You could be a bit nice to me.
You could be just a
little bit nice to me.
- My situation right now feels like...
- Eun Jae!
- I'm playing Russian roulette...
- Try and kill me.
- with a fully loaded gun.
- Eun Jae!
It'll end terribly, no matter what.
I never knew how Eun Jae felt,
even though we live together.
That makes me so upset!
Hey, don't cry. It feels more
serious now that you're crying.
All right, please look over here.
Okay. Face forward!
All right, get closer.
Okay. Good.
- I bought chicken!
- Yay! Chicken!
When your brother passed away, your
family was in a bad place financially
and she collected insurance money
when your grandmother passed away, too.
There's a life insurance plan
in your name, too.
Did you know about that?
Hey, you bitch!
Do you know how worried we were?
I'm... sorry.
It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay now.
It's okay now, because you're back.
Drink it.
So? Where were you?
What? All night?
You didn't get bit by any mosquitoes?
I did.
What were you thinking?
Were you having suicidal thoughts?
Yes.
I was thinking that I should die,
and that there was no other way out.
But...
I didn't want to die, no matter
how much I thought about it.
Why would you have to die?
Yeah, live!
Don't die!
But...
if I think about what'll
happen from now on...
We don't know what'll happen,
but don't worry about it in advance.
You can deal with that issue
when the time comes.
Yeah. I'll take your side,
no matter what happens!
Me too.
I'll take your side, even if everyone
else in the world thinks you're terrible.
Man, I'm hungry.
Let's eat something!
Yeah. None of us even
had dinner last night, right?
Stay seated, Eun Jae.
We all know about it, too,
so please go ahead.
The results came out
yesterday afternoon.
We're sorry.
The toxicology report
revealed to us that...
there was no foul play involved.
Let me apologize one more time
for taking such drastic measures.
I'm sorry.
I'm truly sorry.
What happened?
How old did you say that you were then?
I was in eighth grade.
And what about when your
older brother died?
I was in fourth grade.
Are you sure that there was no
misunderstanding on your part?
I'm not sure.
Yeah. You were in your teens. You said
you couldn't sleep for a while, right?
You probably just
misunderstood something.
What the... you idiot!
Then you were worrying so much
about nothing, all this time?
Maybe the autopsy wasn't detailed?
So if there was no reagent,
they're not guilty?
Yeah.
So even the autopsy can't
reveal a lot of details, huh?
No, it is.
I looked into it through
a senior that I know
and there aren't any poisons or chemicals
that go undetected by an autopsy.
Yeah. I'm sure you just
misunderstood something.
You idiot.
This is great.
Come on, smile!
She does look pretty, on the surface.
She does have some
cuteness about her, too.
And we have good conversations.
Why aren't you going in?
Is something the matter?
Do you think...
what I did was for the best?
What do you mean?
It's nothing. I don't
want to talk about it.
Hey. Just tell me.
You'll end up telling me anyway.
Are you sick?
Hey, you're scaring me!
Do you have a fever?
Geez, why are you getting
so close? Go away.
You want to tell me, right?
You want to tell me so bad, right?
Just tell me!
I'm going to keep silent,
starting today.
Why? You're the... prettiest
when you're blabbering on.
Really?
Really, now?
Geez.
What?
I just had a super crazy thought
about you, for just a moment.
- How did you know?
- About what?
It didn't smell, or make any sounds!
Wow, you sure are impressive!
Did you just fart, too?
You should be a detective that
specializes in drug cases!
You have a gift!
This is something that
happened to a painter.
Their dad told them they were the first
one to discover their mom's corpse.
When he said that, they were able to
remember the scene from that morning
even though they'd forgotten it.
Their mother drowned to death.
And they remembered her
long hair strewn all about the water
and they remembered the
scene from that morning clearly
as if looking at a photograph.
One-day trip to Busan!
But then, their dad told them later
that he'd made a mistake.
And that someone else had actually been
the one to discover their mom's corpse.
We have to go to the night market,
so I'll try to extend the trip.
Isn't that fascinating?
Huh? Yeah.
It totally is.
We'll eat some stuff at the
night market, and drink a bit, too.
I guess people's memories
really aren't trustworthy.
Right?
Of course! You can't trust them. Yeah.
And if I pass out first...
Why are you smiling?
Just looking at you
makes me smile so much.
Isn't that fascinating?
Hey, Jong Yeol.
Hey, Yool Bin!
You got a haircut?
How does it look?
Does this look suit me?
Wow, Eun Jae.
You look even more adult-like.
Yeah. Continue on your way,
will you, Yool Bin?
See you later, Jong Yeol.
That little...
That punk. He got
really good-looking.
Right?
I don't care about mere looks.
Welcome!
[Bartleby, the Scrivener]
China?
Yes.
When will you be back, then?
I'm not sure. I have a one-month visa,
so I'll be there for at least that long.
And then I'll think about
what to do after that.
She's not asking me to come with her.
I want to do something
capricious for once in my life.
She always makes decisions on her own.
All right. You've been living way
too diligently up until now.
That's a relief.
To be honest, I felt a bit nervous.
It feels like I just jumped off
a moving train by myself.
Does that mean that I'm
a part of her future plans?
Life is long, after all.
A month isn't that long.
Um...
What do I mean to this person--
Give me your address.
I'll write you letters
if I can't call you.
Um, I live in Mapo-gu--
wait, I'll just text it to you.
Hey there.
You cut your hair.
Looking dignified suits me, right?
Isn't that an insult?
You're saying that you look old.
What kinds of gifts do guys like?
- Why, are you going to get me a gift?
- No, not you. Another guy.
Do you think they'll like cologne?
- One iced coffee.
- Yes, ma'am.
Eat up.
Here you go.
What's this?
I got my paycheck.
It's not my first paycheck, but still...
At any rate, I bought it with
money that I earned properly.
But I haven't done anything for you!
Why did you buy me this?
- Is this lotion?
- It's cologne.
Cologne?
Try smelling it.
If you were going to get me something,
you should've got me lotion.
Why did you get me something useless?
You should've bought me
undergarments, or something.
Why should I? I'm not your daughter!
Mister, do you notice
anything different about me?
Different?
What's she saying?
I don't know. It does seem
like you changed a bit, but...
I don't know.
[From: Go Doo Young
To: Jung Ye Eun]
Ye Eun.
I have no idea what I've done.
I feel like I've ruined all the
time that we spent together.
I can't even get any sleep because I
keep thinking about how pathetic I am
The time we spent together
was precious to me.
Ye Eun, you don't need to
forgive someone like me.
But... I hope that you're
happy, at the very least.
I'm praying for you every day.
I hope that you become happy.
How many of these do I have to write?
Until the victim writes back
with a positive message.
You're going to use my room, Yi Na?
Yeah. I'm moving my stuff this weekend.
Eun Jae snores, though.
Really?
You're lying!
You still fall for
these kinds of things?
It's okay. I grind my teeth.
Will you be okay, though?
How are you going to last a
month with just 1.7 million won?
- I'm sure it'll work out.
- What about after you get back?
I don't know.
When that happens...
What?
I was thinking how scary it is
to see people change.
All right, for this special occasion,
let's drink and spill secrets!
We know everything there is
to know about each other.
What other secrets could
we possibly spill?
Secrets are like onions. There's
more and more under the surface!
You start, then.
Me? You all will be
totally surprised, though.
I've still never dated anyone!
You're totally surprised, right?
No, I knew that already.
- Me too.
I'm sure everyone knows that.
Oh, come on now!
Don't you dare laugh, Senior Yoon!
You're in the same boat as me!
Why are you laughing? You're all
trying to make fun of me, aren't you?
Let's make a toast.
- To Belle Epoque!
- Yeah!
One shot!
She's taking her deposit
and going on a trip!
That's her entire fortune!
I never knew Senior Yoon was like that!
You never know with people!
Speaking of which, Senior Kang--
Stop talking about others,
and talk about yourself, Ms. Jung.
Me? There's not much
to say about me, though.
I've been eating and sleeping well,
and my weight hasn't changed, either.
It'd be nice if I lost some weight,
at a time like this.
I guess I really have an
iron-clad mind. I'm totally fine.
I don't think I'll need to
come here anymore, Doctor.
You surprised me!
What are you doing?
- We're sorry.
Please put the luggage
you'll be checking onto the belt.
Your flight will start boarding
in 40 minutes, and your seat is 80A.
- Enjoy your trip.
- Thank you.
She's going for a month!
I'm so jealous.
You should've been born
to better parents, then.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Rule of Belle Epoque:
Once more, to Belle Epoque]