Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
There are two kinds of secrets.
Secrets that you can tell,
and secrets that you can't tell.
Want me to tell you a real secret?
I have a secret that
I can never tell anyone.
To tell you the the truth...
I can see ghosts.
I killed someone.
What?
You can see what?
- Ghosts.
- Really? Since when?
To tell you the truth...
There's one over there right now.
I've killed someone before.
Oh, so I guess I did
kill them that time.
There's someone that
I wish were dead.
It's all just a lie.
I've fallen for Song Ji Won's lies
so many times already!
She's Song Ji Won,
otherwise known as "Liar Song!"
I can't assume that anything that
comes out of her mouth is true.
She totally gets a kick out
of watching me fall for her lies.
She sees ghosts?
Yeah, right.
She might as well tell me that
Song Joong Ki is her older cousin!
It's all a lie. It must be a lie.
Damn it, I'm actually scared!
It didn't scare me at all when she
told me, so why am I scared now?
Look at her, sleeping so damn peacefully.
Damn sinner!
And here I am, unable
to sleep because of her!
All right, stop this already.
Let's go to sleep. It's all a lie. Sleep!
I'm not scared at all. Let's sleep.
Sleep is engulfing my body... sleep.
I'm tired. Let's go to sleep.
What the hell?
Why isn't she breathing?
Is she awake?
What is she doing?
There was a sound just now, right?
Is she moving? Why? To where?
Should I confirm it for myself?
I can't! What if she's looking
directly at me?
I'll pretend that I'm sleeping.
I'm asleep! I'm asleep!
My feet are poking out!
They're in danger! My feet!
What do I do?
God, save me!
What the hell are you doing?
Oh my gosh.
- Give me some of that.
- Come down and take it yourself!
Stop it!
Damn it. I knew I was
craving something sweet.
[LIE]
[EPISODE 2: IS THIS
UNDERWEAR YOURS?]
I knew I was craving
something sweet!
What the hell is this?
What? What is it?
- It's a cockroach!
- Again?
Damn it! We set up
traps for them, too!
Why was this off by itself? Sheesh.
Damn it!
Honey, are you still sleeping?
Yeah.
Did you drink last night?
What are you talking about? No.
Hurry and get up. Hurry! Get up!
Hurry! Get up!
What? What is it?
This is yours, right?
How could you leave
something like this behind?
What is it?
If they know you came into our place
I'll get kicked out!
- What are you talking about?
- You know, the other day.
When my new roommate moved in!
You don't remember that?
Ow!
Oh, that day?
I think you left this behind while you
rushed, and left this in my laundry.
- This isn't mine.
- Really? It really isn't yours?
- Are you sure?
- I don't wear boxers.
I only wear this kind of underwear.
I wouldn't have freaked out so
much if I'd known that it wasn't yours.
Whose could it be, then?
Who brought a guy into our place?
- Get over here.
- I can't.
- Why not?
- I'm on my period.
Then why did you come over?
What?
It's because you're so pretty.
Coming here all dolled up like this,
and then telling me that we can't...
You can't do that to me!
Come over here.
- We can't!
- Ah.
Stop it!
To tell you the truth...
I can see ghosts.
There's one over there right now.
You're back?
- Are you the only one here?
- Yes.
Where did everyone else go?
Senior Yoon went to her part-time job,
and Senior Kang went to work out.
And Senior Ji Won
said she's going on a date.
Again?
I'm Song Ji Won, a junior
majoring in Media Studies.
- Hello.
I'm Park Hae Ra, and I'm also a
junior majoring in the same thing.
- Hello.
And I'm Kim Na Jung, also a
junior majoring in the same thing.
- Hello.
- Um, where do you live?
- Did you go to Bangi High School?
Hey, we're all the same age,
so let's speak informally.
I live in Yeonnamdong, I didn't
graduate from Bangi High School.
And my ideal type of man
is Song Joong Ki.
Nice to meet you all!
She goes on dates and group dates, day
after day. She's crazy for a boyfriend.
She said that she'll get a boy, no matter
what, even if she has to sell her soul.
Geez, she has such a crude
way of putting things.
Figures. Having no action until you're
22 years old would make anyone restless.
At this rate, she could end
up as a 100-year-old virgin.
You should be on the move, too.
You shouldn't be home on a weekend!
It's okay. Senior Yoon
is still single, too.
So, are you going to look to
her as your inspiration?
You're going to live without
any spice in your life
and live without dating or having
sex, like a total wallflower?
Don't do that.
You can't call that living.
That's merely existing.
Oh yeah. That's not what's
important right now, though.
I found this hanging
on the balcony.
That could only mean that
a man was here.
But, why did you have it in your purse?
What?
Well, I was doing some
preliminary investigating, that's why.
What's the most important
rule at Belle Epoque?
No guys allowed in here.
And this means that someone
broke that important rule!
But, why did they leave
their underwear here?
Are you an idiot? Do you think they left
it behind because they took a crap in it?
They definitely did excrete something
from their body, but it wasn't that.
Who do you think it was?
- Well, I'm not sure.
- Who else could it be?
It's definitely Senior Kang.
She said so herself that she's
currently seeing a lot of different men.
And judging from her vibe, I feel
like she does one night stands, too.
One night stands?
What's that?
You're not really
from Yesang, right?
You actually lived in a
monastery all your life, right?
You know, sleeping with someone
on the day that you met them!
Really?
There are people who
really do that kind of thing?
Yeah! Exhibit A, Senior Kang!
It's not like she was
an Olympic athlete.
It's not like she's trying to decrease
her record by a tenth of a second.
All she's doing is jogging
around the neighborhood
so why does she dress like that?
She could just wear sweats
and run!
Are you all right?
Um, yes, I'm fine.
She's doing all of that
to try and seduce men.
That girl is seriously...
She may call it pheromones or something,
but that's definitely not it.
It's clear that she only gets all those
men because of the way she dresses.
Honestly, she's not
even that pretty.
No, she's pretty.
Yeah, she is, but she's not
like, super crazy pretty.
She's just an average
amount of pretty.
Compare her to me, you,
or Song Ji Won.
It's not like she's like, ridiculously
prettier than the rest of us.
- Let's look for evidence.
- What?
Senior Kang has her own room.
So if she had a man here
there will definitely be some
evidence of that, in there.
What kind of evidence?
You'll know when you see it.
And what are you going to do
if you do find evidence?
"RULE ONE OF BELLE EPOQUE: If you bring a
man in here, you'll get kicked out."
You want to kick her out?
She could also pay a fine.
That's a guy's voice, right?
What are you doing?
Why are you here?
Why are you asking me why
I'm in front of my own room?
Who's the man in your room?
Man?
You're Jack the Ripper!
Is that the man that you
were talking about?
You left your TV on again?
Senior Yoon will have a fit
if she finds out!
That's why you have to keep
this on the down low, okay?
I knew that it was strange that
I couldn't understand any of it.
That's that, but... you
brought a man here, right?
This wasn't me.
Hey, come on. It totally was!
This is a knockoff! The men that I see
wouldn't wear cheap stuff like this.
"Men?" As in, plural?
- Yeah, "men!"
- Hey! Stop it!
Also, why would I do that here?
It'd be a pain to clean up afterwards.
I'd much rather go to a motel.
Wow, I bet your mom would be so
proud if she heard you say that!
What the hell?
So it was a knockoff?
Then, who could it have been?
Maybe it was Senior Yoon?
- Nah, no way.
- Why not?
That's because she simply
has no time for stuff like that.
And Senior Yoon has no interest in men.
She doesn't?
Would a person who does,
go around looking like her?
Makeup? As if. She doesn't even
wash her face sometimes!
Do you know why Senior Yoon
is growing her hair out?
It's so that she doesn't have
to go to the hair salon!
Isn't styling your hair into a ponytail
at 28 years old a bit much?
Also, Senior Yoon doesn't have
any brightly colored clothing.
That's so that you can't tell
that they haven't been washed.
And she wears the same
pair of shoes, rain or shine.
There's even a legend that those
sneakers were once white!
Just look at the state she's in. Do you
think any man would be attracted to that?
Well, that's because she's busy.
I'm telling you, Senior Yoon
has no feminine qualities.
- But...
- Asexual reproduction suits her better.
Just like an amoeba.
But psychologically speaking, there are
guys who are into those types of women.
There are men who think,
"I'll make a lady of you!"
Figures. That's just like the character
from the manga, "Candy Candy."
Safe!
You're not late.
Cool off a bit before you go inside.
You still have five minutes left.
- We've got this!
- Yes, sir...
- Fire!
Senior Yoon definitely
isn't the one.
You know as well as I do that
she has no free time whatsoever!
So how could she have
time to sleep with a guy
when she barely has
any time to sleep?
That's true, but...
It's more likely that it's Song Ji Won
than Senior Yoon.
She goes on dates every day, so who
knows? She could have gotten lucky once.
She can be unexpectedly
daring at times.
- What do you like?
- Anything is fine.
Please let me know
when you've decided.
- Okay.
Did you all order?
What, you still haven't?
Give that here.
I'll order for you guys.
Fish cake stew. Stir-fried bean sprouts.
And chili shrimp.
Their fish cake stew
is to die for!
And they give you a large portion
for the stir-fried bean sprouts.
And the chili shrimp is really spicy.
You're okay with spicy food, right?
- Yeah.
Okay. And then, one bottle of soju
and three bottles of beer.
We can order more if we
need more. Okay?
- Yeah.
Excuse me!
I'm taking more alcohol!
Please add that to our tab!
Why aren't you guys talking?
Come on, drink up! Drink...
Let's make a soju and beer
cocktail! Let's do this!
All right. Point your chopstick
of love at the person
who you want to spend the
rest of your twenties with!
Let's do it on the count of three!
One, two, three!
Yeah, it must be Song Ji Won.
- If you want any, tell me now.
- No, I'm not having any!
I just had a snack
not too long ago.
You're really not going to
have any, right?
I had a lot of fun today.
- Oh, me too.
- How are you getting home?
The Bus! Number 7027!
Or the 7501!
Oh really, I'm going that way.
Well, bye, then!
Damn it.
I thought you said that you
weren't having any!
I tried, but... this is your fault!
How could you eat something like this
in front of someone who's dieting?
Why the hell did she say that she
wasn't going to have any, then?
She ate all of it,
and I only got three bites!
Hey!
This is yours, right?
Spill! You brought a
guy here, didn't you?
You two did all sorts of dirty stuff,
and then he left this here, right?
What the hell kind of
nonsense is that?
I wish there was a guy
that I could do that with.
We laughed together
and had a great time!
He laughed so loudly every time
I said something, and only talked to me!
So, why? Why is it that only
the restaurant owner likes me?
I guess it didn't work out for
her this time, either.
What if it's you?
What?
You just turned 20 years old.
You're an adult now.
So naturally, you're at the age when
you want to do all kinds of things.
I heard that girls who look innocent like
you are different than they seem!
- "You trust me, right, Yoon Jae?"
- Stop it.
"It's all right.
This is how adults play."
Why is it that everyone has to
tease me at least once a day?
Everyone? Who else does this to you?
You don't eat peanuts? Why not?
Just because.
- Or, were you saving them for later?
- No.
- Did they go bad?
Did you drop these?
Hey, what do you
think you're looking at?
What?
- Wow.
- Um... that's...
- I can't believe you.
- No...
Hey, even if you want me that badly,
this is sexual harassment!
- No, that's not it.
- Unbelievable.
You really are different
than you seemed.
How embarrassing.
I don't even want to go to
school because of him!
Figures. You just have
a face that says, "kick me!"
Aren't those boxers
your boyfriend's?
I already went and confirmed it.
My honey only wears briefs.
So that means that there was a reason
why you needed to go and confirm.
What are you talking about?
And the fact that you took them
out of your purse is a bit suspicious.
Hey, that's because I...
Song! Ask the ghost
who brought a guy here.
Do I look like a priestess?
How am I supposed to talk to ghosts?
You can't? What the hell? So it doesn't
matter if you can see ghosts?
If that were possible, I'd ask them
when I'd get a boyfriend, first!
Ghosts should tell people things, like
winning lottery numbers. Right?
She's obviously lying
about everything.
You don't see ghosts,
you lying fake!
But I do know who the liar
among us is, though.
Who?
Senior Kang.
How do you know that?
- I can see it.
- Yeah, yeah, whatever.
So you can see lies, and ghosts,
and other people's sins, too?
People all have auras.
A color of sorts that they exude
outside of their bodies.
Forget it. I'm not telling you.
Wait, so what's an aura?
The aura of people who
lie are darker colors.
And Senior Kang's aura is like that.
You really believe that lie,
you innocent thing?
Yes.
Oh, geez. This is why people
always tease you. Sheesh.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Song! Yoon Jae!
Come over here! Hurry...
- Hurry and get out here!
- What?
Look! Look!
You saw us?
- He had a hell of a nice car.
- What does he do for a living?
- Hold old is he?
- How long have you been seeing him?
Tell us everything, right now!
Hey, come on, now.
You can't go just yet.
- What are you curious about?
- Everything!
- What does he do for a living?
- He's a dentist.
- Really?
- Damn it.
- How old is he?
- 38 years old, I think?
Or 39 years old?
Wow, he's totally old, then!
His wife and kids live overseas.
- He's married?
- Yep.
Am I just old-fashioned?
Is it weird to be surprised about this?
I was surprised, too.
But you're old-fashioned.
Wow. I can't believe some
people live like this.
I wish that someone would just
drop a bomb here, or something!
So that people who have boyfriends and
those who don't can all just die!
What?
Senior Kang is such an honest person,
so I don't think she's the type to lie.
Right? See, I told you.
Damn that Song!
She's such a damn liar!
[I HAVE SOMETHING I MUST TELL YOU.
PLEASE, PICK UP THE PHONE.]
All right, take your ingredients
and take a seat.
All right. The dish we'll make together
today is mushroom casserole.
All right, regarding this proposal..
How about we pick topic four,
"silver spoon versus 'dirt' spoons"
and tackle that subject head-on?
We're facing discrimination,
even as college students!
Oh!
I hate it. I'm pulling
the plug on that idea.
Has anyone prepared
any other topics that we can tackle?
You're home?
I feel like I'm going to die.
You must be so happy. You don't have to
worry about employment and stuff yet.
Play as much as you want,
while you still can.
Play hard when you play.
Those rosy days will soon
be gone so quickly.
Happy day will be gone very soon.
I bet it's going to be even worse
when we're seniors!
I'm sure that being a senior
has its own charms.
Just look at Senior Kang.
She doesn't care about her
grades, or getting certifications.
Figures. Senior Kang is so lucky.
She has a job lined up for her.
Why? What does Senior Kang's father do?
Apparently, he runs a
tableware factory.
Really? I heard that he runs a
factory that makes wet wipes.
Well, at any rate,
he does something like that.
Her family is totally loaded.
She must be so happy. She wears
designer stuff from head to toe
and gets her own room.
Don't compare yourself to her.
At least you're not like Senior Yoon.
That's true.
Should I ask Senior Kang to get me
a job at her dad's company?
Me too!
[TWO MEN WHOSE COMMUNICATION
TRANSCENDS TIME]
[PLEASE TAKE CARE OF MY REFRIGERATOR!
EVERY MONDAY AT 9:30 P.M.]
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
How is it that it's taking you longer
and longer to put on makeup?
What are you talking about?
Hello.
Oh, I just woke up.
What should I do?
So, how late are you going to be?
Where are you? I think
I'll be about 30 minutes late.
Oh, that's good. I was
going to be late, too.
I think I'll be there around
the same time as you.
I ended up lying again.
I pretended that I was late
even though I came early.
I pretended that I didn't want to see him
even though I want to see him so badly.
Pretending that I didn't put any effort
into my makeup, when I totally did.
Acting this way and that.
I feel like a fool somehow.
I'm sure that Senior Kang
wouldn't act this way.
[OOPS, I JUST WOKE UP.
WHAT SHOULD I DO?]
Crazy bastard.
And if it were Senior Yoon...
[OOPS, I JUST WOKE UP.
WHAT SHOULD I DO?]
I'll wait exactly
ten minutes for you.
Why the hell are you late?
You buy me food, then!
And the alcohol too, obviously!
I'm going to order
something really expensive!
It's okay. Take your time.
Am I the only weird one?
What are you doing here?
I thought you were going to be late.
So why are you here?
Oh, I just got here,
but I got thirsty.
Oh.
Wow, the weather's great today!
You... don't know what
day today is, do you?
- Of course I do.
- You do? Really?
Of course. I got
you a present, too.
Wow!
It looks nice, right?
Do you like it?
Yeah. I totally do.
And my present?
Where's my present?
Oh, your present?
Hold on.
Oh no, I left it at home.
Let's go to get it after we eat.
Here.
Sorry, I couldn't wrap it
because I didn't have time.
It's what's inside that
counts, though, right?
- You're not going to open it?
- Huh? Yeah.
Oh... it's perfume.
What, do you not like it?
No, I do.
- Is it because it's cheap?
- No. It's not like that.
Thanks.
I'll buy you something
better next time.
Something expensive.
- Do you want to use this?
- What is it?
A makeup store opened
up in front of our school.
It's a free handout since
they just opened.
Why are they giving out
something like this?
He's still there.
He was there when I went to
the convenience store before, too.
How many hours has
he been there, already?
Oh!
Please accept these flowers, Miss.
How sad.
He waited so long
to see Senior Kang!
I wish I could experience
that once in my life!
You like that? I'd hate that!
I'd totally hate that.
Really? I'm kind of jealous.
You're jealous of a guy who waits for
you in front of your house, with flowers?
This isn't 1988.
How old fashioned.
Ugh, it's so tacky!
I'd probably not like the guy as much
if they acted like that toward me.
Really?
You don't know what kind
of person I am, though.
Why do you keep saying that you don't
like me, even though you don't know me?
Do you know me? How well do you know
me that you're saying that you like me?
We're both judging each other
based on outward appearances.
And I'm not interested
in you at all.
And I won't be in the future, either.
So don't ever do anything
like this again.
And don't you dare call me again!
Oh me, oh my. What is love, I wonder?
Oh yeah. What did
you get as a gift?
What?
Is today some special day?
It's their one-year anniversary!
She quit drinking coffee for a month so
she could buy her boyfriend his gift!
I was completely shocked.
So, what did your honey get you?
A purse? A ring?
Why are you so nosy?
I want to become happy
vicariously through you!
Come on, show me!
- Oh no. He forgot, didn't he?
- No!
He planned a trip for us this
weekend. Two days, one night.
You're so lucky.
Where are you going?
Chuncheon.
Then why do you have that
kind of expression?
You look like you got blown off.
Because he didn't even ask me about
my schedule before planning this.
I'm so damn jealous of you.
Talk about first world problems!
What are you going to
do for two whole days?
You're going to this
and that, right?
- Right?
- Stop it, already!
What's wrong with you?
All you ever talk about is sex!
Are you a pervert?
Hey, I was just joking
around a bit...
It may seem like a joke to you, but
it feels like harassment to me!
You've been saying a lot of messed up
stuff lately, without thinking.
You even said last time that you
think that Senior Kang is lying!
You said that she has
a liar's aura about her!
Damn it!
Um, what I meant was...
Wow, that's quite impressive.
How did you know that I was lying?
I'm sorry about before.
I went too far.
I'm sorry, too.
Cheer up and have a good trip.
By the way, Chuncheon's stir-fried spicy
chicken is available as takeout!
Forget it!
What time are you leaving?
How long are you going to
continue doing this?
Eh?
Hehehehehe.
Stop it, already. Hey!
Madame Jung is making her exit!
Come on out, everyone!
- Sheesh!
- She's heading out!
Stop it!
She says she's going to Chuncheon.
She must be so happy, right?
She's going with her love, after all! But
shall I tell you something more shocking?
They can spend an entire
night together, on their own!
Stop it, already!
Okay, okay. Bye, now!
Oh, I'm so nervous!
I'll be back soon, everyone!
Have fun.
Oh, wait, wait!
This isn't much money, but...
use this to buy wine
and scented candles.
And buy some essential oils if
you have any money left over!
Sheesh!
I'll be going, then!
I'm really leaving now!
- Bye.
- Bye!
You better have fun, okay?
Let's go!
- Let's go!
Bye!
My 1,000 won. My 1,000 won.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
You need a light?
No, I'm trying to give it up.
I don't have a lighter, anyway.
Did you enjoy that?
You almost killed me!
You idiot.
Oh yeah. You used three million
won last month, didn't you?
What?
You used way too much!
Sorry. My friend was in
the hospital this month, so...
Limit your spending to
two million won, okay?
It'll be too rough on me
if you spend more than that.
Okay.
Mister.
Look at me.
Is it obvious that I'm a liar?
Figures. Living life itself
is a lie.
Yeah?
What are you doing?
Drinking.
With who?
Seung Chul and Yong Min.
- Where are you right now?
- A sauna.
- With who?
- My friends.
Okay. Well, have fun!
- Okay. You too.
- Drink up!
Damn it, I'm so jealous.
I'm sure they have been
going at it for hours now.
I'm sure they're doing all sorts of crazy
positions that you only see in porn.
What's with that expression of yours?
You look like you just got
mooned by a pervert!
Is it that obvious?
I've been crazy receptive to
other people's vibes lately.
I can't even study properly!
I'm not sure whether I'm having
dirty thoughts because I can't study.
Or if it's because of my dirty
thoughts that I can't study.
I even had a wet dream last night!
In my dream, I...
Stop it! Seriously!
Sheesh.
If you don't want to hear it, never mind.
It's a really great story, though.
- Senior.
- What? You want to hear about it, right?
In my dream last night,
I was in the rain...
No. Not that.
You know the ghost that
you said was in the cupboard?
What does it look like?
You're curious about the
gender of the ghost, too?
What?
Why are all of you curious about that?
Senior Kang asked me about that,
and so did Senior Yoon.
- Senor Yoon did, too?
- Yeah.
I guess all of you have a ghost
that comes to mind.
Oh, then...
I guess I did kill
them that time, after all.
There's someone that I wish were dead.
So?
- So... what?
- Is the ghost a boy or a girl?
You know, the thing is,
Ms. Customer...
Whenever a ghost is mentioned, people
think of ones in folktales and legends
but that's not the case at all.
Ghosts are more like smoke that's
been compacted into a ball.
They don't have any human features.
Now, are you sure you don't
want to hear about my dream?
It's totally erotic and interesting!
Hm?
I didn't know you had it
in you to be so cold.
[MOM]
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Hey. Is this funny to you?
Do you have that little
to do with your life?
I'm going to put your
phone number online
so you can feel the same
way that I do now, you bastard.
- You're home late.
- Yeah.
[24-HOUR SAUNA]
[PLACES WORTH VISITING IN CHUNCHEON]
[GO TO NAMI ISLAND!]
Lies may be similar to makeup.
Just like one puts on makeup
to hide their naked face
people use lies to hide the truth.
- What are you doing?
- Reading.
What book?
"JUSTICE: What's the Right Thing to Do?"
[FIFTY SHADES OF GREY]
There's no way I'd drink
in broad daylight!
I'm taking extra English lessons
today, so I'll be a bit late.
Yeah, I'm going on my
business trip right now.
See you tomorrow.
I tell more and more lies
as my makeup gets thicker.
Since when did I start feeling that going
out with no makeup on was embarrassing?
Since when did I become
so ashamed of the truth?
Yeah. The truth is pathetic, sad,
and pitiful, just like that.
Because it's truly painful when your
earnestness is rejected by someone else.
Acting cool, and acting as if
you like the other person less...
and acting like you're
just joking.
I'm home.
Oh, why are you home so early?
I thought you'd be back late at night.
I have school tomorrow,
and I'm tired.
Wow, you sure look worn out.
Where did you go in Chuncheon?
- We went to Nami Island.
- Did you like it?
It was okay. There were
a lot of people there.
Oh, Senior Yoon, did I
wake you? I'm sorry.
No, it was about time
that I woke up, anyway.
Senior Yoon, you have a nosebleed!
Oh.
- Why is this in the trash?
- Is that yours?
- Yeah.
- What?
You have a boyfriend, Senior?
Wait, am I the only one who
doesn't have a man?
No, Granny Landlord
gave this to me.
She told me to hang
it on our window
since a weird man keeps
hanging around here.
Oh.
He could try something rash if he knows
that only girls live here, after all.
So she told me to hang it up
in a very visible spot.
- Can I have some, too?
- Yep!
That guy is following
Senior Kang around.
Really?
I guess we can throw out
those boxers, then.
- Doesn't it taste good?
- It's okay.
I made it.
You were wrong!
What are you talking about?
You said that those boxers
were Senior Kang's!
When did I say that?
I said that she was lying,
not that the boxers were hers.
That's the same damn thing.
Oh, damn it.
She's such a liar!
Why did you take such a long nap?
I guess I was really tired.
And why is that, exactly?
What were you doing?
Sheesh, seriously!
Let go of me.
Let go, right now!
I told you, I don't like you!
Please, Ms. Yi Na!
Listen to me!
- Song! Eun Jae!
- What?
- Hurry up! Big trouble!
- Hurry!
- What is it?
- Get out of my way.
- You know how I feel!
I thought you said that you
graduated from a good college.
So you must be smart. So why
can't you understand my words?
I don't like you.
I'll like you more to
compensate for that, then.
Geez, you're driving me insane.
What does that have to do with anything?
You're making a mistake.
You're ruining yourself!
- I'll save you.
- Who the hell are you to save me?
What gives you the damn right?
Just go and save yourself.
Go home.
This is my final warning. If you do
this again, I'll really call the cops.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine. Go in.
What you're doing now
is called prostitution!
Those men don't really love you.
- Stop it.
- They're buying you with money!
Why must a beautiful person
like you do something like that?
You're a precious person!
I'll help you!
I don't know what your past
is like, but I'll save you!
You can start a
new life for yourself!
Hey, you son of a bitch.
Who the hell do you think you are
to tell me how to live my life?
I'm the one who made the decision
to sell my own goddamn body!
So why the hell are you
bitching about it to me?
You little shit.
Hey!
Why the hell are you
bitching about it to me?
- Calm down!
- You son of a bitch!
- Senior!
- Ms. Yi Na!
- Senior Kang!
Ms. Yi Na!
Wow.
He said prostitution, right?
Yeah. He said that men have
been buying Senior Kang with money.
- Wow.
- Yeah. Wow.
I thought she said that her dad has
a factory that makes tableware.
I told you, it's a
wet wipes factory!
At any rate, I guess she lied
about her family being rich.
Why would she need to do that
if they were actually rich?
There are plenty of girls
with sugar daddies.
Why would guys buy her designer bags
and give her money for free, though?
There's no way. It's clearly
a give-and-take situation.
She's basically accepting money for sex.
In other words, she's just a hooker.
A hooker.
It's not... like I said
anything that's untrue.
Senior Kang is the one
in the wrong here!
And I don't like that she's been lying
to us up until now, either.
Oh.
The aura of people who
lie are darker colors.
And Senior Kang's aura
is just like that.
To tell you the truth...
I can see ghosts.
Song!
You really do see ghosts, don't you?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
[AGE OF YOUTH]
He's a senior of mine from my major,
but he keeps on bothering me.
Do people get bullied
in college, too?
Don't think of it as being embarrassing.
No matter what I do, I'm the best!
Hello.
Want to go for round three?
- I'm disgusting?
- This is my cup.
My mouth seems dirty to you?
Hey!
Do you know each other?
Are they your friend?
No, they're not friends.
They're just my house mates.
There's an easier way to live life.
Get yourself a boyfriend.
Want me to introduce you to one?
No, thanks.
Your jealousy smells rotten.
[CAN WE ASK YOU HOW
MUCH YOU WEIGH NOW?]
Um... 47 kilograms.
[YOU SEEM TO WEIGH MORE THAN THAT.]
I'm being honest!
If I weigh myself in the morning with
all my clothes off, I'm 47 kilograms!
[IT SEEMS LIKE YOU ENVY KANG YI NA.]
Me?
Why would I envy her?
What, the fact that she has big boobs?
The fact that she's tall?
That's nothing. Sheesh.
[TELL US ABOUT YOUR BOYFRIEND.]
My Honey?
Well, it's been two years
since we first met.
[YOUR FRIENDS DON'T SEEM TO LIKE HIM.]
That's because they don't know him.
My Honey is actually
a great person!
[HE'S OFTEN LATE, CANCELS FREQUENTLY,
ONLY EVER WANTS TO HAVE SEX.]
[AND GIVES YOU SAMPLES AS GIFTS.
YOU STILL THINK HE'S A GOOD PERSON?]
That's... all guys are like that!
He's really good to me,
when he's being nice!