Subtitles by DramaFever
[Kang Yi Na]
We love you, Valued Customer!
Allow me to process your payment.
Oh, wait.
Please use this instead.
[Hwang Dae Jung]
I live an easy life.
And that's all thanks to
my youth and looks.
However, people scorn
those who live easy lives.
I don't get it.
Is there something wrong
with living an easy life?
Does it mean that you're living properly
just because you're living a hard life?
One cannot know what's truly right and
wrong in life, unless you live twice.
This is just how life is.
That's just how life is.
That's just how it is.
[I searched for love like a madman all
my life, but I've never loved myself.]
[Episode 3: I've Never Once Loved Myself
#Rotten Roots]
I'm not trying to brag, but men
always flock to me, wherever I go.
Please enjoy.
And quite unexpectedly so.
Or maybe I should say,
in general.
Honestly, they're a bit
too clingy sometimes.
- Um, excuse me.
- You're here early?
Yeah, because I missed you, Honey!
One Americano, please.
There was so much traffic! I was driving
so fast because I wanted to see you
but my battery totally died!
This man is my lover.
I met this man six months ago.
Can I get you a drink?
Why?
Because I've taken a liking to you.
I liked his confidence.
I have two other lovers
besides this man.
Is Ms. Kang Yi Na here?
Right over here.
Um, are you Ms. Kang Yi Na,
by any chance?
Yes, I am.
- Here's a flower delivery for you.
- For me?
Yes.
- Ms. Kang Yi Na, right?
- Again?
Please, take it.
Who is this from?
My second lover approached me
as if he really wanted to date me.
I liked my third lover
because he was right to the point.
He'd been supporting his wife and child
who lived overseas for five years
and he was a dentist.
Can I buy you a drink?
There are my three current lovers.
Oh, and this guy is just a friend.
He works in the same industry as I do,
so he's kind of like a coworker.
Wow, what a nice view!
I'm a fake lover for these men.
All of us involved know
that this is a fake relationship.
One way to put it is that I've been
hired to play a certain role by each man.
And what I get in exchange
is spending money.
- That was such a good shot!
- What are you talking about?
Just wait until you get to my age.
This kind of shot can be considered good!
There's no way. It's clearly
a give-and-take situation.
She's basically accepting money for sex.
In other words, she's a prostitute.
That's right.
I'm a prostitute.
Prostitute...
It's something I
was definitely aware of
but it really hits home
to hear it said by someone else.
This is where I find my lovers.
Three is a good number, but...
Spending three million won is too much.
Let's limit it to two million
a month, all right?
It's getting hard on me.
But this guy keeps
bringing up money.
It's time for me to move on
to someone else.
I have certain criteria that must be
met when I accept new lovers.
- Oh, you're here?
- Yes. Here.
Oh, thank you.
He's way too old for me.
Work is work, but one must
take a bit of pleasure in their work.
[1.2 million won]
[1.5 million won]
[1.45 million won]
[1.1 million won]
[5.5 million won]
[12 million won]
Oh no, he's dangerous.
I dated a guy like him once
when I was naive.
In some ways, a lot of what we get
paid is hazard pay, in my line of work.
When you share a bed with a man
you don't know, anything can happen.
[23,000 won]
[15,000 won]
[10,000 won]
[25,000 won]
[8,000 won]
But what's most important is a man's
"economic prowess," per se.
There will always be issues with guys
who have to save money
to give you an allowance.
And there's living proof right there.
Do you know how much that costs?
200,000 won!
The Madame of this establishment
met a man seven years ago.
The man gave her a gift
every time she saw him.
A necklace. A bag.
Cosmetics.
And then, the cops came to look for her.
The man was a banker, and he'd
been embezzling his customers' money.
When he got out of jail after
a year and two months
he didn't have a job or a family left.
Would you like to order something, sir?
Oh, yes. Anything's fine.
Something like whiskey.
Would you like it neat, or on the rocks?
Anything's fine.
I'll give it to you neat, then.
I don't always snag myself a lover on
the same day I find myself needing one.
I'm sure it's like that for everyone.
Really? Oh my gosh.
You know, Senior Kang is also lying
about the fact that she's in college.
I asked someone in her major's school
newspaper to look into it for me.
They told me that there isn't a
girl named Kang Yi Na in that major.
How could she do that?
What's even real about her, then?
I wonder if her name is
actually even Kang Yi Na?
You know, there was a movie like this.
You know, that girl who
lied about everything.
- "Helpless!"
- Yeah, that's right!
Oh my gosh, I have goosebumps.
Speaking of which...
when she gets back she looks different
from when she left.
What do you mean?
Um... her makeup,
and her overall feel.
Why? What was her makeup like?
Um...
I'm heading out!
I'm home!
- I'm not sure.
- What the hell?
Figures. She didn't even know Piketty
when she's supposedly a Business major.
What's "Piketty?"
You know, Thomas Piketty.
The economist.
Hey, how is a Nutrition major like me
supposed to know an economist?
You don't know them either, right?
"Capital in the Twenty-First Century."
You're such an idiot.
You're a fake too, aren't you?
If she's not a student,
she's not doing this for tuition
and it doesn't seem like she's
sending money to her family, either.
So why is she doing this, then?
Probably to live an easier life.
Well, yeah.
Figures.
I hear that there's a lot of college
students doing that, nowadays.
People who accept money
for being someone's lover.
Oh my. Oh my.
What is wrong with this world?
I sounded like a middle-aged
woman just now, didn't I?
Why are you so surprised over nothing?
You little--
Senior Yoon!
You know, apparently Senior
Kang isn't a college student!
Really?
Song asked her friend
and they said that there's nobody
by that name in that major.
Isn't that ridiculous?
How could she do that to us?
Huh? Why isn't she saying anything?
It's because she has a poker face.
I'm sure she's surprised, too.
She should save her poker face
for when she's playing poker!
Why does she have to go
and use it all the time?
What's wrong?
What's up?
Do souls have colors, too?
You said that you knew Senior Kang was
lying because of the color of her aura.
That's right!
Do ghosts have colors, too?
What color is it?
Grey.
Oh.
It's depressed, and sad.
That's the feeling I get from it.
Why? Why is it sad and depressed?
Beats me.
Senior Yoon!
Does the spirit hear all of
the things that we say?
I'm not sure.
Did something happen at this house
a long time ago?
For example, did someone die here?
Or... did they get murdered?
No.
What could it be, then?
I guess it followed you here, Eun Jae.
Right? I mean, it apparently only
appeared here not too long ago.
And it was after you came here.
Do you know anyone who's dead now?
It might be someone who's not dead yet.
What do you mean?
You only become a ghost if you're dead.
What about a brain-dead person?
Where do the souls of
brain-dead people go?
Song.
Are you sleeping?
Nope.
You feel uneasy, right?
- Huh?
- I'm talking about Senior Kang.
I'm sure she sleeps with
tons of different guys.
If she gets some sort of STD...
some of them are contagious.
Yeah, that's true.
Yeah?
What is it?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Why do you come here, Mister?
You don't like you're used
to places like these.
Yes, that's true.
A place like this
doesn't suit a guy like me.
You're similar to me, then.
I have a place where I don't
quite fit into right now, too.
They treat me like
I have AIDS, or something!
It's funny, but it also pisses me off.
I'm wondering if I should maybe
just fight with them about it.
It's not like I don't get where
they're coming from, though.
But still, it makes me feel like crap!
But, um...
is it all right to tell me
these sorts of things?
What?
The fact that I have sugar daddies?
Well, who cares? It's not
like I'd date you anyway.
Oh, did you want to date me?
Um, no.
No.
What, you don't like nasty
little insects like me?
Why are you talking about
yourself like that?
Because I get treated like one.
So, what are you going to do now?
Are you going to move out?
I have to move out if they tell me to!
But honestly, why do I have to move out?
What did I do wrong?
You lied to them.
That's all?
It's not like they tell the
truth all the time, either!
If anything, they're even worse than me!
They spend tons of money, saying
they're using it for cram school!
They say they're doing
field work with their professor
but go on a trip with their lover.
And my clothes, my shoes, my makeup...
They use my stuff as much as
they want to, and then lie about it!
If you put things this way,
I really don't lie that much!
I told my customers too,
that I'm not a college student.
But the other kids who
do the same work as I do
all lie and say they're
college students.
It's easier to make money that way.
If you put things this way,
I really am the paragon of honesty!
Hey, you're pissing me off.
You just laughed at me, didn't you?
No, I didn't.
You know, I don't lie, if only
because it's such a hassle.
Lying is such a hassle.
So why did you lie to those girls?
Was there a reason you wanted to live
there, even if you had to lie so much?
Just a moment.
Hello?
Oh, Honey!
Where are you right now?
Oh, in front of the bank?
I'll come out now. Okay.
Can't we eat first?
You're hungry?
You should've told me sooner!
I don't want to do anything
because I'm hungry.
I think I'd perform really well
if I had something to eat first.
- Damn it.
- Please?
We'll be back later.
- What do you want to eat?
- Steak!
- Here you are.
- Thank you.
- Please enjoy.
I'll give you the wine list
and the menu.
Did you see the bag that
the girl at Table 7 has?
It's from Ortega.
It's a high-end brand.
We'd have to work
500 hours to afford it.
Damn, it pisses me off.
Why aren't you eating?
You're the one who wanted to eat.
Sorry. It's not that good, right?
No, it tastes good.
Hey, stop right there!
Stop right there!
- Hey, stop right there!
Hey, stop! Where the hell
are you running to?
How dare a whelp like you seduce
another woman's husband?
- You enjoy living like that?
- You little slut!
- You think your face--
- Stop it.
I told you to stop it!
- What's it to you?
- If you continue, I'll call the cops.
Hey, do you even know
what kind of girl this bitch is?
I don't care if she stole your husband.
You're being a nuisance to our business.
And stop talking down to me.
Why, you little--
Why, I ought to--
- Damn it.
- Let's just go.
- You're dead next time!
- You little...
Consider yourself lucky today, bitch!
Can you move?
Then... can you move over?
You're right in front of the door.
Wow.
How do you like it?
Do you like it?
Yes.
Jin Myung!
She's the one who'll be using this room.
But... she says that she wants
to use this room by herself.
Did you talk to her about
the rent and the utilities?
Yep.
I guess you must come
from a rich family.
Um, no.
- Are you a student?
- Yes.
What are you thinking about?
The beginning of the lie.
Are you done?
Let's go.
We have to get a nice workout,
now that we've eaten.
Okay!
Oh, excuse me! Does this bus go
to Yeonnam-dong, by any chance?
Yes, it does.
Um, do you go to the Yeonnam-dong
Community Center, then?
Yes. Please, get on.
You're slower than you look.
How many days have you
been running for the bus, now?
Senior Yoon!
Oh, should I not call you that anymore?
What is it?
Is Sangam-dong where
your part-time job is?
Yeah.
Oh, so I was right.
I thought it might've been you
when I was having dinner before.
You didn't see me?
- I did.
- So why didn't you say hi?
I can't do that to customers.
Oh.
Isn't it hard?
It looked like a really hard job.
Yeah, it is a hard job.
There's an easier way to
live life, you know.
Get yourself a boyfriend.
Want me to introduce you to one?
No thanks.
Figures.
With that face and that body...
People call me over, saying "student!"
when they're asking for directions.
It's because they think that everyone
around my age is a student.
But when you tell them that you're not
a student, things get more complicated.
"What's your job?
Why don't you go to school?"
That's why I'm just trying
to pass as a student.
Because it becomes a nuisance otherwise.
It's not because I was trying to lie.
That's simple enough, right?
Did you wait for me to tell me that?
I wasn't exactly waiting
for you, per se.
I'm just saying.
- Miss, It seemed to me that you--
- Why are you calling me that?
It makes you sound so old.
What should I call you, then?
- To me, it seems that you--
- Why are you referring to me as that?
Whatever.
Just call me "Miss."
Miss, it seems to me that you
really care about that student.
- Who?
- The one who lives a hard life.
The one that has tons of part-time jobs.
You're saying that I care a lot
about Senior Yoon?
Why would I?
- Who knows?
- No... no way.
Why would I?
Why would I care about her?
Can I sit here?
All right.
Good work.
- Yes, thank you!
- Yes.
- Goodbye.
- All right.
Welcome!
- That'll be 2,500 won.
- Okay.
Thank you.
[Climax Control Cream]
That'll be 1,000 won.
Thank you.
- Hello, sir!
All right, I've taken a look at your
assignments that you uploaded online.
I'll give you feedback on
that individually.
You shouldn't be such a picky eater.
You won't grow taller
if you're so picky.
Do you have a boyfriend?
No.
What, there aren't any
guys who are your type?
What kind of guy do you like?
Oh yeah, what are you doing this weekend?
Let's go eat some chicken breasts.
Oh, there's a senior I know
over there, so...
Senior.
Can I sit here?
I'll just eat in silence, I promise!
Why, is something the matter?
That guy is a senior from my department,
and he keeps on bothering me!
He keeps giggling during
class and staring at me
and he keeps talking
about perverted things.
Senior.
Do people get bullied in college, too?
I'm not sure.
What should I do?
To be honest, I was bullied
a bit in high school...
Well, no. More like I had no friends.
So I wanted to make friends and visit
fun places in college, no matter what...
I'm sorry.
You can keep reading.
Is that what you're worried about?
Yes.
It's nice.
It's befitting of your age.
[109,000 won has been transferred
into your transportation card.]
I wish I had worries like that.
Instead of things like rent and taxes.
- Psychology Majors!
- Yeah!
You sure are good at drinking.
Oh no.
Our drink tab is going to be huge!
I'm sorry.
Sheesh!
Why are you so cute?
Let's go.
Wait!
Wow, your perm looks so nice! Right?
Um... yes.
- What the hell is that?
- Oh no!
Hey, don't take your shoes off.
Which salon did that to you?
This is the first time I've ever
complained about anything!
If you don't turn this
back to the way it was
I'll have 12,000 students
boycott your salon!
I'm not a cruel enough person to just
sit and watch this happen!
Change it back.
Selling defective clothes
without telling the customer
is nothing short of a scam!
And the fact that you put
the tag where the hole is
shows that this was deliberate!
This is unacceptable!
If you don't allow her to
return this, I'll report you.
We came here to eat noodles, not this!
What is going on here?
We're sorry!
We'll make you a new one!
What's this?
Thank you for earlier.
This is on the house.
All right, we'll accept it.
All right.
Eat up.
Senior!
You're so cool!
Do you like stuff like this?
All you have to do is lose yourself.
And allow your arms and legs
to move naturally.
Just do what feels right.
Watch carefully.
Take in some energy.
Don't try to look cool. And don't
think of this as being embarrassing.
Say, "I'm the best, no matter what!"
Shake your booty, while thinking that!
Give it a shot.
Just move!
With more confidence!
Put your soul into it!
Your soul!
Here, try to feel it.
Feel this wave!
Don't be so stiff!
Sheesh.
You sure are a difficult one.
A date?
Hell-to-the-yes!
I'd go even it killed me!
Thanks, friend!
- Okay.
- What does he look like?
Is he hot?
Friend?
Where you at, girl?
Come back! It's okay
even if he's ugly! [crying face]
Oh ho!
Hello.
- Please, have a seat.
- Okay.
- You're quite pretty.
- Thank you.
You're a lot more handsome
than you were in your photo.
You're back?
I'm back.
What's with you? You look like
you won the lottery!
His height, voice, personality, and
butt are all totally my type!
- And how did he feel about you?
- I killed it, obviously.
A French person put their laundry
in the dryer. What did they say?
Marseille! (sounds like Korean
phrase for "please dry!")
Our sense of humor are
exactly the same, and...
Ew! Did you have alcohol?
Oops!
Oh my, oh my! You drank
with him on the first date?
I almost didn't come home tonight!
And so? What happened after the date?
- I'm going to take that one.
- Oh, really?
Oh, it's already here.
I had a lot of fun today.
I'll call you!
- Bye!
- Have a safe trip home.
Call... call me!
Bye!
Bye, now!
Have a safe trip home!
Oh, wow.
A powder-pink skirt
blows in the spring wind...
She's totally lost it!
Wow!
What are you doing, Honey? Hehe.
Seriously, what is he doing?
What's the matter?
I just got a text from my friend.
What did they say?
[He said that you're a really fun, nice
person, but he just wants to be friends.]
Apparently, he can't see me as a woman.
Why is that? Do I lack female hormones?
Should I go get estrogen shots?
What if I have XXY syndrome?
My neck seems to be
getting thicker these days.
Here, look! Do I look like
I have an Adam's apple?
You did impersonations when
you went on your date, right?
Did you do this, too?
- You did, didn't you?
- But he thought it was funny.
And we had such great conversations.
Sheesh.
How much did you talk, compared to him?
Did he talk as much as you did?
Okay, then did you talk
60 percent of the time?
You talked 70 percent of the time?
To be precise, I talked about
75 percent of the time.
That's not a conversation!
That's a lecture!
Whatever. I had to keep the conversation
flowing! What else was I supposed to do?
It gets so awkward
when nobody's talking!
Damn it, I don't know how
others can stand it.
Damn it.
Why isn't he texting me?
It's not like he's that busy,
since he's a student!
He doesn't even study!
He has time to hang out with friends,
but no time to text me back? I get it.
Do you know which
number I hate the most?
One! That damned one, that tells
me that he didn't read my message!
- What?
- You damned bastard.
Did his freaking finger break?
Why isn't he contacting me?
"He used to ask, every
breakfast, lunch, and dinner..."
'Did you eat? What did you eat?
Did you make sure to chew well?'
"He texted me so damn much when he was
following me around, saying he liked me!"
"But his passion has cooled.
He got himself another girl!"
When will I ever get to say such things?
It's because you don't know.
People feel the loneliest when
you're with tons of other people
and people feel poorest when
you're around someone who's rich.
I feel lonely,
even though I have a lover--
I'm in front of Hongdae.
Want to come?
Never mind. Everyone pretty much feels
done. Let's see each other next time.
What the hell? Being wishy-washy
as you please... you're so annoying!
That's good.
I was tired anyway.
What the hell, am I
supposed to be on standby?
Do I have to run out if you tell me
to come at the middle of the night?
If you're going to do that,
take your credit card back.
I won't use it.
I don't care!
That's your problem!
I can't go out.
I won't go out!
I'm hanging up.
I can't chat for long.
I'm going to sleep, so don't contact me.
I hung up, didn't I?
I didn't say anything!
Weren't you heading out?
This is my cup!
Sorry.
You think "sorry" is going to fix it?
How disgusting.
What did you say?
Who knows what you did with that mouth?
You think that my mouth is disgusting?
Yeah, it is!
I'm sure you put that mouth
on tons of nasty things!
Oh, really?
Make sure you examine your
mouth constantly, to see if it rots off.
You crazy bitch!
I'll kill you,
you trashy bitch!
Hey!
It's okay.
She kissed you?
She's such a crazy bitch.
- Did she use tongue?
- Honey!
Oh, okay, okay.
Stop crying, already.
What's wrong with her?
You want me to go over there
and yell at her?
It's fine.
I'll do it myself.
I'm going to make her pay!
I was about to kill her,
but stopped myself just in time.
It's not like she's the freaking
Virgin Mary, either.
She's sexually active too,
but treats me like scum!
Oh. You know, she's hated
me from the very start.
She calls me "senior" to my face, but
she's thinking shitty things about me.
And she thinks I wouldn't know.
What? Do you think
I'm a crazy bitch, too?
You got scratched right there.
How is it?
It's nice.
All you need to move here is yourself.
Who used to live here?
Don't misunderstand. I used to
come here to hang out with my friends...
Tell me what you want replaced.
I'll replace anything you want.
The view is nice, too.
And you can drink wine here, too.
And we can play here at any time.
It's kind of annoying that we have to
worry about being seen sometimes.
You don't pick up my calls sometimes.
And there's too many instances
when I couldn't get in touch with you.
You'll move in here, right?
I'll think about it.
What's there to think about?
We can live here together, with matching
cups, pillows, and pajamas.
How about it?
We'll be just like newlyweds.
But it'll all be a lie.
We can just pretend
that it's all real, in our hearts.
There's an easy way to live life, too.
Get yourself a boyfriend.
Want me to introduce you to one?
No thanks.
I'm hungry.
Oh.
I'm going to sit here.
- We're still clearing that table, so...
- I'll wait, then.
Why? That table is fine.
I want to sit over there, though.
- We'll wait, then.
- Yes, sir. Please come this way.
- Let's go.
- What? Oh, sure.
I'll take your orders.
Is it really okay if I buy
a new bed and sofa?
Sure. I don't mind.
How much am I allowed to spend on them?
Well, I don't know.
- Maybe two million won?
- Two million?
Hey, there.
I'm back.
Do you know her?
Is she a friend?
No, as if.
She's my housemate.
Oh.
She said that she can't
act as if she knows me.
Just pretend that you don't know her.
Just leave her a tip, okay?
Here, have some.
It's good.
It's good, right?
It's so good.
And not greasy at all.
We enjoyed the meal.
You're not busy right now, right?
Help me out a bit.
Yes, sir.
Take a seat right there.
Eat it.
Eating sweets helps when
you feel worn out.
Did I seem that worn out to you, sir?
Why are you worn out so early today?
I don't know. I don't know
why I feel so worn out.
It's only 9 p.m., after all.
I shouldn't be so worn out already.
But, how did you know?
That I was worn out, I mean.
You come to know people's
quirks when you like them.
How does it taste?
It's good, right?
I made them not too long ago.
Wow, you know how to joke
around too, Ms. Jin Myung?
I'm being honest, though.
The custard cream is too burnt.
And the pastry isn't crispy at all.
Eat up, and come back
after you get some rest.
Yes, sir.
Excuse me.
Just a moment.
Get in.
No thanks.
You said that you have
one semester left, right?
Yeah.
You'll be done suffering soon, then.
Which company do you want
to work for the most?
Samsung?
Hyundai?
How much do people who work at Hyundai
make a year? Is it over 50 million won?
You work all day and night
but I heard most people burn
out after they turn 40 or so.
You have to kiss your boss's ass,
and drink even when you don't want to.
Do you like having to do that?
Is that how you want to live your life?
It makes me feel like,
"how can she work so hard?"
It almost makes me wonder
how you can be so diligent.
But I want to know if your dream
is to merely work at a company
after working so hard.
Right?
I sometimes feel embarrassed, too.
It'd be nice if my dream was to be an
astronaut or the UN's secretary-general.
- Oh yeah. Did you get the tip?
- Yeah. You sure left a lot.
It wasn't a mistake, right?
That much is nothing for those people.
I told him about you, and he asked
if I wanted him to pay your tuition.
How about it?
Should I ask him to do it?
Why?
What do you mean? It's because
it hurts me to watch you suffer.
No thanks.
They're not asking you to be
their lover, or anything.
Just think of it as a scholarship.
Then, make it so that I can take the
proper steps to get that scholarship.
You're so frustrating.
It can't be helped.
You don't like me, do you, Senior Yoon?
What about you?
Why do you hate me?
Do you hate me, or...
or my poverty?
I hate you because
I'm jealous of you.
I hate you because you have nothing to
your name, and yet make me feel so poor.
I hate you because you
make me envy you.
I hate you because I want
to become like you, but can't.
So I can't help but to hate you.
That's why it smells.
There's a rotting smell
coming from my envy.
But there's no rule saying, "only college
students are allowed to live here."
The fact that she isn't a
student isn't important!
What's important is that she lied to us!
And for over two years, at that!
Even that's a flimsy excuse. It's
not like she hurt anyone with that lie.
What are you talking about?
She hurt me!
What, are you opposed
to kicking her out, then?
You want her to stay?
Not exactly, but...
What about you?
What are you going to do?
Me?
Well, it hasn't even been long
since I moved in here, and...
Who cares about that?
Just state your opinion!
I... want to abstain from voting.
Wow, you two sure are hospitable.
You two are so tolerant, really.
Since when have you been
so hospitable toward sluts?
Kang Yi Na is a prostitute!
She sells her body!
You're living in the same house
with a woman like that!
Are you okay with that?
Who knows what'll
happen with her?
A guy might break in here
or one of her boyfriend's wives
might come and break everything!
Also, imagine if your parents found out.
Do you think they'd stand for this?
Senior Yoon!
What are you going to do?
We're discussing whether or not
we should kick Kang Yi Na out.
These people are so damn kind
that they don't really care.
But, I can't do that.
If Kang Yi Na continues living
here, I'm moving out, so--
There's no need for that.
I'm going to leave this place.
Happy now?
[A place she frequents]
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Age of Youth]
There's a person that lied
about being a college student, so...
Thank you.
It's good to be sure.
What's your name?
What?
- Goodbye!
Go ahead and drink it.
She's too plain.
People should be fine with coming and
going, and lie a little, you know!
And you know, live dynamically!
Sup.
How is it this hard to get a housemate?
- Song.
- Yes, ma'am?
Don't be nice to me.
Because if you're nice to
me, and then you stop...
it'll make things harder for me.
Can't I just keep being
good to you, then?
I can keep being
good to you, right?
[How many lovers do you have currently?]
Don't you know, since you've
seen them all already?
[How much money do you
earn and spend, per month?]
I'm not sure. I've never calculated it.
Maybe around 8 million won?
[It's been revealed that you're
jealous of Yoon Jin Myung!]
[Tell us why exactly
you're jealous of her.]
She lives diligently, almost to
the point she seems stupid.
[It shocked us when you kissed
Jung Ye Eun. How did it feel?]
What kind of question is that?
[Some say that it was an
act of sexual harassment.]
Sue me, then.
[Do you know that you're sexy?]
I do look at the mirror every day, so...
- [Your favorite body part?]
- The curve along my hips to my butt.
[What does this bracelet mean to you?]
It's a talisman.