Subtitles by DramaFever
[Paldang Station]
There was once a time
when I longed to be special.
I believed that I had a
special fate in store for me
and that my life would be
different than that of others.
I told myself that I wouldn't end up
becoming average, no matter what.
To be average means to be comfortable.
To be average means
to not catch anyone's eye.
To be average means to be boring.
To tell me then that I was
average was a direct insult.
I was curious if what you wanted
after working so hard
was to work at a mere company.
Yeah. I'm going to work at a company.
I'm going to try my damnedest,
just to become average.
I told you to wait in the lobby.
Here.
Sorry for inconveniencing you.
You can go now.
All right.
I'm even less than average right now.
[Episode 4:
My Dream is to Work at A Company]
I'll be back.
- Bye!
- Bye, Senior!
Ah, Friday. The day of the week
that makes Senior Yoon crap out blood.
Ew, why do you have to put it like that?
What can I say?
It's a talent.
Just how many part-time jobs
does Senior Yoon have?
There's probably three
that she does full-time.
Not including the ones she
only does occasionally.
Goodbye!
Bye!
- Um...
- You're already done?
Wow, that was quick.
- Well, goodbye.
- Wait, wait!
Sheesh, why are you always so busy?
I made this to give to you, Teacher.
What container should I put this in?
Here we go.
You said that you don't live
with your parents, right?
It must be so hard to
get a good square meal!
Here, take it.
Come on!
Thank you.
I'll enjoy it.
Does she only work at the
restaurant on weekends?
No. She works there from Friday
to Sunday, so three days a week.
All right, let's eat!
- Here, a plate!
- Here.
All right!
Friday to Sunday is when
restaurants are busiest, though.
I know someone who used to work part-
time at a restaurant at that time slot.
She didn't last a month.
Her body couldn't keep up.
And she's the manager of a gym, too!
But Senior Yoon's being doing
that for two whole years.
You don't see many people
like her these days.
She'd probably take
just about any type of job.
Hey, this is fun.
I told you, this is the best thing
to do to pass time!
Hey, pass me the yellow.
But why does she work the graveyard
shift at the convenience store?
Isn't it dangerous?
And there aren't many people
who come in, either.
Oh, does she get paid more for that?
No, the pay is the same.
She does that so she can study at work.
And there's not many
customers during that shift.
How much money do you think
Senior Yoon makes per month?
Let's say that she gets 300,000 won
per month from tutoring.
She only earns that much from tutoring?
I thought she earned a lot
of money from that job.
Tutors don't get paid much these days.
So 300,000 won from tutoring. And the
restaurant job pays 7,000 won hourly.
So... she probably gets 400,000 won
from that job per month.
She works at the convenience store
for 6 hours, 5 days a week. So 30 hours.
And assuming she gets minimum wage,
that's about 720,000 won per month.
So in total, she makes about
1.4 million won per month.
Wow, 1.4 million won?
That's probably less than
Senior Kang gets from one lover, though.
Really?
How much does Senior Kang get?
I'm sure that Senior Kang gets at
least 2 to 3 million won per month.
Let's make some calculations.
The world has lost its
damn mind, I tell you!
- We'll be going home now, Manager!
- All right. Goodbye.
- Goodbye.
- Thank you for your hard work.
I'm sorry for being late.
- Why were you late?
- I'm sorry.
Make sure it doesn't happen again.
Yes, sir.
Let's go.
You'll miss the bus.
Yes, sir.
Don't be nice to me.
If you're nice to me, and
then stop being nice to me
it'll be even harder on me.
Wouldn't it be okay if I just continued
being nice to you, then?
I can be nice to you, right?
Um, this is my place.
Go inside.
How are you going to get home?
The last bus already left.
Well, I can just go to
the sauna up front.
Go inside now.
You're being foolish.
Hmph. All you had to say
was "thank you."
Go inside.
- You're back, Senior Yoon?
- You're home, Senior Yoon?
What's the matter?
It's nothing.
Oh no!
Are you okay?
Um, do you have a form of ID,
like a student ID?
Um, it's just because there was someone
who lied about being a college student.
It's good to be sure.
Thank you.
I heard that you already live
in another house with roommates.
Why do you want to leave that place?
Well, the people are all nice,
but they don't really clean...
Figures. That's what roommates
tend to argue about the most.
When you see someone half-assing it
when you're putting your all into it
- it pisses me off.
- Exactly!
One should keep the living room
and bathroom area clean, right?
They're shared spaces, after all.
Exactly!
The people I lived with only cleaned
the bathroom once a week!
Excuse me?
And they only cleaned it for 30 minutes!
How can you call that cleaning? That's
just dousing things down with water!
Well, what could I expect from people
who wash their underwear
with their normal clothes, anyway?
Abracadabra!
It seems like there's something
going on with Senior Yoon.
Why?
She's drinking beer by herself
on the balcony.
Is that all?
It's Sunday night. Senior Yoon
always has a beer on Sunday nights.
You didn't know that?
Oh.
Stop it!
Ow!
Hey!
If you went on a retreat, you
should've just spent time bonding.
How dare you lock eyes with a guy!
- No, it wasn't like that!
- You sure talk back a lot, sinner!
- Spill everything, now!
- You think we won't get it out of you?
Senior Yoon, please stop them!
What kind of guy is he?
She asked you what kind of
guy he is, sinner!
- Hey, it's really nice here!
- Yeah!
- Wait, that's our group's!
- I know.
- Give that back!
- I'll hold it for you.
It's fine!
You're probably going to
tease me somehow, later.
Fine! You hold it then.
Here, hold everything!
Idiot.
Are you talking about the Senior that
we saw at the cafeteria last time?
Yes.
He always teases me, harasses me,
and says that I'm ugly!
That's why I have to be wary of him.
Really?
Well, if it's not that guy,
then who is it?
Oh my, my. Carrying all that,
with your thin arms?
This should be taken care of
by us guys.
I'm thankful enough
that you came at all.
So I definitely can't allow you
to carry all that.
Give it here.
Wait a second.
So the guy that you like
isn't that first guy?
No!
So... you like that second guy?
The guy who was all like, "Oh my, my.
How could they make a girl carry that?"
"This should be taken care of
by us guys." That guy?
Are there still people
like that, these days?
Ew. Ew.
Well, whether it be this guy
or that guy, keep one thing in mind.
What?
Make sure to use a condom
when you have sex.
Stop it!
You're embarrassing me!
Oh ho.
I should go wash up.
The order is ready for table four.
Here's one carbonara,
and one gamberoni.
Oh, Ms. Jin Myung.
You're not doing anything after, right?
Mr. Jae Hwan got an award
so we're having a staff dinner.
Oh, sir! You're here?
The kitchen staff have a lot to do!
Come on, let's hurry!
- Ms. Hyun Hui! Ms. Hyun Hui!
- Yes?
Where's Ms. Jin Myung?
She left already because
she has another part-time job.
- Here, eat.
- No, I don't want to.
Say "ah!"
You're so cute.
It was hard for you today
because of Chief Park, right?
Yeah, I was so pissed!
Welcome!
Damn, why are there so many
convenience stores in this neighborhood?
This is the fifth one
I went to, already!
What?
Here, give that to me.
- No.
- No, it's fine. Give it to me.
Go ahead.
- I can just throw it out here, right?
- Yes.
Did you come to look for me?
Why?
Oh, um...
just a second.
It's a bit weird to drink
coffee at night, so...
- That'll be 2,300 won.
- Okay.
Which one would you like to drink?
[Seo Dong Joo]
[Group Chat: Belle Epoque Girls]
[Eun Jae: I'm going grocery shopping.
Does anyone want to come with me?]
[Ji Won: Go by yourself...]
[Ye Eun: Can you get
some panty liners for me?]
[Eun Jae: Is there anyone who
needs something besides Ye Eun?]
[Yi Na: There's nothing in the fridge.]
[Ji Won: Are you loaded, or something?
You only ever use money for your guy!]
[Ye Eun: When did I ever?
I'm really not like that!]
[Ji Won: As if. Then you buy
pork belly for us today!]
[Jin Myung: Just buy what you need.]
[Jin Myung: You can buy stuff for
everyone when people pitch in.]
Back then, I thought you were haughty
because I heard you were in college.
I guess I had an inferiority complex
since I only graduated from high school.
I'm still a work in progress.
Give me your hand.
What, does this look like
a mere twist-tie to you?
This is definitely a ring.
Give me your hand.
Come on.
You're going to become Gollum now.
What's your name?
What?
Um, where are you from?
G-G-Gyeonggi-do.
- Goodbye.
Compared to her, you talk as much
as someone who has ADHD.
How is it this hard
to get a new housemate?
Are we being too picky?
No, I don't think so.
We just want someone with an average
amount of cleanliness, manners
and communication skills.
Yeah! That's all I want from them.
Maybe the ghost is sabotaging us?
Oh, let's sign that, Honey.
Please sign our petition to create
a law against puppy mills!
- Please sign our petition!
This practice is unacceptable!
Um... oh! There's a movie at 3:20 p.m.
Let's see that.
If we see the movie, it'll be the perfect
time to have dinner afterwards!
What's the matter, Honey?
I'm not in the mood
to see a movie today.
Honey!
Get out.
Honey.
What... did I do wrong?
You're asking as if you
really don't know?
What? I really don't know what I did.
This is why people say that
you're a rude little bitch.
Why did you write down your school
when you signed the petition earlier?
Huh?
You were trying to act haughty since
you go to a better college than me!
No, that's just because they
asked me to fill in an occupation.
You could've just written
"college student," then!
Whatever.
Get out.
Get the hell out!
Ow!
Who the hell are you?
Who the hell is this bastard?
Why is he treating you like this?
Who is she?
Senior Kang!
Is that bastard your boyfriend?
- Whatever. Get out.
- Break up with him immediately.
What the hell does it
have to do with you?
Are you an idiot? Why
are you dating a thug like him?
Leave me alone!
Hey, you crazy bitch.
Are you an idiot?
Why are you seeing him?
That kind of bastard is--
Shut up! I don't want to hear it!
I'll take care of my own damn love life!
You ---- idiot! You still
want to date him even after--
What about you, then? It's not
like your love life is much better!
What do you know?
Hey, do you think you and
I are alike, you idiot?
Why did you come here and start
bitching at me? This is our house!
Go back to your own place!
I'm going!
Don't ever come back!
I wouldn't come even
if you begged me, bitch!
Damn it.
Pathetic.
Where's my laundry?
Huh? Oh... it's in your room.
Damn it, how humiliating!
Why her, of all people?
Wow, family meal is so good today!
Thank you!
- Did you make this?
- Hello!
- Oh, hey!
Thank you for the meal!
- You're done already?
- Yes.
- There's still food there, though.
- No, I'm done.
Mr. Jae Hwan!
Yeah?
Here's a congratulatory gift for you.
You didn't need to get
anything like this for me!
It's nothing.
It really is nothing.
All right. Here's one
M-steak, and one ribeye.
Yes, sir.
Hey, are you going to sharpen
your knife all day?
Aren't you going to work?
I apologize.
Please, enjoy your meal.
- Hey, check on that.
- Yes, sir.
Yoon Jin Myung.
Give me your hand.
Do you think you'd want to eat food
that was served by a hand like this?
What if a customer complained about it?
Everyone else can leave.
I put myself through college too.
I did it by tutoring my cousin.
I took care of my room and board like
that, but I was worried about tuition
and my transportation fees.
I was always worrying about money.
Before, well... there were other
people watching, so...
I know how hard things
must be for you right now.
Here, eat up.
Yes, sir.
I'll help you with the check, ma'am.
Goodbye.
I'll ring you up.
That'll be 125,800 won.
I mean, isn't it weird?
He was screaming at her yesterday as
if he was going to fire her right there
and said, "wouldn't you lose
your appetite, as the customer?"
So, how did she get to work
at the counter overnight?
She gets paid 7,500 won per hour for
standing around and pressing buttons?
How is that any of your business?
Why are you so mad about it?
It's making it hard on me because
the new person keeps messing up!
You have such a nasty temper.
Something definitely happened
between the two of them.
Hurry the hell up!
Yes, I'm coming now!
It was so risky last night.
I almost called my lover!
And tell him things like,
"come over. I'm lonely."
You can't call him?
Idiot. Of course not.
You know, the relationship
between men and women...
is like a see-saw.
If I go up, the other person goes down.
If one person gets clingy,
the other person runs away.
Anyway, that's not the important thing.
What... should I do?
About your bad dreams, you mean?
It's so annoying!
I keep having this nightmare
ever since I moved.
So, what happens in the dream?
You know, that is...
I've fallen into water.
The water is pitch black...
but something is staring
at me inside the water.
It seems like a person's eyes...
but it also seems like it could
be the eyes of some beast.
Those eyes get farther, and farther...
but they keep staring at me.
But I...
Want to come to my place, Mister?
No, that won't work.
It's my lover's place
so it's not good manners for me
to bring another man there.
Even I have enough manners
not to do something like that.
Just a second.
I need to use the bathroom.
I waited for you at the
back door yesterday, too.
The manager drove me home.
Do you know that people
are talking about you?
Tell me that it's not like that.
What do you mean by that?
Would you trust me if I told you?
Yes.
- I'm in here!
- Hey, I'm about to pee.
Get out. It's coming out!
It's coming out! Hurry up!
Hey, hurry up!
It's coming out!
It came out!
Sorry.
What the hell?
It looks like she's really drunk.
Yeah, that's whatever.
But why is she here?
Maybe it's like what
General Kim Yusin said?
People usually go back to
where they're used to going.
Senior Kang is here.
I know. I saw her on the way up.
My bad.
Thanks for letting me use
your bathroom. I'll be going now.
- Song.
- Yes, ma'am?
The ghost over there is gone now, right?
Huh?
You don't see it anymore
nowadays, right?
I'm sure you don't.
It followed me to this house, after all.
That ghost is way too busy nowadays
appearing in my dreams.
- Oh no.
- Hey, hey!
You.
Don't see that guy anymore.
I just don't want you to get hurt.
I'm worried about you.
- Ugh.
- Ow!
You're seriously such an idiot.
This girl doesn't realize
what a catch she really is.
She doesn't even know that, and
is dating some thug-ass punk.
Sheesh.
Geez. What's with her, blabbing
drunkenly at someone else's place?
Do you know that people
are talking about you?
Tell me that it's not like that!
I can't.
Work at the counter until
your fingernail is fully healed.
And if you have anything that ever
troubles you, think of me as an uncle...
I can't tell him that nothing happened.
He knew the meaning behind that action.
Thank you.
Yeah.
And I knew the meaning
behind that action, too.
I hated you all this time.
I thought that I was
a better person than you were.
But in reality, I wasn't.
It's just that...
I never had to face as much
temptation as you did.
Oh, it's Sunday.
I'm sorry, everyone, for the
trouble I caused yesterday.
That ghost...
has been here this whole time.
What?
You said yesterday that you thought
that ghost followed you here.
I said that?
You don't remember?
At any rate, it's been here this
whole time. It didn't follow you.
Really?
Then... what was that?
Can't I just live here?
I know that it's stupid of me to
move out, and then move back in
and I know that I lied to you all.
I know that, but...
But, still.
Can't I live here?
- Here, have some.
- Thank you.
I'm a bit nervous.
I'll be going now.
- Goodbye.
I don't really like her.
What exactly don't you like about her?
Just her vibe, in general.
I didn't really like her much, either.
What about you, Senior Yoon?
Me too.
I didn't exactly love her, but...
Right? I didn't like her much, either.
She's too plain.
Exactly! She's way too plain.
She's no fun.
People should have the vibe of just
coming and going as they please
and seem like they may lie a bit.
Life, you know, should be more dynamic--
[Mom]
Hello?
My pitiful child!
Oh no!
What am I supposed to do?
He can't live, or die...
my heart hurts so much! My heart!
Joon Myung!
My child! Joon Myung!
It's all due to your wretched mother
that you ended up like this!
It's all my fault!
Oh, my son!
Don't worry.
His condition has stabilized.
What?
He's back to normal.
- Good work today!
- Goodbye!
- All right, bye!
Did something happen to you?
My younger brother didn't die.
He hasn't died for two whole years now.
I thought he'd really die this time.
I was really hoping that he'd just die.
Do you like me?
Do you still like me?
Yes.
Don't.
When I think that someone
may like me, I become weak.
And if I become weak now...
it'll really be the end for me.
So...
don't like me.
Senior Yoon.
Did something happen?
My fingernail... fell off...
but I didn't know
that it'd hurt this much.
It hurts so much...
that I feel like I'm going to die.
It hurts so much.
It hurts so much...
that I feel like I'm going to die!
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Did your fingernail heal okay?]
Yes. It's fine now.
[You're 28, and yet you haven't
graduated college. Why is that?]
I kept having to take time off school.
[Do you know how much
Kang Yi Na earns in a month?]
I have a rough estimate, yes.
But that has nothing to do with me.
[What is the thing that
you want most right now?]
Money.
[And after that?]
Next question, please.
[Who's in your family?]
It's my mom and me.
[Your mom is your only family member?]
I have a younger brother.
Um, when is this going to be over?
[Did you think the ghost in the shoe
closet was relevant to your brother?]
I don't know.