Subtitles by DramaFever
Where else did you get hurt?
Did you get hurt in here?
Hey, you idiot! It's not like
you're a terrible catch!
Why the hell are you
dating a guy like him?
Stop it! I don't want to
hear this anymore!
Hey, let go!
What did I do wrong?
Why did you write the name of your
college when you signed that petition?
What?
You were just acting high and mighty
about going to a better school than me!
You could've just
written "college student!"
- I mean...
- Get the hell out!
Everything's over.
My love is over.
There's nothing I can do anymore.
No matter how much it hurts,
it's over when it's over.
Honey.
I liked you.
I liked you a whole lot.
You can't even imagine
how much I liked you.
I was happy because of you
and because of you...
- Hey, what's wrong?
- What happened?
There was a huge electrical
current, and I almost died!
- Again?
- Sheesh.
Oh, was it that scary, sweetie?
Did you cry? Did your nose run a little?
Do you know how
dangerous electricity is?
What's with me nowadays?
What? What happened this time?
That's because Senior Yoon is a
bargain hunter and bought a bad bulb.
What about the fact that the
toilet got clogged last week?
That was because I drank a ton
and pooped out three days worth of poop.
Sheesh!
Ew!
But... it is a bit strange.
I hear a knocking sound sometimes,
even when I'm alone.
I've heard that too.
That's just the sound of the
tree branches against the house.
I only ever hear it when I'm
home alone, though.
That's because it's too noisy to
hear when we're all home.
Oh.
But Senior Kang left,
and then moved back in.
Well, that's...
And Senior Yoon's nail fell off.
This is all because of...
that thing.
All these things only started happening
after you saw the ghost here!
Such old-fashioned views,
in such a modern era!
You're the one who said
that they saw ghosts.
I know, right? So, can't you
do anything about it?
Can't you kick it out?
What do we do?
I guess they heard me!
Man, you're done for.
The ghost is going to target you now.
There's always God.
So pray to Him.
Ms. Jung over here isn't exactly
on the best terms with God.
She hasn't gone to church in forever.
So her faith for God is long gone.
We have no other choice, then.
Just carry this around.
What's with this cucumber?
Does it protect people, like garlic
protects people from vampires?
Devote yourself to phallus worship.
Phallus worship?
What's that?
Damn it, you pervert!
How dare you ignore the
wisdom of our ancestors?
You know, our ancestors used to put
phallic objects near haunted places.
Why, you ask?
Because ghosts are "yin,"
and the phallus is "yang."
Really? Is that really true?
Yes. I've read about that in a book.
That's why we should put phallic
objects all around our place--
Stop shaking that around, already!
The phallus...
The phallus!
My precious phallus!
You'll definitely be cursed.
Shut it.
Hey, should we throw a party?
Instead of putting phallic objects all
over the place, we can invite real men.
The real thing will probably
be better than just a cucumber.
Yes, let's do it.
Senior Kang is back now, and
our midterms are over now, too!
Each of us will invite guys we know!
You! Bring that senior of yours!
And you, Ms. Jung! Take this chance
to get yourself a new man!
No thanks.
Why not? You can't break up with him?
You still haven't gotten over him?
Whoever said that?
Then, let's do it!
It'll be great!
Who cares if we want to do it?
What if Senior Yoon is against it?
Do whatever you guys want.
It's not like I can be here
for that, anyway.
You're not using money from our
collective money pool for this, right?
What about our landlady?
Um...
What is it?
Are you going somewhere?
Yeah. I'm going on a vacation.
When are you coming back?
On Sunday.
I was actually about to
come upstairs just now.
Please feed my Damien while I'm gone.
- Have a safe trip, ma'am!
[Episode 5: The Reason Why One Wishes
to Love Someone, or Wishes Not To]
[Three Nights Before "The Night of Men"]
I was a bum.
I desperately begged for love
while prostrating myself.
I was so thankful for a tiny display of
affection, or a small smile.
I was like a dog.
Even though I kept getting abused,
I'd wait for him to call me.
I shook my tail so hard
that it almost broke
and licked your hand
with my bruised mouth.
[Anonymous Kang,
"Some Eulogy"]
Fine, Go Doo Young!
Dating you has rendered my
self-esteem into nothing!
Instead of giving me a proper present
for our one-year anniversary
you gave me a damned free sample.
Here.
And yet, you eagerly accepted
my own gift for you!
Wow!
That damned jacket was 130,000 won!
And that was only because it
was on sale for 30 percent off!
I gave up on coffee for a
month to buy that for you!
Did you even know that?
You're late because there's traffic, or
because you drank the night before.
Or you're late because you overslept!
And you don't even reply to my
texts or calls most of the time!
How dare you give me
the silent treatment?
It wouldn't even be enough if you
were begging for forgiveness!
Evil bastard.
All right. Today, we'll be
working on some chicken.
Please carve it well,
part by part.
That's your goal for today.
All right, everyone.
Begin working on your own chicken.
And then, all you want to do
when we meet up is to have sex!
Am I a damn prostitute?
The feeling that comes next is rage.
After that comes sadness,
which paves the path for acceptance.
The interesting thing, though,
is that the grieving process
for cancer patients and those who've
suffered from heartbreak is similar.
- That's how much heartbreak--
- Son of a bitch.
Wow, you demolished that thing.
One feels intense rage at first.
After that, one comes to acknowledge
reality more and more.
And then, after they've acknowledged
reality to a certain extent
they begin to fall into depression.
And after one is past the
stage of depression
one becomes more and
more in tune with reality
and come to accept
their situation.
All right, that concludes
our lecture for today.
Good work today.
- Thank you, sir!
What?
You don't seem to have a fever.
Why are you acting like we're close?
What if he misunderstands?
Who?
Senior. I have something
I need to ask you.
So you've finally grown
interested in me!
It does feel a bit overdue, but...
What is it?
You know...
Does Senior have a girlfriend?
Huh?
A girlfriend.
Does Senior have one?
Does Senior have a girlfriend?
Come on! Does Senior
have a girlfriend, or not?
No.
No!
Definitely not.
Really?
Are you sure?
I mean, it seems strange
to you too, right?
The fact that such a fine
man is single, I mean.
But you know, miraculous things like
this happen every once in a while.
So... hey!
Hey, I'm still talking here!
Ow!
Hey, come on!
This is sexual harassment, you know!
Why don't you do it to me too, then?
Damn it!
I should just...
How can someone like you be a woman?
Im Sung Min. What are
you doing on Saturday?
Why?
On Saturday, at my place...
- A party?
- Yeah.
There'll be a cute girl, a lovely
girl, a glamorous girl
and best of all...
Me.
Will there be alcohol, too?
Of course!
Sure. I'll come, then.
Really?
This is a promise, all right?
This is a promise!
Here, promise me.
All right, I took care of that!
Hey, don't think things
like that, all right?
What are you talking about?
That you'll take this opportunity...
to make me your woman.
That kind of foolish thought.
- What?
- Caught you red-handed, didn't I?
Don't misunderstand, all right?
I'm just inviting you as a friend.
I have no ulterior motives.
Hey, I'm not coming, all right?
I'm not coming, then!
I won't go if you're going to
be so nasty about it!
Hey, no need to get all upset, now!
Then... just do whatever you want.
You can keep liking me. What can you do
about your feelings, after all?
Ah... what is love?
Damn it, it's so spicy.
Hey, come on!
- Isn't it spicy?
- Drink some damn water, then!
Stop making such perverted noises!
What are you talking about?
Anyways, you'll come, right?
- When did you say it was?
- Saturday, at 6 p.m.
You can't dress too over-the-top
on that day, all right?
Basically, you're asking me
not to dress like a player.
Why are you so easygoing today?
Don't you dare try to make a move
on any of my babies, all right?
They're just average girls.
What about me, then?
What's with you today?
No reason.
You just look so happy.
What are you talking about?
Mr. Jong Gyu!
Yeah?
- When did you get out?
- It hasn't been that long.
If I'd known that you got out of jail,
I would've brought you some tofu.
What a nice thing to say.
Oh, but did you find that damned girl?
You know, the one who you said you'd
teach a lesson, when you got out.
I did find her.
Goodbye.
[Conversation with:
Chef Park Jae Hwan]
I miss you.
Do you like me?
Don't.
If I think that someone likes
me, I'll become weak.
And if I become weak now...
it'll really be the end for me.
So...
don't like me.
[Me too...]
[Two nights before the "Night of Men"]
Losing love sure
makes me feel bitter.
Farewell, short nights.
Farewell, the fog of winter
that hovered near my windowsill.
Goodbye, you candles who knew nothing.
Goodbye, goodbye.
Goodbye, desire that is no longer mine.
[Exerpt from Gi Hyung Do's
"Empty Home"]
There's someone in here.
Go Doo Young. Just hearing your name
made my heart melt.
Go Doo Young.
Every time I think about your name,
it brings tears to my eyes.
Go Doo Young. If you'd just
apologize to me now, I'd...
If you'd just apologize to me now....
Are you all right?
Do you want to sit down?
No.
Thank you.
Oh, no! There's been
an accident over there!
Oh no!
Oh my.
Sheesh!
They should've been more careful.
Ye Eun!
Ye Eun! My little piglet!
Even if such a thing were to happen,
it has nothing to do with me.
Ye Eun!
My little piglet!
[I'm sorry, and I love you.]
Ye Eun!
That has nothing to do with me!
Honey!
No!
Wait!
Ye Eun!
Please... please!
Please!
Your jjajjangmyun is here.
Coming!
- You can put that here.
- All right.
How much is it?
- 15,000 won.
- Okay.
Damned bastard!
He's perfectly fine!
Goodbye!
- Hey, hey!
- Hurry!
Yeah, just like that.
Damn it!
Hey, focus.
Hey, focus!
Focus, all of you.
Got that? All right!
- Good game.
What are you looking at?
I was pretty good, wasn't I?
I don't know.
You know, Senior.
Listen carefully.
What?
- Mr. Senior?
- Huh?
- Senior?
- What?
Oppa? (Term used with an older
guy that a girl is close to)
Yeah?
Which one sounds the best
out of those three?
"Oppa," of course!
Oppa!
"Oppa" is definitely
the best among them.
But...
it's embarrassing to say.
That little...
Oh, hey!
Samuel Johnson, right?
- Yeah, I'm...
- How are you?
I'm sorry, who are you?
Don't you remember me?
I'm Song!
My name is your Song!
Just call me Song!
Ah! Oh, I'm so sorry. Song!
We're having a big party at my house!
You should come!
And bring your friends, too!
- Do you want to go?
- Yeah, sure!
- Okay!
- Okay.
- I'll call you back.
- Okay. Bye!
Bye!
- Ooh!
These are pretty.
I'll take ten of these.
And this, this, this, this, this,
this, this, this, this, and this.
You got all that, right?
- Thank you!
- Thank you, goodbye!
- Oh!
- What? What now?
How much is this?
I wish I could be at peace.
I wish that he wouldn't keep
popping up in my mind.
I wish I wasn't curious
about him anymore.
About whether or not he's
thinking about me, too.
Or if he misses me.
Are you going to your part-time job?
Yeah.
Go, then.
Yeah, you too.
Oh, my little piglet!
Yes, yes.
- Oh, my little piglet!
- Hey, let go!
- Hey, come on!
- You're my little piglet!
Stop it! Why are you
calling me a pig?
You're my little piglet!
Piglet! Piglet!
I must be crazy.
You still haven't found a
guy for the party yet?
- Senior!
- "Hello, Senior."
"I'm Yoon Eun Jae, a freshman
majoring in Psychology."
- Senior!
- "This Saturday"
"we'll be having a
small party at my place."
"I'd like to invite you..."
What is this bullcrap?
Even a elementary schooler's invitation
would be written better than this!
What am I supposed to do, then?
Just talk to him, face to face!
That's... I can't do that.
That's why.
Damn it, you're making me
feel so frustrated!
That's not hard at all!
Just go to him, and be like, "Senior.
What are you doing on Saturday?"
"Do you want to come over to my place?"
That sounds too much like
I'm trying to seduce him!
Because you are, sweetie.
It's because you're acting like
you're not trying to, when you are
that you're at a loss for words!
I'm home.
What about you? Did you find
a man to bring to the party?
What, you didn't?
Why, you little!
- Hey, open up!
- Hold on!
Open up, already!
What?
- Open up.
- No, I can't!
No, no, no, no, no!
- Why are you so strong?
- No!
Wow!
Look, you punks!
Hey, come on! I was
going to surprise you guys!
- Some people use their precious time...
- I have tons of free time, though.
and their own money
to prepare for the party!
So, what about you two? Huh?
This won't do.
If you don't bring a man,
I'm going to punish you.
That's not fair!
So bring a man, then!
What kind of punishment
are you going to give us?
A totally astoundingly scary one.
- No!
- You can't!
You little...
What's our goal? Huh?
It's to get as many guys here as we can,
and fill this place with male energy!
But still.
Why are you just doing as you please?
Why don't we each write
out a punishment, then?
We'll each write one, and then
you can pick one at random.
That's okay, right?
I bet they'll write
stupid stuff, though.
Then you and I can
write totally terrible ones.
I knew it.
What does it say?
[Cleaning the windowsill]
Hey, what the hell?
I mean, the windowsill is pretty
dirty and the window doesn't open easily
so from time to time...
Our dear, youngest Eun Jae.
You know, this thing called a party
is to break away from the norm,
to have an abnormally good time.
So how could you write something
so boring and realistic?
You said that we could
write what we wanted to.
All right, I'm done.
That's right! This is the kind
of thing I'm looking for!
[Confess your love to a stranger
and get their number!]
How are we supposed to
pull off something like this?
This is only possible for
people like you!
Did you forget? I might have to pick
a punishment out of the box, too.
Oh!
[Going to an early
morning prayer session]
Hey, why not?
Religious stuff is off-limits.
You shouldn't mess
with religion.
What am I supposed to write, then?
I don't have anything else to write!
I'll write one for you, then.
No, you can't!
Here, you write it,
Senior Jung.
What did you write?
Telling the Landlady that her
lipstick color doesn't suit her!
How pointless and boring.
It's my choice!
Well, it doesn't matter.
There's a super-punishment among all
of your useless so-called punishments.
Senior Song.
What did you write?
Drumroll, please!
Ta-da!
Oh, come on!
- No!
My feelings of love and hate for you
are all just sad stories now
that have vanished into thin air.
[Three Nights Before "The Night of Men"]
- Ow! Be more gentle!
- Sheesh!
You should've been
more careful riding it!
Hey, are your hands okay?
Yes, I only tripped a little.
Where did you get that piece of trash?
You better throw that out
as soon as possible!
I'm sure it'll be fine after
I get used to riding it.
Hmph.
It must be time.
Let's go.
Breaking up with
someone means that
even if something good happens,
you can't be happy together.
And that you can't worry about them,
even if something bad happens.
The fact that you've broken
up with someone means that
you can no longer be
curious about each other.
The fact that you've broken
up with someone means that
the future that you'd imagined,
with you being alongside them
is something that you must give up on.
Um... do Nutrition majors cook, too?
Yes.
What kinds of things
are you good at cooking?
Spicy stewed chicken
and potatoes.
Hey.
Is spicy stewed chicken and
potatoes a sad dish, or something?
You're the one who asked me to
introduce you to some new guys!
What are you doing, after I went through
the trouble of bringing them here?
Sorry.
Smile a little.
Okay?
Okay.
Got it.
What...
are you doing on Saturday?
All right, smile for me a little!
One, two!
Wow, you look so cool!
Just a sec. One more time!
All right. Put on an expression
that conveys victory!
One, two!
- Yes! Good work, everyone!
- Thank you!
Good work. Also, if you need to get
in touch with me, here's my information.
And if you'd like a copy of the photo,
please let me know! I'll send it to you.
- Okay? I'll send it to you.
- All right.
Please get in touch!
Also, what are all of you
doing tomorrow?
- Tomorrow?
Oh, um, it's because there's going to
be a small party at my place tomorrow.
If any of you have time,
come and stop by!
- Wow!
How are they having trouble
with something so simple?
Senior.
What are you doing this Saturday night?
We're going to have a party at my place.
Would you like to come?
Damn it!
Senior...
What are you doing?
Huh?
You sure looked like you
were having a jolly old time.
I wonder what's on your mind?
Um...
I have a favor to ask you.
If I don't bring a guy, I'll have to
face a really scary punishment.
But, I don't know anyone in Seoul.
So could you come, Senior?
I'd really appreciate it.
That's what you want me
to tell that guy, right?
Yes!
So you want me to ask that,
to that creep over there?
Yes.
Well, um, he's not creepy.
Wow, Yoon Jong Yeol.
How did you end up in this mess?
You little!
That's not right, right?
Yes, that's not right.
Just forget about it.
I'll ask him myself.
I'll talk to him.
- Where are you going?
- Huh?
I'll do it, damn it!
Hey, Yool Bin.
Hey, Jong Yeol.
You know, a summer sunset
is like a young girl's sigh.
You can shove that bullshit
right back up your ass.
Anyway, um...
You...
Do-you-have-time
-tomorrow-night-by-any-chance?
What?
Um, Yoon-Jae-said-that-she...
wanted-you-at-her-party.
You know?
You don't understand what I'm saying?
No. Not at all.
Hey, Jong Yeol.
What is it?
Never mind.
Just keep appreciating
that sunset, all right, Yool Bin?
You know. Your sunsets
and sighs, and whatnot.
Don't follow me.
I know what you're going to say.
Really?
- Hey!
- Yes?
Why are you acting like that?
Square your shoulders!
Okay.
Are you crying?
No.
Geez, you little brat!
Let's go! I'll buy you a drink.
Pace yourself.
What?
He was my first love.
Hey, what do you mean, "love?"
Love, my ass!
You weren't even close to love!
It was love!
He's the first guy that I've ever loved!
Hey! You never even had a crush
on your teacher, or anything like that?
It's okay.
It'll get better.
No. It'll never become okay.
You'll forget about it, with time.
No, I won't.
I told you, you'll forget
about it really quickly!
How do you know, Senior?
That's how love is.
Though one can't call your
meager feelings love.
You know that much about love?
Yeah, I do.
I know about it very well.
Well, how many times have
you been in love?
Tons of times.
Hey.
It wasn't just once or twice.
You know, I...
How nice!
Hey, what did you like so much
about that punk, anyway?
Everything.
His looks, his voice...
The way he talks,
the way he smiles...
His name is so cool, too.
Shin Yool Bin!
Senior Yool Bin!
Yool Bin-oppa!
What a load of bull.
I even planned names for
our future children!
I was going to name them
Na Ra if they were a girl
and Sae Gae if they were a boy!
Damn, just how far did your
imagination take you?
It's all over!
What do I do now?
Oh, crap.
Ta-da!
What do I do?
I'm going to get punished.
What's the punishment?
Ta-da!
Wow. So, what are you going to do?
You're in deep trouble now.
What do I do?
I'll have to get a part-time job,
or something.
I'll probably get paid hourly, right?
Hey! Why are you trying to solve
everything with money?
That's a terrible habit.
If you really need me to,
I'll come to your party.
You?
But, why?
Just because.
I feel bad for you.
Could you, then?
What's with your reaction?
Oh.
Thank you.
What will you do for me if I go?
I have to do something for you?
See a movie with me,
and pay for the tickets.
Three times.
I'll just find a part-time job.
Paying for three movies, plus
transportation, is over 50,000 won...
I'll pay.
Happy?
But, why?
Think of it as "community service."
Happy now, you idiot?
Damn it!
Excuse me!
One more bottle of soju, please!
Wow!
Wow! You did all of this yourself?
- Yeah. How do you like it?
- Wow!
It's freaking amazing.
What about Jung, and our youngest?
They're not home yet?
- They're sleeping.
- Those little!
How dare they not help out!
What's with your attitude,
when you're the youngest, huh?
Did she drink?
Yeah.
Well, if it's because of alcohol,
it can't be helped.
Madame Jung!
What are you doing?
Did you drink, too?
[The Day of the Party]
Damn it.
Hey, how many guys are
on the basketball team?
Five?
Twelve, including the people
who are on the bench.
Hey, if twelve people from the
basketball team come to our place...
that'd be totally awesome!
- Do you think this is enough alcohol?
- Of course not!
Let's go.
Evil bastard! See?
He didn't even text us once!
Maybe it's because he's so sorry
that he hasn't been in touch?
Hmph! Either way,
he hasn't been in touch!
It's over!
It's! Over!
It's okay, it's okay!
Even if it's hard now, this will be
a good memory down the line!
It's a core memory for First Love-Land!
Did that guy...
really ever love me?
Senior Jung.
Ugh.
I wrote it wrong.
Are you guys done?
There will be 12 guys from the
basketball team, plus three more guys.
So I'm sure that I'll be able to
score with one of those 15 guys.
Just choose a guy among that group.
You need to use a man
to get over another man!
Here, you try!
[Dad]
- Are you okay?
- Why?
Your eyes are all swollen.
Come on, why are you
making her cry again?
No crying!
Stop!
You're even worse!
And why are you crying, now?
Because Senior Jung is crying.
It's hard now because you loved him.
If you were fine after you parted ways,
that'd be even weirder!
Hey, don't try to sympathize
with her, with that kind of voice.
Senior Yoon!
It'd be nice if you were
doing this with us, too!
Can't you skip work, just for today?
I'll call in sick for you.
With that voice?
I don't have as much free
time as all of you do.
If you're not teasing me,
stop it already.
I wasn't trying to tease her.
I feel sorry toward Senior Yoon.
I know, right? I feel guilty, and that
we might be inconveniencing her.
Excuse me, Student.
Do you know where this may be?
Here you go.
[Seoul Mapo-gu, Donggo-dong,
203-36, Belle Epoque]
Oh.
Go straight down this road
and then make a right turn at the
intersection with no streetlights.
- I see.
- Um, are you, by any chance...
Song Ji Won's...
Oh, you know my Ji Won, too?
What's with this
"Night of Males," anyway?
For example, if you called it "Night
of Females," it'd sound weird!
Really? It's kind of a
weird name, isn't it?
Yeah.
Should we change the name to "The
Night of Male Energy Rejuvenation," then?
They're both weird.
Where do I keep hearing this noise from?
Huh?
What the... why are there
so many missed calls?
Dad?
What is it?
Yes, Senior Yoon?
- What?
Senior Song's dad is coming.
Okay.
- My dad is coming!
- What?
Hey, come on!
Hide this stuff!
Hey, it's not him!
Oh, I'm sorry if I stopped you
when you're busy.
No, it's all right.
Move!
- It's this way.
- Oh, really?
Hey! You, Eun Jae's man!
Move the sofa!
- You mean me?
- He's not my man.
- Hurry!
- Yes, ma'am!
Where should I move this?
Over there!
Are you going to
graduate soon, Student?
- Yes.
- I see.
So you're older than Ji Won, eh?
Yes.
Yes. Since you're older than Ji Won,
please look after her.
She doesn't know anything
about the world, you see.
Excuse me?
It's because she's a country bumpkin.
She can't say a word anywhere she goes,
and is the embodiment of innocence!
Senior, help me with this!
Okay!
- Help me with this, too!
- Okay!
Hurry! Hurry!
We're here, sir.
Oh, this is it?
Oh, I'm so sorry.
You seem so busy, too.
You can go now.
- It's all right. Go on.
- Okay.
It's really him this time.
It's really him this time!
Ji Won!
- Hurry!
Got it!
Move, hurry!
- Where?
- Over there!
- Here?
- Yes!
Wait, why me?
Ji Won!
- Everything is ready, right?
- Yeah.
Dad! Sorry, I kept you waiting.
What took so long?
Oh, who's this?
- Please accept my bow!
- Oh, yes!
- Please accept one more!
- Senior Kang!
It was hard to get here, right?
- Oh, kimchi!
- Is this for me?
Yeah, it's kimchi.
- It's hot, right? Come in!
- Please, come in!
Your mom spent all morning
packing these for you.
Put them in the fridge so
that they don't get overripe.
Sheesh.
I actually like overripe kimchi!
Right, guys?
Yeah. Kimchi should be
eaten when it's overripe!
It has tons of probiotics
when it's like that, too!
Well, yes. It's nice to eat overripe
kimchi as a young person, I suppose.
Dad, that's my room over there.
Let's go in there.
Come on, let's go.
Let's go.
- Let's go!
- Oh, it's so hot.
Is this your desk?
Yes.
What about your closet?
It's that one.
Oh. What about your bed?
It's the one that's not lofted.
Why are you swallowing like that?
Um... because I'm thirsty.
Hey, what kinds of thoughts
are you thinking?
Do you think that when guys
swallow like that, it's always...
Just how much porn do you watch? Sheesh.
- I don't watch porn.
- Then, how do you know?
That when guys swallow
like that, it's always... like that.
Well, um...
I saw it in... um... cartoons.
Just what kind of cartoons
are you watching?
Your schedule, huh?
Why'd you come to Seoul, Dad?
Oh, for my friend's daughter's wedding.
You took kimchi to someone's wedding?
You could've just sent it as a package!
It's not like sending packages is free!
Sheesh! I ate so much at the
wedding that I'm so tired.
Dad! No!
You can't sleep! Bad things
will happen if you do!
What? I want to get some shut-eye
before I head back home.
You shouldn't do that! Even if you eat
wherever, you shouldn't sleep wherever!
Get up right now.
This isn't even my bed!
It's getting late,
so hurry and go!
What do you mean, late?
It's not even 5 p.m. yet!
Hey!
Old men like you shouldn't be
wandering the streets late at night!
What?
Go home while the sun is still up.
Don't worry your daughter, all right?
Do you know how dangerous
the world is nowadays?
Geez, you're a dad that always
makes his daughters worry!
- Bye, Dad!
- Okay, go inside!
- Get home safely!
- All right!
All right.
Shall we start over?
Let's go. We have
tons to do.
We have tons to do!
Let's redecorate the place!
We have so much to do!
Come on, let's go!
Come on, girl!
Let's do it!
[From: Honey
What are you doing?]
Hey, Madame Jung!
What are you doing?
Huh?
Go on ahead.
Okay.
[From: Honey
What are you doing?]
I had an average romance.
And I'll have an average farewell.
So... I'll forget him, as time passes.
I know that I'll forget him eventually.
I know that I'll be
forgotten eventually.
Those words help ease my pain,
but they also make me sad.
I'll forget this person,
and date a new person.
And I hope that the next person I date
likes me more than I like them.
Because I have more
than enough experience
being the one who likes
the other person more.
I know that the right thing
to do is to break up with him.
I know that.
That man isn't a good man.
He always does as he pleases, and
breaks promises like they mean nothing.
And gets angry over the smallest things.
And he's even lied to me.
There's plenty of reasons why
I shouldn't like that man.
And the worst reason
among those is that
he doesn't love me as
much as I want him to.
- An Americano, please.
- Yes, sir.
You said that you had something to say.
Go ahead.
Thanks... for everything.
What?
Even if we're breaking up...
I want us to break up properly.
You want to break up?
The reason why
I shouldn't like this man...
- is because...
- Tell me.
You want to break up with me?
There's just one reason
why I like this man.
So why are you saying
things like that?
- That's because...
- It's because I like him.
It's because I like him!
It's because I like him, so, so much.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Age of Youth]
Males, whose hearts are
beating, have all gathered.
This is it!
Youth.
Even though I don't know
what tomorrow brings
I'm going to drink as if
there's no tomorrow.
How far have you
gone with Yoon Jae, Oppa?
We're just schoolmates!
In your imagination?
- That's rated NC-17.
- Rated NC-17!
How could you invite your
dad here, Senior Kang?
You never said that there
was an age restriction.
Are you throwing a party for
old people, or something?
- I thought you broke up.
I got on my knees and
begged for forgiveness.
A silly joke.
Are you going to do
something stupid again?
A passing glance.
A small occurrence that
you thought was nothing.
If only I'd known then.
You have feelings for
Senior Kang, right?
Thinking back on it now
I may have set the stage for
chaos, without meaning to.
[Your nickname is
"The Female Shin Dong Yup."]
Yes, I do like to talk
about perverted things a bit.
I mean, it's fun.
[There are some people
who aren't comfortable with it.]
Who? Are you talking
about Madame Jung?
She likes it too. She's
just pretending not to.
What's wrong with talking
about things like that?
Is there a law saying that only guys
can talk about perverted stuff?
[You also chose the theme: A Night of
Males. Isn't this sexual discrimination?]
I should've called it "The Night of Male
Energy Rejuvenation," right?
[Have you really never
been a relationship, ever?]
You can't believe it, right? After all,
just look at my looks, and my nature
and my personality!
It really is a mystery.
[You've never had your first kiss, then?]
No, I've had that.
As a part of a drinking game.
I was going to use tongue,
too, but they freaked out.
[I don't get why you're so desperate
for a guy. You're still young.]
You think this is normal, then?
When did you first have sex?
[What do you think about
Yoo Eun Jae and Yoon Jin Myung?]
Eun Jae is still really young,
and Senior Yoon is... well...
At any rate, I...
I'm definitely going to lose my
virginity this year, no matter what!
If things keep going like this,
I might die a virgin!
Ugh! Ugh!
No. That can't happen.
Should I just grab any random guy
and ask him to have sex with me?