BioskopKeren,org
This is what it should've been like,
Ah, the energy of virile young men!
Our party,,, no, my party,,,
should've been just like this,
So, why?
Why, damn it?
We have a scrimmage that
came up all of a sudden,
We're sorry,
- You didn't change your number, right?
- No, it's the same number,
The number you have called
is not in service,
Hey, come on, honey, How could you
call me out of the blue like this?
I have plans and stuff, too--
Oh,,, I drank a ton of alcohol,
Hey, Im Sung Min!
You can't fall asleep, man!
- Bye,
- You'll die if you hang up! Wake up!
This is a nightmare,
I have sleep paralysis, is all,
Let's wake up,
I have to wake up!
Wake up!
There we go!
Hey, wake up!
You have to face reality!
Reality?
No,
No!
You can give reality or
whatever to the dogs,
I want to lose consciousness now,
I'm going to the Land of Imagination!
- You can't!
That's not a wall, I'm sure that there's
a door to Hogwarts there somewhere!
I'm going! I'm going,
no matter what it takes!
[Episode 6: You'll Realize Later The
Events of That Day Was a Foreshadow]
Um, what year did you start college?
Uh, in 2013,
Oh, me too!
But I re-took the college exams a
couple of times, so I was born in '93,
Oh, really?
I was born in '94,
but my birthday is early
so I have a lot of
friends who are '93s,
Hey, that doesn't count!
I'm a late '68,
Senior Kang, how could
you bring your dad here?
You never told me that
there was an age limit,
Did I really need to say that, though?
Are you trying to throw a party
for old people, here?
So who told you to choose such
an outrageous punishment?
Ta-da!
Yeah, It's all my fault,
It's all my damn fault!
It's all my fault!
I'm not talking about yours,
How can I clean the windowsill?
That's gross,
Madame Jung!
You said you broke up with him,
I thought you said that he was
a good-for-nothing bastard!
Well, you know, Things just
ended up turning out like this,
Do you know how much I've
cursed him out in my head?
Damn that -----, I didn't
like his stupid mug from the start,
Bastards whose eyes look like that
tend to have ---- tempers,
They have nothing better to do with their
brawn, so they use it against women!
You should castrate assholes like him!
He doesn't deserve to have his tainted
DNA passed down, goddammit!
I ought to chop that
---- eating piece of ---- up!
You weren't the only one,
Great job! Great job!
It's a good thing you broke up,
Why should you waste your time
on a ----- like him?
It'd be better for you to live as a nun,
Guys like him are rotten
to the goddamn core,
What, you wanted to fix that
bastard's temper with your love?
Hey, ----! That piece
of shit is never going to change,
Why are you laughing?
Is it because you didn't curse at him?
Excuse me,
It's awkward, right?
It's a bit embarrassing, right?
You're wondering to yourself
why you're here, right?
At times like this, there's,,,
Music!
Alcohol!
Here!
All right, Let's get things started by
getting sprayed, shall we?
You want it? You want it?
Come on, don't you want to be refreshed?
Looks like it's getting
less lively in here!
Let's just see who'll be
on the receiving end of this!
Let's just see!
I'll just let this go like,,, pshhhh!
Let's down our first drink with one shot!
Come on, everyone, stand up!
All right, gather all the energy you can
muster, and down it in one shot!
- Cheers!
This is so stupid!
Who downs beer in one shot?
It's my decision, all right?
- I'm the king today!
- How come?
Why? Well, because
I'm the only one who's by myself here!
Let's party!
The king will now ask questions!
Mister, What kind of relationship
do you have with Senior Kang?
We just see each other
every now and then,
Hey, come on!
It's true,
So why did you come
here today, then?
Well, she made an emergency
request to me, so,,,
and I had nothing else to do,
You like Senior Kang, right?
If you don't want to answer,
down another beer in one shot!
One shot!
- Whoa,
- What about you, Mister?
- Why are you calling me that?
It's my decision, Why? Because
I'm the only one who's by myself here!
You two fought, right?
How did you make amends?
Do you want to break up with me?
So why did you say
something like that, then?
Because you,,,
I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
It's all my fault,
I got on my knees and
begged for forgiveness,
So why did you do something that you'd
have to apologize like that for?
- Hey, don't ask stuff like that!
- Shush!
I know, right?
I'm kind of an idiot,
Are you going to do
anything idiotic again?
Hey, why are you drinking?
Don't drink!
Hey!
You can't!
I know that our baby Eun Soon
has a crush on another guy,
So how did you get invited here?
Um, Yoon-Jae-said-that-she,,,
wanted-you-at-her-party,
Let's go,
What?
Well,,,
- How far have you gone with Eun Jae?
- We're just schoolmates--
In your imagination?
- That's rated NC-17,
- NC-17!
All right, truth bomb time!
Why is it that Song Ji Won
is so unpopular among guys?
It's quite mysterious, isn't it?
I mean, just look at my face,
And my body,
I even have a great personality,
to boot, So why?
Do you hate perfect women?
Well, no, Rather than that,,,
I hate -blank- type of woman!
Fill in the blank!
Women who talk a lot,
Girls who are nosy!
Girls with no tact are a bit,,,
So,,, a woman who talks a lot,
is nosy, and has no tact! That is,,,
- You!
- Look, this is as big as your tooth!
- Wow!
- How'd you find that?
- Here, compare it! Look!
Right?
Hey, why are you comparing people's
teeth to that? It makes me feel bad!
It really does look alike, though,
- Hey!
- What, is there someone in there?
You're being too much!
Allow me to help you with your payment,
All right,
Table 32, 220,000 won, please,
I'll assist you with your payment,
Thank you,
- Thank you for the meal!
- Please come again!
Um,,, the person you think would
sleep butt-naked! One, two, three!
You,
No, I totally bundle myself up
right before bed,
- Drink! Drink!
- Get the alcohol down! Down! Down! Down!
- How long will I have to dance like--
- Drink!
- Whoa!
All right,
I'll be asking a question now,
The person among us who'd most
likely molest someone on the subway!
One, two, three!
You,
Why me?
Why? Based on what?
- Your physiognomy,
- The impression you give off,
It just seems like you
have that kind of fate,
- You too,,,
- Drink!
- Get the alcohol down! Down! Down! Down!
All right, I'm drinking,
How long will you make
me dance like this?
- Whoa!
The person among us,,,
- Ew!
- Ew! Gross,
who's most likely to be
hiding a huge secret!
One, two, three!
I'm not doing this anymore,
I'm not doing this anymore!
Damn it!
Why do you all hate me?
It's not fair!
Geez, he's so petty,
- Why is he--
- Hey, what are you doing?
Did you eat that?
Spit it out!
Quick!
There are peanuts in here,
Are you okay?
Can you breathe? Are you itchy
anywhere, or have any rashes?
Is your neck swelling up?
Sheesh,
Why are you so careless, when
you said you have an allergy to them?
I don't have an allergy to peanuts,
What?
Yeah, you do!
You told me in the cafeteria before
that you're allergic to them,
so you can't eat them,
Well, it's true that I don't eat peanuts
but I'm not allergic to them,
My older brother
had an allergy to them,
What the hell?
You scared the crap out of me!
Yeah, I thought something
terrible happened,
- Oh my, oh my,
- What is this?
You,,, like Eun Jae, right?
- Senior Song, it's not like that!
- Yeah,
What?
I do like her,
What did you say?
I said that I like her!
Congratulations!
- Let's drink to Jong Yeol's love!
- Yeah!
- Is everything going okay?
- Yes,
Did you give that customer from
before a discount on their wine?
- Are you done?
- Yes, Chef!
Hey!
What the hell are you
so distracted about?
I'm sorry, sir!
Hurry and wash it off!
Okay, okay,
- Good work, everyone!
Mr, Jae Hwan,
you're going home now, right?
Take me home, please!
Looks like you did me a favor
by getting yourself a motorcycle!
Yoon Jin Myung!
The tabs don't quite match up,
- 197,000 won,
- Next,
230,000 won,
Next,
801,000 won,
You feel like I was too hard on you
over just 3,000 won, right?
No, that's not true,
No matter how small the figures are,
the numbers need to be exact,
That's the fundamentals of pretty
much everything, really,
Are you worried about
missing the last train?
I'll take you home, so don't worry,
I have about thirty minutes,
If you're going to be
like that, just go,
How am I supposed to talk freely
when you're acting like that?
Enjoy,
Hey, this pose is the one
that's all the rage lately!
- What are you talking about!
- It totally is!
- No, it is!
- What are you saying?
- Sheesh,
- Nah, Girls love this,
- No, they like this!
- Hey, come on!
- Hey, we had a great time!
- Bye, honey!
- Okay, see you again!
- Bye!
- Goodbye,
Honey!
Yeah?
- Call me, okay?
- Okay,
Eun Jae!
Um, excuse me,,,
Eun Jae, Eun Jae,
Eun Jae!
Go on, now,
- I'll be going, then,
- Bye!
- Are you okay?
- Senior Kang!
Are you okay?
Damn it, why did you
spill beer on the floor?
You were clapping before,
saying that you liked it!
Hey, when are we going
to clean all of this up?
Yeah, who knows,
Did that thing disappear?
Huh?
You said that it'd disappear if there
was enough yang energy,
- That's weird,
- What is it?
Why is it acting like that?
What?
It's totally red,
What does that mean?
Rage,
It's super angry,
Ugh! Ugh!
I can't stand it,
What? What's the matter?
It's so angry that it's
making my head hurt,
Hey! You're just acting because
you don't want to clean, right?
Get out here and clean! You're the
one who made the biggest mess!
- Damn it,
- No, I have to lie down,
Hey, let's clean tomorrow,
What, huh?
Dad?
Damn it, I drank way too much,
I'm really going to
regret this tomorrow,
Hey, no!
That was weird,
Senior Kang was being weird,
and Mister was being weird, too,
Everyone is so weird!
Ugh, I feel sick,
The person among us who's most
likely to be hiding a huge secret!
Secret, huh?
Well, everyone has secrets,
Secret,
Secrets,
Oh well, I have the universe on my side!
The person among us who's most
likely to be hiding a huge secret!
One, two, three!
- Drink! Drink!
- Get the alcohol down! Down! Down! Down!
Wow, you're awesome!
The celebration was over,
The anticipation and excitement
surrounding this event were all but gone
and everyone returned to their safe
and boring everyday lives,
Eun Jae,
Your older brother has an allergy?
Yes,
But you said that you didn't
have an older brother,
What's going on?
- Do you have an older brother?
- No,
- I had an older brother,
- So what happened?
He died because of his peanut allergy,
Wow, allergies are so scary,
However, their everyday lives
that started again after that night
were not the same
as they'd been before,
The slight anomaly in our lives
came to affect our daily lives,
This irregularity caused
a fracture in our routines,
No matter how much we'd sweep and clean,
our daily lives would never be the same,
The impact that this
celebration had upon us--
That's enough of your damn soliloquy!
Start cleaning with us, already!
You're the one who made
the biggest mess!
I feel like I'm going to die,
If I get up now, I'll vomit,
I'll definitely vomit,
So who told you to
drink so damn much?
Youth,
Even though I don't know
what tomorrow brings
I'll drink like there's no tomorrow,
About that guy from yesterday,,,
what does he do for a living?
- I'm not so sure myself,
- Huh?
You brought a virtual
stranger here, then?
And through the fracture
that this celebration created
we soon became privy to the deepest
and darkest parts of each other,
Is the creature living on the dark
side of the moon a rabbit?
Or, is it a monster?
I'll stop!
Geez,
Wow, we sure drank a lot,
- Senior,
- Yes, my child?
Guys joke about things like
that all the time, right?
They say that they like people
during drinking games and stuff
and say things like, "let's go out,"
Yeah, there are some guys like that,
Right?
I'm sure that's what it was,
Our daily lives, which the
celebration affected,
Secrets that we'd hid under the surface
came to see the light of day, and--
Ugh! Ugh, I feel like I'm going to die!
Oh my gosh, If I ever touch
alcohol again, I'm Dog Ji Won!
Ugh, my head,
I'll leave the rest to you, child,
- Want these?
- Hmm,
Wow, there's so many different kinds!
Hey, this looks good!
Wow, look at these colors!
They're so pretty!
[Senior Kang/Kang Yi Na]
Oh! I was going to do the dishes,
Oh, it's okay, I'll do it,
You can just get some rest,
- Honey,
- Huh?
Why are you being so good to me?
Because I don't know when
I'll be cruel to you again,
Please, enjoy,
It's best to spend money
that you got easily, with carelessness,
What good would it do you
to be stingy with that money?
Geez,
I'm right though, aren't I?
You remind me of my bathroom mirror,
What are you talking about?
You're too honest, which pisses me off,
Friends shouldn't Photoshop the
reality of their lives to one another,
So? Who did you bring
to the party instead of me?
Um,,,
Do guys cry too?
What are you talking about?
When was the last time you cried?
Last week,
Why, so you could get money
from your sugar mama?
Yep,
No, I haven't cried since I was 15,
Hey!
That has nothing to do with me,
Hey, come on, now,
Family is family,
You know that old tune?
"Forget about all of your woes,"
"My mother, who works
tirelessly night and day,,,"
Oh, and, "my mother's debt is my debt!"
Trying to make people pay for
other people's debts is against the law,
You little--
You're not going to get ready?
- That little--
- Hey, hey,
Keep still, punk,
You can't even fight,
I'll help you process your payment,
That'll be 118,500 won,
Did you enjoy your meal?
Yes,
Thank you,
- Let's go,
- I'm so worn out,
Joo Hyun Hee already left,
I'm not waiting for Ms, Hyun Hee,
About those people from earlier,,,
will you be all right?
Yes,
I'll take you home,
Why?
Do I really need a reason--
Do I,,,
really need a reason to do that for you?
I told you not to be nice to me,
Do you think that it was easy
for me to say that to you?
What, do you think
this is easy for me, then?
Do you think I'm totally
fine with being rejected?
Every time you push me away like this,
I hate it, and I feel so humiliated!
So that's why,,,
you shouldn't,
I like her,
I like Yoon Jae,
No way,
I like Yoon Jae!
I like you,
Oh, you're wearing a skirt!
Oh, I was organizing my
clothes, and saw it, so,,,
and I thought it'd be a waste
to throw it away, so I put it on,
It looks weird, right?
- I'll go change,
- No, no!
Come over here!
You look pretty!
Look, It's cute, right?
I bet Jong Yeol will be so happy
that he'll piss himself,
You and your nasty mouth!
Why, I ought to,,,
Oh ho,
Come with me for a second,
Look, You look different just
by trimming your eyebrows!
Don't you have any other bags?
No,
- Oh,,, oh well, then,
- I'll be going, then!
Wait!
You think that a bag
is just a bag, right?
Make sure you take
good care of my baby,
Be super careful,
And be gentle with it!
- Hello!
- Have you all been well?
- Yes!
All right, we'll be talking about
evolutionary psychology,
And we'll be focusing on the
psychology of relationships!
All right, Why do men
like glamorous women?
Why do girls like rich guys? Why are male
animals usually more fancy-looking?
We'll be delving into our topic
by using these questions,
Well, men wish to pass down their DNA by
dating as many women as possible,
And women want a reliable man
who will provide for her and the family,
I've made a list of relevant readings and
sent them out as an announcement
so those of you who are interested
can go ahead and read those materials,
And all of you, date a little! Got that?
All right, that's it for today,
- Thank you!
Wow, I can barely recognize you,
You've become a fine lady overnight,
Did you drop something?
Your neck is going
to look like a turtle's,
Square your shoulders a bit!
What's this, huh?
Don't do it,
If you do it, I'll charge you
for attempted murder,
What, do you have hemorrhoids again?
Ew, come on!
- Wow, that got a rise out of you,
- What do you want?
What goes around comes around!
Those who break their promises
will get their comeuppance!
You said that you got the
basketball team to come, too,
It wouldn't have mattered
if I was there or not,
Figures, It's a good thing
you didn't come,
Nobody would've been able to see
you among all those tall guys!
Did you have a good time?
Totally,
The guys on the basketball team
sure know how to have fun!
I got so drunk, and a bunch of other
people from our school came, too,
And do you know who else came?
- Seo Jang Won!
- What? Really?
He was so tall,
Aw man, I should've come!
That's weird,
You're here, ma'am?
["The Bracelet Brought Me Luck":
Survivor Ms, Kang Yi Na]
[Ms, Kang (age 18) Seeking Therapy
After Suffering Severe Wounds]
- Hey,
- Yeah?
Do you remember what you said
when I said I'd work for you?
What did I say?
"Don't you dare think
of dating while working,"
I said that?
What, am I the only one who
took those words to heart?
Why, do you want to date someone?
Not exactly, but,,,
Just a second,
[From Unknown Number: Hello!]
[Try to guess who this is,]
Look at this punk,
playing around,
[The "Night of Males" party,]
[I'm the guy who was the
most charismatic of the lot,]
Tell me who you are
before I block your number,
[Heh, you have a temper,]
It's Go Doo Young,
Crazy bastard,
I'd like to meet up with you,
And why would I meet up with you?
I have something to talk to you about,
What?
It's something I should talk
to you about in person,
It's about Ye Eun,
What is it that you wanted
to talk about? Shoot,
We should act our age
at places like these,
Here,
You don't like the fact that
I'm dating Ye Eun, right?
Was it that obvious?
I don't like the fact that I'm
dating Ye Eun, either,
All I'll do is make her into a bad girl,
A good girl like Ye Eun
should be dating a better man,
Then you can just become
a better man for her,
I can't, It's too late for me,
Break up with her, then,
I can't do that, either,
My mom committed suicide,
When I was in first grade,
And my dad was with another
woman when it happened,
He got remarried after a year or so,,,
but then he got another woman,
Why are you telling me this?
Just because,
- I wanted you to know,
- Why?
Why me, of all people?
Because I feel like you have
as many scars as I do,
Look at this punk, messing around,
Does this sob story usually
help you win over women?
What kind of bullshit
are you trying to pull?
You feel like you're a bad boy, right?
No, you're not a bad boy,
You're an evil bastard,
Son of a bitch,
How dare you,
Oh, you're home already?
I thought you said you had plans,
I was planning to drop by
secretly, and then leave,
Just like "The Snail Bride,"
You can't!
I'm all sweaty, so I smell,
Honey,
Why do you even like me?
What do you like about
a bastard like me?
Hey, what's wrong?
Did something sad happen to you?
Hey there!
I'm home!
What's with her?
- There's a reason,
- What is it?
The fact that I don't know
is the problem,
What the hell,
What's with her?
- I'm sure there's a reason,
- Oh, whatever,
What's the matter? You were in
such a good mood this morning,
This is all you Seniors' fault!
I told you that
that wasn't the case!
But you kept saying that he liked me,
though you didn't even know anything!
Now I have feelings for him,
when he doesn't have feelings for me!
My heart just totally skipped a beat,
Aw, me too!
She should say things like that
in front of that bastard!
Hey, Ugly,
When do you want to see the
movie? Let's go tomorrow,
Let's go inside,
What kind of unfair trade is this?
I went to the party for you,
saved you from getting punished
and now,
I'm buying you tickets for a movie,
This is so unfair,
What the hell? You're the one
who offered to do this,
What are you saying?
Speak up and stop mumbling!
How come you didn't wear
a skirt today, though?
You looked so pretty with a skirt on,
Wow, the ending of that
movie was crazy, right?
I wonder how the director
thought of such an ending?
Right?
What do I do if he wants to kiss me?
Damn it, I should've asked
the rest of the girls before I came!
There were onions in that
sandwich I ate before, too!
I should've used mouthwash
one more time after that!
He'll definitely try to kiss me,
Am I supposed to tell him
that he shouldn't?
But, what if he gets
angry if I say no?
Oh, we're already here,
You can't cross this line, okay?
If you do, I'll get kicked out,
All right,
I won't cross that line,
Go inside,
Go on ahead,
No, you go inside first,
No, you can go ahead first,
Um, no, You have to go in first for me to
go home without worrying about you,
Go inside, then,
Okay,
You can't!
Um, you can't!
That wasn't my intention,
Oh,
Wow, And here, I was going to
try to take things slow,
But if you're in that much
of a rush to speed things up,,,
- Have a safe trip home!
- Ow!
What's the matter?
Was someone chasing after you?
- What?
- Oh,
That's not it,
Judging from the redness of her
cheeks and the color of her aura,,,
It was a kiss!
You locked lips with your honey!
- No, I didn't!
- Oh, please,
You look like you two
used a bit of tongue, too!
Sheesh!
That's weird,
What could it be?
What are you talking about?
I feel like I've forgotten
something important,
Like what?
I'm frustrated because I don't
know what that is, obviously,
It feels just like having enoki
mushrooms stuck between my teeth,
What could it be?
Oh!
There's no use in protesting,
- Please, no!
- You're the one who wrote this down!
I'm sure you never thought that
you'd be the one to be punished,
Ji Won is the one who
wrote that punishment down?
Yes, She's the one
who came up with this,
Ta-da!
Hey, come on,
Might as well get it over with,
Fine! I'll do it!
I'll do it, damn it!
I can't wuss out now,
All right!
I'm doing it!
- Song Ji Won!
All right, already!
Oh ho!
What the hell! I don't
look good in those photos!
What? You look just
like yourself,
What are you saying?
I don't look like this!
Look! Do I look like this?
Yeah, you totally look like that,
No, I don't!
I don't look like this!
You don't know
what your face looks like,
Why wouldn't I?
I see it in the mirror every day,
But you've never seen
your face for yourself,
That's why you don't know if the mirror
or the camera is more trustworthy,
Then, you're the only person
who can't see your own face,
Isn't that kind of scary?
Oh, whatever,
Anyway, delete it!
Delete it right now, Song!
Yes, ma'am,
Did I get fatter?
Our electricity bill this
month was too high,
You should've taken it easy,
We're out of toilet paper, too,
Let's go and buy it together tomorrow,
What the hell!
I didn't gain any weight!
No, you totally did,
Damn it!
No incident starts out dramatically,
Everything that happens in our
daily lives is due to cause and effect,,,
- Do you have an older brother?
- No,
To tell you the truth,,,
I can see ghosts,
And there's one over there right now,
In retrospect, there were
signs hidden everywhere,
There's someone whom
I wish were dead,
Oh, so I guess I
did kill them that time,
A small joke,
A passing glance,
The meaning behind a sigh
that you thought meant nothing,
If only I'd known what
they'd meant, back then,
Then, what about people
who are comatose?
Where are their souls?
- I did have an older brother,
- I don't have any allergies,
He died when I was in 4th grade,
and he was in 7th grade,
But, just as foreshadowing only
becomes obvious in hindsight
one only realizes the gravity of
each passing second only after it's gone,
Dad?
What is it this time?
That thing over there,,,
is the spirit of someone
who was murdered,
Thinking back on that day now,,,
I may have set the stage for everything,
despite not having any bad intentions,
Subtitles by Dramalove,TV
[Yoo Eun Jae's Fashion Sense]
My fashion sense?
People tell me that I dress
like a student quite often,
She dresses like a high schooler,
It's a real issue,
No, even high schoolers don't dress like
that anymore, Maybe middle schoolers?
Fashion is a challenge,
Well, I don't know, I
haven't really thought about it,
[Jung Ye Eun's Fashion Sense?]
Lovely?
It is cute, but it's a bit,,,
She goes overboard,
It's not like she's in kindergarten,
Having no self-confidence means
that you have little dignity
and having little dignity means that
one has no confidence in oneself,
And the fact that one has
no confidence in oneself
means that one doesn't
know oneself very well,
Pink is a bit,,,
[Kang Yi Na's Fashion Sense]
It turns heads,
It does look pretty,
It's too much,
Well, there are times she walks
around naked, so that's an issue,
She does dress well, but,,,
I've never really
thought about it,
[Song Ji Won's Fashion Sense]
- My fashion sense, eh?
It embodies freedom,
- It's a bit strange,
- It's a never-ending challenge,,,
To put it simply,
it's a disaster,
An expression of my identity,
A crazy bitch,
One could call it avant-garde,
[Yoon Jin Myung's Sense of Fashion]
- Senior Yoon's sense of fashion?
- What?
Whatever is easiest to wear,
[Rate everyone in terms of looks!]
Senior Kang, Me, Senior Jung,
Senior Yoon, and then Senior Song,
Me and Senior Kang are about the same,
Then Yoo Eun Jae, then Senior Yoon,
And then Song Ji Won?
Hmm,
Senior Kang, Me, Yoo Eun Jae,
Madame Jung, Then Senior Yoon,
I'm first, and then the rest of them
are about the same, don't you think?
Why are you asking me
something like that?