Subtitles by DramaFever
What now?
The ghost over there...
is the ghost of someone
who was murdered.
I don't have any allergies.
He died when I was in fourth grade,
and he was in seventh grade.
Dad?
Joon Myung! My child!
Do not worry.
His condition has been stabilized.
What?
He's back to normal.
If I think that someone likes me,
I'll become weak.
If I become weak now,
it'll really be the end for me.
Hey!
Going to your part-time job?
Wait, no. You don't go to the
restaurant on Thursdays.
Are you moving today, then?
Wow, you didn't even put on makeup
properly, and your lips are all chapped.
Wouldn't it be nice if someone
was helping you out
since you're living so diligently?
Shame on your mom.
Oh well, then. I'll have to help you.
I'll take off the last month's
interest. Well? How about it?
Want to pay me in twenty installments?
I'm doing you a favor, you know!
You have 8 million won
in your bank account
so I'm sure that you could
get 2 million more, somewhere.
If you don't have any money,
I'll introduce you to a good lender.
There's tons of lenders that
are great, with low interest!
Think about it, okay?
Got it?
- What is this?
- Where is this coming from?
- Hey, come on!
- Hey!
- Go, go, go!
- Damn it!
Damn it, I got wet down to my underwear!
It's the ghost of someone
who was murdered.
What are you doing here?
What did you use the documents
you asked me last time for?
I already told you that I'm never
repaying your debts again!
Is that what you came here
to talk about?
You've never once asked me
how your brother is doing.
Why do I need to ask
how a dead person is doing?
[Episode 7: I'm Someone Who Should
Not Be Happy - Sleep Paralysis]
I like you.
I like you!
Eun Jae!
I like you, Eun Jae!
- Hello.
- Oh, hello.
- Someone's sitting here.
- What?
- Hey!
- Yeah.
Sit here.
Oh, sorry.
Can I sit here?
Who else would, if not you?
Of course this seat is for you.
You're early.
Yes.
Do you take this class too, Senior?
No. I'm just here to see you.
All of this was a prank,
this whole time!
You fell for it, right?
You totally fell for it, right?
I think she did!
Right?
Wow!
What are you doing?
What?
Oh... nothing.
Geez, you silly girl!
What are you so distracted about,
so early in the morning?
Senior!
This is seriously the last time!
- If you ask me a favor like this again--
- All right, all right.
I love you,
Kim An So Young!
I love you!
Ugh, geez.
Sheesh!
Let's go inside.
I like you.
I like you!
Whatever. You say that to everyone!
- I l-like you.
- But you love someone else?
Who are you talking to?
Is Senior Jung in her room?
- What's she doing?
- Madame Jung? Just chilling in her room.
- Why?
- I have a question for her.
Ask me instead!
But I don't think you'd
know anything about it.
Say what?
I don't know something that
Madame Jung knows about?
What the hell do you
take me for, punk?
- What is it?
- Just a second!
When you first started going
out with your boyfriend...
how did things start off?
So, um... did you two say,
"we're dating now!"
Or did you two start things off
more naturally?
Why?
Well... just because.
Your man is being lukewarm, eh?
No, it's not like that, but...
You know, kids nowadays
are so sly that they do everything
that should be saved for a
proper relationship, without dating.
- That's called "hooking up."
- Really?
Well, did he officially ask you out?
- Officially--
- "You and I are dating, starting today."
Or something along those lines.
Did you and your boyfriend
start off like that?
Of course! He gave me flowers saying,
"this is our first day as a couple."
Did he say for sure that he likes you?
Well, there was just that time,
here, at the house...
- That's not a confession!
- No, it isn't!
You're supposed to look
each other in the eye
and say, "I like you.
Do you like me back?"
Yeah! If he's going to do things
properly, he should be on his knees!
Well yes, but times have changed.
Let's stop.
We're going to make her cry.
You're uneasy about a
lot of things, right?
You feel like he may have said
that he liked you impulsively
and it feels like you're the
only one that likes him.
Did you feel that way, too?
You know, your phone is really silent.
Shouldn't it be going off like crazy?
Yeah. And you miss him,
even if you're with him!
And whenever you turn a corner,
you think about him!
And when you wake up,
there's a text from him!
Sheesh, it's so fun to tease you.
Stop it!
Oh, so he is hitting you up! Whoo!
Mom?
Oh, never mind.
I bet she's in for a hard time.
When girls like her
date for the first time--
Mom! I can't understand what
you're saying, if you talk like that!
Here, breathe first.
Are you okay?
All right, talk to me.
There was a car accident,
so they're at the hospital now?
Then first, take a cab
to the hospital. Got it?
I'll call you again in 30 minutes.
I think I have to go.
Something came up with my family.
Huh? Okay.
Huh? You're here, Eun Jae?
You were the one who got hurt, Mister?
Oh, um... I just got a small scratch.
Your mom overreacted again, didn't she?
She said that the car crashed
into a truck, so I was shocked.
That's a relief.
Yeah.
Ms. Jung Yi? Ms. Jung Yi.
Eun Jae is here.
Huh?
Eun Jae.
I really thought something terrible
had happened!
He was bleeding so much from his head--
What are you talking about?
It wasn't like that at all!
I only bled a teeny bit!
Geez, thinking about how
shocked I was before...
All right, all right.
I'm sorry.
Here, have some ice cream.
Here.
Do you want this, Eun Jae?
No, that's fine.
I'll go and wash my hands.
- This is so good!
- It's good?
That's good.
All right, eat up.
Well, that's how it is.
It can't be helped.
Thanks for a fun time up until now.
- I'll call you sometime.
- Don't.
If you do, it'll be hard for
me to forget about you.
If we're breaking up,
it's best to break off all contact.
Is that right?
Would you like to order?
I'll have the jjajangmyun.
Me too.
Yes, I'll get that for you.
Men are so simple.
When they're trying to win you over,
they buy you multi-course meals
but whenever you're breaking up, it's
always jjajangmyun or jjamppong.
Oh, but if it's sushi,
you know that he's loaded!
How come you've never told me
not to live like this, though?
I don't have the right to tell
others how to live their lives.
What kind of work do you do, Mister?
Oh. How about this?
Let's ask each other one thing
we're curious about.
I'll start things off.
Do you have a lover, or a wife?
What? Why not?
It's my turn, isn't it?
Ah.
Why do you live your life like that?
What the hell? This is different
from what you just said.
I'm not telling you
not to live that way.
I'm just wondering if there's
a specific reason why.
It's hard to explain, but...
Let's say that you're crossing
the street on the crosswalk.
You're supposed to cross when
the light is green, right?
And you're supposed to be
careful while doing so.
But, if you get hit by a
drunk driver, you're done for.
Isn't that right?
So what I'm trying to say is, you don't
know what may happen to you, in life.
So what's the point of
living a diligent life?
Living recklessly is the best!
You know, people who open 10-year
investment accounts fascinate me.
How does that person know that
they'll still be alive in ten years?
Isn't that right?
It's my turn now, right?
Why did you cry that day?
The night you did the shadow puppets.
Oh.
Well...
rather than saying that I cried...
Sheesh.
It's because I was reminded of the past.
About what, exactly?
When I used to play with my daughter.
Oh.
She's dead now.
It's your turn now, Mister.
What you said before, about not
knowing what'll happen to you in life...
how did you come to think like that?
You're still quite young.
To tell you the truth...
I've been on TV before.
And in the newspaper, too.
Once, I went on a trip in high school,
and almost died.
People say that life seems precious when
they have a close-to-death encounter
but that wasn't the case for me.
Nothing felt real, no matter what I did.
And concepts like the future, or a
future career all seemed like a joke.
And I didn't want to study anymore.
Well, I never liked studying,
anyway, but...
It's my turn now, right?
What kind of women do you like, Mister?
What kind of woman is your ideal type?
I don't really have anything like that.
Come on, you can't pass on a question.
You have to answer everything.
Go ahead.
An innocent girl
with long, flowing hair?
A black girl?
A woman with hair like Shin Saimdang,
with her hair all done up?
Which one is it? Tell me!
If you don't tell me,
I'll just keep going.
A glamorous woman?
Back in my day,
short hair was all the rage.
A short-haired girl, eh?
Ask me your question.
How did you survive that accident?
Why are you curious about that?
Just because.
There was no method, per se.
It was all just luck.
Just like drawing straws.
It wasn't because of my
personality, or my age.
It's red. It's angry.
It's full of rage.
It's the ghost of someone
who was murdered.
This is no fun.
Let's stop, and just drink.
Did you get home?
How's your mom?
I can't fall asleep,
trying to sleep by myself.
I can't sleep with another
person in my bed.
Oh, it's fine! I won't
move an inch while I'm sleeping!
I'll get in touch with you later.
Who is that?
Nobody.
Ah, this is so nice!
So nice! So nice! So nice!
Does Mister know about this side of you?
Yeah. He says that it's cute.
Hey!
Did you get a call from your
dad's sister, by any chance?
No, I didn't.
They're moving,
but they're short on cash.
So they kind of seem as if they
want me to give them some money.
What should I do?
Just pretend like you don't notice.
Whatever.
But, she knows how much life insurance
money we got from your father's death!
I'd feel bad acting like I don't notice.
Should we give them
a little bit of money?
Don't!
If you give them money once,
they'll keep asking for it.
But still--
That money isn't yours!
Oh... fine, then.
You know, you get
really scary sometimes.
Dad!
Oh, it's okay.
It's okay.
Mom.
Huh?
Do you think about Dad?
Of course.
I do, sometimes.
When?
He just pops into my mind
every now and then.
If I see someone that looks similar
to him, I think about him
and I think about him when
I see his favorite foods.
I saw some peaches
when I went to Janghae last time
and I thought of your dad.
Your dad loved peaches.
I'm sure he'd be eating tons of
peaches if he were still alive.
Well, I'm sure he's eating all the
peaches he wants, in heaven.
Heaven?
Well, yeah.
Since he was a good person.
I'm sure he went to heaven.
Right?
You should feel thankful toward me, Mom.
You should really feel
thankful toward me, Mom.
Hello?
I'll show you to your seat.
I wanted to drop by here,
since I heard that it just opened.
What do you want to eat?
The menu looks similar to ours.
Excuse me.
What's the chef's special here?
I'm someone with lots of money.
It's not in the millions range.
It's billions of won.
So why would a person like
that open a restaurant?
To make pennies off
the business, as profit?
No. I'm just working on the details,
while working on a much bigger picture.
On production, distribution,
and sales, too.
I'm starting off getting
involved in a business
and I think I'll be in charge
of a chain restaurant.
I have to start a new business, but...
I need someone who has
relevant work experience
but knows about
business management, too.
Oh, but did you say that you were aiming
to work for a huge conglomerate?
- No.
- Really?
That was the best, back in the day.
Well, that's taken care of.
I've watched you for a long time, and
I know what kind of person you are.
I do, but...
I don't know if you're
loyal to me or not.
Mr. Manager!
- Oh!
- Hello.
What brings you here?
I heard that this place just opened up,
so I wanted to see what it was like.
It's similar to what
I imagined it'd be like.
But...
how are you going to manage to scope the
place out, when it's just you two men?
Well, we just need to know how
skilled their kitchen staff is, so...
- Goodbye, then.
- Yes.
Please take a seat here.
It seems like it's mostly
steak on their menu.
What are you doing? Eat up.
Well? How is it?
- It's crappy.
- What?
It's not that bad.
Does it hurt?
A little.
Does it hurt a lot?
Sheesh, you should've been careful!
Your body isn't yours anymore!
Half of it is mine now!
All right?
I'm serious!
I can point out exactly which
parts of you are mine now, but...
Is your mom okay?
Yes.
Oh yeah. You said you'd contact me
yesterday, so why didn't you?
Are you playing hard to get with me?
Geez, you just went and learned
the bad stuff, didn't you?
It's fine. You can touch it.
I'm completely yours, so...
touch me as much as you want.
Senior.
You're terrible.
How could you call me "Senior?"
You could call me "Honey," "Darling,"
or even "Mr. Jong Yeol!"
What? What do you want to say?
Can you buy me some ice cream?
Ice cream?
I saw someone eating it yesterday,
and I've been wanting some since then.
Why didn't you buy
one for yourself, then?
Because I wanted to ask you
to buy it for me.
Sheesh!
So you know how to say cute things too,
my little troublemaker?
Let's go. I'll buy you some ice cream.
- It's delicious!
- Is it?
Mom, you should be thankful toward me.
You really should be thankful toward me.
Happy?
Did you have a prior engagement?
I have to go to my part-time job
at the convenience store.
You don't need to do things
like that anymore.
If the project I told you
about before goes well
you won't have to do part-time jobs.
Let down your hair.
It looks a lot nicer down.
How about you transform a bit,
once in a while?
It's no fun if you look the
same all the time.
Take your hands off.
That hairstyle looks better on you.
Have some self-confidence.
The more confident a woman is,
the prettier she is.
I...
thought that we were going to a cafe,
or something like that.
How could we talk about important things
at a place like a coffee shop?
And it won't create the
right atmosphere, either.
It's quiet here, so it's
perfect for talking.
What are you doing?
Come inside.
What are you doing? You're here,
already. Stop acting old-fashioned.
It's Pororo.
I had these at my house, too.
It's pretty common to see
everywhere, isn't it?
Yes. It's pretty common to see.
It's nothing major.
Thinking about it,
they're not too different than me.
But for some strange reason,
they make me scared
and make things hard for me.
Just like someone who has an
overwhelming amount of power.
I guess other people can haunt you, too.
What are you saying?
You make me feel
as if I'm being haunted.
As if I'm stuck in sleep paralysis.
What are you saying?
Are you just going to
keep standing there?
If you have something to say to me,
I'll listen to you from here.
How am I supposed to talk about
something important while I'm standing?
Hey, have you even heard anything
that I've said to you thus far?
I need to confirm for myself
whether or not you're loyal to me--
And what does it mean
to be loyal to you?
Just the two of us drinking alcohol,
at a place like this?
If that's what it entails, I have no
intention of becoming loyal to you.
You... hey.
You still haven't hit
rock-bottom yet, have you?
No. I have hit rock-bottom.
That's why I'm suffering from this
"sleep paralysis"
you're putting me through
and that's why...
I came all the way here, too.
If you have nothing to say,
I'll be going now.
Fine. Go, if you want to go.
I'm not driving you back, though.
Go!
There's no more buses for today.
Where are you headed?
Get in. I'll take you
wherever you need to go.
It's fine.
Senior, the water is boiling!
What happened?
Are you okay?
Did you burn yourself?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Oh, you should've been more careful!
Looks like you're quite unlucky lately.
You keep getting hurt.
I know the reason why.
It's because she's distracted,
thanks to her Honey.
You dating scamps!
How dare you leave me in the dust and
get yourself a boyfriend before me?
You wicked thing! So, how did you do it?
How did you seduce him, huh?
What's your secret?
What does he like about you?
Your depressing attitude?
Your puppy-like face?
Your flat chest?
What, are you laughing?
Hey, I'm pissed as it is!
How dare you laugh!
Tell me how you seduced him, right now!
Spit it out!
He said that my smile is cute.
Your smile?
I can do that, too!
Stop smiling!
It's so creepy!
But didn't our Eun Soon
like a different guy?
Yeah, the guy who looks like
he jumped out of the 80s!
Why did you change your mind?
- I like her.
- What?
I said, I like her!
What? Are you serious?
Wait, so you like him just because
he said that he likes you?
How dare you date
in such a passive manner!
- Break up with him, right now!
- What?
What are you going to do
if he says that he doesn't like you?
Are you going to hate him, too?
Just break up with him.
You should be an independent
woman who don't need no man!
This is the 21st Century!
And you're any better, when you're
desperately seeking out a man? Shut up.
It's not like you need to actually date
to know how it works!
Do you need to eat it to know
if it's bean paste or just poop?
- Yep.
- Damn it!
Hey, shut up.
All you need to do is
remember this one thing.
Just like the other person
less than they like you.
What if you end up liking
them more, though?
You have to hide that fact,
and pretend like you like them less.
Do you really have to do that?
Yeah, do you really have to do that?
Do whatever you want, if you want
to be at the other person's mercy.
Whatever. Just like him
as much as you like him.
Like him as much as your heart desires!
The fact that you have someone that
you like is a blessing in itself.
But if the person that you like
actually likes you back
that's a straight-up miracle.
Hallelujah!
Geez!
Owie.
Is there a bus that goes to Seoul?
They've already all left.
What?
You still haven't seen "that" yet?
No, I haven't.
This is bad. Did you think babies
just pop out of people's bellybuttons?
No, right?
You didn't think a stork
brought people babies, right?
Senior, have you seen "that," too?
Yeah. When I was in ninth grade.
Girls like her who aren't even ready
have been given this god-given chance
while people like me who've
been ready for ages
have been waiting for
our chance for so long.
Oh well.
I have no choice but to expose you
to this special folder of mine.
- Let's go!
Come on, get over here! Quick!
Watch carefully.
Your life will be split into two
parts from now on.
The era before you'd seen this,
and the era after you've seen this.
Shut up and play it, already!
I've carefully curated
all of these myself!
Shut up, already!
[Porn Folder]
It'll make you weak in places
you never knew existed!
Come on!
What is this?
Senior Yoon?
Gangpyeon?
Why are you there?
Yeah. I'm sorry.
Can I ask you to do this for me?
Yeah.
Excuse me.
Um, do you know how to use the scanner?
You go like this... and then,
when you hear the beep
you press this, and the
cash drawer will come out.
And then, you just
have to push it back in.
Hey, eyes up here!
Oh, it's so cold!
Good work, everyone!
Damn, why are there
so many people here?
We should've just slapped them
across the face.
What? Why?
I don't know!
They piss me the hell off!
Just beat them all up!
Look at their makeup.
Are they really students?
Well, they're wearing uniforms,
so I'm sure they're students.
Why are they going around
like this, at this time of night?
You crazy bitch!
Stop slobbering everywhere!
Shut the hell up!
Goodbye!
Wow, there's still tons of people here.
What, were you scared too, Senior Kang?
What, I can't be scared?
Weren't you just like them?
What are you talking about?
I never caused trouble as a student!
Oh, as if. What part of you
never caused trouble, exactly?
My... eyes?
Stop bullshitting!
No, no, it wasn't like that.
Repeat after me. "Stop bullshitting!"
- Stop bullshitting!
- No, no.
You have to put your chin up,
and say it really belligerently.
Stop bullshitting!
This is so funny! Should I
try this out on my boyfriend?
What the hell are you doing?
What, does this spiel usually
work on women?
What's the matter?
How did Senior Yoon manage to
stay here all alone at night?
Right? I was thinking the same thing.
[Chef Park Jae Hwan]
[Ms. Jin Myung]
- Welcome!
Welcome!
You're the one who covered for me?
I'm not the only one here.
Is it morning already?
Senior Yoon?
Let's go home.
Oh my, oh my!
Why did you do that?
I'm going to the bathroom.
Okay.
[What are you doing?]
I'm on a date with Ye Eun, the prettiest,
cutest, sexiest girl in the world.
[Her]
What do you want to eat for dinner?
Um... dumplings!
Why do you always want dumplings?
Come on, let's have dumplings!
Oh, all right.
Let's eat dumplings.
Hey! Whose is this?
It's mine, sir.
When did you last sharpen your knife?
I'll do it now.
- Do your work correctly!
- I'm sorry, sir.
Can I borrow your knife sharpener?
- I don't have one.
- Yes, you do!
I don't!
I lost it.
Your fingernail is all healed now, right?
Go back to your original position.
What, do you have something to say?
No, sir.
Thanks.
- Get inside safely.
- Okay. Bye!
Okay.
Bye!
[Her]
Damn it.
You're back early. You sure have
a lot of stamina,  huh?
Can you put this on for me?
Did you take my bracelet,
by any chance?
It's a blue plastic bracelet.
It's not really your type, though.
Why are you asking me, then?
Huh?
Why are you asking me about your stuff?
Because you take my stuff
and use it sometimes.
It wasn't me.
Never mind, then.
Don't touch what's mine.
What?
If you do, I'll kill you.
Hey!
I don't know what that
bastard said to her
but I didn't do a single thing to her!
What the hell am I supposed to do about
her dumbass boyfriend contacting me?
Damn it, this pisses me off.
That crazy bitch.
Only she would like a pathetic
bastard like him.
I'd refuse even if you brought me
a truckload of those kinds of guys!
Is that bracelet important to you?
It's a cheap thing that
they sell on the street.
It's nothing, really, but...
But?
Well, it's kind of a good-luck charm.
You know how they say that lightning
doesn't strike the same tree twice?
It's kind of like that.
It's kind of my souvenir from
when I almost died, but lived.
Are you sick, Madame Jung?
Why are you so quiet?
About that... you said that it was the
ghost of someone who was murdered.
It's just like saying, "this tastes like
a persimmon" when eating persimmon.
I just said what I felt,
so to ask me why--
It might be a premature ghost.
It could be a ghost that will be
murdered later, but has appeared now.
What the hell?
Why is she being so scary?
Where did you go?
I thought you left.
I just had to use the bathroom.
You know, you're a little weird.
What, because I come to places
like these, even though I'm broke?
No, it's not anything like that.
The way you look at me is different
than the way everyone else looks at me.
How so?
You have no lust in your eyes.
How funny.
Want to date me, Mister?
I have a slot open now.
I'll give you a discount,
since you're poor.
You don't have to give me
spending money
and you can just eat with me sometimes.
And drink with me.
And hear what I have to say.
Wow, way to put me in a bad mood.
Why are you laughing?
You're poor and old.
I'm trash, and I'm rotten...
and I've killed someone.
So how about we just go for it?
Want to go with me somewhere, for a bit?
Where is this?
This...
This.
This is your good-luck charm, huh?
What do you mean by that?
Why do you have this?
What did you mean when you
said that you killed someone?
Who are you, Mister?
The father of the child who
originally owned this bracelet!
Tell me! Why do you
have my daughter's bracelet?
It wasn't me!
Did you kill my daughter?
Tell me!
Who's there?
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Age of Youth]
Maybe he's the strange man
that the landlady said she saw?
Maybe?
[10 Missed Calls from Mister]
- But, why is he chasing you around?
- What did you hear from your boyfriend?
It's clear, even if
he didn't say anything.
You just go around flirting with
any man that comes around!
Stop it.
- Come on, why not?
- Stop it! I don't want to!
I broke up with my boyfriend.
There are times when
I want to cry out loudly.
- Saying that it wasn't my fault.
- I did a good thing, right?
Sometimes, I want to act
like a spoiled child
toward a person, or toward my fate.
What is this smell?
I'm sure that there's no way that
you, of all people, put on perfume.
- Are you doing your best to endure?
- What is this?
You can't put on anything that smells
whether it be perfume or
pain-relieving patches!
Don't you know that?
Is that what living life means to you?
- Just enduring?
- I'm sorry.
"That's enough.
You've done enough."
"Please... look at me."