Subtitles by DramaFever
[Lately, there has been a strange
man loitering around the house.]
[Make sure to keep the doors locked well
and be careful when going out late.]
[From the Landlady, who has
a maternal love for you all]
That child will get up on her own.
Children don't cry when there
is no use in doing so.
Ji Young!
Mom!
Oh, Ji Young! You tripped?
Where did you get hurt?
Does it hurt a lot?
When there's someone to ask you if
you're okay, and tell you it's okay.
Don't cry.
When there's someone
to tell you not to cry.
Children only cry when there
is someone on their side.
[Episode 8 - Hope, That
Damned Hope; Strange Man]
- Here.
- I'm sorry.
Make sure you use proper words
when speaking to them.
Yes, sir.
What is this smell?
Someone like you wouldn't
think to put on perfume, so...
What is this?
Don't you know that you
can't have any smell on you
whether it be pain-relieving
patches, or perfume?
What? Got something to say?
I'm sorry.
All right, we're opening
in five minutes!
We go through this every day
because of a certain someone.
Ugh.
Pisses me off.
If you do that again, I'm shoving your
hand in a pot of boiling water.
Damn it! That crazy bitch!
[Mister]
The person you're trying
to reach is unavailable.
Yes, coming!
Hey, don't get that!
It's a package, though.
- Hello.
- A package for you, ma'am.
- Thank you!
- Yes, goodbye.
Goodbye!
Wow, he sure sent a lot.
Oh, Dad!
Madame Jung, have some peaches!
That guy from before,
who did this stuff?
Yeah.
Then, maybe he's the "strange man"
that the landlady mentioned?
Probably.
So things turned out like that, huh?
Even though you said it wasn't like that.
And that's still true.
Why's he following you around, then?
At any rate, you never know,
so don't just open the door for anyone.
Wow, you sure have a great eye for men!
What's your secret?
All you have to do
is be is an easy woman.
Men love that.
That's right!
Smile, but not too much. And spare
them a few glances, but not too much.
And loosen a few buttons,
but not too many.
Yes, that's right.
I was doing it all wrong!
How do I look?
Am I pretty yet?
Would you like anyone?
Would you like any man who
says that they like you?
This is so good.
Now, if you're done eating, get up.
You said you're not feeling
good today, right? Get up.
- Let's go and sleep!
- Hey!
What the hell is wrong with you?
What?
If you have something to say, say it,
instead of beating around the bush.
Like what? I have nothing
to talk to you about.
Oh, do you have something to say to me?
That sniveling little...
Wow, you're really stuffing yourself.
Guess you're not watching your weight.
So? You like that?
Why would I be happy
about you getting fatter?
Because you'll look
better in comparison.
Yeah, I'm coming out now.
Apparently, he was
originally a carpenter.
He specialized in working on
temples and traditional homes.
But he doesn't to do that work
anymore, after he got out of jail.
Jail?
He got 10 years in jail for battery
that led to death, and got out in 7.
What does "battery that
led to death" mean?
It means that he beat someone to death.
Turn him in to the cops.
I'll do it later.
You can't even work as of late, right?
What's going on? I need to know,
if I'm going to help you!
- Hey! Are you okay?
- Are you all right, Miss?
Hey, do you know her?
Here you are.
Please have a nice time.
- Excuse me.
- Yes?
I ordered a medium-rare.
I'm sorry. I'll go and
check this for you.
I'm sorry.
- Chef!
- Yes?
There was an error
with Table Three's order.
What are you saying?
They asked for it well-done!
I'm sorry.
- Hey, broiler!
- Yes, Chef?
- Give me two medium-rares! Quick!
- Yes, Chef!
Yoon Jin Myung!
What did Table Three complain about?
Their order was put in wrong.
Was it put in wrong,
or did the wrong food come out?
- I rectified the situation.
- Oh, did you?
What about the cost of the
meat that was wasted?
What about the amount of the time
the customers were left to wait?
Everyone else can go home.
Yoon Jin Myung.
You're really not going
to apologize, are you?
Are you feeling good about yourself?
What are you going to do about the
damage you've done to our restaurant?
[Bus Schedule]
Get on.
That was the last bus for the night. If
you're not going to take a cab, get on.
Just quit.
Quit working at the restaurant.
You're only a part-timer anyway, and you
can find tons of other jobs like that.
You're home?
Senior!
Yeah, it's me, your Senior!
Just what--
Are you okay?
Hey, this guy looks really familiar!
I'll go buy some medicine for you.
What medicine?
- A pain reliever?
- Whatever! I don't need it!
- What about a band-aid?
- Band-aid, my ass.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to be totally decimated
if I try to surprise you again.
It's because you popped out of nowhere!
A surprise is supposed to surprise you!
It wouldn't be one
if I warned you in advance!
Sit!
Closer!
Who's the one who kicked me before?
They need to become a UFC fighter!
- Does it hurt a lot?
- Only I could've survived that.
If it had been someone else, they
would've been dead by now!
Did you drink?
Where did you go to drink?
In front of Hongdae.
- With who?
- My friends from high school.
They all told me to call you
and tell you to come, but I didn't.
Why not?
What do you mean, why?
Because you're mine.
Because only I get to look at you.
This part hurts the most.
The spot where you hit me.
It's all red.
I might even get a brain hemorrhage.
Do you know how scary
brain hemorrhages are?
It'll be bad if it bruises!
What? He's doing a hell of
a good job! He deserves it!
Where did you learn all these
perverted, old-man mannerisms?
Are you making fun of me?
Apologize, right now!
Senior Kang is scary.
Don't go over there.
That'd be best.
It's a learning experience!
- Bye.
Right now?
Just a moment.
Okay, that's fine.
Where do I need to go?
- I told you, yes!
- Really?
Wow, you lost so much weight in your
face! Maybe because you were sick?
Yeah! That's why I'm
planning to eat a lot today!
Good. CEO Oh is buying,
so eat as much as you want!
- Oh, thank you!
- Sure.
Why are you buying, Honey?
Because I have a great personality.
Great personality?
Why, I ought to flip this table over!
Just eat!
Hey, how long does it take to
get to a golf course from here?
Why? Did you get some
practice in, in the meantime?
Well, you do have to
pay me back for lunch!
- See you later, then.
- Yeah.
We need to talk.
It'll only take a second.
Talk about what?
I have nothing to talk to you about!
Let go!
Who are you, Mister?
Why are you avoiding me?
What happened that day?
Tell me, damn it!
I have nothing to talk
about with you! Let go!
Who do you think you are?
I'm that girl's father!
And as her father, I need to know!
- How my daughter died, and why!
- Hey, Mister.
Tell me!
Please, tell me!
Hey.
- You can't act this way here, sirs!
- Oh, damn it!
Stop him.
Please, tell me!
What happened that day?
Please! Tell me!
How did you end up
meeting a guy like him?
I'm sorry.
This sucks. My schedule's
all out of whack now.
Yeah.
No, I'll come out.
I told you, don't come here!
Hey, you surprised me!
But you still think I'm cute, right?
You think that I'm lovable, right?
Geez, I thought my lower back
was going to give out.
Get in!
I planned everything, and looked
for good restaurants to eat at.
First, go toward the
Boamdong Citizen's Center.
If you head behind that building,
there's a dirt path.
Apparently, a lot of locals
frequent that area. Won't that be nice?
Why are you in such a good mood?
I'm happy as long as I have you.
Don't you feel the same way?
What are you doing?
Let's go.
Here, Honey.
Say "ah."
Wait, slow down!
Wait just a sec.
Say "ah!"
Oh, you're back?
Who's that?
Oh... Dong Shik.
What does he want?
Nothing big. He just wants us
to go have a drink.
Man, that guy is a total alcoholic.
He drinks about eight times a week!
And he has such a low
tolerance for alcohol, too!
Want another glass?
- I'm leaving.
- What?
Hey!
What's with you, all of a sudden?
Did I do something wrong?
- No.
- What, then?
I don't feel well.
I think I got indigestion.
Then you should've said so!
Are you feeling really bad?
Yeah.
Let's go. I'll take you home.
I'll take the bus.
There's a bus that takes
me straight home, so...
That'd be better for me.
[Senior Kang - Kang Yi Na]
The person you're trying to reach is
currently conversing with someone else.
[Honey]
The person you're trying to reach is
currently conversing with someone else.
You will be redirected to
the voicemail system.
Why did you cry on that day, Mister?
Because I was reminded of the past.
My daughter...
Tell me.
Did you kill her?
- Tell me!
- Who do you think you are, Mister?
It's because I'm her dad!
I have to know, as her dad!
Please, tell me!
What happened that day?
Please! Tell me!
Hey, it's me. You told me before that
guy lives at a student hostel, right?
He doesn't have any
other family members?
Who knows?
It's not like I'm a private eye.
Want me to look into it for you, though?
Hello?
Hey, I'll call you back.
Hey!
- Why are you acting like this?
- What?
Why have you been acting
so weird recently?
What?
What did your boyfriend tell you?
I don't know what
that bastard said, but--
Stop calling him a bastard!
How dare you!
I seriously have nothing to do with him.
That bastard just overreacted,
all on his own.
Get the facts straight before
you go bitching at someone!
You flirted with him first.
Did that bastard tell you that?
That I flirted with him first?
He doesn't need to
tell me for me to know!
You flirt with every damn guy
that passes by!
Are you freaking kidding me?
If I'd actually tried to seduce him,
I would've had him by now!
- Good for you!
- Yeah, I'm better than you.
- You little--
- Hey! Stop!
Please stop!
Crazy bitch.
You're the same as that bastard!
That's why you two are dating!
You crazy bitch! Don't you dare lay
a hand on my Honey! I'll kill you!
I wouldn't take him even if you
offered him to me, you ---- bitch!
- Let go.
- Huh?
Let go, already!
It hurts!
Oh... sorry.
They sure are feisty.
Just get yourself a bowl of rice,
and sit. Let's eat together.
Okay!
How can you eat rice, first thing
in the morning? Eat bread.
Don't you know how bad
white bread is for you?
And it's like a calorie bomb, too.
Who cares if you count calories,
when you're always getting so fat?
It's because you're not educated
that you know nothing.
Figures.
The only news you read is entertainment
news, and you're always shopping.
I wonder if it actually feels
good to live that way?
You and your yo-yo diets.
Yeah, it's awesome to
live like this, all right?
- I wasn't talking to you!
- And neither was I.
- So, are you going to eat, or not?
- What are you going to eat?
Where are you going, Senior?
- The public sauna.
- I'll come with you!
I need to exfoliate. I haven't
done it in a while, you see.
So I keep getting ashy.
Wait for me! I'll be right out!
Why are you torturing her like this?
Sheesh. What's with you two?
Why does Senior Ye Eun have
to date a guy like that?
I mean, she's pretty,
smiles a lot, and is really cute.
It'd be nice if she could
date a better guy.
You don't know the story
about Ye Eun's older sister, right?
She has an older sister?
Yeah. She's studying abroad
in Germany right now
but apparently, she's
like a super-genius.
And she's been like that ever
since she was younger.
And she'll be getting her
doctorate this year.
How old is she?
The same age as Ye Eun.
The two of them are twins.
Wait, really?
Ye Eun has a twin?
Yeah. They're fraternal twins,
but she's a lot prettier, and taller.
She's pretty, and is
super smart, to boot.
I'm sure that Ye Eun's felt
bad since she was young
since her twin sister is so much
better than her in every way.
Her sister got all the attention.
And it's not like she could ever
surpass her sister in any way.
It's only natural that she has low
self-esteem, with a sister like that.
That's true.
This is what happens when people with no
confidence date the wrong person.
I thought Senior Ye Eun grew up in a
nice house, with a happy family.
Exactly.
That's weird. Senior Ye Eun
said that she was an only child.
What, did you lie to me?
Sheesh, why would you lie to
me about something like that?
After hearing my story, you thought, "I
understand why she's like that," right?
So my point is, my story
isn't exactly the answer
but everyone has their own
circumstances to deal with.
And until you know
the circumstances they're in
you can't tell people
how to live their lives.
It's not just Ye Eun.
It's Senior Kang and Senior Yoon, too.
I'm sure you have something
like that about you, too.
Something that others can't understand
about you, but you can't help.
That's why you can't
judge people willy-nilly...
What? Was I acting way
too holier-than-thou?
No.
I just feel like...
you're really...
Really... what?
Cool!
It's different than your usual self.
What? What am I usually like, then?
Do you usually like me, but now
you feel like you like me more?
That's what you meant, right?
You totally respect me, right?
You're totally in awe
of my intellect, aren't you?
Figures. All right,
let's get you exfoliated!
[Written Examination]
Wow, how much does a
company like this pay?
- Maybe 3 to 4 million won per month?
- Wow!
Really? Do they really
pay people that much?
Let's just say that the monthly
salary is 3 million won.
Then she'll only have to work for
three months to pay the debt off!
Hey, how would she get by if she used
her entire paycheck to pay us back?
Geez, this punk has no sympathy at all!
We need to account
her living expenses!
All right. Let's say that her living
expenses are 1 million won per month.
You can pay us 2 million per month, so
5 months. 6 months, including interest.
That'd be perfect!
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
All you have to do is sign,
and all of us will be happy!
Okay?
Hey! Student!
Are you really okay with this?
You don't care what happens to your mom?
She has no money,
no matter where she looks
and her only daughter
refuses to help her pay.
We'll really have
to do things our way, then.
Are you okay with that?
If you're done reading it, sign here.
Here, too.
Just quit.
Quit working at the restaurant.
It's just a part-time job anyway,
there's plenty of other jobs like it.
I can't quit.
To me, this place is like a test.
A trial run, kind of.
If I can't last here,
I won't be able to last anywhere.
But if I can last here...
I can last anywhere.
I've decided that,
on my own.
So I...
won't quit this job.
So you're just enduring?
Is life...
just a series of obstacles
to endure, for you?
Yes.
Do whatever you want, then.
All right, we have
a group of VIPs today.
Broil Team, I'm going to need two t-bone
steaks, and two ribeye steaks.
And two pairs of wine pairings.
- Make sure you prepare that.
- Yes, sir.
Let's be precise, all right?
Okay. Next...
Ye Eun!
When did you get here?
You didn't even tell me you'd be coming.
What are you doing?
You're not coming in?
Want some beer?
Did you get your hair done?
No.
I feel like something
has changed about you!
It feels like you've gotten
a bit sexier, too!
Maybe because it's been so long
since I've seen you?
- Stop it.
- Come on, why not?
Stop it! I don't want to do this!
Damn it!
What the hell are you doing?
What's with you lately?
If you have something
to say, then say it
instead of making me walk on
eggshells around you all the time!
Eggshells? Please.
Have you ever cared about how I feel?
What?
I'm leaving.
Hey!
Damn it!
Ye Eun! Let's stop drinking, already.
- No.
- Hey, stop it, already!
- Are you going to pay for all this?
- Hey, where are you going?
Ye Eun!
- Come on, pace yourself!
- You'll get sick!
Where are you going?
- Hey! Ye Eun!
- Hey! Where are you going?
Ye Eun and her boyfriend
aren't doing well, right?
Man, I wish she'd take this chance
and break up with him, already!
Sheesh. I'll bet you 50,000 won
that she won't be able to.
I bet she'll cling onto him even if he
asks her to break up with him first.
Why is she like that?
Seriously.
- Hmm?
- What are you doing?
I heard bad things about that guy.
Oh, he's a common one-night stander.
[Dong Joo]
Hello?
Yeah.
My roommate?
Which one?
You know, the one that almost got
hit by a car in front of your house!
Yeah. The skinny, pretty one.
What about Ye Eun?
Really?
Oh, whatever. It's not
like she's a minor. Who cares?
Oh, whatever! Bye!
I'm going to sleep!
Want to get out of here?
I'm sorry. Sorry to ruin your fun time.
Excuse me for a second.
Come on.
Let's go home.
No, I don't want to!
Who do you think you are?
I get it,
so let's talk about this at home.
I'm not going home!
What would I even do there?
I'm going to play here.
And drink.
Hey, do you think that
this is free booze?
Do you think that they're crazy,
buying you alcohol for free?
I know.
I'm well aware.
She says she can come.
So do you want to play with us?
Whatever, then.
- You're just going to leave?
- She says she knows what she's doing.
Just give me money for a cab.
Let's go. It's a place where people
who know each other play together.
- Ow!
- Get out.
Who the hell do you think you are?
Why are you doing this?
Me? I'm her lover.
Get out here!
Let go! Ow!
Hey! Hey!
Let go of me! Ow!
Let go! Let go!
Hey, this hurts!
Let go!
Hey, you did that on
purpose, didn't you?
Ugh, disgusting. Why did you get
piss-drunk, if you're going to vomit?
Why don't you do the city a favor and
swallow her vomit for her, then?
It's all the same, anyway!
Don't you dare fall asleep.
- This is so humiliating!
- Good, so you know!
Stop it! I'm done!
Apparently, that guy is super infamous.
I'm sure he mixed something
into your drinks.
That's why a total prude
like you got so horny.
- It doesn't matter.
- You sure?
Were you really going to
have a one-night stand?
Yeah.
You go around doing that all the time.
The guy that I like likes you,
who does that kind of thing.
So I can't do that?
You idiot. You thought that it'd
be a mere one-night stand?
A video of you would be
floating around the web!
You need to be more careful
about the way you rebel.
What does that matter,
when I'm already ruined?
Oh, shut up.
You don't even have a single
scratch on you, punk, compared to me.
I hate you.
I hate you too.
- You're the worst!
- Sure, sure. Let's leave it at that.
I wish that you were the one
who did something wrong.
Then... I'd only have to hate you.
That'd make me feel less pathetic.
Rather than having the man I love
be such a pathetic person...
You pathetic creature.
What am I going to do with you?
I really seem like an idiot, right?
At least you're self-aware.
I'm seriously such an idiot!
Wipe yourself off.
Wow.
How is it?
Does it taste good?
It's salty.
Yeah. It really is salty.
Really?
Yeah.
Oh, it's so salty!
It's super salty! It's so salty.
Don't eat it, then.
- Why?
- You said it was salty.
It's fine! I'm eating it!
No, don't eat it!
I'm going to eat all of this, even if
the sodium level in my body doubles!
- No!
- Give it!
- I told you, I'm eating it!
- No, don't eat it!
- I'm eating it!
- Give it back!
- Hey! I'll eat it!
- Senior!
Let go of her hand, right now!
What are you doing right now?
What?
What you're doing right now
is sexual harassment!
Being all touchy-feely with just anyone!
And you!
Get it together!
If you don't like it,
speak up and say so!
It's because of passive girls like you
that sexual harassment is still an issue!
Hey, what do you mean,
sexual harassment?
- We're--
- Sorry.
"Sorry?"
"Sorry," huh?
You're sorry?
What are you sorry about?
The fact that you didn't
push my hand away?
Or the fact that you weren't angry
about being "sexually harassed?"
Why can't you speak up?
Why couldn't you say, "he's my man?"
I'm sorry.
It just came out of my mouth
before I realized it.
So you disowned me
without even realizing it?
Who do you think you are, Apostle Peter?
Disowning me three times,
like he did to Jesus?
You better tell that girl
tomorrow that we're dating.
What, you don't want to?
Why not, though?
Are you ashamed of me,
by any chance?
No! That's not it.
Then?
Well... it still hasn't hit me yet.
The fact that you like
me feels like a lie...
and the fact that someone likes me
makes me feel like I'm dreaming.
I want to show you off,
but I feel like I shouldn't.
And it's the first time I've ever
liked someone like this, so...
it makes me happy.
But it makes me uneasy.
I don't know what I should do.
I'm quite a frustrating person, aren't I?
Are you really angry?
Yeah.
Do you... not like me anymore,
by any chance?
You're actually a pro at
dating, aren't you?
What?
You're playing hard-to-get
right now, right?
- N-no.
- You little!
You little rascal!
Senior, I have to go to class.
Stay for just five more minutes.
Okay.
Sheesh, you're so obedient!
You seductress.
Why do you even like me?
What do you like about
a bastard like me?
There's countless reasons
why I shouldn't like that man.
Why are you being so nice?
Because I don't know when
I'll be mean to you again.
And the worst thing
among those reasons...
- is that...
- Get the hell out!
he doesn't like me.
There's countless reasons
why I shouldn't like that man.
You're late today, too.
It's because you called me out,
out of nowhere!
What? What is it that you
need to talk about?
Go ahead.
Let me drink my coffee first.
You've really been getting
on my nerves lately.
- Can I get an iced Americano, please?
- Yes, sir.
Honey.
What?
Let's break up.
Is this a joke?
No.
Thanks for everything up until now.
Bye.
- You're back?
I broke up with my boyfriend.
I did a good thing, right?
Good job.
It's okay.
You'll be okay.
Sometimes, I want to cry out loud.
I want someone to hear me crying.
I want them to hear me cry,
and tell me everything will be okay.
I want someone to pat me on the back,
and tell me that it's not my fault.
Honey...
[Joeun Bank: Your payment has
bounced due to insufficient funds]
Sometimes, I want to throw a tantrum.
At a person, or at my fate.
And tell them, "stop it, already."
"Haven't you done enough?"
"Please, just spare me."
And...
I'll find hope, once more.
[You've passed our company's
2016 written exam.]
Who is it?
Yes?
What's your daughter's name?
Sol.
It's a monosyllabic name.
What kind of name is that?
Mister.
I killed your daughter.
So I...
killed your daughter.
Mister.
Are you going to kill me, too?
Subtitles by DramaFever
[What do you do at the restaurant?]
I'm the sous-chef.
[What do you feel for Yoon Jin Myung?]
I feel bad for her.
I feel bad for her,
so I want to be nice to her.
[Is it pity?]
I think it's love.
[Did you know why Jin Myung
was eating with her manager?]
No. I didn't ask her about it.
Well, honestly, I had my doubts at first.
But I know that Ms. Jin Myung
isn't the type to do stuff like that.
[What kind of relationship
do you have with Kang Yi Na?]
Um, you could say that we're co-workers.
We give each other intel, too.
[It seems that you have
complicated feelings for Kang Yi Na.]
Not really.
[Are you really only friends?]
Of course.
We're friends.
Friends.
[Explain your relationship
with Song Ji Won.]
Relationship? We're just in
the same club at school.
[It looks like you two flirt a lot.]
What?
Oh, not at all!
[Isn't Song Ji Won an okay catch?]
Well, if you're just judging
from her looks, yes.
[You never thought of her as a woman?]
A woman, huh?
[What's the most appealing
thing about Yoon Eun Jae?]
She's pretty.
[Some think that she has
a frustrating personality.]
Well, yes, kind of.
But still, she's pretty.
[Don't you feel like she
confuses you sometimes?]
Yeah. Sometimes, I wonder why
she acts the way she does.
But... she's pretty.