Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
[DELETE CONTACT]
[ARE YOU SURE?]
[YES]
Valued Guests, we'll now be
taking some photos.
Everyone, please take a seat.
Ladies and gentlemen,
sit down please.
Wow, that took a lot out of me!
[DELETE > YES]
- Yay!
All right, next!
[DELETE > YES]
- Yay!
- Yay.
Hey, can't she just delete
all of them at once?
If she wants to delete
every single trace of him
she'll have to empty the
trash at least once.
- Yay!
Yay!
[CONGRATS ON THE END OF YOUR
DISAPPOINTING RELATIONSHIP]
Everyone, my happy
la-di-da days of dating are over!
That man is merely a
part of my past now!
One can't try to have a boat float on
water that's already gone downstream!
I, Jung Ye Eun, will not
look back on the past.
I will only face forward, as I walk on!
[EPISODE 9: YOU WON'T LOSE
YOUR WAY IF YOU STAY STILL]
- Landlady!
- Why is it so loud up here?
- What?
- What are you all doing, that...
I'm here by myself right now.
What are you saying?
I heard a bunch of people saying,
"yeah!" not too long ago!
No. I was just studying by myself.
I wonder where that sound came from?
Have a safe trip back downstairs!
Wait!
You said that you were
by yourself, right?
Yes. I'm here by myself.
It's so late, though!
I even warned you all that there's
a strange man lurking about
and yet everyone is
even later than usual!
What if something happens to them?
Exactly, ma'am.
There's no use in regretting it after
something actually happens.
Of course, ma'am.
You're right.
If something happens to someone
that lives at my house
how do you think I'd feel?
I'm sure that your heart will
feel as if it's being ripped apart!
Oh, of course!
There was a strange man lurking
around outside not too long ago, too.
- Oh my.
- Be sure to lock the door well!
- I definitely will, ma'am!
- Okay.
Goodbye!
Please be careful on your way home!
You all heard what she said, right?
The weird guy was lurking
around here today, too.
What, do you have any suspicions
as to who it may be?
Do you think that he came here to
beg you for another chance?
No! He's not the type to ever do that.
If it isn't that stinking bastard...
I already took care of things on my end.
So did I.
My Senior is away for training
for the reserve forces.
I never asked, all right?
I'm just saying.
How far have you two gone?
You two kissed last time.
Did you cross the "line that
should never be crossed" yet?
- Senior!
- Ow!
Hey, if it's not true,
all you have to do is say so.
- It's not true!
- But how do we know that?
It's not like we saw you two!
No, that's not it...
Why are you doing this to me?
All right. For the sake of our precious
Eun Soon's special day that's yet to come
I'll introduce to you the great scholar
of all things erotic, Prof. Kang Yi Na!
Our other guest is Ms. Jung Ye Eun!
Whoo!
Oh, how embarrassing!
Honey, try and catch me!
Get back here, my pink squirrel!
Oh, Honey!
Why is it always me?
Yes, I'll be right out!
I'll be right out!
Hello!
Is this the guy that the
Landlady said she saw?
You're cute. How old are you?
- I'm 27...
- What brings you here?
- That's, um...
- Who are you?
Oh, um, I...
Is there a person named
Yoo Eun Jae here?
[INSURANCE CLAIMS INVESTIGATOR
KIMG CHANG HWAN]
What's an insurance claims investigator?
They're different from
insurance salespeople, right?
Of course. Insurance
salespeople sell insurance
and investigators investigate.
- So, what do they investigate?
- Huh?
You know... this. And that.
Um, excuse me.
Why did you come seek me out?
Well, our company did
some self-investigating
and, um... they told us
to re-investigate cases
in which one person received more than
three insurance payouts in ten years.
And Ms. An Jung Hui, who is your
mother, falls under that criterion.
- I'm sorry.
- What?
About what?
Um, just about
this situation in general.
I'll be sure to wrap this up
as soon as possible.
All right, so... seven years ago,
Sir Yoo Dong Gun...
Actually, I'll just refer to him as
"Mr. Yoo Dong Gun."
When your older brother passed away,
his store wasn't doing too well
and when your father passed
away four years ago
the relationship between the lender...
Um, this is something that I just
discovered when we reopened this case.
Also, when the mother-in-law
passed away 17 years ago...
Mother-in-Law?
So, um, your mother's mother-in-law.
So your grandmother.
So, when your grandmother passed away,
she collected an insurance payout.
- I don't really know...
- Of course.
Yes, I'm sure you don't.
You were only two years old then.
Or were you three years old?
- Um...
- Yes?
So, what is it that you
want to say to me?
Um, so...
Your stepfather got into a car accident
not too long ago, right?
He wasn't too badly hurt, though.
Yes, that's right.
It's quite a relief, too.
But I'm not sure if
that's really a relief...
when your father suffered from
a car accident before, too.
The location of the accident
makes one wonder how there
could've been an accident.
It was a curved road,
but it was quite wide
and this isn't a place where
accidents could normally happen.
Have you been there, by any chance?
No.
Oh, so you haven't.
Do you like your mother or father more?
What?
So, um... if you follow your mom,
you'd be betraying your dad
and if you believe your mom, I think
your dad would probably feel upset.
It's not a life-or-death choice, but...
There was an insurance plan
in your name, too.
Did you know that?
[CONTRACT SIGNED BY: AN JUNG HUI
THE INSURED: YOO EUN JAE]
It wasn't a big deal, or anything.
They had to talk to them because of the
accident that my stepfather was in.
But they couldn't get
in touch with them, so...
The two of them went on a trip abroad.
- Oh.
- I see.
Let's go to sleep.
- Is the door locked?
- Sheesh, I was so worried.
Thankfully, your father's body
was buried properly.
If he'd been cremated,
we would've been out of options.
Mom, when are you coming back?
Text me when you get this.
Madame Jung!
[GO TO EARLY MORNING PRAYER]
All these reports that
say I dumped him
and I am available aren't true.
This is a decision we made together,
as adults.
Please make a sentence
with your life, Ye Eun.
Okay. Um...
I dumped my boyfriend!
I'm available!
Good job! I'm available, too.
Really? That's insane!
Hey, did something good happen to you?
Me? I broke up with my boyfriend.
Hey, let's meet up!
It's been a while.
So, when are you free?
Yeah.
Saturday?
[LET'S LIVE A BUSY LIFE!]
Um, I have plans for Saturday.
How about Sunday at 5:00 p.m.?
Okay. See you then!
Let's jump! Hop, hop!
Wow, it's so slippery!
- I'd let it air out.
- Why?
Ew! Hey!
I warned you.
- You're going out again?
- Yeah. See you later!
It looks like she's overdoing it, right?
Yep. It's as if she's desperate to
not be alone for even a second.
These people who don't even know
how withholding taxes works
only keep asking me to lower taxes.
So, ever since April, for the past two
months now, my weekends have been busy.
Anyway, I worked my butt off until May!
I need to rest a bit to recharge!
So, I went straight to the Maldives!
And it was super nice!
After going there...
Aw, man!
I'm hungry!
Let's eat!
- Wow!
Wow, it's so good!
It's delicious! Senior Yoon,
hurry over here!
Okay!
- I love this side of Madame Jung!
- Oh, stop it.
Are any of you free tomorrow,
by any chance?
I need to buy some clothes,
and I need someone to help me.
Clothes?
By clothes, do you mean
like the things you wear?
They want me to come and interview.
- That place from before?
- Yeah.
- Senior Yoon!
- Wow!
- This is great!
- Congrats! Congrats!
- This is awesome!
I told you, I still have to
pass the interview!
But still, we should congratulate you
when we can!
Congrats, Senior Yoon!
Senior Kang!
Senior Yoon got an interview!
She passed all the preliminary stages!
Oh, that's great.
Sit, sit, sit.
- Really, congrats!
- This is great.
- Yi Na, let's eat together.
- Nah. I already ate.
All right, then. Let's drink to
Senior Yoon passing her interview!
Congrats!
That's a public enterprise, right? If
you get the job, you'll be set for life.
Wow, that must be great!
How much will your annual salary be?
I told you, I'm not hired yet.
I bet she'll get at least
35 million won per year!
Wow! 35 million won per year?
You can't just ignore us
after you make it big, okay?
You have to buy us food every time
you get a promotion, okay?
I mean, if you passed all the preliminary
stuff, you're pretty much hired.
Oh yeah! Let's have a ten-year
reunion among ourselves.
It'll be fun, right?
In ten years, I'll be 32.
I don't know about that.
By then, I'll be a journalist-turned-
novelist, so I'll be super busy
making media appearances, and
dealing with publishing companies.
So I don't know if I'll have time then.
We can just meet up with you
at the broadcasting station, then.
I'll be food columnist, Jung Ye Eun!
I hope that cooking shows
will be popular until then!
What will you be doing?
Um... a psychological counselor?
Wouldn't it be funny to have
a socially awkward counselor?
"Um... so... what... brings you here?"
But still, you must be happy.
You'll only be 30 in 10 years.
Yeah.
And as for Senior Kang...
How am I supposed to know
what'll happen in ten years
when I don't even know
what'll happen tomorrow?
- Cheers!
Here's to a 35 million won salary!
- Wow, this beer is good.
- Ow!
Hurry up! Let's go!
- What about Senior Kang?
- She said she has plans.
Aw. I feel like Senior Kang would
be best at picking out clothes.
Don't you worry.
FaPe is here!
Fashion People!
I know, but... is that "fashion
person" you, by any chance?
Senior Yoon, you jokester!
All right, let's go!
- Shopping for clothes!
- Whoo!
Madame Jung.
The clothes here are expensive.
Senior.
Over there.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Sheesh!
- Senior!
- Huh?
Try this!
This!
Isn't it pretty?
Um...
Welcome.
This, this, this.
I can try them on, right?
It's pretty, though.
Um...
Try this.
- How is it?
- It looks like a school uniform.
Whoo!
The arms are a bit weird.
It's totally pretty, though.
Buy this, okay?
I really hope that Senior Yoon
gets the job.
She will.
Right? I think she'll
really get it this time.
Why?
It's because of the timing. They say
that life is full of ups and downs
Her life has been full of downs now, so
it's about time things looked up for her.
I don't know about ups
and downs, or whatever
but if I were the boss, I'd pick
someone who'd work well.
And there's nobody who looks like
they'd do a better job than Senior Yoon.
- No, there isn't.
- Nope, there isn't.
Right?
She could've gotten eliminated
during the preliminaries
because of her resume or age.
But since she made it to the
interviews, she has this in the bag.
Ooh!
Does it look okay?
Allow me to assist you
with your payment method.
Here you are.
Please give her a discount,
since she's paying all in cash!
Can you give her an employee discount?
Please! Thank you!
Hey, middle-aged lady!
Over here, middle-aged lady!
Sheesh, you wicked old lady!
Stop laughing!
Well, kids would consider you a
middle-aged lady. What's the big deal?
Just wait until someone
calls you a middle-aged man.
I've been hearing that since
I was in high school.
And from a middle-aged woman, at that.
- It pisses me off.
- Why are you still thinking about it?
They were just kids.
Because I'll really become a
middle-aged lady, sooner or later.
And then, I'll become a grandma, too.
What, were you planning to
never get old, or something?
Did you want to become a
monster that never grows old?
Why do you care?
It's cold.
Oh yeah.
So what happened with that guy?
So, I...
killed your daughter.
Mister.
Are you going to kill me, too?
Leave.
Please, leave.
Mister.
Get lost!
Didn't you hear me?
Get away from me, right now!
Everything worked out well.
I won't have any reason
to see him anymore.
What's with your face, then?
What, what's wrong with my face?
Hey, let's go and eat.
I can't. I have to go and work.
Damn it. You should've
said so before, then!
Are you going somewhere?
Yeah.
That was hard on you, huh?
Oh, that was nice.
What the heck is this?
I just turned on my phone!
What is it?
Is something the matter?
Huh? I think something
happened to Eun Jae!
Um, excuse me.
So? What did you tell him?
So what did he say then?
Why did you say that?
What do you think they'd think if they
knew that dad knew, before he died?
How is that a lie? Knowing how they look
doesn't make you acquaintances!
That's why I told you to call me first!
Why the hell did you go on a trip abroad
as soon as you got the insurance payout?
All right. Sorry I got mad, but...
You should take care of that yourself,
Mom! Do I need to tell you everything?
So who told you to get
so many insurance plans?
If you do that now,
they'll doubt you even more!
Mom, I have to go to class now.
Yeah.
Wow, seems quite serious.
Is something the matter?
No.
It's time for my lecture, so...
Please enjoy.
Wait, wait, wait! Not yet.
Let me take a photo first.
Who are you even taking these photos for?
These are all memories!
A page of my fleeting youth!
Can't you change the
blurb on your profile?
Why? What's wrong with it?
Just like a camel,
walking through the desert...
I mean, what do you even mean by that?
You know, diligently walking along my
own path without getting distracted.
The fact that you even said that makes
me think that you're already distracted.
Let's go to Gyeongnidan-gil tomorrow.
I heard that they sell the second
most delicious mocha cake in Korea!
You'll come, right?
Right? Right?
Geez.
Is she still in there?
- Why? Who's in there?
- Senior Jung.
Stop it already, and come out!
Come on! Finish it up and come out,
already! I'm about to go in my pants!
Did you clog the toilet?
When did she go in there?
Thirty minutes ago!
I really have to go.
What are you doing in there?
No way.
Jung Ye Eun! Madame Jung!
Open the door!
- She was in a good mood, though.
- Hey, here.
That's why there's something
weird about this!
Does it makes sense that she's in a
good mood, when she got her heart broken?
Are you okay?
What's the matter?
You endured so well up until now.
- My armpit hair...
- Yeah, what about it?
I have so much armpit hair!
What about her armpit hair?
It's one of the symptoms
of being single.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Make sure you win that
interviewer over! Whoo!
Good luck, Senior Yoon.
These are the luckiest
things I own. Good luck!
Is today the day of your interview?
Yeah.
What?
Oh, nothing.
Good luck.
All right.
Damn it, I just can't
seem to work properly.
Damn it!
For good luck.
Good luck!
Please introduce yourselves,
starting from the one on the right.
Hello. I'm Number 147,
Kim Yu Jin.
Hello! I'm Number 128,
Jeon Tae Min.
Hello. I'm Number 119,
Yoon Jin Myung.
Ms. Jin Myung, you've attended
school for quite a long time.
Is there a reason for that?
I took breaks due to having to work
to pay back my student loans.
However, I do not believe that
I'm lacking in credentials.
What I mean by credentials
is not licenses
but having a great amount of
experience in the work force.
I have a ton of working experience
and I'm confident that I'd be
a good employee.
Hey, what took you so long?
You're the one who wanted to meet up.
You have to buy me something
delicious now, okay?
This is my mom.
Hello.
I was so busy that I couldn't keep
an eye on my son, and now...
I think you've misunderstood, ma'am.
I've no intention of marrying this man.
So you don't need to worry.
See, Mom? I told you that we don't
have that kind of relationship!
We're just dating for fun.
You should still set standards
for the types of fun you indulge in!
You say that you have no intention
of marrying him, which is fine.
It seems like you two have a
give-and-take thing going on
so why aren't you adhering to the rules?
You spent more than 2 million won
last week, in one day.
Do you really think you're worthy
of spending that much of his money?
So why did you spend...
so much this month?
I'll return everything.
That'd be nice.
Goodbye.
Wow, is today a special day?
- I had an interview.
- Oh. Did it go well?
Yes. I think so.
Interview, my ass.
- All right. Next.
- Yes.
Allow me to get you another.
Here you are.
Have a lovely time.
Thank you.
I have so much armpit hair!
[♪INSURANCECLAIMINVESTIGATOR
♪CONDUCTINGAUTOPSY]
Good morning!
Insurance Claim Investigator...
Conducting Autopsy...
Results of interview.
Is my life really okay
the way it is now?
What's wrong?
[♪SOMUCHARMPITHAIR]
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
What, huh? What is it now, huh?
What do you want to rant about now?
My life is way too easy.
There are no bumps whatsoever.
It's like it's a straight road,
with no twists or turns.
Geez. What kind of nonsense is that?
My life will probably just continue
being uneventful like this, until I die.
Is this really okay?
What's going to go in my autobiography?
Geez. You'll only come to your senses if
you get dropped into the middle of Syria
and get forced to run zigzag
to avoid getting bombed, huh?
Hey, you still call yourself
a college student?
Are you a politician, to be
spouting such nonsensical things?
Send me to Syria, then.
Want to go out with me?
W-what?
How about we have a scandalous
little fling? Please?
- Come on, Sung Min!
- Ew, stop it! What are you doing?
Are you trying to drive me crazy?
Man. Life sure is boring.
- You!
- What?
Don't you dare go off
and do something weird!
Huh?
Remember last fall, when you
disappeared and left a will behind?
I heard you only did that
because you got bored!
- Wasn't it amusing?
- As if!
I almost called 911!
If you do anything like that
one more time, just watch.
I think it's already too late for that.
What?
I have something to ask you.
Yes?
It's important, so think carefully
about it before you answer.
What is it?
Are you ready?
Telepathy... mind reading... ESP.
You can have one of these superpowers.
- Which one would you choose?
- What?
I'd choose telepathy.
It does overlap a bit with mind reading,
but I'd want telepathic powers.
Having our feelings be conveyed to each
other when we hold hands, like this.
Wouldn't that be cool?
We'd never misunderstand
each other, either.
And you wouldn't have to learn languages
to communicate with foreigners!
Can't someone invent a
machine that lets you do that?
I don't have that kind of superpower
and nobody has invented a
machine that lets you do that.
So what can we do, but communicate,
even though words fail us sometimes?
Something's been going
on with you lately, right?
Tell me.
I'm totally head over heels
for you right now
so I'm confident that I'll be totally
accepting of anything that you say.
So now's your chance!
I can't make any guarantees
if you let this chance slip by!
Are you a spy, by any chance?
Are you an alien?
It won't be anything like that, right?
That's fine, then.
Don't worry, and just tell me.
Go ahead.
There's nothing going on.
Really?
Yes.
[WE'D LIKE TO ANNOUNCE
OUR RESULTS FOR 2016.]
Hello.
Welcome.
I thought to myself,
"why are they all trying so hard?"
Life is more fragile than a cheap toy.
So how is it that they all consider
their lives to be that precious?
I'm curious.
- Keep pedaling!
- Don't let go!
- Don't worry, I haven't!
Of course! Hey, step on the
pedal harder! Keep pedaling!
Keep going forward!
Okay, okay! Great job!
Great job!
I thought about why everyone is
trying so hard to move forward.
Even though they don't
even know what awaits them.
I felt like people who plotted
out a point somewhere
and worked hard to get
there seemed strange.
Keep pedaling! Keep going straight!
Good! Good! Great job!
Great job!
- Ow!
- Oh, are you okay?
Oh no. I'm sorry.
You let go, didn't you? It's all your
fault! It's because you let go!
No, it's because you didn't
pedal hard enough!
Bicycles fall over if you stop pedaling.
Okay. Daddy won't let
go this time, okay?
Let's go!
Here.
You said it was like a good-luck
charm to you, didn't you?
Just use it as your good-luck charm.
Why?
I thought you hated me.
Why would I hate you?
It just so happened that
things turned out this way.
I hope you have a happy life.
Are you going somewhere?
Someone that I know asked me
to work with them, so...
Mister!
About that time...
On that day, at that time...
If your daughter had
survived instead of me...
what would you want to say?
To your daughter, I mean.
I'm sorry.
To live.
To not feel guilty. Surviving is
nothing to be ashamed about.
So, I'd tell her to live.
To live a good life.
To keep living like that.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
I'll do that.
I'll do it.
Who's the person who went
into the wine cellar today?
Two bottles of wine are missing.
Where's your bag?
- I'll bring it here.
- No, that won't do.
Do you take me for a fool?
Mr. Jae Hwan!
Hurry over. They said that
some wine has gone missing.
Open your locker.
Where did you hide it?
What are you doing?
Damn it.
Apologize.
What?
Apologize to me, and
put my stuff back in my bag.
Are you out of your mind? Hey!
Hey! You're a suspect!
How dare you ask for
a freaking apology?
Apologize to me!
And put my stuff back in my bag!
Are you out of your damn mind?
Hey!
Apologize.
Apologize!
What the hell did I do wrong, huh?
How much more are you
going to make me endure?
Apologize to me!
Apologize right now, damn it!
- Ms. Jin Myung!
- Apologize to me!
- Apologize to me, right now!
- Ms. Jin Myung!
- Hey!
Geez. Move!
Don't have that sort of
expression on your face, please!
I thought that people only got lost
when they tried to go somewhere
and I thought that people's lives only
got hard because they set objectives.
But staying in the same
place for too long
makes you lose your way too, it seems.
I may have been...
stuck underwater all this time.
As I slowly sank downward.
So... who was the one who'd
held me back all this time?
What are you doing?
Saying goodbye.
What?
I just said goodbye.
[UNFORTUNATELY, YOU DID NOT PASS.
THANK YOU FOR YOUR INTEREST IN US.]
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
[AGE OF YOUTH]
- What? What is it?
- What? What?
What time is it?
Senior Yoon is acting strange.
I always wanted to just meet you,
drink coffee, talk, visit restaurants
and other things like that.
Just like everyone else.
Oh, hey. Long time no see.
- You didn't have lunch yet, right...
- See ya.
So chubby!
You're... not going to class?
- No. Something came up, so...
- Sure.
Did you know that hope brings calamity?
Senior Yoon!
Do you know where that is?
You know, the hospital where Yoon
Jin Myung's younger brother is.
You couldn't live, or die,
for six whole years.
I'm sure that it's been terrible for you.
Right?
[WHERE WERE YOU
WHEN YOUR DAUGHTER DIED?]
I was in jail.
[CAN WE ASK YOU WHAT
YOU WERE IN JAIL FOR?]
I went to try and get the payment due
to us that was three months overdue
but they said something so ridiculous
that I couldn't stop hitting him, and...
[HOW DID YOU KNOW THAT KANG YI NA
WAS RELATED TO SOL'S DEATH?]
All I could do in jail was watch the
news or read the newspaper.
I saw the photo that was
featured in the article.
And that bracelet that
Kang Yi Na was holding
is something that I'd bought for Sol.
At the rest stop at Haengdam-do.
[WHAT KIND OF DAUGHTER WAS SOL?]
[YOU TOLD KANG YI NA TO LIVE.
WHAT DID YOU MEAN BY THAT?]
Thinking about it,
she was a victim, too.
And it would've been nice if she hadn't
gone through something like that.
I just wanted to tell her, "it's not
your fault, so stop being miserable."
And that having survived that
is nothing to be ashamed of.
Even if Sol... had been alive...
I think I would've wanted to
tell her something like that.
[DO YOU HAVE ANY EXCUSES
FOR HOW YOU'VE ACTED?]
What? Excuses?
Did I do something that
warrants such actions?
[WHY DID YOU TAKE YOON JIN MYUNG TO
YOUR VACATION HOME SO LATE AT NIGHT?]
Oh. I told you, already. I brought her
there to discuss something important.
But she misunderstood, and...
This is why you can't do anything with
stupidly old-fashioned girls.
I mean, why would I even be
attracted to her? Sheesh.
Crazy bastard.
[YOU TOOK HER OFF COUNTER DUTY AFTER THAT
AND CHANGED HER BACK TO A SERVER.]
What, do I have an obligation
to keep her at the counter?
I was only letting her work there
until her fingernail healed!
I was just being kind to her, and...
[HONESTLY, WEREN'T YOU THE ONE IN
THE WRONG DURING THE WINE INCIDENT?]
As a restaurant manager,
I have responsibilities to uphold.
If there's something that sparks
doubt, I have to investigate it.
If the cops have a potential suspect,
but their innocence is proven
do they have to apologize for that?
- [YES, THEY DO.]
- Oh, really?
I'll apologize, then.
Sorry. Geez.
[CRAZY BASTARD]
These people...
You're the one who cursed at me, right?
You, with the glasses! Get over here!
Punk.