Over here.
Here, coffee. You drink coffee, right?
What's with you today?
First you buy me that crappy meal.
Now this coffee.
The food in the cafeteria is really good.
Forget it. What do you want?
You have something to say,
don't you?
Do you want to attend a piano concours?
I think this would be perfect for you.
I think In Ho has really tamped down
his temperament lately.
I can see the unique colors of his
that you spoke of...
I see them shining through.
Yes, that's good.
I would like to do something for him
at this point in time.
At a time like this,
it would be good to have an actual goal.
Then what about a competition?
Ah, that sounds good.
Next month, there is
a national piano concours.
With In Ho's skills and one month...
I think we could do it if we work hard.
I think a small concours would be better
than a big one right now.
With a personality like that,
would he do a small one?
What is it? You don't want to?
I want you to know that your tastes
are quite old-fashioned.
Old-fashioned?
Are you looking down on it
for being a small event?
A bit.
Are you doing it or not?
I have to, of course.
I'm even thankful for this right now.
I knew you'd say that.
I can really do this, right?
Of course! Just work hard.
Concours...
[Episode 12]
This guy keeps posting pictures.
Oh, I'm positive that this is
Yonyi University.
This guy keeps getting worse and worse.
- Who is this nosy person?
- This is fun. Don't stop him.
Isn't it a matter of time
before we find out who it is?
Do whatever you all please.
Once I catch who it is and report him...
But if they ask me
if I really stalked her...
Will they contact Hong Seol too?
Is he filming me right now?
I don't think so.
That wild boar.
Why doesn't he just look for food?
- Why is he so nosy?
- What are you doing there?
All right, all right.
I have to stop this before rumors start.
This caller is unavailable...
He won't pick up.
I should have just told him quickly.
I only didn't because
we hadn't been talking for a while.
We just made up and we're fighting again.
That expression he had before wasn't
simply because he was a little mad.
Show yourself.
If you don't come out,
I'm going to report you to the police.
You could just run now.
Seol...
Don't come any closer
and talk from there.
Seol, I was wrong.
Why are you doing this? Are you crazy?
I was wrong about everything, including
bothering you all you this time.
I won't harass you ever again.
Please forgive me just this once.
Would you?
I'll even sign a contract
promising not to see you.
So tell that thug friend of yours
to give it a rest, okay?
What?
That guy put up photos of me on the
internet calling me a stalker.
It's that thug, right?
Stop him for me.
If you do that,
I will stay quiet and not report him.
You made such a big fuss
ever since last year.
Now you even show up in my neighborhood?
Are you sane?
Well...
You ignored my sincerity
and were cruel with my feelings.
That's why I'm here today.
So it's all my fault?
Have you ever actually considered me?
I...
find it really frustrating
that I like someone like you.
Whenever you see rich and handsome guys
like Yoo Jung, you go nuts.
Pull yourself together.
You're always bringing up Senior.
To me, you can't even compare to
someone like Senior.
Not in any respect.
What's so great about Yoo Jung?
Yoo Jung is the one who started
all of this.
He pretends to be nice and makes me
the bad one in front of others.
Because of him,
I became a outsider at school.
You know clearly that he was the one who
convinced me that you liked me.
Then he goes behind my back
and starts dating you?
He's the one who really has done wrong.
It was him who deceived me and did
everything that was truly strange!
Why is it me
who gets treated like garbage?
Why? Why, why, why!
So...
You wanted to get revenge on him?
You were only using me to get revenge
on Senior.
You didn't like me.
What do you know to show off like that?
Wow, really...
You really don't get it.
Hey, should I really scare you?
Should I make you shake in fear
every time you go home?
Should I make it so you can't go to
school anymore?
Should I grab your hair in front of
your restaurant to knock sense into you?
If you don't want that, shut up and
tell that thug to delete those posts.
Or else I'll kill you and him.
Baek In Ho has nothing to do with it.
What?
Because I did it.
Seol, do you really think this is okay?
Let's not put it up. I'm scared.
It'll be fine.
It's better if I put it up.
I can't hold back anymore.
Young Gon is a stalker.
Hey, I'm watching everything.
So why don't you stop at this point?
So, you...
You were the one playing me?
I warned you to stop.
You were the one who didn't listen.
Ah, you're right.
Your face was blurred out
in every single photo.
You're dead!
Ow! Hey!
Hey, stop! My eyes! Stop right there!
Mission complete.
That loser followed your girlfriend
home today.
I filmed it all.
You're going to say I did a good job.
Hey, should I really scare you?
Should I make you shake in fear
every time you go home?
Should I make it so you can't go to
school anymore?
Should I grab your hair in front of
your restaurant to knock sense into you?
You've kept everything you filmed safe,
haven't you?
Send everything to me.
Yeah, Eun Taek?
Stop right there.
Hong Seol, stop!
I told you to stop!
Dad, Dad!
My eyes!
- Dad.
- Who are you, punk?
No one, I'm just Seol's friend.
Hi, Seol. Goodbye.
Stop right there. I said stop, you punk!
I'll kill you if I catch you.
- Dad, Dad!
- Stop!
Stop right there!
Hey, who is that kid? What's with him?
Dad, are you okay?
I'm okay? Are you okay?
- Yeah.
- Are you hurt anywhere?
- Really?
- Dad, shoes...
I'm fine. I am.
Oh Young Gon went crazy
and even came to my neighborhood.
He must be truly crazy.
Wow.
Are you okay, Seol?
I ended up recording it
so if I show this file and the pictures,
he won't be able to do anything.
Oh yeah.
You are finally free.
It could become a problem
that I put up those posts.
Now we'll both go down together.
Anyway, I have all the evidence,
so it's done.
Young Gon is the one who started
stalking and writing posts first.
He did it all first.
Yeah, he bothered you so much.
It will be okay, Seol.
Heart.
I'm sure it will.
What about Senior...
Well, he won't pick up even if I call.
Young Gon is here.
Oh, you're all here.
Hi, hi, hi, hi.
This worked out well.
You're all going to eat, right?
What should we eat?
It's my treat.
Meat... how about meat?
- Meat?
- Yeah.
I don't want it.
Come on, Senior!
You're going to come, right?
You know I love you, Senior.
Oh, how about we go for neck meat?
It's just too rough.
Then how about marbled beef?
They always give you too little.
Ribs... how about ribs?
- Ribs?
- Yes.
My lovable junior, Young Gon!
My lovable senior, Sang Chul!
Sang Chul? You dropping honorifics?
Hey, whatever! Let's get going.
Young Gon is buying meat.
Do Hyun, let's go.
- I guess I can go.
- Let's go!
- Ribs, ribs, ribs!
- Ribs, ribs!
Ribs!
This is so tiring.
Oh Young Gon is so annoying.
Kim Sang Chul is even worse.
He goes crazy over meat.
He sure has a lot of money.
The one who buys and the ones who
follow are on the same low level.
It's not like they're in grade school.
Why do they all follow just to get meat?
He knows he can't win over girls,
so he's trying to get the guys.
Why are guys so simple-minded?
Just ignore him.
Everything is over for him,
but he doesn't know it.
Quite pathetic.
Eat up, everyone! Eat up!
Eat the meat and the vegetables too.
The vegetables are good for you.
- I'm only going to eat meat.
- Really?
As always, spend your money
and they will all come running.
Oh Young Gon, did you really cheat?
You know that woman who slapped you?
She was not bad for a second.
Pass her to me if you're not meeting her.
Yeah, I was really curious too.
I just happened to be missing that day.
- Hey, tell us.
- Yeah!
The thing is...
Honestly, I was cheating.
Wow, really?
Young Gon, I'm feeling
more and more close to you.
I'm sorry, Senior.
All the girls are saying crap about you,
but the guys are jealous of you.
That woman who came to school
was really beautiful.
I love bodies like that.
I only dated her because she kept
following me around.
And I know I became a really bad guy
last time.
But actually, I was a victim too.
She was cheating with Yoo Jung.
Cheating? What about Seol?
Well, he is a guy too.
And to tell you the truth,
Yoo Jung's with Seol because of me.
Because I said I wanted to date Seol,
he started to feel threatened...
What are you doing now?
There's something strange written about
you on the school site.
Take a look.
Young Gon, there's a picture of you
on the school site.
Ah, not my good-looking face again.
[THIS PERSON]
Hey, hey. This isn't me.
There's something about Do Hyun too.
- What is it?
- There's something written here.
I don't look like this.
Wait. What is this?
"He's already in fourth year,
but is trash that still creeps on girls."
- Senior, it wasn't me.
- Just hold on!
"Worst of all, he only goes
after girls younger than him."
"Last time, he tried flirting with
a younger girl"
"and got dumped at the retreat."
"At this point, he should be wearing
an electronic ankle monitor."
Hey, did I ask for the intro?
You offered to introduce me to her!
Did you say I got dumped?
I dumped her, you punk!
Yeah, you dumped her.
"With a good-looking face,
he goes around seducing men."
Senior, is that what you think of me?
No, let's drink.
Sang Chul,
there's something about you too.
- No...
- What could he say about me?
That's right, Senior!
You don't need to look.
Young Gon likes me a lot.
- You can't see it.
- Wait, wait.
- There is something.
- Where, where?
"He's the most senior, but is always
poor and mooches off others."
"He steals his junior's notebook
and always wants to eat meat."
"He's almost 190 centimeters tall
with a tummy that sticks out."
"He's a total bum."
"I don't know how he got into our school.
I feel sorry for his parents."
- You insult my parents, huh?
- Senior.
I said it's not me.
I even kept your stalker stuff to myself.
- Hey, hey.
- Stop it.
Wait. Hold still!
Stay put.
He's a total stalker.
His pictures are all over the internet.
I saw him following girls
and taking their pictures.
- You psychopath trash!
- Wow, you're psychotic.
Wait a minute.
"Whenever Sang Chul calls for him,
he runs off like a servant."
"He always wears fake luxury goods
and asks if it's obvious."
"Poor idiot in class of 2009."
Hey, there's one more.
"They're all dirt poor,
and Yoo Jung buys them meals."
"So they all gather around happily
like bums."
"I bought them meals too
and, like bums, they gathered around me."
"Why are there so many bums
in such a prestigious school?"
What? Bums?
"Honestly, these people should all be
taken out..."
"and cleaned out."
- Clean?
- Cleaned out?
Wow, clean out the trash, huh?
Say something!
Why don't you say something?
Am I trash that needs to be cleaned up?
- Hey, where are you going?
- Pay before you go!
How did they find out?
Gosh, seriously!
Hong Seol? Hong Seol, that wench.
She took it down from that site
and then put it up on the school site?
I'm going to kill her.
I noticed you did something entertaining
to Seol yesterday.
What is this?
How did she find out?
Pick up. Please, pick up.
- This caller is currently not...
- Just pick up!
You must feel guilty about something too.
Yoo Jung told you to do it, right?
The two of you planned this
and you're trying to screw me over.
Yoo Jung, you, Hong Seol...
And that thug too.
I'm going to sue you all.
I will never settle.
Who do they think they're dealing with?
You're going to sue? You?
Stalking, attempted assault.
Threatening, defamation, and contempt.
I assume you're going to sue because
you're prepared to deal with all this.
What... what is this?
My face is showing in these.
My face is in all of these. You bastards!
My face!
Don't send them. Please don't send them.
You only approached me to do this,
didn't you?
I'm going to kill you all.
Don't you dare show yourself to me.
You talk a lot for a guy who can't even
tell when someone's being fake.
Fake... fake...
He's totally fake. Can't you see it?
He's completely fake!
Why are you all talking when you can't
even tell someone's being fake?
I'm returning that phrase to you.
Yoo Jung.
Hey, should I really scare you?
Should I make you shake in fear
every time you go home?
Should I make it so you can't go to
school anymore?
You're Yoo Jung, aren't you?
Is that what's important?
You better behave yourself from now on.
Or I'll be putting that video up
on the school site too.
Where are you right now?
Come out now.
Come out, you bastard!
This is my last warning.
It would be best if you didn't show up
in front of me.
He... Hello?
You jerk!
What are you looking at!
Get lost!
Get lost! I said get lost!
Those bastards!
They totally got me.
You received my phone, right?
I think we're done crushing that loser.
I'll receive your gratitude later
after I get back everything that's mine.
Isn't the weather nice, children?
Should we go have fun in our house?
I won't need anything more from you.
I don't know. Do you think so?
I'll get you some friends before we go.
Where should I get them from?
I deleted the posts I put up.
The person who put up the new posts
on the school site...
- The person who put them up...
- Okay, it was me!
Did I do something wrong?
I think I did well.
Hey, was it really you?
What if you get sued for it?
Seol said she'd take care of it
and not to do it.
Hong was in trouble last night
and that's why I did it.
I wanted to end it for good.
You have no fear, do you?
You had that trouble with Oh Young Gon
last year too.
Gosh, what are you going to do, Hong?
Shouldn't you tell Senior?
Well...
I can't tell them we fought again.
I don't want Senior to know about
Oh Young Gon.
Ah, well...
Um, well...
Hong, um...
- What?
- Uh...
Well, actually...
- What happened this time...
- What?
Yoo... Yoo Jung helped me out with it.
- Hey! What happened?
It's been since midterms.
I told everything regarding Young Gon
to Yoo Jung.
I shared all the pictures and videos.
It was Yoo Jung who said to put it up
on the school site too.
Senior knew everything?
So you want me to put up all the things
Young Gon wrote on the school site?
Yes.
That way everyone at school can see it.
He cares about what other people think,
so I think that will be good.
Yeah, I guess you are right.
Take out anything to do with Seol.
Only put up the things Young Gon wrote
about people at school.
Why are you telling us now?
Because Yoo Jung was waiting
until Seol told him herself.
That's why I didn't say anything.
Senior isn't ordinary.
His girlfriend was being stalked
and harassed, so how...
Could you act that way?
Oh no! I'd run right over
and just pound his head in.
If anyone bothers you, I'll fly over
and chew them up with my gold teeth.
And then I'll make a gold ring for you.
That's not necessary.
You're a bit much too.
How could you let things go this far
and not say anything to Senior?
If it were me, I'd be so angry
and tell him everything every single day.
I'm going to leave now. Sorry.
Where are you going?
They are kind of alike
if you think about it.
They aren't very ordinary.
I guess people who are alike
are left together in the end.
What are you saying?
I just need to give you a gold ring now.
You're going to get hurt by Yoo Jung
at some point.
Think about it carefully.
Why would he have sent me to you
last year?
Yoo Jung threatened me and made me
throw away his report.
So you could have the scholarship.
This hand...
Yoo Jung did it.
Be careful of Yoo Jung.
He's not everything he seems.
Senior, please say something.
You're the one who chose the topic
and you even sent the slides to me.
I understand Jung.
So with understanding and compassion,
we have a give and take relationship.
Both parties win.
So if you don't think you can handle it,
just leave already.
Don't make Jung suffer for no reason.
Hey, Baek In Ha!
Hold on, Mister.
You're already home. Where are you going?
You can go, sir.
What is all this?
Oh, In Ho? Are you going to work?
Where did you get the money for this?
Oh, this?
Jung gave it to me.
- Yoo Jung?
- Yeah.
He took all your money,
but then gave you this?
- Yeah.
- You should learn to lie better.
Seriously, I need to get my own place
and leave already.
Aren't you being too nosy
just because we live together?
If you don't tell me everything,
I'm going to throw this out.
What are you doing?
Follow me.
Be careful! Give that back.
Can I come in?
Come here. Sit down.
Why did he give you this?
You wouldn't know if I told you.
I know, so just tell me.
I made a deal with Jung.
What deal?
About Hong Shil or Hong Sam, that girl.
He wanted me to get rid of that loser
he had stuck on her before.
- So I did.
- Loser?
Would you even know if I told you?
There's this guy. A loser.
Who is the loser?
You mean stalker?
Oh, you know so well!
You know everything about her!
So in return for getting rid of him,
you got this?
Hey, what could I do?
Jung needed me so much.
You just don't know anything,
but do you know how busy I was?
Jung looks for me when he needs anything.
He only depends on me.
What can I do? I had to help him.
Then I got my cards re-opened
and bought these things myself.
Don't touch them!
So...
It was Yoo Jung who got you
to bring that loser around.
And it's now Yoo Jung
who's trying to get rid of him too?
Then... he's just playing around, right?
He was playing her.
Go and ask him.
He was playing around from the beginning.
Yoo Jung, that jerk.
Yesterday, why...
did you just leave like that?
Was it because I looked friendly
with Baek In Ho?
Is that why you didn't answer my calls?
No.
I was busy. That's why.
Oh really?
Baek In Ho and I...
To be honest, we have gotten closer.
I received a lot of help from him lately.
So I wanted to help him too.
I wanted to help him play the piano.
And I wanted to help him get his GED.
That's everything there is
regarding Baek In Ho.
As for Oh Young Gon...
You've heard everything from Eun Taek.
You know he even came to my home
yesterday.
Yes.
It seemed like you didn't want
to talk about it.
I just pretended not to know.
I'm sorry I couldn't tell you
about that beforehand.
I didn't feel comfortable talking about
these things with you.
Well, it's all over now.
- Let's stop talking about it.
- No.
It's not over.
Right now...
I'm trying really hard.
And saying all of this to you.
Now, I want to hear your answer.
What answer?
Your honest answer.
Do you feel like I'm hiding something?
There's that answer you always give.
"I didn't know Oh Young Gon
would go that far."
"I didn't intend for it to go that far."
These are not the answers that I want.
Then what?
What is it that you want me to say?
Let's stop talking about Oh Young Gon.
This isn't an Oh Young Gon problem.
This is a problem between us.
Stop avoiding it.
"Seol, I sent that text to Oh Young Gon
because I disliked you so much."
"I didn't miss your calls
because I was busy."
"I was angry because of Baek In Ho,
so I avoided them on purpose."
These are the answers that I want.
Why...
do you want to hear things like that?
I said many times.
I asked you to be honest with me.
And when you weren't,
it made me angry and frustrated.
I thought it was all your fault.
But I realized something this time.
I didn't tell you my inner feelings.
And I demanded you be honest
about your feelings.
I won't do that anymore.
So I want you to do that too.
Don't hide things anymore.
I want to see you the way you are.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Let's go. I'll take you home.
Baek In Ha, what's with you?
Just to get stuff like this,
you do chores for Yoo Jung.
Don't you have pride? Are you his toy?
Hey!
Are you crazy?
So pathetic.
Pride? Does that feed me or house me?
Who are you to be concerned about me?
What right do you have?
To me, you're much more of a bad guy
than Jung will ever be.
Do you know that?
This is so expensive!
How dare you kick it.
Tada!
- What is it?
- Look.
Daniel Redkovich?
- That pianist you always talk about?
- Yeah.
I didn't think I'd get to see his concert
before I die.
But he's coming here to Korea.
Wait and see.
I'm going to look online and find
the sheet music for his arrangements.
Then I'll get him to sign it
and keep it forever.
Isn't this on the day
of your piano concours?
Yes, I'll skip it.
Annoyingly, it's on the same day.
You can't, man. My dad's going too.
No, who knows when he's coming back.
I don't know.
If you really want to go,
you can try to convince my dad.
Gosh, you unfeeling jerk.
Only your name is Yoo Jung [AFFECTION].
You actually have no feelings.
My joke is funny, right?
Hey, let's go play piano.
Why would I go there?
I'll be bored. Just come watch.
Come in. I'll be bored.
Hi, Jung.
Hey, Yong Soo.
Are you attending the concours too?
Yeah. You knew?
Right, you get support from
Yoo Jung's family too.
Why don't you do better then?
How come you never win a prize?
What is this?
Are you studying for a test?
What? This is why you don't do well.
Your playing has no soul.
Hurry. Go and don't practice.
Get going.
Be careful how you talk.
What? I'm saying it all for his own good.
Anyway, I'm not going to the competition
this time.
- Baek In Ho.
- What?
I've been in first many times.
I'll rest this time
and place first next time.
I thought Jung was coming with you.
Why isn't he here?
He said he had to be somewhere.
He said he'd come before it ends.
It's not just any other day though.
There's not much going on at school,
is there?
If there were, I would have told you
already.
- Mister?
- Yes.
Where are we going to eat today?
That restaurant near here
was really good.
- Oh yeah? Then we'll go there.
- Yes.
I have something to talk about too.
Really?
Oh yeah!
Adopt?
I see you're very surprised.
It's been a long time
since you both came to stay.
Now we're pretty much like family.
And I'd like if you were
like real siblings to Jung in the future.
So before it's too late, I'm thinking of
adding you two to our family register.
What do you two think?
You don't need to decide right now.
Take your time and think about it, okay?
No, I don't like it!
Be quiet.
Why wouldn't you like it?
We'll become a real family.
Family, yeah right.
I have to marry Jung.
I can't be registered in his family.
- Think about it.
- You're still saying that?
You think just because you ask,
he'll do it?
I'm going to kill you.
Stop saying nonsense
and just do what Jung's dad says.
I'm sure Jung won't like it either.
What are you saying?
He did seem taken aback,
but so were we.
He definitely didn't have an expression
of not liking it.
Do you think that's his sincere feeling?
Do you still not know Jung at all?
I know him better than you.
- Is this really for me?
- Of course.
This is really hard to get. Wow...
What is it? What's the big fuss?
What is this?
A signed Daniel Redkovich CD?
That's mine. Give it to me.
Where did you get this?
Jung, I'll see you in class.
Okay.
Hey... hey!
I gave it to him.
What?
I went to that concert.
So you didn't come to my concours
and went to that concert? So...
Why are you giving that to him?
I thought it would good for Yong Soo
to hear.
Hey, are you mad at me about something?
- No.
- What do you mean no?
Do you think I'm stupid?
It's totally obvious.
Is it because of that?
- What your dad said...
- The adoption?
That's Dad's decision.
Not your dad. How about you?
How do you feel about it?
If you don't like it, just say so.
What kind of a guy...
It makes no difference to me.
It makes no difference?
So you don't like it or dislike it?
It makes no difference to you?
Yes, it makes no difference.
Jung, what do you do on the weekend?
I just stay home if I have nothing to do.
How about you?
I just study or go for a walk.
I go fishing. Have you been fishing?
No, never.
You've never fished?
I went fishing last weekend.
I caught a 30-centimeter fish and then...
- Right on that spot...
- Gosh, this tastes bad.
You're making me lose my appetite.
Just have an orange.
Yoo Jung, I prepared
these incredible girls just for you.
You know that place "Remember,"
right?
8:00 p.m. at "Remember."
I'll be waiting. See you.
- Make sure to come.
- My English sounds good today.
Remember!
- Yong Soo.
- Yeah, Jung.
Are you going somewhere with those guys?
- Where?
- That place "Remember."
Don't they hang out in dangerous places?
They're not so bad
once you get to know them.
- Do you want to go too?
- Me?
With you?
Sure, I'll go too.
Hey, why don't you practice instead of
going to places like that?
Baek In Ho, do you want to go too?
Forget it, it's obvious
what they're going to do there.
Is that what you do these days...
Anyway, be careful.
Don't do anything weird.
You're in trouble if your dad finds out.
How would Dad find out
unless someone tells on me?
Right?
What are you saying?
I heard
you're attending another concours.
You should be practicing instead of
going to places like that.
You're getting financial support.
What if you can't even make it
past preliminary round?
Watch your expression.
Cheers, cheers!
You're all so tacky.
I'm not sure we can hang out with you.
Don't you have whiskey?
Pour a little bit at a time and drink it.
Then it tastes good.
What are you doing here?
Jung said he'd be here.
Yoo Jung? Did he say he'd come?
I don't know.
What is this?
Nice going!
How old are you that
you're already drinking with girls?
You get caught
and dirty your school's name!
Hey, Park Yong Soo.
Why are you in this group?
Am I really not allowed to go to
my piano concours?
You sure are funny.
You got caught too.
You want to be the only one unpunished?
Who told you to hang out
with guys like this?
Get down on the floor. Get down!
Who ratted us out?
No one knew about that place but us.
You should be practicing instead of
going to places like that.
You're getting financial support.
What if you can't even make it
past the preliminary round?
I know who.
What?
I know who reported us.
- Let go.
- You reported us to the cops.
Get up, you punk.
- You want to die?
- Let go, punk!
It wasn't me, you crazy bastards!
Stop it!
Stop it, you punks!
It's all your fault!
I'm sorry.
I really just...
wanted you to become siblings to Jung.
Was it that uncomfortable?
In Ho.
It's not true, right?
That it was you.
What should I say
to put your mind at ease?
Was it really you?
I'm asking if it was really
you who did it.
Of course not.
You're the one who did it, not me.
Give it some thought.
You son of a bitch.
Why on earth did you do that to me?
Why on earth did you do it?
Why is it that people covet
what doesn't belong to them?
They mistakenly think that what actually
belongs to someone else is theirs
and ultimately lose what belongs to them.
Did you do this to me...
because you hated the idea of us
being adopted into your family?
Just because of that?
Think whatever you want.
Baek In Ho!
Where are you going?
I don't know. Don't wait up for me.
Fine. Go on.
You're always like this.
I must've momentarily forgotten.
You're someone who can abandon me
whenever he wants to.
Leave.
You better leave and never come back.
I'll do fine on my own.
Just try and come back!
I won't stand for it.
Thank you for driving me home.
Seol.
I'm going.
Where are you? Come see me.
What have you done to Baek In Ha?
I guess she couldn't wait
and opened her mouth.
Acting like a victim
while getting everything she wants...
- I'm sick and tired of it now.
- This jerk, to the very end...
How long are you going to
keep hanging around Seol?
It seems like you're doing it
to make me upset.
But doesn't it seem
pathetic to you, too?
Come to your senses
and think of your future.
I...
Let me ask you for a favor.
Let me punch you just this once.
I really want to hit you.
One fight, man to man.
What do you say?
Sounds good.
Fine, let's try to kill each other
tonight, you son of a bitch.
Tonight sounds real good, you jerk!
Let's try to kill you!
Geez.
I've put up with you long enough.
What a load of shit, you bastard!
Get up, you bastard.
Wow.
How did a guy who's so good at
beating people up hold back for so long?
You should've showed your true colors
sooner, you double-faced bastard!
If you had done so, our friendship
would've never gotten this bad.
Blaming me again, are you?
This bastard keeps acting like a victim
while coveting what's not his...
What about you then?
You get your hackles up like a porcupine
whenever anyone provokes you.
You sent a stalker to the subway
and now you're trying to use someone
to get rid of that same stalker.
Is that your way of protecting Dog Fur?
Shut up, you bastard.
I'll take care of it.
But still!
I thought that your feelings
for Dog Fur were genuine.
Do you even know what it means
to like someone, you son of a bitch?
What does it matter to you?
Because I like Dog Fur.
It matters to me because
I like Dog Fur, you bastard!
Fine.
This is what you're best at.
You act like a friend, but then
you stab people in the back!
Who stabbed whom in the back first?
Ah...
This isn't considered stabbing
someone in the back, is it?
Stay away from Seol!
Says who?
Geez!
So what can you do for Seol?
Your own life is cumbersome enough.
Then tell me, you bastard.
Just like you did to me...
can you guarantee that you won't
do the same to Dog Fur?
Are you confident
about that, you bastard?
Geez.
A son of a bitch like you
will eventually show
his true colors in time.
Even if someone like me knows that
you think Dog Fur won't be able
to figure it out?
Hide what's actually worth hiding,
you bastard!
You're the reason why
everyone's lives are ultimately ruined.
The one who should truly
stay away from Dog Fur...
isn't me, but you, you bastard.
You crazy bastard!
Ow, seriously.
You bastard.
How long will it take for you
to come to your senses and...
You're the one who should
stay away from her, you bastard!
Dog Fur... you bastard!
- Hey...
- Let go!
You jerk!
It hurts!
Stop it!
Seol, I'm standing outside your house.
Could you come out for a bit?
What could it be?
Senior.
Senior!
What's with your face?
What happened?
Who did this to you?
Stay still.
Does it hurt?
Let me see.
Look at your face.
How are you going to go to work tomorrow?
You fought with Baek In Ho, didn't you?
He started it.
So did you just agree to it
and fight him?
Yeah.
You two used to only fight with words,
but now you're using your fists.
Why? What's wrong?
Let's say it was about
Baek In Ho's hand...
but why did you do it?
Sorry.
Still fighting over something
that happened in high school...
I honestly don't get it.
You're not the type to get into fights.
Why do you hate Baek In Ho so much?
- I have one more.
- Oh?
I like this more than the original one.
Is this my score?
Wow, this is the arranged one!
You're a real fan.
What's your name?
In Ho Baek.
Thanks for attending
my concert tonight, In Ho.
Thanks. Thanks for playing tonight.
- Hey, is it your turn?
- Yes.
Did you hear me?
I totally got into the mood.
The audience was so moved
by my performance...
- I saw the Chairman is here.
- Mister?
He came to see me tonight.
He still comes even though
I tell him not to.
But... how did you get to be
such good friends with Yoo Jung?
Why? Do you want to
become friends with him too?
Because Mister is your benefactor?
Dream on.
He may smile at you, but on the inside,
he hates guys like you.
Yoo Jung hails from a wealthy family
and he's popular and a good student.
- Everyone envies him.
- Is that something to envy?
It must be because
you don't hang out with him...
He's a pitiful fellow
once you get to know him.
What good is it if your family is rich?
Jung has no dreams
and can't do anything he wants to do.
That's why things are so easy for him.
I might be the only person
who understands him.
He's a really pitiful guy.
In any case, don't be nervous
and put on a good performance.
Fighting!
Adopt?
Now we're pretty much like family.
And I'd like if you were
like real siblings to Jung in the future.
So before it's too late
I'm thinking of adding you two
to our family register.
What do you think?
I already had the idea of
adopting them on my mind.
I've imposed on you so much,
Doctor Baek.
I'm saying that I'll take care of
your grandchildren.
Why on earth would you
say such a thing?
Why would anyone who abandoned
their children try to get involved now?
Jung won't be against the idea either.
There's no reason for him
to be against it.
What?
Keep tabs on?
How does that count
as keeping an eye on him?
You know what Jung is like.
It's not that I think he's strange,
but you said if he's left on his own
he'd always have trouble with
personal relationships.
If someone isn't by his side
to take care of him
he can't survive on his own.
That's why he needs siblings.
Anyway, I've made this decision
for Jung's sake.
I'll take care of
the kids' adoption process...
so don't concern yourself
about this matter anymore.
It was from that time...
It's not that I hated the idea
of them being adopted.
It was a bit of a shock,
but I could accept it.
But...
but the people
whom I thought were my friends...
that they were keeping tabs on me...
It was hard to put up with that.
Father knew everything.
As if... he was always
watching over us.
He always took hold of
my shoulder and told me...
"Be meek." "Don't get greedy."
"Always concede to others."
As if I was being scolded
for doing something wrong.
Did I really appear to be that strange?
Do I... really seem...
that strange to you?
Senior.
We really didn't get along
in the beginning, didn't we?
We both hated each other and treated
one another like weird people.
But if I think about that now...
we weren't weird...
but I think we were different.
You were like this...
and I was like that.
Just... different people like that.
I used to frequently hear that I was
sensitive and frustrating to be around.
So I worried a lot about that.
But my conclusion was...
"That's just who I am."
I might not be fully certain,
but you, Senior...
I don't think you had many chances
to be honest with people.
It must've been really lonely for you.
Don't have a hard time
on your own from now on.
We'll go through it together.
I really want to get to know you.
I was scared.
That you might leave me
if you found out who I truly am.
I...
like you a lot, Senior.
Much more than before.
You were different than
everyone else to begin with, Seol.
You've always observed me...
and it was always obvious
whenever you didn't like something.
This may sound funny,
but I always found that helpful.
No matter how minor
they may have seemed to you.
It might have been because
you were scared of me.
Scared that you might
end up provoking me.
I don't like that.
But it's not like that now.
Now...
I'm scared that you might leave me.
I like you a lot too.
Very much.
I like you.
It hurts.
Ah, it's cold. It's cold.
Did you put ointment on?
Do you want to give me that
when it wasn't enough to ask why
your boyfriend beat me up?
That sort of threat
doesn't work on me anymore.
- Seol knows everything now.
- How much does she know?
She won't ever be able to understand you.
Oh, Hong! It's a paper!
All you need to do is graduate!
It's not a paper
you worked that hard at.
Does Hong know that you like her?
Don't hang around her
and act like her friend.
It's game over the moment she finds out!
We won't be alone by ourselves
other than when we're studying.
I'm giving you a week
for that 10 million won.
Don't get any funny ideas.
I can ruin you and everyone around you.
Do you have someone you like?
Don't worry about
tutoring me anymore.
- Is something wrong?
- What does it matter to you?
Hey, wake up! A doctor!
Open your eyes! Dog Fur!
Sorry. I'll make sure that you
never get hurt like this.
I'll always be by your side.